<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 17:17:41 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Are Never Trumpers Abandoning Biden and Moving Toward...Trump?</title><link>https://redstate.com/nick-arama/2024/05/09/never-trump-moving-towardtrump-n2173979</link><description></description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 22:12:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Former GOP Rep. Fortenberry charged with lying about illegal campaign contribution</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/former-gop-rep-fortenberry-charged-lying-illegal-campaign-contribution</link><description>Republican former Nebraska Rep. Jeff Fortenberry has been charged with lying to federal authorities about an illegal, $30,000 campaign contribution by a Nigerian billionaire.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 22:00:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Speaker Johnson: Olive Branch Offered to Rep. Greene</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/mike-johnson-speaker-marjorie-taylor-greene/2024/05/09/id/1164146</link><description>House Speaker Mike Johnson, R-La., said Thursday he extended an olive branch to Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene, R-Ga., after her motion to remove him was soundly defeated.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:42:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RFK Jr. Doubles Down on Support for Full-Term Abortion</title><link>https://redstate.com/jeffc/2024/05/09/rfk-jr-doubles-down-on-support-for-full-term-abortion-n2173985</link><description></description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Taxpayer-funded ID program for illegal immigrants expected to begin this summer</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/ice-eyes-summer-rollout-for-id-card-program-for-illegal-immigrants</link><description>Immigration and Customs Enforcement is looking to roll out a controversial ID card pilot program for illegal immigrants as early as this summer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:31:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rep. Fleischmann to Newsmax: Equal Representation Act Counters Radical Left</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/fleischmann-left-immigration/2024/05/09/id/1164138</link><description>The House bill passed Wednesday that would add a citizenship question to the census and require that only citizens count when determining the number of congressional seats a state receives will counter what the radical left has done, Rep. Chuck Fleischmann said.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:02:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Waving the Bloody Shirt - Again</title><link>https://redstate.com/adam-turner/2024/05/09/waving-the-bloody-shirt-again-n2173983</link><description></description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:15:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mike Pence accuses Biden of impeachment hypocrisy amid Israel arms threat</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/mike-pence-accuses-biden-impeachment-hypocrisy-amid-israel-arms-threat</link><description>Former Vice President Mike Pence called out President Biden for threatening to withhold arms aid to Israel during a CNN interview, warning the Israelis not to go farther into Rafah.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:04:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oklahoma Judge Blocks Anti-ESG State Law</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/oklahoma-esg-law-judge-sheila-stinson/2024/05/09/id/1164131</link><description>A judge in Oklahoma, a major oil and gas producing state, blocked a state law prohibiting state pension systems from contracting with more than a dozen companies that limit investment in the oil and gas industry.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 20:51:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OPINION: As a Black Man, I’ll Take Ann Coulter’s Racism Over Kathy Hochul’s</title><link>https://redstate.com/jeffc/2024/05/09/as-a-black-man-ill-take-ann-coulters-racism-over-kathy-hochuls-n2173982</link><description></description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:00:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anti-Israel occupiers could lose federal student loans under new GOP Senate bill</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/anti-israel-occupiers-lose-federal-student-loans-new-gop-senate-bill</link><description>Sen. Thom Tillis, R-N.C., introduced a bill to strip financial aid from protesters who break the law at universities.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 20:41:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Texas to Compensate Landowners for Damage From Border Crime</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/texas-border-security-ken-paxton/2024/05/09/id/1164124</link><description>Texas Attorney General Ken Paxton initiated a program to compensate landowners along the Texas-Mexico border for damages to their property that may have been the result of illegal border crossers, smugglers and drug traffickers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 20:11:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>They're Special but Not You; NY College Holds Special Graduation Ceremonies for Certain Student Groups</title><link>https://redstate.com/mdempsey/2024/05/09/theyre-special-but-not-you-ny-college-holds-special-graduation-ceremonies-for-certain-student-groups-n2173972</link><description></description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 20:38:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>House GOP drafting Biden impeachment articles over Israel aid cutoff threat</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/house-gop-drafting-biden-impeachment-articles-israel-aid-cutoff-threat</link><description>House Republicans are coming out with calls for President Biden to be impeached after he threatened to halt offensive weapons aid to Israel if it invaded Rafah.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 20:22:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>McConnell Warns Biden: Refusing Israeli Aid Will Prove 'Grave'</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/mitch-mcconnell-biden-israel/2024/05/09/id/1164123</link><description>The "consequences will be grave" if President Joe Biden can't find the "political courage to stand up to radicals on his left flank" and support Israel, Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell warned in a speech on the Senate floor Thursday.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 20:06:45 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>