<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:39:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>TikTok Launches Lawsuit Against US to Stop Ban and Some Experts Believe They Will Succeed</title><link>https://redstate.com/brandon_morse/2024/05/07/tiktok-launches-lawsuit-against-us-to-stop-ban-and-some-experts-believe-they-will-succeed-n2173886</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:35:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GOP rebels back off threat to force Johnson ouster vote this week as they seek deal</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/gop-rebels-back-off-threat-force-johnson-ouster-vote-week-seek-deal</link><description>Reps. Marjorie Taylor Greene and Thomas Massie are in talks with Speaker Johnson as they threaten to force a vote on his ouster.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:10:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WH Pressures Israel to Close 'Gaps' in Cease-Fire Talks</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/white-house-israel-gaps/2024/05/07/id/1163830</link><description>The White House, for the second time in as many days, put the squeeze on Israel in its negotiations with Hamas terrorists to reach a cease-fire for hostages' deal.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:05:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Education Secretary Falls Apart When Asked Whether He Would Force His Daughter to Undress In Front of Men</title><link>https://redstate.com/jeffc/2024/05/07/education-secretary-falls-apart-when-asked-whether-he-would-force-his-daughter-to-undress-in-front-of-men-n2173883</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:25:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NPR CEO Katherine Maher declines House hearing invite amid bias scandal</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/npr-ceo-katherine-maher-declines-house-hearing-invite-bias-scandal</link><description>NPR CEO Katherine Maher won't be testifying before a House committee on Wednesday as requested.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 20:59:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>D.C. Mayor to Testify on George Washington Encampment</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/muriel-bowser-pamela-smith-james-comer/2024/05/07/id/1163825</link><description>Washington, D.C., Mayor Muriel Bowser has agreed to testify in front of the House Committee on Oversight and Accountability, which is holding a hearing on why the city has not responded to requests by George Washington University to clear an anti-Israel tent encampment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 20:48:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Massachusetts: Bear Drags Car Crash Victim's Body Into Woods</title><link>https://redstate.com/wardclark/2024/05/07/massachusetts-bear-drags-car-crash-victims-body-into-woods-n2173882</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:12:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden plan to extend ObamaCare eligibility to illegal immigrants gets pushback in Congress: 'Madness'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/biden-plan-extend-obamacare-eligibility-illegal-immigrants-pushback-congress-madness</link><description>Rep. Nancy Mace is introducing a resolution of disapproval to oppose a Biden administration rule to grant ObamaCare to some illegal immigrants protected by a 2012 order.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 20:48:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rep. Tlaib to ICC: Arrest Netanyahu for Genocide</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/rashida-tlaib-benjamin-netanyahu-israel/2024/05/07/id/1163821</link><description>Rep. Rashida Tlaib, D-Mich., called for the International Criminal Court to issue an arrest warrant for Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu and charge him with committing genocide during the Israel-Hamas war.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 20:27:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Behind Bars? Mayor Adams Insists Rikers Island Is 'Prepared' to House the Former President</title><link>https://redstate.com/wardclark/2024/05/07/trump-behind-bars-mayor-adams-insists-rikers-island-is-prepared-to-house-the-former-president-n2173878</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 20:57:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New poll reveals what voters think will happen in NY vs Trump</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/nearly-two-thirds-voters-believe-trump-convicted-some-charges-criminal-trial</link><description>Nearly two-thirds of voters say former President Trump will be found guilty on some charges in his unprecedented criminal trial in New York City, according to a new national poll</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 20:17:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Foundation Hopes to Stop Funding ESG Agenda With Pension Money</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/esg-public-pension-funds-foundation/2024/05/07/id/1163819</link><description>A new effort launched by the State Financial Officers Foundation is pushing back on the use of public pension funds to finance ESG (environmental, social, and governance) initiatives that further political agendas.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 20:10:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Judge Slaps Down Trump's Mistrial Request in 'Hush Money' Case As Stormy Daniels' Testimony Rocks Court</title><link>https://redstate.com/bobhoge/2024/05/07/judge-slaps-down-trumps-mistrial-request-in-hush-money-case-as-stormy-daniels-testimony-rocks-court-n2173881</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 20:16:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anti-Israel encampments share common traits with Marxist revolutionaries, BLM and the KKK</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/anti-israel-encampments-share-common-traits-marxist-revolutionaries-blm-kkk</link><description>The anti-Israel demonstrations sweeping American college campuses share similar traits to Mao's Cultural Revolution and the Black Lives Matter movement.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 19:51:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rep. Jordan Questions Trump Classified Documents Probe</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/classified-documents-trump-trial-tainted/2024/05/07/id/1163815</link><description>Following revelations that the boxes of files recovered from Donald Trump's Mar-a-Lago home were altered or manipulated, House Republicans are investigating whether the former president's classified documents investigation is tainted, the Daily Mail reported.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 19:42:23 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>