<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 13:15:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>To Meet Electric Vehicle Goals, California Must Spend $20 Billion on Grid Updates</title><link>https://redstate.com/wardclark/2024/05/02/to-meet-electric-vehicle-goals-california-must-spend-20-billion-on-grid-updates-n2173651</link><description></description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 17:55:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden pressured to sanction China for role in US fentanyl crisis</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/biden-pressured-sanction-china-role-us-fentanyl-crisis</link><description>Rep. Jim Banks is unveiling new legislation to force the Biden administration to severely hike penalties against China and its allied actors over the U.S. fentanyl crisis.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 18:00:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Conservative Group Fights WH Student Loan Push</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/student-loan-biden/2024/05/02/id/1163259</link><description>Heritage Action, the advocacy arm of the conservative Heritage Foundation think tank, has launched a campaign seeking comments on President Joe Biden's attempt to cancel student loans.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 17:34:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>UPDATE: Photojournalist Arrested During University of Texas Protest Is Now Facing New Assault Charges</title><link>https://redstate.com/bradslager/2024/05/02/update-photojournalist-arrested-during-university-of-texas-protest-is-now-facing-new-assault-charges-n2173650</link><description></description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 17:40:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden calls Japan 'xenophobic' for not accepting many immigrants, compares to China, Russia</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/biden-calls-japan-xenophobic-not-accepting-many-immigrants-compares-china-russia</link><description>President Biden called the allied nation of Japan "xenophobic" during a speech on Wednesday, comparing the island country to rival powers China and Russia.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 17:20:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sen. Joni Ernst Presses Biden to Halt Gazan Refugee Proposal</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/gaza-hamas-terrorists/2024/05/02/id/1163258</link><description>Sen. Jon Ernst, R-Iowa., sent a letter to President Joe Biden on Wednesday demanding his administration halt their proposed plan to accept Gazan refuges into the United States.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 17:32:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Morning Joe' Mika Has a Meltdown When Al Sharpton Compares Campus Riots to Jan. 6</title><link>https://redstate.com/nick-arama/2024/05/02/morning-joe-mika-has-a-meltdown-when-al-sharpton-compares-campus-riots-to-jan-6-n2173642</link><description></description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 17:12:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>President Biden condemns violent anti-Israel protests, won't call up National Guard</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/president-biden-condemns-violent-anti-israel-protests-wont-call-national-guard</link><description>President Biden has broken his silence Thursday regarding the anti-Israel demonstrations that are roiling colleges and universities around the nation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:16:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GOP Lawmakers Introducing Bill Aimed at Fauci</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/debbie-lesko-j-d-vance-anthony-fauci/2024/05/02/id/1163256</link><description>House Republicans are reportedly ready to introduce a bill prohibiting past health officials from profiting off medical research - a move aimed directly at former National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases head Anthony Fauci.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 17:20:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Boeing Whistleblower Dies Suddenly After Exposing Problems With Manufacturing Practices</title><link>https://redstate.com/jeffc/2024/05/02/boeing-whistleblower-dies-suddenly-after-exposing-problems-with-manufacturing-practices-n2173649</link><description></description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 17:01:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump slams 'radical left lunatics' creating chaos on college campuses nationwide</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-slams-radical-left-lunatics-creating-chaos-college-campuses-nationwide</link><description>Former President Trump slammed the "radical left lunatics" on college campuses nationwide for creating chaos amid their protests against Israel.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 15:05:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Drea de Matteo to Newsmax: Dream Government 'Might Not Exist'</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/drea-de-matto-conservatives-actress/2024/05/02/id/1163252</link><description>Actress Drea de Matteo told Newsmax on Thursday that she'll always consider herself far left, but she's feeling "more aligned" with conservative values</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 17:04:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MSNBC Says Antisemitic, Pro-Hamas Demonstrators Aren't the Problem — It's 'Bad Faith' Republicans!</title><link>https://redstate.com/mike_miller/2024/05/02/msnbc-decides-antisemitic-pro-hamas-demonstrators-arent-the-problem-its-bad-faith-republicans-n2173643</link><description></description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:52:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anti-McCarthy GOP rebels distance themselves from push to oust Speaker Johnson</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/anti-mccarthy-gop-rebels-distance-themselves-push-oust-speaker-johnson</link><description>Seven of the eight House Republicans who ousted ex House Speaker Kevin McCarthy are still serving in Congress, and nearly all of them are outright opposed to ousting House Speaker Mike Johnson right now.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 15:03:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sen. Barrasso Demands Dismissal of University Leaders</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/john-barrasso-college-pro-palestine/2024/05/02/id/1163247</link><description>Sen. John Barrasso, R-Wyo., called for the dismissal of college administrators over their handling of the pro-Palestine protests on campuses nationwide, many of which have resulted in arrests and violent clashes with police.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:48:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>