<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 06:58:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Trump Visits FDNY Station After Court, Buys Them Pizza. Their Response: 'Save Us, Please.'</title><link>https://redstate.com/bobhoge/2024/05/02/trump-visits-nyfd-station-after-court-buys-them-pizza-sir-save-us-please-n2173680</link><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:43:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden brings up Islamophobia amid the worst antisemitism outbreak in decades</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/biden-brings-up-islamophobia-amid-worst-antisemitism-outbreak-decades</link><description>President Biden, while condemning anti-Israel violence at college campuses across the country, brought up Islamophobia despite the worst antisemitism outbreak in decades.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 10:00:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden to Let 100,000 Migrants Enroll in Obamacare</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/health-care-insurance-migrants/2024/05/03/id/1163349</link><description>Roughly 100,000 immigrants who were brought to the U.S. as children are expected to enroll in the Affordable Care Act's health insurance next year under a new directive the Biden administration released Friday.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 11:23:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Loses to the Teleprompter Trying to Spell a Word, and Tells a Whopper About Walmart</title><link>https://redstate.com/nick-arama/2024/05/02/bidens-walmart-tall-tale-and-reading-off-the-teleprompter-again-n2173674</link><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:09:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>VP Stakes: Trump meeting with potential running mates this weekend</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-huddling-potential-running-mates-top-republican-donors</link><description>Donald Trump moves from the courtroom in New York City to the banquet rooms in South Florida on Friday, as he headlines a gathering of top Republican donors and teams up with potential running mates.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 09:08:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fmr PM Boris Johnson Barred From Voting by His Own Law</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/boris-johnson-voting-photo/2024/05/02/id/1163333</link><description>Former British Prime Minister Boris Johnson was turned away from voting on Thursday after forgetting to bring a photo ID, a stipulation from a law that he introduced in 2022.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 03:07:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Story of the Hero Beekeeper From the Dodgers-Diamondbacks Game Just Keeps Getting Better</title><link>https://redstate.com/sister-toldjah/2024/05/02/the-story-of-the-hero-beekeeper-from-the-diamondbacks-dodgers-game-just-keeps-getting-better-n2173675</link><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 01:12:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FLASHBACK: Biden confidante made revealing admission about Obama DOJ in unearthed interview</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/flashback-biden-confidante-revealing-admission-obama-doj-unearthed-interview</link><description>A former U.S. Senator and longtime Biden ally said in 2012 that the Department of Justice is "full of Biden people" renewing concerns about the departments impartiality.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 09:00:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ala. Gov. Ivey Signs Bill Ensuring Biden Is on November Ballot</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/biden-ballot-access-alabama/2024/05/02/id/1163332</link><description>Alabama officials on Thursday approved legislation to ensure President Joe Biden will appear on the state's November ballot, mirroring accommodations the state made four years ago for then-President Donald Trump.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 03:04:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Don't Try This in SEC Country: Ole Miss Students Wreck Pro-Hamas Protest, Chant 'We Want Trump!'</title><link>https://redstate.com/bobhoge/2024/05/02/dont-try-it-in-sec-country-ole-miss-students-shut-down-pro-hamas-protest-chant-we-want-trump-n2173676</link><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 00:48:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NY v Trump: Remaining alleged gag order violations hang in balance as trial resumes</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/ny-v-trump-remaining-alleged-gag-order-violations-hang-balance-trial-resumes</link><description>The NY v. Trump trial will resume Friday for its 11th day as the court will hear continued testimony from computer forensic expert Doug Daus.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Governors: Don't Move Air National Guard to Space Force</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/governors-pentagon-lloyd-austin/2024/05/02/id/1163330</link><description>All but two governors signed a letter opposing the Pentagon's plan to unilaterally move some Air National Guard units into the U.S. Space Force, saying it "undermines over 100 years of precedent."</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:27:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Report: 'Operation Hide Joe Biden' Takes a Troubling Turn After Pathetic Speech on Pro-Hamas Protests</title><link>https://redstate.com/sister-toldjah/2024/05/02/new-operation-hide-joe-biden-takes-a-troubling-turn-after-pathetic-speech-on-pro-hamas-protests-n2173673</link><description></description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 23:53:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Which states could have abortion on the ballot in 2024?</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/which-states-could-abortion-ballot-2024</link><description>It is not yet clear how many states will vote in November on measures to preserve abortion access following the 2022 decision by the U.S. Supreme Court to overturn Roe v. Wade.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:00:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ark. Gov. Orders State to Defy Biden Revisions to Title IX</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/sarah-huckabee-sanders-arkansas-defy/2024/05/02/id/1163328</link><description>Republican Arkansas Gov. Sarah Huckabee Sanders is following the lead taken by other red states in directing her government to defy changes to Title IX made by the Biden administration regarding transgender students.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 02:24:34 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>