<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 15:18:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Government Employee Arrested for Falsely Accusing Colleagues of Involvement in Jan. 6</title><link>https://redstate.com/jeffc/2024/05/03/government-employee-arrested-for-falsely-accusing-colleagues-of-involvement-in-jan-6-n2173703</link><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 19:20:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden's controversial DHS 'experts' panel shuttered after being slapped with lawsuit</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/bidens-controversial-dhs-experts-panel-shuttered-slapped-lawsuit</link><description>The Department of Homeland Security is winding down a controversial experts group after a lawsuit from a conservative legal group who said it was in violation of federal law.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 19:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Made in China:' Sen. Manchin Blasts Biden's EV Policy</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/joe-manchin-joe-biden-electric-vehicles/2024/05/03/id/1163420</link><description>West Virginia Sen. Joe Manchin, a Democrat, is ripping the Biden administration's new policy on which electric vehicles are eligible for tax credits, saying they are endorsing "Made in China."</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 19:36:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NEW POLL: Surging Trump Enters 'Blowout Territory' As He Increases Lead Over Embattled Biden</title><link>https://redstate.com/mike_miller/2024/05/03/new-poll-surging-trump-enters-blowout-territory-as-he-increases-lead-over-embattled-biden-n2173697</link><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 19:14:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zoom call reveals 'Squad' Democrat's message to anti-Jewish agitators at university encampment</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/zoom-call-reveals-squad-democrats-message-anti-jewish-agitators-university-encampment</link><description>Rep. Rashida Tlaib, a member of the far-left "Squad," told anti-Israel agitators encamped at the University of Oregon she loved them and thanked them during a Zoom call.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 18:52:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fmr Govt Official Charged With Falsely Accusing Colleagues of Jan. 6 Involvement</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/government-official-charged/2024/05/03/id/1163417</link><description>Federal prosecutors this week charged a former government official with falsely accusing multiple colleagues of participating in the Capitol riot on Jan. 6, 2020, Politico reports.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 18:57:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Almost Face Plants Coming Off Helicopter, While Trump Lights It Up in New York</title><link>https://redstate.com/nick-arama/2024/05/03/biden-almost-face-plants-while-trump-lights-it-up-in-new-york-n2173682</link><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 18:35:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Democratic Texas Rep. Henry Cuellar indicted by DOJ on conspiracy and bribery charges</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/democratic-texas-rep-henry-cuellar-indicted-doj-azerbaijan-investigation</link><description>The DOJ filed indictments against Democratic Rep. Henry Cuellar of Texas on Friday in connection with an investigation into bribes he allegedly took from an Azerbaijan-based company.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 16:35:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Louisiana Gov. Jeff Landry Fires Back at Mick Jagger</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/landry-jagger-rolling-stones/2024/05/03/id/1163415</link><description>Louisiana Gov. Jeff Landry, a Republican, took a playful written jab at Mick Jagger after the Rolling Stones' legendary singer was critical of his policies.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 18:49:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Iranian and Houthi Universities Offer Scholarships to Expelled Pro-Hamas Students</title><link>https://redstate.com/jeffc/2024/05/03/iranian-and-houthi-universities-offer-scholarships-to-expelled-pro-hamas-students-n2173700</link><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 18:20:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Campus 'occupation guide' taps into agitators' 'rage,' instructs how to 'escalate' chaos</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/campus-occupation-guide-taps-agitators-rage-instructs-how-escalate-chaos</link><description>Agitators on the University of Pennsylvania's campus are passing around multiple "how-to" guides on protesting the war in Israel, including breaking into buildings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 16:06:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Biden Campaign Abortion Ads Aimed at Latino Men</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/biden-abortion-ads/2024/05/03/id/1163414</link><description>Joe Biden will ramp up spending this month as part of a new advertising push aimed partly at convincing Latino men that abortion rights are a vital issue that affects them, the U.S. president's 2024 campaign said on Friday.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 18:42:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TSA to Passenger: Are Your Pants Full of Snakes or Are You Just Happy to See Us?</title><link>https://redstate.com/wardclark/2024/05/03/tsa-to-passenger-are-your-pants-full-of-snakes-or-are-you-just-happy-to-see-us-n2173698</link><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 18:10:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>These illegal immigrants are eligible for Obamacare after Biden rule change</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/these-illegal-immigrants-eligible-for-obamacare-after-biden-rule-change</link><description>Over 100,000 illegal immigrants protected by an Obama-era executive order will soon be able to obtain health care coverage under the Affordable Care Act, officials said Friday.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 15:05:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hope Hicks Takes the Witness Stand in Trump Trial</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/hicks-testify-trump/2024/05/03/id/1163413</link><description>Hope Hicks, who was Donald Trump's 2016 campaign press secretary and went on to hold various roles in his White House, took the witness stand in his New York criminal case Friday.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 18:42:28 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>