<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 01:07:41 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>'Death to America': NYPD Stunned at Hateful Signs Found in NYU Pro-Hamas Camp</title><link>https://redstate.com/bobhoge/2024/05/03/death-to-america-nypd-stunned-at-hateful-signs-found-in-nyu-pro-hamas-camp-n2173733</link><description></description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 03:23:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dean Phillips becomes first House Democrat to call on Rep. Cuellar to resign after indictment</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/dean-phillips-first-house-democrat-call-dem-rep-cuellar-resign-indictment</link><description>Rep. Dean Phillips was the first House Democrat to call on colleague Rep. Henry Cuellar, also a Democrat, to resign after his bribery and conspiracy indictment Friday.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 02:58:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Slams 'Deranged' Special Counsel Over Foul-Up</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/trump-jack-smith-docs/2024/05/03/id/1163466</link><description>Republican presumptive nominee Donald Trump seized on a mistake by special counsel Jack Smith's office on Friday, which admitted it mishandled classified documents that Trump stands accused of mishandling.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 03:26:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Feel-Good Friday: Storm Chaser Saves Family From a Texas Tornado, Transports Them to the Hospital</title><link>https://redstate.com/jenniferoo/2024/05/03/feel-good-friday-storm-chaser-saves-family-from-a-texas-tornado-transports-them-to-the-hospital-n2173718</link><description></description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 03:10:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Border Patrol sector stops hundreds of Chinese illegal immigrants in just two days as numbers soar</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/border-patrol-sector-stops-hundreds-chinese-illegal-immigrants-just-two-days-numbers-soar</link><description>The San Diego Border Patrol Sector has seen a surge in migrants from China, encountering more nationals in two days than the entire border did in FY 21.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 00:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Republicans Bash Philadelphia DA Over Crime, Policies</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/gop-hearing-philadelphia/2024/05/03/id/1163464</link><description>House Republicans blasted Philadelphia District Attorney Larry Krasner and his "pro-criminal policies" during a field hearing on Friday in Center City, Pennsylvania.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 03:07:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>No, Antisemitism Isn't Scriptural</title><link>https://redstate.com/jerrywilson/2024/05/03/no-antisemitism-isnt-scriptural-n2173731</link><description></description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 02:50:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fox News Politics: Mr. Broke It</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/fox-news-politics-mr-broke-it</link><description>The latest updates from the 2024 campaign trail, exclusive interviews and more Fox News politics content</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 22:53:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rep. Perry to Newsmax: 'People Who Hate America' Spur Protests</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/gaza-israel-perry/2024/05/03/id/1163453</link><description>Rep. Scott Perry, R-Penn., said Friday that the protests on campuses of U.S. colleges and universities are "the result of bringing people that hate America to America."</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 00:49:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ted Cruz Wallops Marjorie Taylor Greene Over Effort to Oust Speaker Mike Johnson</title><link>https://redstate.com/jeffc/2024/05/03/ted-cruz-wallops-marjorie-taylor-greene-over-effort-to-oust-speaker-mike-johnson-n2173729</link><description></description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 01:10:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prosecutors repeatedly reference Trump’s Access Hollywood scandal after judge ruled tape itself 'prejudicial'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/prosecutors-repeatedly-reference-trumps-access-hollywood-scandal-judge-ruled-tape-itself-prejudicial</link><description>New York prosecutors continue to heavily reference the infamous leaked Access Hollywood tape capturing Trump's crude comments about women despite judge deeming the tape itself prejudicial.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 22:45:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DOJ Threatens to Sue Iowa if It Acts on Immigration Law</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/iowa-doj-immigration/2024/05/03/id/1163452</link><description>Iowa will face legal consequences if it enforces a recently passed immigration law that prohibits people from being in the state if they were previously denied entry into the United States, the Des Moines Register reported.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 00:32:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Columbia Prez Breaks Silence on NYPD's Raid on Pro-Hamas Mob, Statement Will Please Exactly No One</title><link>https://redstate.com/bobhoge/2024/05/03/columbia-prez-breaks-silence-on-nypds-raid-on-pro-hamas-mob-statement-will-please-exactly-no-one-n2173730</link><description></description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 01:03:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nancy Pelosi, John Kerry, other Biden allies awarded Presidential Medal of Freedom</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/nancy-pelosi-john-kerry-biden-allies-awarded-presidential-medal-freedom</link><description>President Biden awarded 19 individuals with the United States' highest civilian award, the Presidential Medal of Freedom, on Friday — including many Democratic allies.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 22:12:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sen. Vance Decries Biden Opening Obamacare to Migrants</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/vance-biden-daca/2024/05/03/id/1163451</link><description>Sen. J.D. Vance, R-Ohio, decried the actions of President Joe Biden on Friday, saying he is spending Americans' "hard-earned money" to cover the healthcare costs of illegal migrants.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 00:13:51 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>