<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 17:28:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Biden Defines Low Energy in Campaign Meeting, Gets Confused About Candidates - They Don't Seem Impressed</title><link>https://redstate.com/nick-arama/2024/05/08/biden-defines-low-energy-in-campaign-meeting-and-they-dont-seem-impressed-n2173931</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 22:00:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Arkansas cannot prevent 2 teachers from discussing critical race theory in classroom, judge rules</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/arkansas-cannot-prevent-2-teachers-discussing-critical-race-theory-classroom-judge-rules</link><description>U.S. District Judge Lee Rudofsky has ruled 2 Arkansas high school teachers cannot be prevented by the state from discussing critical race theory in their classrooms.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:33:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Administration to Unveil New Asylum Rule</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/joe-biden-asylum-immigration/2024/05/08/id/1163985</link><description>The Biden administration plans to unveil new changes to the asylum system Thursday, including expediting the expulsion of migrants who officials consider national security or public safety risks, according to media reports.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 22:05:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Florida School Shuts Down Christian Club After Complaint From Rabid Atheist Zealots</title><link>https://redstate.com/jeffc/2024/05/08/florida-school-shuts-down-christian-club-after-complaint-from-rabid-atheist-zealots-n2173930</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:55:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>House antisemitism hearing: NYC schools leader reveals case that has 'troubled' him the most</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/house-antisemitism-hearing-nyc-schools-leader-reveals-case-troubled-him-most</link><description>New York City Public Schools Chancellor David Banks on Wednesday told lawmakers there have been 281 reported antisemitic and Islamophobic incidents within his school system since Oct. 7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:28:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Reps. Jordan, Comer Refer Ex-Trump Atty. Cohen to DOJ</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/michael-cohen-donald-trump-merrick-garland/2024/05/08/id/1163979</link><description>Two high-ranking Republican members of Congress have referred the former attorney for Donald Trump to the Department of Justice on the grounds of perjury and knowingly making false statements to Congress.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:29:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RedState Sports Report: It’s May, So Let’s Look at the NFL</title><link>https://redstate.com/jerrywilson/2024/05/08/redstate-sports-report-its-may-so-lets-look-at-the-nfl-n2173929</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stefanik grills NYC schools chief on pro-Hamas teacher kept on payroll after antisemitic riot</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/stefanik-grills-nyc-schools-chief-pro-hamas-teacher-kept-payroll-antisemitic-riot</link><description>Rep. Elise Stefanik, R-N.Y., blasted New York City Public Schools Chancellor David Banks over the former Hillcrest High School principal's employment status after an antisemitic riot.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:25:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sen. Graham Slams Biden Admin. For Pausing Israeli Aid</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/lindsey-graham-joe-biden-israel/2024/05/08/id/1163977</link><description>Sen. Lindsey Graham, R-S.C., slammed the Biden administration Wednesday for pausing Israeli military aid over concerns that the country is planning to launch a full-scale assault in the southern Gaza city of Rafah.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:03:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NAACP Asks Biden to Pardon Marilyn Mosby, Says Baltimore DA Case Was 'Malicious Persecution' by Trump DOJ</title><link>https://redstate.com/mike_miller/2024/05/08/naacp-asks-biden-to-pardon-marilyn-mosby-says-baltimore-da-claims-malicious-prosecution-by-trump-doj-n2173926</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:37:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WATCH: Dem governor swarmed by anti-Israel agitators while celebrating daughter's college graduation</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/gretchen-whitmer-swarmed-anti-israel-protesters-celebrating-daughter-college-graduation</link><description>Video captured anti-Israel protesters swarming Michigan Gov. Gretchen Whitmer as she celebrated her daughter's college graduation at a local restaurant.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:20:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Republicans Seek to Change Census, Reap Benefits</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/census-bill-illegal-immigrants/2024/05/08/id/1163973</link><description>A bill being considered in the House this week would add a citizenship question to future census counts could have big implications.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 20:56:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WaPo Gushes for Brittany Griner As She Plays Victim And Plays Her "Donald Trump" Card</title><link>https://redstate.com/jimthompson/2024/05/08/wapo-gushes-for-brittany-griner-as-she-plays-victims-and-plays-her-donald-trump-card-n2173928</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:04:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fox News Politics: Literal Brain Worms</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/fox-news-politics-literal-brain-worms</link><description>The latest updates from the 2024 campaign trail, exclusive interviews and more Fox News politics content</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:06:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Set to Tighten Asylum Access at US-Mexico Border</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/border/2024/05/08/id/1163971</link><description>The Biden administration is set to tighten access to asylum at the U.S.-Mexico border via a new regulation that could be issued as soon as Thursday, three sources familiar with the matter said, in a targeted move aimed at reducing illegal crossings.The regulation would...</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 20:49:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>