<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 07:54:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Is China More Capitalist Than the United States?</title><link>https://redstate.com/heartlandinstitute/2024/05/08/is-china-more-capitalist-than-the-united-states-n2173904</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:40:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RFK Jr re-ups Trump debate challenge, suggesting venue in 'perfect neutral territory'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/rfk-jr-re-ups-trump-debate-challenge-suggesting-venue-perfect-neutral-territory</link><description>Robert F. Kennedy Jr. challenged former President Trump to a debate at the Libertarian Convention in Washington, D.C., where both are scheduled to appear.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>George Washington Protest Cleared Before Mayor Bowser's House Testimony</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/campus-protests-George-Washington/2024/05/08/id/1163875</link><description>Police began to clear a Pro-Palestinian tent encampment at George Washington University in Washington, D.C., early Wednesday, hours after dozens of protesters left the site and marched to President Ellen Granberg's home.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 11:36:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Latest Data Red Flags That Have to Have Biden Freaking Out</title><link>https://redstate.com/nick-arama/2024/05/07/latest-data-red-flags-that-have-to-have-biden-freaking-out-n2173901</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 03:00:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump says keeping FBI in DC will be 'centerpiece of my plan' rebuilding capital city</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-keeping-fbi-dc-centerpiece-plan-rebuilding-capital-city</link><description>Former President Donald Trump wrote on Tuesday via his social media platform Truth Social that if elected to a second term, he would ensure the FBI headquarters stays in Washington, D.C.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:14:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rep. Jordan to Newsmax: Cases Against Trump 'Falling Apart'</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/jim-jordan-donald-trump-criminal/2024/05/07/id/1163863</link><description>As the case against former President Donald Trump regarding classified documents was put on hold indefinitely by Florida Judge Aileen Cannon, it seems that all the cases against him "are falling apart," Rep. Jim Jordan, R-Ohio, told Newsmax on Tuesday.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 03:18:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blame Game: Judge Merchan Tells Trump Defense They Should Have Objected More to Stormy Daniels' Testimony</title><link>https://redstate.com/bobhoge/2024/05/07/blame-game-judge-merchan-tells-trump-defense-they-should-have-objected-more-to-stormy-daniels-testimony-n2173900</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 01:21:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>California Gov Gavin Newsom roasted over video promoting state's ‘record’ tourism: ‘Smoke and mirrors’</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/california-gov-gavin-newsom-roasted-over-video-promoting-states-record-tourism-smoke-and-mirrors</link><description>Governor Gavin Newsom took to social media over the weekend to announce that California’s tourism is at “an all-time high," while on top of the Golden Gate Bridge.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 11:00:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dems Dread Speaker Johnson's Closed-Door Talks With MTG</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/democrats-house-speaker/2024/05/07/id/1163861</link><description>House Democrats expressed concern as Speaker Mike Johnson, R-La., engages in lengthy discussions with Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene, R-Ga., raising questions about the potential implications of their private negotiations, Axios reported.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 03:00:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Manhattan Trial Tuesday Evening Wrap-Up - 'What the Hell Happened?' Edition</title><link>https://redstate.com/smoosieq/2024/05/07/trump-manhattan-trial-tuesday-evening-wrap-up-what-the-hell-happened-edition-n2173892</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 00:50:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Republicans keep pressure on NPR and controversial CEO amid political bias scandal</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/republicans-pressure-npr-controversial-ceo-political-bias-scandal</link><description>Republicans are keeping the pressure on NPR and CPB after a senior editor at the former alleged a partisan bias in the newsroom that affected coverage.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 09:00:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GOP Rep. Spartz Fends Off Rivals to Win Indiana Primary</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/indiana-primary-election-victoria-spartz/2024/05/07/id/1163860</link><description>Two-term Rep. Victoria Spartz won a contentious Republican primary to defend her seat just months after she decided to run for reelection in a campaign that focused attention on her opposition to sending aid to her native Ukraine.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 02:56:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zelensky and Other Top Ukrainian Leaders Narrowly Avoid Russian Assassination Attempt</title><link>https://redstate.com/streiff/2024/05/07/zelensky-and-other-top-ukrainian-leaders-narrowly-avoid-russian-assassination-attempt-n2173898</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 00:31:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Top 5 moments of Trump trial after 'salacious' Stormy Daniels testimony</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/top-5-moments-of-trump-trial-after-salacious-stormy-daniels-testimony</link><description>Former President Trump's criminal trial reached a fever pitch Tuesday amid salacious testimony from Stormy Daniels that prompted a motion for a mistrial and a scolding from the judge.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 09:00:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rep. Comer to Newsmax: AG Garland Protecting Biden</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/james-comer-merrick-garland-subpoenas/2024/05/07/id/1163859</link><description>Rep. James Comer, R-Ky., said he is certain AG Merrick Garland is trying to protect President Joe Biden by thwarting the House Republicans' impeachment inquiry into allegations of influence peddling and other criminal activity by Biden and members of his family.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 02:53:27 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>