<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 09:14:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Israel Enters Rafah As Negotiations With Hamas Breakdown and Bibi Tells Biden Where to Put It</title><link>https://redstate.com/streiff/2024/05/10/israel-enters-rafah-as-negotiations-with-hamas-breakdown-and-bibi-tells-biden-where-to-put-it-n2174002</link><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:47:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Michael Cohen to testify in Trump trial on Monday</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/michael-cohen-testify-trump-trial-monday</link><description>Michael Cohen, ex-lawyer for former President Donald Trump, is expected to testify on Monday, Fox News has learned. He is expected to be a start witness for DA Alvin Bragg.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 14:06:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Pro-Israel PAC Vows to Help Defeat Biden</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/super-pac-joe-biden-red-line/2024/05/10/id/1164209</link><description>The chief of a new pro-Israel super PAC is vowing to "go all in" on helping to defeat Joe Biden in November after the president's comments about drawing a red line on U.S. aid to Israel.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MORTON: DOL’s Contractor Rule Is a Threat to Truckers' Livelihoods</title><link>https://redstate.com/redstate-guest-editorial/2024/05/10/the-dols-contractor-rule-a-threat-to-truckers-livelihoods-n2173666</link><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:00:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blue state Dems turn on governor as homeless council can't account for $20B in spending</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/blue-state-dems-turn-governor-homeless-council-cant-account-20b-spending</link><description>Democrats and Republicans alike are taking issue with California Gov. Newsom as his homelessness council has failed to track its billions spent on the state's homelessness crisis.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:30:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IRS' Plan to Target Wealthy With Audits 'Incredibly Concerning'</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/irs-audits-wealthy/2024/05/10/id/1164201</link><description>The Internal Revenue Service's plans to aggressively increase audits is "incredibly concerning" to many economists and others who warn of targeting specific economic groups.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:26:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Friday Morning Minute</title><link>https://redstate.com/smoosieq/2024/05/10/friday-morning-minute-n2173998</link><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:00:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alabama legislative session adjourned without final vote on gambling bill: 'Frustrated'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/alabama-legislative-session-adjourned-without-final-vote-gambling-bill-frustrated</link><description>Alabamians won't have a chance to vote on gambling within the state this year after lawmakers failed to come to an agreement during the latest legislative session before it adjourned.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:02:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Prosecutors Prepare to Call Final Witnesses in N.Y. Trial</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/donald-trump-prosecutors-witnesses/2024/05/10/id/1164197</link><description>Donald Trump is set to return to court Friday after porn actor Stormy Daniels' lurid testimony about her alleged sexual encounter with him, as prosecutors prepare to call their final witnesses in the first-ever criminal trial of a sitting or former U.S. president.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:01:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WATCH OUT: NOAA Issues First 'Severe Geomagnetic Storm Watch' in 20 Years, Could Hit Mid-Day Friday</title><link>https://redstate.com/jenvanlaar/2024/05/10/watch-out-noaa-issues-first-severe-geomagnetic-storm-watch-in-20-years-could-hit-mid-day-friday-n2174001</link><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 08:09:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IRS urged to probe tax-exempt groups supporting anti-Israel protests</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/irs-urged-probe-tax-exempt-groups-supporting-anti-israel-protests</link><description>Several Republicans signed onto a letter calling for a number of groups to have their tax-exempt statuses investigated over their support for anti-Israel protests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 09:00:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Playbook for Nationwide Campus Unrest Discovered</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/campus-protests-pro-palestinian-playbook-lawsuit/2024/05/09/id/1164178</link><description>A strategy document for the National Students for Justice in Palestine, the U.S.'s largest pro-Palestinian college campus group, called for a "unity intifada" at colleges across the country on Oct. 8, the day after Hamas' terrorist attack in Israel.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 03:31:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Another Day, Another Biden Whopper - but This One Is Truly Shameless</title><link>https://redstate.com/nick-arama/2024/05/09/biden-shameless-falsehood-n2173994</link><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 02:29:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GOP rep calls on Biden to denounce, reject cash from progressive groups fueling anti-Israel protests</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/biden-should-denounce-progressive-groups-fueling-anti-israel-protests-reject-cash-from-shared-donors-gop-rep</link><description>GOP Rep. Darrell Issa told Fox News Digital it would 'very helpful' if Biden denounced progressive donors who are fueling anti-Israel protests but acknowledged its unlikely.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 09:00:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Axelrod: Biden 'Pride' on Economic Message Could Cost Him WH</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/david-axelrod-joe-biden-pride/2024/05/09/id/1164177</link><description>David Axelrod, a longtime strategist and senior adviser to former President Barack Obama, criticized President Joe Biden for his economic messaging, asserting he should be leading "with empathy" for those who are not experiencing this great economy he continues to tout.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 03:14:12 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>