<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 07:52:33 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>It's 2020 All Over Again. Google Bans Trump Ad Targeting Black Voters</title><link>https://redstate.com/streiff/2024/05/07/its-2020-all-over-again-google-bans-trump-ad-targeting-black-voters-n2173858</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 12:44:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden warns Netanyahu against Rafah invasion as Israel prepares for action</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/biden-warns-netanyahu-rafah-invasion-israel-prepares-action</link><description>President Biden called Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu over the phone on Monday, warning the prime minister against continuing with plans for an invasion of the Gaza city of Rafah.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 12:09:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Heritage Foundation: Biden Admin Colluded With Dem Groups to Sway Vote</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/biden-democrat-groups/2024/05/07/id/1163739</link><description>A new report by the Heritage Foundation's Oversight Project indicates Biden administration officials worked with Democratic Party-aligned groups to craft and implement a seemingly neutrally worded executive order for the practical effect of activating traditionally...</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 12:40:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Power Grab: Biden Admin Tries to Control National Guard, Texas Gov. Greg Abbott Claps Back</title><link>https://redstate.com/bobhoge/2024/05/07/power-grab-biden-admin-tries-to-control-national-guard-texas-gov-greg-abbott-claps-back-n2173856</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 12:00:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Group of conservative judges vows to not hire Columbia University law students due to anti-Israel protests</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/group-conservative-judges-vow-not-hire-columbia-university-law-students-due-anti-israel-protests</link><description>A group of conservative federal judges sent a letter to Columbia President Minouche Shafik, vowing to not hire graduates because of the school's response to anti-Israel protests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 09:00:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Japan Tells US That Biden's 'Xenophobia' Comment Is Regrettable</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/japan-immigration-joe-biden/2024/05/07/id/1163731</link><description>Japan has described as "regrettable" President Joe Biden's comment that "xenophobia" is stifling the Asian nation's economic growth, the top government spokesperson said Tuesday.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 12:02:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tuesday Morning Minute</title><link>https://redstate.com/smoosieq/2024/05/07/tuesday-morning-minute-n2173854</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 11:00:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NY v Trump to resume after former president threatened with jail, told trial to last at least 2 more weeks</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/ny-v-trump-to-resume-after-former-president-threatened-with-jail-told-trial-will-last-at-least-2-more-weeks</link><description>The unprecedented criminal trial of former President Trump resumes Tuesday morning after the 2024 presumptive Republican presidential nominee was again held in contempt of court.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 09:00:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rob Schmitt Investigates: Secret Billionaires' Leftist Crusade</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/rob-schmitt-newsmax-investigation/2024/05/06/id/1163709</link><description>In a Newsmax special presentation, "Rob Schmitt Tonight" turned the spotlight on the network of billionaires and their radical-left causes that are funding everything from the anti-Israel protests on college campuses to making sure Donald Trump never sees a second term.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 03:12:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WATCH: Pro-Hamas Freaks Win Hearts and Minds By Vandalizing a WWI Memorial and Burning an American Flag</title><link>https://redstate.com/bonchie/2024/05/06/watch-pro-hamas-protesters-vandalize-wwi-memorial-and-burn-an-american-flag-in-front-of-it-n2173853</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 02:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GOP committee chair demands answers from DC officials on controversial noncitizen voting law</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/gop-committee-chair-demands-answers-dc-officials-controversial-noncitizen-voting-law</link><description>The head of the House Administration Committee is expressing concern about what he sees as D.C. officials encouraging non-citizen voting in upcoming elections.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 09:00:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Democrat Rep. Tim Kennedy Sworn In, Narrowing GOP Majority</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/democrats-tim-kennedy-sworn-in/2024/05/06/id/1163708</link><description>Rep. Tim Kennedy, D-N.Y., took his oath on the House floor Monday, succeeding retired Rep. Brian Higgins, D-N.Y., tipping the balance of power with the GOP holding just a one-vote margin on any partisan vote, The Hill reported.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 03:08:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Endorsement of Fani Willis May Just Be the Funniest Ever</title><link>https://redstate.com/nick-arama/2024/05/06/this-endorsement-of-fani-willis-may-just-be-the-funniest-ever-n2173851</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 02:46:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Squad' member caught at fundraiser hosted by Islamic leader who praised Hamas attack on Israel</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/squad-member-caught-fundraiser-hosted-islamic-leader-praised-attack-israel</link><description>New York Rep. Jamaal Bowman, a member of the far-left "Squad," was caught attending a fundraiser co-hosted by an Islamic leader who said he was "happy" about the Oct. 7 Hamas attack.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 09:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden to Condemn Antisemitism in Speech Amid Gaza Protests</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/biden-condemn-antisemitism/2024/05/06/id/1163707</link><description>President Joe Biden will speak out against antisemitism at a Holocaust memorial ceremony Tuesday, as tensions remain high over nationwide campus protests against Israel's war in Gaza.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 03:01:03 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>