<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 06:58:09 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Friday Morning Minute</title><link>https://redstate.com/smoosieq/2024/05/10/friday-morning-minute-n2173998</link><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:00:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alabama legislative session adjourned without final vote on gambling bill: 'Frustrated'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/alabama-legislative-session-adjourned-without-final-vote-gambling-bill-frustrated</link><description>Alabamians won't have a chance to vote on gambling within the state this year after lawmakers failed to come to an agreement during the latest legislative session before it adjourned.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:02:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Playbook for Nationwide Campus Unrest Discovered</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/campus-protests-pro-palestinian-playbook-lawsuit/2024/05/09/id/1164178</link><description>A strategy document for the National Students for Justice in Palestine, the U.S.'s largest pro-Palestinian college campus group, called for a "unity intifada" at colleges across the country on Oct. 8, the day after Hamas' terrorist attack in Israel.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 03:31:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WATCH OUT: NOAA Issues First 'Severe Geomagnetic Storm Watch' in 20 Years, Could Hit Mid-Day Friday</title><link>https://redstate.com/jenvanlaar/2024/05/10/watch-out-noaa-issues-first-severe-geomagnetic-storm-watch-in-20-years-could-hit-mid-day-friday-n2174001</link><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 08:09:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IRS urged to probe tax-exempt groups supporting anti-Israel protests</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/irs-urged-probe-tax-exempt-groups-supporting-anti-israel-protests</link><description>Several Republicans signed onto a letter calling for a number of groups to have their tax-exempt statuses investigated over their support for anti-Israel protests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 09:00:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Axelrod: Biden 'Pride' on Economic Message Could Cost Him WH</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/david-axelrod-joe-biden-pride/2024/05/09/id/1164177</link><description>David Axelrod, a longtime strategist and senior adviser to former President Barack Obama, criticized President Joe Biden for his economic messaging, asserting he should be leading "with empathy" for those who are not experiencing this great economy he continues to tout.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 03:14:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Another Day, Another Biden Whopper - but This One Is Truly Shameless</title><link>https://redstate.com/nick-arama/2024/05/09/biden-shameless-falsehood-n2173994</link><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 02:29:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GOP Rep calls on Biden to denounce, reject cash from progressive groups fueling anti-Israel protests</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/biden-should-denounce-progressive-groups-fueling-anti-israel-protests-reject-cash-from-shared-donors-gop-rep</link><description>GOP Rep. Darrell Issa told Fox News Digital it would 'very helpful' if Biden denounced progressive donors who are fueling anti-Israel protests but acknowledged its unlikely.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 09:00:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sen. Ron Johnson to Newsmax: Dems Want Open Borders for Political Gain</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/ron-johnson-democrats-open-border/2024/05/09/id/1164176</link><description>Sen. Ron Johnson, R-Wis., asserted in an interview with Newsmax on Thursday that Democrats are deliberately fostering an open border policy to bolster their political power, allowing millions of undocumented immigrants to enter the country unchecked.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 03:08:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Another One Bites the Dust: Cornell University President Martha Pollack Resigns in Surprise Email</title><link>https://redstate.com/bobhoge/2024/05/09/another-one-bites-the-dust-cornell-university-president-martha-pollack-resigns-in-surprise-email-n2173997</link><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 02:04:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'We are so innocent': Top 5 moments of Trump trial, from mistrial denials to Stormy Daniels' testimony</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/we-are-so-innocent-top-5-moments-trump-trial-mistrial-denials-stormy-daniels-testimony</link><description>Former President Trump will attend court Friday after a week of salacious testimony from Stormy Danials and the denial of multiple mistrial motions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 09:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rep. Waters Backs FDIC Chair After Sexual Harassment Report</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/maxine-waters-fdic-ig/2024/05/09/id/1164175</link><description>The head Democrat on the House Financial Services Committee criticized a third-party investigation of sexual harassment and misconduct at the Federal Deposit Insurance Corp. (FDIC), The Hill reported.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 03:07:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Manhattan Trial Thursday Evening Wrap-Up - Did We Weather the Stormy?</title><link>https://redstate.com/smoosieq/2024/05/09/trump-manhattan-trial-thursday-evening-wrap-up-did-we-weather-the-stormy-n2173989</link><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 01:25:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden admin's National Guard 'power grab' slammed by former general as governors put up rare united front</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/biden-admins-national-guard-power-grab-slammed-former-general-governors-put-rare-united-front</link><description>A plan that could let the Air Force transfer Air National Guard troops to the Space Force has been met with fierce opposition from governors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lara Trump to Newsmax: 'Cool Opportunity' for Barron Trump</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/lara-trump-donald-trump-barron-trump/2024/05/09/id/1164171</link><description>Republican National Committee co-chair Lara Trump told Newsmax on Thursday the political debut of Barron Trump, the youngest son of GOP presumptive nominee Donald Trump, is a "cool opportunity" for him and "historic in so many ways."</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 02:16:03 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>