<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 13:41:37 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Biden Finally Speaks to Campus Chaos During Holocaust Remarks, but He Says One Thing While Doing Another</title><link>https://redstate.com/nick-arama/2024/05/07/biden-holocaust-remarks-n2173868</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:22:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Johnson warned against making 'side deals' with GOP rebels: Don't 'grease a squeaky wheel'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/johnson-warned-making-side-deals-gop-rebels-dont-grease-squeaky-wheel</link><description>House Republican lawmakers are calling on Speaker Mike Johnson to resist acquiescing to the demands of GOP rebels who are threatening to oust him.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:21:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Scheduled for Graduation, Dinner on Same Day</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/donaldtrump-minnesota-graduation/2024/05/07/id/1163800</link><description>It is going to be a busy May 17 for former President Donald Trump. Trump is scheduled to give the keynote address at the Minnesota Republican Party's annual Lincoln-Reagan Dinner on the same day he will be attending his son Barron's graduation from high school.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:19:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mike Johnson Meets With Marjorie Taylor Greene to Hash Out Their Differences Amid Ouster Threats</title><link>https://redstate.com/jeffc/2024/05/07/mike-johnson-meets-with-marjorie-taylor-greene-to-hash-out-their-differences-amid-ouster-threats-n2173874</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:05:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hamas sympathizers could be added to list that includes terrorist suspects if GOP bill becomes law</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/hamas-sympathizers-could-be-added-list-includes-terrorist-suspects-if-gop-bill-becomes-law</link><description>Legislation by a Republican senator would put terrorist supporters on the no-fly list, including if they had been disciplined for such conduct, in response to college protests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:09:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Mediating Rep. Greene, Speaker Johnson Impasse</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/donald-trump-mike-johnson-marjorie-taylor-greene/2024/05/07/id/1163798</link><description>Former President Donald Trump is not only making public statements in support of House Speaker Mike Johnson, R-La., but he is trying to mediate between the speaker and the Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene, R-Ga., threat to file a notice to vacate.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:13:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WATCH: The Sidenote to the UNC-Chapel Hill Palestinian Flag Raising That Makes It So Much Worse</title><link>https://redstate.com/sister-toldjah/2024/05/07/the-sidenote-to-the-unc-chapel-hill-palestinian-flag-raising-that-makes-it-so-much-worse-n2173869</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:55:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chip Roy demands sanctions on ICC officials going after US, Israel</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/chip-roy-demands-sanctions-on-icc-officials-going-after-us-israel</link><description>House GOP lawmakers are pushing for a new bill to force President Biden to sanction ICC officials who go after Americans or U.S. allies.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:00:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bipartisan Bill Introduced to Recoup UNRWA Funds</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/unrwa-israel-hamas/2024/05/07/id/1163795</link><description>Bipartisan members of Congress are seeking a refund on U.S. aid that was given to a controversial United Nations agency this year.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:44:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WATCH: The Tornadic Devastation of Barnsdall, Oklahoma, Drives Home the Importance of Weather Awareness</title><link>https://redstate.com/smoosieq/2024/05/07/watch-the-tornadic-devastation-of-barnsdall-oklahoma-drives-home-the-importance-of-weather-awareness-n2173867</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:45:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Flights for illegal immigrants without IDs targeted in FAA bill as deadline looms</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/flights-illegal-immigrants-ids-targeted-faa-bill-deadline-looms</link><description>GOP senators are looking to include a measure in the FAA reauthorization bill to stop illegal immigrants from flying without proper identification.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:00:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Condemns Antisemitism at Holocaust Memorial</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/president-joe-biden-condemns-antisemitism/2024/05/07/id/1163794</link><description>President Joe Biden on Tuesday warned that the threat of antisemitism is growing, in remarks honoring the 6 million Jews killed in the Holocaust, as his support for Israel's assault on Gaza divides his Democratic Party.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:38:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bitter Man-Child David Hogg Announces 'One Thing Men Want,' Is Mocked Into Middle of Next Week</title><link>https://redstate.com/mike_miller/2024/05/07/bitter-leftist-david-hogg-declares-the-one-thing-men-want-is-mocked-into-middle-of-next-week-n2173865</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:25:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eric Trump slams Stormy's testimony from front row court seat: 'Garbage'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/eric-trump-slams-stormys-testimony-front-row-court-seat-garbage</link><description>Eric Trump, former President Donald Trump's son, slammed the Manhattan trial's testimony from former pornographic actress Stormy Daniels as "garbage."</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:50:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Philadelphia Set to Clear Homeless Encampment, 'Drug Market'</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/philadelphia-homeless-encampment/2024/05/07/id/1163793</link><description>Philadelphia will clear a homeless encampment Wednesday out of an area that is known as the center of the city's opioid crisis, a fulfillment of a campaign promise of recently elected Mayor Cherelle Parker.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:37:32 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>