<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 07:11:41 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Over the Line: Georgia Rep. Collins Posts Tasteless Tweet Mocking RFK Jr. Over Family's Assassinations</title><link>https://redstate.com/bobhoge/2024/05/08/over-the-line-georgia-rep-collins-posts-tasteless-tweet-mocking-rfk-jr-over-familys-assassinations-n2173953</link><description></description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 03:30:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Barron Trump to enter politics as Florida delegate at GOP convention</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/barron-trump-enter-politics-florida-delegate-gop-convention</link><description>Barron Trump, the youngest child of former President Trump will enter the political fray for the first time when he will be an at-large delegate to the Republican National Convention.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 12:01:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Barron Trump, 18, to Make Political Debut</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/election-president-republican/2024/05/08/id/1164009</link><description>Former President Donald Trump's youngest son, Barron Trump, has been chosen to serve as a Florida delegate to the Republican National Convention, the state party chairman said Wednesday.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 03:43:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden's Comment About Trump in Burnett Interview Has Everyone Talking About Dems and 'Small Ds'</title><link>https://redstate.com/nick-arama/2024/05/08/biden-remarks-on-trump-n2173951</link><description></description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 02:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alabama lawmakers strengthen penalties for falsely reporting a crime after Carlee Russell kidnapping hoax</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/alabama-strengthen-penalties-falsely-reporting-crime-carlee-russell-kidnapping-hoax</link><description>Falsely reporting a crime to law enforcement is one step away from becoming a felony in certain circumstances in Alabama after the bill passed the state legislature on Wednesday.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 10:45:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sen. Paul to Newsmax: Biden Immigration Policies Led to Tragic Murder</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/rand-paul-biden-immigration/2024/05/08/id/1164006</link><description>In a scathing rebuke of the Biden administration's immigration policies, Sen. Rand Paul, R-Ky., asserted that the recent murder of nursing student Laken Riley should be enough for Americans to reject the administration's approach.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 02:54:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Joe Biden's Insane Interview With Erin Burnett Should Be the Final Straw for American Voters</title><link>https://redstate.com/bonchie/2024/05/08/joe-bidens-insane-interview-with-erin-burnett-should-be-the-final-straw-for-american-voters-n2173950</link><description></description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 02:17:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden national security adviser's wife launches run for House seat in key swing state</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/biden-national-security-advisers-wife-launches-run-house-seat-key-swing-state</link><description>Maggie Goodlander, a former top Biden administration official and the wife of National Security Adviser Jake Sullivan, launches a Democratic congressional campaign in battleground New Hampshire</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 10:30:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>British MP Lammy to Newsmax: UK Can Work With Trump If He Wins</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/david-lammy-uk-donald-trump/2024/05/08/id/1164005</link><description>David Lammy, Britain's Shadow Foreign Secretary, told Newsmax on Wednesday that although he has been a critic of Donald Trump, he is confident his country can work with the former president should he prevail in November's election.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 02:19:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WATCH: Gutfeld Mocks Kristi Noem Over Show Cancelation, Hilariously 'Interviews' Dana as Noem, Instead</title><link>https://redstate.com/mike_miller/2024/05/08/gutfeld-torches-kristi-noem-over-last-minute-cancelation-hilariously-interviews-dana-as-noem-instead-n2173939</link><description></description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 01:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FIRST ON FOX: Biden gets boost from major health care group warning Trump poses 'threat to public health'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/biden-boost-major-healthcare-group-warning-trump-threat-public-health</link><description>A group of 48 former high-level medical officials have penned a letter pleading with Americans not to put former President Trump back in the White House.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 10:00:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FDA Chief Tells Senate Agency Is Preparing for Bird Flu Mutation</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/fda-bird-flu-robert-califf/2024/05/08/id/1164004</link><description>The Food and Drug Administration (FDA) informed legislators on Wednesday that the agency is making preparatory measures in case the current avian flu is able to mutate and transmit to humans on a massive scale.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 01:19:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Gets Busted on Big Lie in Wisconsin With New, Ridiculous Tall Tale</title><link>https://redstate.com/nick-arama/2024/05/08/biden-gets-busted-on-big-lie-in-wisconsin-with-new-ridiculous-tall-tale-n2173947</link><description></description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 01:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ohio AG defends letter warning 'woke' masked anti-Israel protesters they face prison time: 'We have a society'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/ohio-ag-defends-letter-warning-woke-masked-anti-israel-protesters-they-face-prison-time-we-have-a-society</link><description>Ohio's Republican Attorney General is pushing back against 'woke' critics of his recent letter reminding anti-Israel protesters of a law that could mean prison time.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 09:00:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Israeli Amb Slams Dem Accusations of Withholding Aid to Gaza</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/michael-herzog-democrats-aid/2024/05/08/id/1164003</link><description>Israel's ambassador to the United States, Michael Herzog, has strongly rebuked nearly 90 lawmakers for accusing Israel of purposefully withholding humanitarian aid from Gaza's 2.2 million Palestinians, Politico reported.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 00:53:55 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>