<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 23:56:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>WATCH: ASU Senior Is Triggered After Learning Her Arrest During Pro-Hamas Protests Has Consequences</title><link>https://redstate.com/beccalower/2024/05/04/watch-asu-senior-is-triggered-after-learning-getting-arrested-during-pro-hamas-protests-has-consequences-n2173768</link><description></description><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 03:38:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anti-Israel groups accuse Chicago, DNC of trying to ‘protect’ Biden from protests at 2024 Dem convention</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/anti-israel-groups-accuse-chicago-dnc-trying-protect-biden-protests-2024-dem-convention</link><description>A coalition of anti-Israel agitators claim their First Amendment Rights have been violated by Chicago as they seek to protest outside the Democratic National Convention in August.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 20:56:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dick Morris to Newsmax: Biden 'Waffling' Finally Costing Him in Polls</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/joe-biden-terrorists-antisemites/2024/05/04/id/1163503</link><description>President Joe Biden attempted to hang on to votes of antisemitic leftists who support Hamas' campaign against Israel's existence, but ultimately they have abandon him along with those Democrats who support Israel, presidential campaign adviser Dick Morris warned.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 23:27:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Video May Explain Part of the Reason Joe Biden Seems Clueless on the Economy</title><link>https://redstate.com/nick-arama/2024/05/04/this-video-of-jared-bernstein-explains-why-biden-team-economic-understanding-is-such-a-mess-n2173763</link><description></description><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 02:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Conservative beer brand plans 'Frat Boy Summer' event celebrating college students who defended American flag</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/conservative-beer-brand-plans-frat-boy-summer-event-celebrating-college-students-defended-american-flag</link><description>Ultra Right Beer Company will host an event at a UNC-Chapel Hill fraternity house to celebrate the actions of the students who defended the American flag from anti-Israel protesters.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 18:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jim McLaughlin to Newsmax: Trump Has Deep Bench of VP Choices</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/jim-mclaughlin-luke-ball-trump/2024/05/04/id/1163502</link><description>A wide slate of potential running mates for former President Donald Trump is in Florida this weekend while he works to narrow down his shortlist, but that just shows "how deep the bench is right now," pollster Jim McLaughlin told Newsmax Saturday.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 23:17:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Still a Big Issue': Jim Jordan Predicts 'Urban Crime' Will Have 'Electoral Consequences' for Biden</title><link>https://redstate.com/mike_miller/2024/05/04/still-a-big-issue-jim-jordan-predicts-urban-crime-rate-electoral-consequences-for-biden-in-november-n2173739</link><description></description><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 01:20:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Stop the invasion': Migrant flights in battleground state ignite bipartisan backlash from lawmakers</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/stop-invasion-migrant-flights-battleground-state-ignite-bipartisan-backlash-lawmakers</link><description>Montana representatives are sounding the alarm on the southern border crisis, after a group of migrants flew into state late Wednesday night.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 15:31:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Campus Protests Wane After Crackdowns, Biden Rebuke</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/campus-protests-israel/2024/05/04/id/1163499</link><description>Pro-Palestinian protests that have rocked U.S. campuses for weeks were more muted Friday after a series of clashes with police, mass arrests, and a stern White House directive to restore order.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 22:20:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HOT TAKES: Joe Biden, Actor Mark Hamill Mocked Into Next Week Over Creepy Star Wars Video</title><link>https://redstate.com/bobhoge/2024/05/04/hot-takes-joe-biden-actor-mark-hamill-mocked-into-next-week-over-creepy-star-wars-video-n2173764</link><description></description><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 00:27:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Former Trump official announces major 'Deport Them All' border initiative amid bid to flip crucial Senate seat</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/former-trump-official-deport-them-all-border-plan-bid-flip-battleground-senate-seat</link><description>Dr. Jeff Gunter, Republican Nevada Senate candidate and former U.S. ambassador to Iceland, announced a new initiative to help end the border crisis.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 14:00:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bernie Kerik to Newsmax: Root Out Funders of Anti-Israel Unrest</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/bernie-kerik-police-protests/2024/05/04/id/1163496</link><description>The Biden Justice Department must take a moment out of its busy schedule pursuing Donald Trump or Catholics or school board protesters, according to former NYPD Commissioner Bernie Kerik on Newsmax, and hunt down the funders of the anti-Israel protests.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 21:39:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Former Police Chief Jailed for Alleged Sexual Assault at Pennsylvania Rehab Center</title><link>https://redstate.com/jeffc/2024/05/04/former-police-chief-jailed-for-alleged-sexual-assault-at-pennsylvania-rehab-center-n2173762</link><description></description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 23:35:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Georgia senators find little oversight over how Fani Willis spends taxpayer dollars: 'Like the Wild West'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/georgia-senators-find-little-oversight-fani-willis-spends-taxpayer-dollars-like-wild-west</link><description>Georgia lawmakers heard testimony from Fulton County officials Friday that suggested there is little oversight over how District Attorney Fani Willis manages her $36.6 million budget.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 13:08:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rep. Lawler to Newsmax: Must Stop Antisemitic Hate, Violence</title><link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/lawler-antisemitism-protests/2024/05/04/id/1163492</link><description>While colleges and universities should should support and encourage the expression of ideas, violence and antisemitic hate are unacceptable and must be thwarted, Rep. Mike Lawler told on Newsmax Saturday.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 20:19:29 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>