<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>AP News - US News</title><link>https://apnews.com/us-news</link><description>Top US News stories from AP News</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 15:36:40 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Missouri lawsuits allege abuse by priests, nuns; archdiocese leader in Omaha among those accused</title><link>https://apnews.com/article/church-abuse-allegations-missouri-nebraska-6d7913d8a612ff99996a171969033b58</link><description>Sixty people allege in new lawsuits filed in Missouri that they were abused as children by dozens of priests, nuns and others, and the man who now leads the Archdiocese of Omaha, Nebraska, is among the accused.</description><pubDate>2024-07-25T15:36:40.340679</pubDate></item><item><title>Video game performers will go on strike over artificial intelligence concerns</title><link>https://apnews.com/article/sagaftra-video-game-performers-ai-strike-4f4c7d846040c24553dbc2604e5b6034</link><description>Hollywood’s video game performers are going on strike, throwing part of the entertainment industry into another work stoppage after talks for a new contract with major game studios broke down over artificial intelligence protections.</description><pubDate>2024-07-25T15:36:40.340787</pubDate></item><item><title>Man dies at 27 from heat exposure at a Georgia prison, lawsuit says</title><link>https://apnews.com/article/georgia-prison-death-heat-lawsuit-department-corrections-27b73f63e450bb10f29098ad2e1c26e2</link><description>Juan Ramirez Bibiano, an inmate at Telfair State Prison in Georgia, died of heart and lung failure after officers left him in an outdoor cell in the summer heat for five hours without water or ice, despite instructions from a warden to limit the amount of time inmates spend outdoors, a lawsuit filed</description><pubDate>2024-07-25T15:36:40.340850</pubDate></item></channel></rss>