<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 08:44:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Nicki Minaj's Fans Fuming Over Disaster Dublin Gig, Turns Up Late, Short Set</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/10/nicki-minaj-fans-refund-dublin-concert-late-costume-changes-curfew/</link><description>Nicki Minaj fans are pissed off -- this after they paid big bucks for tickets, only for her to show up over 90 minutes late for her Dublin gig ... lea...</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:10:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oil prices log first gain in 4 sessions with crude supply down a second straight week</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/oil-prices-fall-after-weak-china-data-sparks-demand-concerns-f4cae71d?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Oil futures finished higher Wednesday for the first time in four sessions, finding support after official U.S. data revealed a weekly decline in crude...</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 21:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Baked Alaska</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/baked-alaska/</link><description>Impress everyone with this gorgeous Baked Alaska dessert! It’s surprisingly easy to make with just 5 ingredients. Layers of cake,…</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What is laryngeal chondrosarcoma?</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/what-is-laryngeal-chondrosarcoma/</link><description>You may have heard about a recent first at Mayo Clinic, a total larynx transplant. What you may not have heard was what precipitated that transplant. ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:25:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elon Musk does not owe ex-Twitter staffers $500 million in severance, court rules</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/10/elon-musk-does-not-owe-ex-twitter-staffers-500-million-in-severance-court-rules/</link><description>Elon Musk faces several lawsuits for firing more than 6,000 Twitter employees, including then-CEO Parag Agrawal, following Musk’s 2022 takeover of the...</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 20:58:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IHG negatively changed its dynamic award pricing algorithm: Here’s what we know</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/ihg-points-devaluation/</link><description>IHG One Rewards slowly rolled out dynamic award pricing in 2020, starting with properties in Greater China and eventually reaching U.S. properties. Th...</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 21:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wander Franco Formally Charged With Sexual Abuse Against A Minor</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/10/wander-franco-formally-charged-sexual-abuse-against-minor-dominican-republic-tampa-bay-rays/</link><description>Tampa Bay Rays star shortstop Wander Franco has been formally charged with sexual abuse and sexual exploitation against a minor in the Dominican Repub...</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:10:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The stock market now is ‘numb to all news’ — but the trend is still your friend</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/the-stock-market-now-is-numb-to-all-news-but-the-trend-is-still-your-friend-0613751d?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>The U.S. market is due for a correction, this veteran trader says — but he’s staying invested.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 20:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Homemade Boursin Cheese</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/homemade-boursin-cheese/</link><description>Homemade Boursin Cheese is soft, creamy, and bursting with herbal flavor. Its texture is similar to cream cheese, making it…</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 02:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tomorrow’s Cure: How DNA guides cancer detection</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/tomorrows-cure-how-dna-guides-cancer-detection/</link><description>What if you knew you'd get sick before you ever felt symptoms? If it was a cold, that information is useful. In the case of cancer, it is lifesaving. ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 13:46:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meta will soon let kids aged 10 to 12 interact with others in VR with their parents’ approval</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/10/meta-will-soon-let-kids-aged-10-to-12-interact-with-others-in-vr-with-their-parents-approval/</link><description>Meta announced on Wednesday that users aged 10 to 12 will soon be able to interact with others in VR if they have their parents’ approval to do so. Up...</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 19:14:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Now open: Finnair’s huge new Schengen Lounge with expanded capacity and space for Oneworld elite members</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/finnair-new-lounge/</link><description>Editor’s note: This post was updated with new information. Finnair is showing off photos of its new Schengen Lounge that opened at Helsinki Airport (H...</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 20:30:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>George Stephanopoulos Says Biden Can't Serve Another 4 Years</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/09/george-stephanopoulos-president-joe-biden-cant-serve-4-more-years-sidewalk-election/</link><description>6:28 PM PT -- George Stephanopoulos tells TMZ in a statement from his rep, "Earlier today, I responded to a question from a passerby. I shouldn't have...</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:10:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>They don’t make $1.8 million houses like they used to: Home inspectors use TikTok to reveal ‘shoddy’ new homes</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/they-dont-make-1-8-million-houses-like-they-used-to-home-inspectors-use-tiktok-to-reveal-shoddy-new-homes-58c8f61c?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>In TikTok videos, home inspectors are highlighting flaws in newly built homes, some of which can cost upwards of $1 million.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 20:22:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Make Cheesecake (The Ultimate Guide)</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/how-to-make-cheesecake/</link><description>Cheesecake is my absolute FAVORITE dessert! I have perfected my method and I can’t wait to teach you how to…</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Breaking the silence: First known total larynx transplant on a patient with active cancer as part of landmark clinical trial</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/breaking-the-silence-first-known-total-larynx-transplant-on-a-patient-with-active-cancer-as-part-of-landmark-clinical-trial/</link><description>On Feb. 29, Marty Kedian made history by successfully undergoing a groundbreaking surgery at Mayo Clinic that is providing hope to thousands who have ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AWS App Studio promises to generate enterprise apps from a written prompt</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/10/aws-app-studio-promises-to-generate-enterprise-apps-from-a-written-prompt/</link><description>Generative AI is everywhere these days, but Amazon Web Services has been perceived in some circles as being late to the game. In reality it’s still ea...</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>It’s back: Sapphire Reserve holders can enroll for Marriott Bonvoy Gold status</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/sapphire-reserve-marriott-bonvoy-gold/</link><description>Editor’s note: This post has been updated with the latest information. There’s good news for Chase Sapphire Reserve® cardholders: Chase and Marriott h...</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 20:00:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Barron Trump Makes Debut at His Father's Rally for President</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/10/barron-trump-appearance-debut-rally-campaign-donald-biden-florida-doral/</link><description>Barron Trump made a surprise appearance at his father's campaign rally in Florida Tuesday night, and he quickly became the crowd favorite ... even bri...</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:10:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Paris Olympics will cost an estimated $8.2 billion to host. Here’s how that compares with other recent Olympics.</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/the-paris-olympics-will-cost-an-estimated-8-2-billion-to-host-heres-how-that-compares-with-other-recent-olympics-67131100?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>The 2014 Winter Olympics in Sochi were the most expensive ever, costing nearly $25 billion.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 20:19:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Creamy Pesto Sauce (Dairy-Free)</title><link>https://minimalistbaker.com/creamy-pesto-sauce/</link><description>We’re throwing a pesto party, and you’re invited! With all the herby, savory goodness of traditional basil pesto, this CREAMY dairy-free pesto SAUCE i...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic marks medical milestone with world’s first known successful total larynx transplant performed in a patient with an active cancer as part of a clinical trial</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-marks-medical-milestone-with-worlds-first-known-successful-total-larynx-transplant-performed-in-a-patient-with-an-active-cancer-as-part-of-a-clinical-trial/</link><description>PHOENIX — Mayo Clinic announces a groundbreaking achievement in organ transplantation, offering hope to thousands who have lost their ability to speak...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 13:34:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TechCrunch Minute: The FTC bans anonymous social app NGL from serving minors</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/video/techcrunch-minute-the-ftc-bans-anonymous-social-app-ngl-from-serving-minors/</link><description>Not gonna lie, things aren’t looking great for NGL. The Federal Trade Commission (FTC) is banning NGL from serving minors or advertising to them, mark...</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Threat to credit card rewards growing as states look to regulate</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/credit-card-rewards-legislation-roundup/</link><description>The battle against swipe fees is heating up. If you’ve been reading TPG for the past year and a half, you’ve probably seen our reporting on the Credit...</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 19:00:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Competitive Eater Nick Wehry Accused Of Cheating In Hot Dog Contest, Denies Claim</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/10/competitive-eater-nick-wehry-accused-cheating-hot-dog-contest-denies-claim/</link><description>Competitive eater Nick Wehry -- husband of women's champ Miki Sudo -- is facing bombshell allegations stemming from this year's hot dog contest ... be...</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:10:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sorry, but retiring ‘comfortably’ with $100,000 in savings is a myth for most people. Here’s why.</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/sorry-but-retiring-comfortably-on-100k-is-a-myth-for-most-people-heres-why-4fa709b1?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>There are a lot of ifs involved in just being “OK” at that savings level, too.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 20:10:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tater Tot Nachos</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/tater-tot-nachos/</link><description>Tater Tot Nachos (Totchos) are made with crispy golden tater tots, topped with seasoned beef, scoops of refried beans, corn,…</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Preeclampsia’s lingering shadow</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/preeclampsias-lingering-shadow/</link><description>Researchers are searching for a cure for preeclampsia and have just uncovered some biomarkers that may lead to future treatments. The post Preeclampsi...</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Microsoft emails that warned customers of Russian hacks criticized for looking like spam and phishing</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/10/microsoft-emails-that-warned-customers-of-russian-hacks-criticized-for-looking-like-spam-and-phishing/</link><description>Cybersecurity experts are criticizing Microsoft for data breach notification emails that are confusing customers. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserv...</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 17:52:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Best Mediterranean cruises in 2024 and 2025</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/best-mediterranean-cruises-to-book/</link><description>The Mediterranean region has it all — amazing food and wine, famous historical and cultural landmarks, scenic seaside towns and gorgeous island beache...</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 19:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>