<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 22:42:10 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Mauricio Umansky Snuggles Up With Actress Nikita Kahn In Greece</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/19/mauricio-umansky-holding-hands-actress-nikita-kahn-greece/</link><description>Mauricio Umansky is logging some quality time with actress Nikita Kahn over in Greece ... snuggling up at a famous beach club and looking very much li...</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 03:38:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bitcoin jumps thanks to Trump, as investors weigh Democratic ticket change</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/bitcoin-jumps-while-tech-stocks-slump-thanks-to-trump-and-crowdstrike-outage-fd0867f7?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Bitcoin’s price jumped on Friday as crypto investors continued to be buoyed by Republican presidential front-runner Donald Trump’s embrace of digital ...</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 01:56:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Grilled Tri-Tip</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/grilled-tri-tip/</link><description>Grilled Tri-Tip is a flavorful, juicy steak that will be the star of your barbecue! It’s marinated in a simple,…</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: Preventing traveler’s diarrhea</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-preventing-travelers-diarrhea/</link><description>Traveler's diarrhea is a common and uncomfortable digestive tract disorder that can affect people when they travel to new environments. According to t...</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Faulty CrowdStrike update causes major global IT outage, taking out banks, airlines and businesses globally</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/19/faulty-crowdstrike-update-causes-major-global-it-outage-taking-out-banks-airlines-and-businesses-globally/</link><description>Security giant CrowdStrike said the outage was not caused by a cyberattack, as businesses anticipate widespread disruption. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rig...</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 02:01:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deal alert: Points and miles travel deals for July 2024</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/points-and-miles-travel-deals/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. Some of the below offers may be targeted. Citi is a TPG ad...</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 23:00:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Philadelphia Gunwoman Allegedly Shoots Baby, Parents Flee Without Him</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/19/philadelphia-woman-shoots-baby-leg-parents-flee-video/</link><description>A seven-month-old baby in Philadelphia is miraculously in stable condition after being shot and left to fend for himself -- with his ordeal caught on ...</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 03:38:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘I’m not jealous — just genuinely curious’: How can a woman work from home and mind her 3-year-old child at the same time?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/im-not-jealous-just-genuinely-curious-how-can-a-woman-work-from-home-and-mind-her-3-year-old-child-at-the-same-time-14a9c311?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>“What do you all think about employees who work from home and have little kids to watch at the same time?”</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 01:37:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sugar Cream Pie (Hoosier Pie)</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/sugar-cream-pie/</link><description>Sugar cream pie, or Hoosier pie, is a creamy, delicious treat with deep roots in the Midwest, especially in Indiana.…</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In case you missed it: This week’s Top 5 stories on social media</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/in-case-you-missed-it-this-weeks-top-5-stories-on-social-media-20/</link><description>Check out a few of the most popular News Network stories on @mayoclinic social media this past week. Can you prevent cancer with lifestyle changes? Ne...</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>US cyber agency CISA says malicious hackers are ‘taking advantage’ of CrowdStrike outage</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/19/us-cyber-agency-cisa-says-malicious-hackers-are-taking-advantage-of-crowdstrike-outage/</link><description>CISA confirmed the CrowdStrike outage was not caused by a cyberattack, but urged caution as malicious hackers exploit the situation. © 2024 TechCrunch...</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 01:55:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to skip long rental car pick-up lines for free</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/avoid-waiting-in-rental-car-line/</link><description>Editor’s note: This post has been updated with new information. The last thing you want after your flight is to see a long car rental pick-up line — o...</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 22:00:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Richard Simmons' Cause of Death Still Unknown, Buried in L.A.</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/19/richard-simmons-cause-of-death-still-unknown-buried-los-angeles/</link><description>Richard Simmons' death certificate sheds no further light on the mystery surrounding his death ... but does provide some interesting details on his fi...</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 03:38:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘She screamed and raged at me’: I have power of attorney for my mother’s $3 million estate — but my sister feels sidelined. How do I get her off my back?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/she-screamed-and-raged-at-me-i-have-power-of-attorney-for-my-mothers-3-million-estate-but-my-sister-feels-sidelined-how-do-i-get-her-off-my-back-b5bc0a83?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>“I want to act ethically and responsibly on behalf of our mother.”</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 01:35:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Boursin Pork Chops</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/boursin-pork-chops/</link><description>Boursin Pork Chops are savory, tender, and covered in a delicious cheesy cream sauce. This one-pan recipe is the perfect easy…</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Demystifying my diagnosis of autism</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/demystifying-my-diagnosis-of-autism/</link><description>After receiving a diagnosis of autism as an adult, a Mayo Clinic graduate student addressed her educational needs — and embarked on research to make t...</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>These startups are trying to prevent another CrowdStrike-like outage, according to VCs</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/19/these-startups-are-trying-to-prevent-another-crowdstrike-like-outage-according-to-vcs/</link><description>The global outage is a perfect reminder how much of the world relies on technological infrastructure. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For pers...</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 01:11:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quick Points: Earn bonus points and miles by booking group travel</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/earn-bonus-points-miles-booking-group-travel/</link><description>Trips with family and friends can be a blast for everyone involved — and a great opportunity for you to even earn extra points and miles. You can easi...</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 21:00:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Joy Behar Calls Trump Narcissist for Saying God Helped Him During Shooting</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/19/joy-behar-donald-trump-narcissist-claims-god-watched-over-during-shooting/</link><description>Joy Behar's Sunday schooling Donald Trump on live TV ... slamming the former prez for claiming God was watching out for him during the attempt on his ...</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 03:38:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘She’s a danger to herself’: Our late brother left us $3 million, but my sister is in hospital with schizophrenia. Should I take control of her finances?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/i-want-to-get-control-of-her-money-my-brother-left-my-sister-and-me-3-million-but-she-is-in-hospital-with-schizophrenia-will-this-inheritance-be-the-worst-thing-for-her-0f5cabe2?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>“At the moment, we are both in Florida, but the inheritance is in a California probate court.”</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 01:31:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sheet Pan Ratatouille with Crispy Baked Tofu</title><link>https://minimalistbaker.com/sheet-pan-ratatouille-with-crispy-baked-tofu/</link><description>What could be better than the saucy, savory goodness of classic ratatouille!? Answer: SHEET PAN ratatouille! Say “au revoir” to stovetop babysitting, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: Role of the larynx and how to protect it</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-role-of-the-larynx-and-how-to-protect-it/</link><description>A medical milestone at Mayo Clinic, a total larynx transplant performed on a patient with active cancer, has generated headlines recently in the medic...</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CrowdStrike outage: How your plane, train and automobile travel may be affected</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/19/crowdstrike-outage-how-your-plane-train-and-automobile-travel-may-be-affected/</link><description>The CrowdStrike outage that hit early Friday morning and knocked out computers running Microsoft Windows has grounded flights globally. Major U.S. air...</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 00:37:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 10 best hotels in Scottsdale, Arizona, for a dreamy desert getaway</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/best-hotels-scottsdale/</link><description>Set amid the scenic Sonoran Desert, dotted with towering Saguaro cacti and under the gaze of majestic Camelback Mountain, Scottsdale is a true oasis t...</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 20:30:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Brittney Griner, Wife Welcome Baby Boy</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/19/brittney-griner-wife-birth-son-wnba-all-star-mercury/</link><description>Brittney Griner made a special announcement Friday ... she and her wife, Cherelle, have welcomed their first child!! The Phoenix Mercury star dropped ...</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 03:38:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘I’ve been locked in a battle to recoup my money’: My debit card was cloned and charged $2,300, but my bank insists my actual card was used. What can I do?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/ive-been-locked-in-a-battle-to-recoup-my-money-my-debit-card-was-cloned-and-charged-2-300-but-my-bank-insists-my-actual-card-was-used-what-can-i-do-5c7065a5?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>“At the time, I only had one family member in the state, and they did not have access to the card.”</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 01:27:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Red Robin Campfire Sauce</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/red-robin-campfire-sauce/</link><description>Red Robin campfire sauce is the best pairing for your burgers, fries, and more. Whip it up in minutes with…</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic recognized for disability inclusion</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-recognized-for-disability-inclusion/</link><description>Mayo Clinic recently received the highest possible score on the Disability Equality Index and was named a "Best Place To Work For Disability Inclusion...</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 14:10:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Don’t Fall for CrowdStrike Outage Scams</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/crowdstrike-outage-support-scams/</link><description>Swindlers are spinning up bogus websites in an attempt to dupe people with “CrowdStrike support” scams following the security firm's catastrophic soft...</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 00:19:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Yet another giant cruise ship is heading to Los Angeles as competition heats up</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/royal-caribbean-los-angeles-cruise-ovation/</link><description>Cruise fans in Southern California are about to have another major option for sailings to Mexico. This week, Royal Caribbean executives revealed that ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 20:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>