<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 02:39:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Thomas Matthew Crooks Was in College Honors Society, Set to Transfer to University</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/18/thomas-matthew-crooks-honors-society-college-set-transfer-university/</link><description>Thomas Matthew Crooks was a member of an academic group in college -- and before he tried killing Donald Trump, he was all set to transfer to a univer...</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 07:54:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CrowdStrike stock could see its worst day ever after worldwide outages</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/crowdstrike-stock-could-see-its-worst-day-ever-after-worldwide-outages-426f0999?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>CrowdStrike Holdings may be looking at worst single-day stock-market performance ever, after a computer outage worldwide was pinned on the cybersecuri...</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 12:36:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Grilled Tri-Tip</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/grilled-tri-tip/</link><description>Grilled Tri-Tip is a flavorful, juicy steak that will be the star of your barbecue! It’s marinated in a simple,…</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: Role of the larynx and how to protect it</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-role-of-the-larynx-and-how-to-protect-it/</link><description>A medical milestone at Mayo Clinic, a total larynx transplant performed on a patient with active cancer, has generated headlines recently in the medic...</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>We Asked AI to Take Us On a Tour of Our Cities. It Was Chaos</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/littlefoot-ai-chatbot-travel-planner/</link><description>We had a specialty chatbot to curate perfect days out in London and New York for under $100 each. We're still recovering from our journeys.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Major global IT outage derails travel — everything we know so far</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/crowdstrike-it-outage-travel-delays-cancelations/</link><description>A global Windows operating system glitch has caused significant disruptions across various industries worldwide, including travel. The major IT outage...</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 12:41:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hulk Hogan Speaking At RNC, Loves America &amp; Eager to Support Trump</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/18/hulk-hogan-speaking-republican-national-convention-rnc-support-trump/</link><description>Hulk Hogan is gearing up to back Donald Trump at the RNC with all the enthusiasm of a wrestling match -- 'cause he thinks he needs his support now mor...</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 07:54:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I’m 42, married with kids and live overseas. I don’t have a 401(k) and I don’t expect Social Security. What can I do?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/im-42-married-with-kids-and-live-overseas-i-dont-have-a-401-k-and-i-dont-expect-social-security-what-can-i-do-ad5d81e6?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>“My employer typically gives housing, insurance, and schooling.”</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 12:34:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sugar Cream Pie (Hoosier Pie)</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/sugar-cream-pie/</link><description>Sugar cream pie, or Hoosier pie, is a creamy, delicious treat with deep roots in the Midwest, especially in Indiana.…</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic recognized for disability inclusion</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-recognized-for-disability-inclusion/</link><description>Mayo Clinic recently received the highest possible score on the Disability Equality Index and was named a "Best Place To Work For Disability Inclusion...</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 14:10:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Huge Microsoft Outage Linked to CrowdStrike Takes Down Computers Around the World</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/microsoft-windows-outage-crowdstrike-global-it-probems/</link><description>A software update from cybersecurity company CrowdStrike appears to have inadvertently disrupted IT systems globally.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 10:40:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is the Capital One Venture Rewards card worth it?</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/is-capital-one-venture-card-worth-it/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. If you’re wondering whether a travel rewards credit card i...</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 00:30:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pete Davidson's Reckless Driving Case Dismissed, Completes Diversion Program</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/18/pete-davidson-reckless-driving-case-dismissed-completes-diversion-program/</link><description>Pete Davidson's putting his reckless driving case in his rearview ... 'cause a California judge just dismissed the case after Pete completed a pretria...</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 07:54:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘It’s been crazy’: I’m facing a Social Security overpayment and put $6,000 on my credit card. Should I use my emergency savings to pay it off?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/its-been-crazy-im-facing-a-social-security-overpayment-and-put-6-000-on-my-credit-card-should-i-use-my-emergency-savings-to-pay-it-off-1f5a3403?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>“I also have $125,000 in a traditional IRA that I haven’t withdrawn from yet.”</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 12:25:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Boursin Pork Chops</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/boursin-pork-chops/</link><description>Boursin Pork Chops are savory, tender, and covered in a delicious cheesy cream sauce. This one-pan recipe is the perfect easy…</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic study uncovers genetic cancer risks in 550 patients</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-study-uncovers-genetic-cancer-risks-in-550-patients/</link><description>PHOENIX — Current screening protocols fail to catch a notable number of people carrying genetic mutations associated with hereditary breast and ovaria...</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CrowdStrike update causes major IT outage, taking out banks, airlines and businesses across the world</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/19/banks-airlines-brokerage-houses-report-widespread-outages-across-the-globe/</link><description>Businesses across the world are reporting IT outages, including Windows “blue screen of death” errors on their computers, in what has already become o...</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 09:40:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why having the Spirit Airlines credit card isn’t crazy</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/spirit-airlines-credit-card/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. There’s an airline credit card that can offer incredible v...</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 23:30:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bob Newhart Dead at 94</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/18/bob-newhart-dead-dies-short-illnesses/</link><description>Bob Newhart -- an absolutely iconic figure in stand-up comedy, TV and film -- has died. Bob passed away Thursday at his Los Angeles home after a serie...</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 07:54:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The market has wobbled. Why one firm just increased its S&amp;P 500 target</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/the-market-has-wobbled-why-one-firm-just-increased-its-s-p-500-target-91c2a9f5?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Stocks have had a wobble but UBS reckons the bull market has further to run</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 12:22:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sheet Pan Ratatouille with Crispy Baked Tofu</title><link>https://minimalistbaker.com/sheet-pan-ratatouille-with-crispy-baked-tofu/</link><description>What could be better than the saucy, savory goodness of classic ratatouille!? Answer: SHEET PAN ratatouille! Say “au revoir” to stovetop babysitting, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paving the way for future larynx transplants through regenerative science</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/7-17paving-the-way-for-future-larynx-transplants-through-regenerative-science/</link><description>Surgeons at Mayo Clinic in Arizona perform a total larynx transplant Mayo Clinic envisions a day when regenerative science makes it possible to offer ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paytm loss widens and revenue shrinks as it grapples with regulatory clampdown</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/18/paytm-loss-widens-and-revenue-shrinks-following-regulatory-clampdown/</link><description>Indian fintech Paytm’s struggles won’t seem to end. The company on Friday reported that its revenue declined by 36% and its loss more than doubled in ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 08:21:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ITA Airways is offering a generous status match, including expired elite status</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/skyteam-status-match-ita-airways/</link><description>A new status match opportunity offers SkyPriority benefits on SkyTeam alliance flights like those operated by Delta Air Lines, and, in a unique twist,...</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 23:15:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lou Dobbs, Longtime Conservative Political Pundit, Dead at 78</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/18/lou-dobbs-conservative-political-pundit-dead-dies/</link><description>Lou Dobbs -- a controversial conservative commentator who spent decades at CNN -- has died ... TMZ has confirmed. The longtime conservative political ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 07:54:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Netflix's Next Act Will Be Slower to Catch On</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/netflixs-next-act-will-be-slower-to-catch-on-6b8d7e43?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>The streaming giant made it clear that advertising growth will take time as the boost from its password-sharing crackdown fades.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Red Robin Campfire Sauce</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/red-robin-campfire-sauce/</link><description>Red Robin campfire sauce is the best pairing for your burgers, fries, and more. Whip it up in minutes with…</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tomorrow’s Cure: How nuclear medicine helps cancer patients</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/tomorrows-cure-how-nuclear-medicine-helps-cancer-patients/</link><description>Nuclear medicine therapy is sometimes the best option for people who no longer respond to other cancer treatments. It is often helpful for patients wi...</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fandango founder dies in fall from Manhattan skyscraper</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/18/fandango-founder-dies-in-fall-from-manhattan-skyscraper/</link><description>J. Michael Cline, the co-founder of Fandango and multiple other startups over his multi-decade career, died after falling from a Manhattan hotel, New ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 01:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Choice Privileges Select Mastercard review: Elite status and bonus points each year</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/choice-privileges-select-mastercard-review/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. Choice Privileges Select Mastercard overview The Choice Pr...</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 23:07:37 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>