<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 06:59:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Dr. Dre Says Snoop Dogg's Calling Him 'Braveheart' For Olympic Archery Dream</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/15/dr-dre-snoop-braveheart-olympics/</link><description>Dr. Dre's training to compete in archery for Team USA at the next Olympics, and his buddy Snoop Dogg's already got the perfect nickname for him ... an...</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 07:56:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>History shows investors should keep a tight leash on risk once the Fed cuts rates, strategist says</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/history-shows-investors-should-keep-a-tight-leash-on-risk-once-the-fed-cuts-rates-strategist-says-085ddf09?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Trimming stock positions depends on the reason for the Fed reducing borrowing costs</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 12:33:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chocolate Whipped Cream</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/chocolate-whipped-cream/</link><description>Fluffy Chocolate Whipped Cream is a wonderful combination of chocolate and fresh whipped cream. It’s the perfect topping for fruit,…</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Start A Successful Health Coaching Business (Yes, You Can!)</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/4-tips-to-starting-successful-health-coaching-business</link><description>Start your journey helping people make life-changing health shifts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 11:27:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>UK neobank Revolut valued at $45B after secondary market sale</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/16/uk-neobank-revolut-valued-at-45b-after-secondary-market-sale/</link><description>Revolut has confirmed a new valuation of $45 billion via a secondary market share sale, shortly after the U.K.-based neobank secured its own banking license in the U.K. and in Mexico. The news positions Revolut as one of Europe’s most valuable private tech companies. Founded out of London in 2015, Revolut is one of numerous […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 12:47:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deal: Singapore Airlines business class between New York and Frankfurt for just 56,700 miles, or 36,400 miles in premium economy</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/singapore-krisflyer-spontaneous-escapes/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. While Singapore Airlines has a reputation for offering an ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 23:40:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Caitlin Clark Autographs 2-Week-Old Baby</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/15/caitlin-clark-autograph-baby/</link><description>Even babies fresh out the womb are fans of Caitlin Clark ... 'cause the WNBA star just got asked to autograph a two-week-old child -- and she delivere...</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 07:56:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>KeyCorp Deal Could Be a Model for Regional Banks</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/keycorp-deal-could-be-a-model-for-regional-banks-05ef70db?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>The market’s upbeat reaction to Scotiabank’s purchase of a stake in the Cleveland-based lender is an eyebrow-raising indicator.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zucchini Roll-Ups</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/zucchini-roll-ups/</link><description>Zucchini Roll-Ups are a delicious, unique meal that the whole family will enjoy. Thin slices of zucchini are rolled around…</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>No Lie, This Supplement Is Like The Fountain Of Youth For Your Skin</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/how-each-mbg-best-skin-ingredient-benefits-aging-skin</link><description>Do you do your skin care routine morning and night? Great. But there's more you can do. Here's how to approach skin aging from the inside out.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 11:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Did Samsung Take Control of My Banking App? Inside Android’s ‘Clobbering’ Dilemma</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/android-clobbering-app-store/</link><description>A US judge is set to force Google to more widely open up Android phones to competing app stores. But as I found, app stores vying for supremacy could leave Android users confused and worried about security.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Massive Social Security number data breach — here’s why you need to ‘freeze’ your credit</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/what-to-know-about-credit-freeze/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. If you’re taking inventory of the security measures in all...</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 23:30:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mariah Carey Rocks Pink Swimsuit, Hangs with Kids Off Amalfi Coast</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/15/mariah-carey-pink-swimsuit-amalfi-coast/</link><description>Mariah Carey's heating up the Amalfi Coast, because even the Queen of Christmas needs a summer break ... and she's taking hers in a skintight pink swi...</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 07:56:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Revolut share sale values U.K. fintech at $45 billion ahead of planned IPO</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/revolut-share-sale-values-u-k-fintech-at-45-billion-ahead-of-planned-ipo-bd3f5056?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Revolut on Friday said a secondary share sale was set at valuation of $45 billion, making it Europe’s most valuable privately-owned technology company.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 12:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Baking Soda vs Baking Powder (Baking Tips)</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/baking-soda-vs-baking-powder-baking-tips/</link><description>Baking soda vs baking powder….what is the difference? I’m here to teach you the basics of each so that you…</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In A Financial Pinch? 7 Small Savings Tips That Add Up To Big Savings</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/small-savings-tips-that-add-up-to-big-savings</link><description>Don’t dismiss the power of baby steps, especially when it comes to saving money. Small money moves can add up to big savings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 21:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>EVs Are Losing Up to 50 Percent of Their Value in One Year</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/evs-are-losing-up-to-50-percent-of-their-value-in-one-year/</link><description>Some electric car brands are hemorrhaging value, with the worst losing as much as $600 a day. In this investigation, WIRED outlines the models to watch, why this is happening, and how you could game the market to your advantage.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scandinavia deal alert: SAS sale has flights to Europe from $398 round-trip</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/deals/scandinavian-airlines-flight-sale-to-europe/</link><description>Scandinavian Airlines just unveiled a new European travel sale with some great fares on flights from the U.S. to destinations like Denmark, Norway, Sw...</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 23:10:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'RHOSLC' Star Lisa Barlow Lawsuit Over Unpaid Tequila Biz Loans Dismissed</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/15/lisa-barlow-sued-unpaid-tequila-loans/</link><description>3:51 PM PT -- Lisa Barlow tells TMZ ... her lawyers have notified her that this lawsuit was dismissed. 'RHOSLC' star Lisa Barlow and her husband are i...</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 07:56:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Markets Are Way Out of Line With Reality, According to These Measures</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/markets-are-way-out-of-line-with-reality-according-to-these-measures-1209f9fb?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>Three popular stock market valuation tools are saying the rebound of the past couple of weeks is a fools’ rally.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seedy Tahini Snack Bites (Nut-Free!)</title><link>https://minimalistbaker.com/seedy-tahini-snack-bites/</link><description>Nut-free friends, this one’s for you! We’re no strangers to energy bites (and cake bites… and cookie bites…), but a nut-free version of these snackabl...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A 7-Week Plan To Master Pull-Ups (&amp; Why This Move Is A+ For Healthy Aging)</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/how-to-do-your-first-pull-up-7-week-beginner-plan</link><description>Pull-ups are way more than just a flex—they can actively boost longevity and health span.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 13:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ben Horowitz Declares War on Michael Moritz</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/15/ben-horowitz-declares-war-on-michael-moritz/</link><description>A social media spat between billionaire tech investors is raising questions about the journalistic independence of three-year-old news outfit SF Standard, after a reporter representing the outlet reached out to sources for a story about VC Ben Horowitz and his wife Felicia. The Standard’s sole backer is another longtime VC, Michael Moritz, and on Thursday […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 06:31:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How I get this monthly credit on my Delta Amex without even trying</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/delta-amex-resy-credit/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. When I learned the annual fee for my Delta SkyMiles® Reser...</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 23:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kevin Spacey Refusing To Leave Baltimore Mansion After Foreclosure, Buyer Claims</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/15/kevin-spacey-wont-leave-baltimore-mansion/</link><description>Kevin Spacey is digging in his heels ... the guy who bought the actor's waterfront mansion at a foreclosure auction claims Kevin is refusing to leave ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 07:56:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are You Using the Right Tax Breaks to Boost Investment Returns?</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/roth-ira-401k-hsa-529-8a0ffdd8?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>Americans have more options than ever to shelter their investments from taxes. Here’s how to make smart use of five major types of accounts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chocolate Pudding Cookies</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/pudding-cookies/</link><description>Chocolate Pudding Cookies are soft, chewy, and irresistibly delicious! They are quick and easy to bake and will be a…</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Creatine Supplements Bad For Your Kidneys? What's Fact vs. Fiction</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/are-creatine-supplements-bad-for-your-kidneys</link><description>Here's what you should know.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 12:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>California AI bill SB 1047 aims to prevent AI disasters, but Silicon Valley warns it will cause one</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/15/california-ai-bill-sb-1047-aims-to-prevent-ai-disasters-but-silicon-valley-warns-it-will-cause-one/</link><description>SB 1047 has drawn the ire of Silicon Valley players large and small, including venture capitalists, big tech trade groups, researchers and startup founders. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 01:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Get your Epic Passes for ski season before the price increases next month</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/epic-ski-pass/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. Although kids are going back to school and saying a bitter...</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 22:00:16 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>