<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 08:49:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Taylor Swift Says 'Folklore' Fantasy Album Inspired by Ireland</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/30/taylor-swift-folklore-album-inspired-by-ireland/</link><description>Taylor Swift made an entire Irish venue swoon with pride Saturday night after telling them their country was the inspiration and imagery behind her al...</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 07:57:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stocks delivered a disturbing signal last week. Here’s what it may mean.</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/stocks-delivered-a-disturbing-signal-last-week-heres-what-it-may-mean-e7a4a908?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Stocks are going to struggle in the second half of the year if some technical signals play out, says Michael Kramer, founder of Mott Capital Managemen...</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Strawberry Cream Cheese Pie</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/strawberry-cream-cheese-pie/</link><description>This strawberry cream cheese pie has a smooth, creamy filling topped with sweet strawberries and held together by a crumbly…</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Discover the sweet health benefits of summertime melons</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/discover-the-sweet-health-benefits-of-summertime-melons/</link><description>When it comes to melons, which one is your favorite? Whether it's cantaloupe, honeydew or watermelon, these summertime favorites contain some sweet he...</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meta’s ‘pay or consent’ model fails EU competition rules, Commission finds</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/01/metas-pay-or-consent-model-fails-eu-competition-rules-commission-finds/</link><description>Preliminary findings by the European Commission investigating a controversial binary choice Meta has forced on regional users of its social neworks, F...</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:56:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>5 reasons to get the Hilton Honors Amex Surpass card</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/5-reasons-amex-hilton-surpass-card/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. Hotel cobranded credit cards serve a very specific audienc...</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 23:00:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Khloe Kardashian Parties W/ Sisters at 40th Birthday, Snoop Performs</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/30/khloe-kardashian-40th-birthday-party-snoop-kurupt-warren-g/</link><description>Khloe Kardashian knows how to do it up big for her fam, hosting her 40th birthday party, and some huge stars showed up to perform. The party was theme...</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 07:57:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oil ticks higher to begin July as traders eye demand outlook, drilling activity</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/oil-ticks-higher-to-begin-july-as-traders-eye-demand-outlook-drilling-activity-820a063b?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Oil futures edged higher early Monday, building on a solid June gain as investors weighed the outlook for summer demand and a continued fall in the nu...</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sherbet Punch</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/sherbet-punch/</link><description>This bright sherbet punch is perfect for serving on any occasion! It has just the right balance of sweetness, zest,…</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Thriving, not just surviving, after bariatric surgery</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/thriving-not-just-surviving-after-bariatric-surgery/</link><description>A trip to Disney World in 2023 was an eye-opener for Katie Crow. It wasn't the rides, parades or immersive activities that caught her attention but th...</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Not Everyone Loses Weight on Ozempic</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/glp1-no-weight-loss-ozempic-wegovy-mounjaro-semaglutide-tirzepatide/</link><description>For many patients, GLP-1 drugs like Ozempic and Wegovy lead to substantial weight loss. But some see much less benefit, and researchers are trying to ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:04:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Disney Lookout Cay at Lighthouse Point: A complete guide to Disney Cruise Line’s private beach destination</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/disney-lookout-cay-at-lighthouse-point-cruise/</link><description>Editor’s note: TPG’s Ashley Kosciolek accepted a free trip to sail on Disney Cruise Line’s Disney Magic to experience a call on Lookout Cay. The views...</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 21:00:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zach Bryan Brings Out 'Hawk Tuah' Girl to Sing 'Revival' At Nashville Concert</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/30/zach-bryan-hawk-tuah-girl-nashville-concert-revival/</link><description>Zach Bryan got in on the "Hawk Tuah" craze, bringing the now-famous 23-year-old on stage Saturday night during his concert. Zach, who is on his "The Q...</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 07:57:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘My stepmother makes me feel unwelcome’: I bought a house for my father in 2008, but now he wants me to sign over a 50% share for his third wife</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/my-stepmother-makes-me-feel-unwelcome-i-bought-a-house-for-my-father-in-2008-but-now-he-wants-me-to-sign-over-a-50-share-for-his-third-wife-08b914d4?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>“He has been married to his third wife for three years; she has asked him where she will live when he passes.”</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:16:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>4th of July Menu Plan</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/4th-of-july-menu-plan/</link><description>Get ready for a fun-filled 4th of July with my easy and delicious menu plan, complete with a handy shopping…</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In case you missed it: This week’s Top 5 stories on social media</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/in-case-you-missed-it-this-weeks-top-5-stories-on-social-media-17/</link><description>Check out a few of the most popular News Network stories on @mayoclinic social media this past week. How extreme heat and humidity affect your health ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 19:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Japan’s SmartHR raises $140M Series E as strong demand for HR tech boosts its ARR to $100M</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/01/japans-smarthr-raises-140m-series-e-as-strong-demand-for-hr-tech-boosts-its-arr-to-100m/</link><description>The round was led by KKR and Teachers' Ventures Growth, an investment arm of Ontario Teachers' Pension Plan. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. F...</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 11:38:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Everything you need to know about IHG One Rewards’ annual lounge membership</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/ihg-lounge-access-milestone-reward/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. With the launch of the IHG One Rewards program in 2022 cam...</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 19:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Justin Timberlake Cracks Joke about DWI Arrest at Boston Concert</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/30/justin-timberlake-joke-dwi-forget-tomorrow-tour-boston-arrest/</link><description>Justin Timberlake seems ready to move on from his recent legal drama ... 'cause not only has he addressed the incident onstage again -- he's got jokes...</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 07:57:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘She told my grandchildren lies about me so they would despise me’: I’m disinheriting my ungrateful and selfish daughter. Could she contest my will?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/she-told-my-grandchildren-lies-about-me-so-they-would-despise-me-im-disinheriting-my-ungrateful-and-selfish-daughter-could-she-contest-my-will-15096974?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>“I once complimented my daughter and her partner on a nice plant in their garage and they started laughing, and told me it was marijuana.”</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:12:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>No-Bake Cookie Dough Cheesecake</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/no-bake-cookie-dough-cheesecake/</link><description>With the rich Oreo crust, creamy cheesecake filling, and edible cookie dough bites, this no-bake cookie dough cheesecake is something…</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IBD Pride Clinic: Belonging while battling bowel disease</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/ibd-pride-clinic-belonging-while-battling-bowel-disease/</link><description>Dealing with chronic conditions like Crohn's disease and ulcerative colitis can be challenging and sometimes embarrassing. Inflammatory bowel disease ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MIT’s soft robotic system is designed to pack groceries</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/30/mits-soft-robotic-system-is-designed-to-pack-groceries/</link><description>RoboGrocery combines computer vision with a soft robotic gripper to bag a wide range of different items. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For p...</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Porter Airlines bets big on Florida with 7 new routes this winter</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/porter-florida-winter-schedule/</link><description>Porter Airlines, a growing carrier based in Canada, has been on a major U.S. expansion over the last couple of years. This winter, it plans to take a ...</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 18:00:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Michael J. Fox Joins Coldplay at Glastonbury Festival, Plays 'Fix You'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/30/michael-j-fox-coldplay-chris-martin-glastonbury-music-festival-fix-you/</link><description>Michael J. Fox can still shred on the guitar ... taking the stage alongside Chris Martin and Coldplay -- and playing a mashup "Back to the Future" fan...</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 07:57:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘Our children have varying degrees of success’: My husband and I are in our 80s and have $300,000 to leave our 3 kids. Do we give more to our underemployed son?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/our-children-have-varying-degrees-of-success-my-husband-and-i-are-in-our-80s-and-have-300-000-to-leave-our-3-children-do-we-give-more-to-our-underemployed-son-3b4d1c61?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>“At 56, he has few prospects for his future.”</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 12:11:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Easy Apricot Sorbet (No-Churn!)</title><link>https://minimalistbaker.com/easy-apricot-sorbet-no-churn/</link><description>Once upon a time, in the dark streets of San Francisco, a life-changing ice cream cone was enjoyed thanks to Garden Creamery. This apricot sorbet is i...</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Clot-busting medication helps retiree return to the open road after a stroke</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/clot-busting-medication-helps-retiree-return-to-the-open-road-after-a-stroke/</link><description>After dedicated careers, raising a family and preparing for retirement, Tim Fleming and his wife Loretta Fleming were ready for their next great adven...</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI-powered scams and what you can do about them</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/30/ai-powered-scams-and-what-you-can-do-about-them/</link><description>This is by no means a complete list, just a few of the most obvious tricks that AI can supercharge. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For person...</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Your guide to calling a credit card reconsideration line</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/your-guide-to-calling-a-credit-card-reconsideration-line/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. Credit card issuers have the final say over whether or not...</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 17:00:17 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>