<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 02:18:36 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Zach Bryan Brought 'Hawk Tuah' Girl Onstage for Her Own Safety</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/02/zach-bryan-brought-hawk-tuah-girl-on-stage-after-feared-safety/</link><description>Zach Bryan came to the rescue of "Hawk Tuah" girl Hailey Welch before his Nashville show ... arranging the VIP treatment for her after she got worried...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 13:09:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Betting markets give Harris better chance of being Democratic nominee than Biden</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/biden-offers-latest-debate-excuse-as-harris-pulls-level-in-one-betting-market-559b7c7b?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Vice President Kamala Harris on Wednesday moved ahead of President Joe Biden in some betting markets as to who would be the candidate to take on forme...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 17:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Philly Cheesesteak Foil Packs</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/philly-cheesesteak-foil-packs/</link><description>Try these delicious Philly Cheesesteak Foil Packs, a fun new way to enjoy the flavors of the classic Philly Cheesesteak.…</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: A tick to blame for the alpha-gal, meat allergy</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-a-tick-to-blame-for-the-alpha-gal-meat-allergy/</link><description>You may have heard about alpha-gal syndrome also known as the meat allergy illness or tick bite meat allergy. The Centers for Disease Control and Prev...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 17:28:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TechCrunch Minute: YouTube makes it easier to report and take down AI deepfakes</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/video/techcrunch-minute-youtube-makes-it-easier-to-report-and-take-down-ai-deepfakes/</link><description>It’s easier than ever to make a deepfake of another person’s voice or face, but at least YouTube is making some small changes that make it slightly ea...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Save up to 50% on Amazon purchases using just 1 Amex point</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/amazon-amex-membership-rewards-discount/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. Whether you’re stocking up on household staples or splurgi...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 17:30:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Guess Who This Patriotic Kiddo Turned Into!</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/03/guess-who-this-patriotic-kiddo-turned-into/</link><description>Before this blue-eyed boy in his red white and blue Mickey Mouse sweater turned into a global entertainer, he was just taking his action figures every...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 13:09:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I’m in my 60s and mentored Gen Z students from NYU. This is what we taught each other.</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/im-in-my-60s-and-mentored-gen-z-students-from-nyu-this-is-what-we-taught-each-other-e073c6bd?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Why mentoring in unretirement is great for you and young adults</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 17:53:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tri Tip Marinade</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/tri-tip-marinade/</link><description>This tasty tri tip marinade is the best way to infuse your tri-tip steak with delicious flavor and make it…</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sports Safety Spotlight: Mayo Clinic touts advancements in hip, knee replacement to keep seniors active</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/sports-safety-spotlight-mayo-clinic-touts-advancements-in-hip-knee-replacement-to-keep-seniors-active/</link><description>MANKATO, Minn. ― The summer weather inspires people of all ages to head outside and play sports. For seniors, pickleball has become a popular option, ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 16:36:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cloudflare launches a tool to combat AI bots</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/03/cloudflare-launches-a-tool-to-combat-ai-bots/</link><description>Cloudflare, the publicly-traded cloud service provider, has launched a new, free tool to prevent bots from scraping websites hosted on its platform fo...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 17:49:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>8 ways to save money on Amazon orders</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/save-money-amazon/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. It’s time for Amazon Prime Day — one of the best times of ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 17:00:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TMZ TV Hot Takes: BBC Host Wants Biden To Have Trump Killed, Ray J, Ed Sheeran</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/03/tmz-tv-hot-takes-bbc-host-calling-biden-murder-trump-ray-j-melt-down-ed-sheeran-gig-england-soccer/</link><description>A high-ranking BBC presenter wants to see political violence in the United States, Ray J wants back in the BET Awards and Ed Sheeran wants England's s...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 13:09:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Most people earning $100K or more are making this huge 401(k) mistake</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/most-people-earning-100k-or-more-are-making-this-huge-401-k-mistake-0af98ad7?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>For high earners, saving up to your company match isn’t going to be good enough to replace the income you’ll need later on.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 17:38:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Raspberry Fluff Salad</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/raspberry-fluff-salad/</link><description>Fresh and fruity Raspberry Fluff Salad is a sweet and creamy side or dessert with a mix of raspberries, vanilla…</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tomorrow’s Cure: How a lifetime of exposures impact health – exposome explained</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/tomorrows-cure-how-a-lifetime-of-exposures-impact-health-exposome-explained/</link><description>There is a study of the fascinating interplay between the cumulative effects of external exposures on a person's body and genes. It is called exposomi...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 13:21:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Twilio says hackers identified cell phone numbers of two-factor app Authy users</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/03/twilio-says-hackers-identified-cell-phone-numbers-of-two-factor-app-authy-users/</link><description>Twilio says "threat actors were able to identify" phone numbers of people who use the two-factor app Authy. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. Fo...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 17:21:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amex to open first Centurion Lounge in Japan at Tokyo’s Haneda Airport</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/amex-centurion-lounge-tokyo-japan/</link><description>American Express is bringing its Centurion Lounge network to Japan. The issuer shared news with TPG on Wednesday that it would open a Centurion Lounge...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 16:45:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cleveland Browns Urged To End Live-Mascot Tradition After Swagger Jr.'s Death</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/03/cleveland-browns-urged-end-live-mascot-tradition-after-swagger-jr-death-peta/</link><description>PETA's imploring the Cleveland Browns to do away with their live-mascot tradition following the death of their sideline dog ... telling TMZ Sports it ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 13:09:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wall Street’s most bearish strategist is leaving JPMorgan. Here’s a look at his market calls.</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/jpmorgans-top-strategist-marko-kolanovic-is-leaving-after-missing-stocks-historic-rally-69f88bca?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Chief market strategist Marko Kolanovic is departing JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co. following a 19-year stretch with the bank, according to a source from within...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 17:34:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Strawberry Cream Cheese Pie</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/strawberry-cream-cheese-pie/</link><description>This strawberry cream cheese pie has a smooth, creamy filling topped with sweet strawberries and held together by a crumbly…</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: Helping kids with anxiety through exposure therapy</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-helping-kids-with-anxiety-through-exposure-therapy/</link><description>It's normal for kids to feel anxious sometimes. When these feelings get too big and help is needed, experts often suggest cognitive behavioral therapy...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 16:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nano Dimension is buying Desktop Metal</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/03/nano-dimension-is-buying-desktop-metal/</link><description>The news brings closure to more than two years of volleying back and forth between some of the biggest names in additive manufacturing. © 2024 TechCru...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 17:06:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>United Airlines Global Services status: What is it and how to earn it</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/united-global-services/</link><description>Of all the airline loyalty statuses, few are more prestigious than United Airlines Global Services, the airline’s ultra-exclusive tier for its most va...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 16:00:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rick Ross Vancouver Fight Started Due to Fans Pissed About Drake Trash Talk</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/03/rick-ross-fight-started-fans-upset-drake-trash-talk/</link><description>Rick Ross' violent face-off in Vancouver is exactly what it seems -- the end result of the rapper's recent beef with Drake ... TMZ has learned. Source...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 13:09:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Treasury yields extend declines after ISM data provides signs of waning U.S. growth</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/treasury-yields-steady-ahead-of-adp-and-initial-claims-jobs-data-98ea58db?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Treasury yields extended declines seen earlier on Wednesday after the Institute for Supply Management’s index of services businesses produced its lowe...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 17:27:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sherbet Punch</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/sherbet-punch/</link><description>This bright sherbet punch is perfect for serving on any occasion! It has just the right balance of sweetness, zest,…</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Drugs that kill “zombie” cells may benefit some older women, but not all, Mayo Clinic study finds</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/drugs-that-kill-zombie-cells-may-benefit-some-older-women-but-not-all-mayo-clinic-study-finds/</link><description>ROCHESTER, Minn. — Drugs that selectively kill senescent cells may benefit otherwise healthy older women but are not a "one-size-fits-all" remedy, May...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 13:26:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Groups save big at TechCrunch Disrupt 2024</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/03/groups-save-big-at-techcrunch-disrupt-2024/</link><description>Planning to attend TechCrunch Disrupt 2024 with your team? Maximize your team-building time and your company’s impact across the entire conference whe...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Flying internationally? Here’s what you need to know about the Mobile Passport Control app</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/mobile-passport-app-is-now-called-cbp-mpc/</link><description>Editor’s note: This story has been updated with new information. Whether you’re waiting for Global Entry approval or don’t want to shell out $100 (or ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 15:30:03 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>