<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 02:12:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>O.J. Simpson BET Awards Tribute Slammed by Nicole Brown, Ron Goldman's Families</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/01/oj-simpson-in-memoriam-slammed-bet-awards-nicole-brown-simpson-ron-goldman/</link><description>Nicole Brown Simpson and Ron Goldman's families are slamming O.J. Simpson's "In Memoriam" tribute at the BET Awards ... calling it entirely inappropri...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 03:04:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Bucket List for Our Retirement? No Thanks</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/retirement-bucket-list-no-thanks-c877bdb6?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>Checking off boxes seems like a pointless way to enjoy experiences. We’d rather do things that plant the seeds for future adventures.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 03:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Raspberry Fluff Salad</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/raspberry-fluff-salad/</link><description>Fresh and fruity Raspberry Fluff Salad is a sweet and creamy side or dessert with a mix of raspberries, vanilla…</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Celebrate safely: Use caution when using fireworks and sparklers</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/celebrate-safely-use-caution-when-using-fireworks-and-sparklers/</link><description>Americans everywhere will be celebrating Independence Day on July 4, and that often means fireworks and sparklers are involved. While exciting, firewo...</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Audi Q6 E-tron Review: Price, Specs, Availability</title><link>https://www.wired.com/review/review-audi-q6-e-tron/</link><description>The first model on the brand’s new electric car platform, this ChatGPT-enabled EV SUV combines incredible comfort with possibly too much tech.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 02:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Park Hyatt Marrakech finally gets its long-awaited debut</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/park-hyatt-marrakech-opens/</link><description>Park Hyatt is making a much-hyped debut in Morocco. The property officially opened this week after a soft opening phase at the beginning of this year....</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 23:37:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shannon Sharpe Apologizes To Megan Thee Stallion For Sexual Comments On Podcast</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/01/shannon-sharpe-apologizes-megan-thee-stallion-sexual-comments-nightcap-podcast-nfl/</link><description>Shannon Sharpe just issued a face-to-face apology to Megan Thee Stallion for the sexual comments he previously made about her ... saying he deeply reg...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 03:04:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Court Revives Key Part of Biden's Student-Loan Program: What the Latest Ruling Means for Borrowers</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/biden-new-student-loan-debt-forgiveness-plan-explained-14aa442f?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>State lawsuits still threaten the SAVE plan to make debt repayments more affordable.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 00:10:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Strawberry Cream Cheese Pie</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/strawberry-cream-cheese-pie/</link><description>This strawberry cream cheese pie has a smooth, creamy filling topped with sweet strawberries and held together by a crumbly…</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: Tips from a gynecological surgeon on recovery from surgery</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-tips-from-a-gynecological-surgeon-on-recovery-from-surgery/</link><description>Every year, about 4 million gynecologic surgeries are performed in the U.S. Among these, hysterectomies are the most common, with over half a million ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anthropic looks to fund a new, more comprehensive generation of AI benchmarks</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/01/anthropic-looks-to-fund-a-new-more-comprehensive-generation-of-ai-benchmarks/</link><description>Anthropic is launching a program to fund the development of new types of benchmarks capable of evaluating the performance and impact of AI models, inc...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 01:45:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Emirates’ first revamped 777 takes off in August with ‘A380-inspired’ cabin — including premium economy</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/emirates-777-retrofits/</link><description>The start of July marks the beginning of a major project for Emirates. This week, the carrier will kick off a major, nose-to-tail cabin face-lift for ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 22:00:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shaquille O'Neal Parties With 'Hawk Tuah' Girl In Nashville</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/01/shaquille-oneal-parties-with-hawk-tuah-girl-in-nashville/</link><description>"Hawk Tuah" girl's 15 minutes of fame ain't over yet -- and clearly, neither is her time spittin' -- 'cause the internet's newest star was seen over t...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 03:04:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nasdaq Hits Record to Kick Off the Second Half</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/global-stocks-markets-dow-news-07-01-2024-3b0aede0?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>The tech-heavy index advanced 0.8% to its 21st record close of the year. The S&amp;P 500 added 0.3%, which was just shy of its high reached last month.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 22:27:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sherbet Punch</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/sherbet-punch/</link><description>This bright sherbet punch is perfect for serving on any occasion! It has just the right balance of sweetness, zest,…</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Innovation centers spur new biotherapeutics for patients</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/innovation-centers-spur-new-biotherapeutics-for-patients/</link><description>Biotherapeutic medicines focus on rebuilding health while treating symptoms of disease. It's an emerging area of medicine aimed at stopping disease on...</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Senators urge owners, partners, and VC backers of fintech Synapse to restore customers’ access to their money</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/01/senators-urge-synapses-owners-partners-and-vc-funders-to-restore-customers-access-to-their-money/</link><description>A group of senators has banded together to urge Synapse’s owners and bank and fintech partners to “immediately restore customers’ access to their mone...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 00:49:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Flights to Europe starting at 15K miles: Check out Flying Blue’s July Promo Rewards</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/deals/flying-blue-special-promo-rewards/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. When booking discounted travel, there are numerous opportu...</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:00:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bianca Censori, Milo Yiannopoulos Slam Lawsuit Claim She Sent Porn to Minors</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/01/bianca-censori-milo-yiannopoulos-slam-lawsuit-kanye-west/</link><description>Kanye West's former chief of staff, Milo Yiannopoulos, is slamming a new lawsuit claiming the rapper's wife, Bianca Censori, exposed Yeezy employees, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 03:04:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Roaring Kitty' Discloses 6.6% Stake in Chewy</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/chewy-shares-soar-after-roaring-kitty-discloses-6-6-stake-48544805?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>Keith Gill’s stake was disclosed days after he posted an image of a dog on his X account.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 19:36:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>4th of July Menu Plan</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/4th-of-july-menu-plan/</link><description>Get ready for a fun-filled 4th of July with my easy and delicious menu plan, complete with a handy shopping…</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Discover the sweet health benefits of summertime melons</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/discover-the-sweet-health-benefits-of-summertime-melons/</link><description>When it comes to melons, which one is your favorite? Whether it's cantaloupe, honeydew or watermelon, these summertime favorites contain some sweet he...</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>REI’s Fourth of July Sale Has Great Deals on Our Favorite Outdoor Gear</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/rei-fourth-of-july-deals-2024/</link><description>Whether you need a tent, sleeping pad, rain jacket, or new pack, REI’s Independence Day sale has something for everyone.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 00:33:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TSA PreCheck adds 4 carriers to program, bringing total to more than 100 participating airlines</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/tsa-precheck-new-airlines/</link><description>Editor’s note: This story has been updated with the latest information. Flyers who don’t want to deal with the hassle of long security lines can now u...</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 20:30:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New York Jets' Logo Creator Sues Team, NFL, Wants Payment For Design</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/01/new-york-jets-logo-creator-sues-team-nfl-wants-payment-for-design/</link><description>Jim Pons -- the man who created one of the New York Jets' logos -- is now suing the team and the NFL ... demanding he be paid for their use of his des...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 03:04:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maersk shares jump on decision to scrap plans for DB Schenker takeover</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/maersk-shares-jump-on-decision-to-scrap-plans-for-db-schenker-takeover-767323f7?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>The Danish shipping giant’s CEO said Maersk had decided to withdraw from the sales process after identifying challenges with integrating the German lo...</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>No-Bake Cookie Dough Cheesecake</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/no-bake-cookie-dough-cheesecake/</link><description>With the rich Oreo crust, creamy cheesecake filling, and edible cookie dough bites, this no-bake cookie dough cheesecake is something…</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Thriving, not just surviving, after bariatric surgery</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/thriving-not-just-surviving-after-bariatric-surgery/</link><description>A trip to Disney World in 2023 was an eye-opener for Katie Crow. It wasn't the rides, parades or immersive activities that caught her attention but th...</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TechCrunch Space: Star spangled</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/01/techcrunch-space-star-spangled/</link><description>Hello and welcome back to TechCrunch Space. I hope everyone has a fantastic July 4 this week. Go eat a hot dog. Read my story from last week on the ca...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>United and Marriott promo: Select elites can enjoy bonus rewards on flights and hotel stays</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/united-marriott-dual-elite-promo/</link><description>Since the inception of Marriott Bonvoy in 2018, Titanium Elite and Ambassador Elite members have been eligible for United Airlines’ entry-level Premie...</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 20:00:12 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>