<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 01:25:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Longtime U.S. House Rep. Sheila Jackson Lee Dead at 74</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/20/texas-congresswoman-sheila-jackson-lee-dead-dies/</link><description>Shelia Jackson Lee – the Texas congresswoman who spent three decades in office fighting for Black rights – has died. Her family issued a statement say...</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 23:38:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>They Turned 18 and Immediately Had a Credit Score Over 700</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/they-turned-18-and-immediately-had-a-credit-score-over-700-9ac55992?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>Giving a child a credit card can give them a big credit boost. When it doesn’t work, they risk inheriting mistakes.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 03:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tropical Smoothie</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/tropical-smoothie/</link><description>This refreshing tropical smoothie is bursting with tropical fruit flavors, making it the perfect treat for a hot day. Sip…</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pain relief for worn spinal disks</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/pain-relief-for-worn-spinal-disks/</link><description>The fluid-filled cushions between the bones in your spine are called disks. They provide flexibility, allow for spine movement like flexion and extens...</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bethesda Game Studios employees form a ‘wall-to-wall’ union</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/20/bethesda-game-studios-employees-form-a-wall-to-wall-union/</link><description>Employees at Bethesda Game Studios — the Microsoft-owned game developer that produces the Elder Scrolls and Fallout franchises — are joining the Commu...</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 22:32:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 6 best Alaska cruise shore excursions — from heli-hiking to whale watching</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/best-alaska-cruise-ship-excursions/</link><description>There are some cruise destinations — Barcelona, for instance, or Venice — where you really don’t need to sign up for shore excursions. You can just wa...</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 21:00:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bill Maher Scoffs at People Who Say God Saved Trump from Assassination</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/20/bill-maher-donald-trump-god-shooting-assassination-lucky/</link><description>Bill Maher is fed up to HERE with all the talk that God saved Donald Trump from assassination ... and he's here to tell the world, all this God talk i...</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 23:38:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘I feel slighted’: My husband and I are in our 70s. We married 3 years ago. He’s leaving his $1.8 million home to a 10-year-old relative. Is that normal?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/i-feel-slighted-my-husband-and-i-are-in-our-70s-we-married-3-years-ago-hes-leaving-his-1-8-million-home-to-a-10-year-old-relative-is-that-normal-f553e357?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>‘I have almost double his pension income, as his former wives took a considerable share’</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 21:21:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Grilled Tri-Tip</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/grilled-tri-tip/</link><description>Grilled Tri-Tip is a flavorful, juicy steak that will be the star of your barbecue! It’s marinated in a simple,…</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: Preventing traveler’s diarrhea</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-preventing-travelers-diarrhea/</link><description>Traveler's diarrhea is a common and uncomfortable digestive tract disorder that can affect people when they travel to new environments. According to t...</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CrowdStrike’s update fail causes global outages and travel chaos</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/20/crowdstrikes-update-fail-causes-global-outages-and-travel-chaos/</link><description>This week saw one of the most widespread IT disruptions in recent years linked to a faulty software update from popular cybersecurity firm CrowdStrike...</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 22:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Flight cancellations soar past 5,000 as woes spill into Saturday; Delta and United hardest hit</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/flight-cancellations-it-outage-weekend/</link><description>Flight cancellations continue to climb this weekend in the wake of Friday’s IT outage that wreaked havoc globally — affecting everything from air trav...</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 18:18:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Thomas Matthew Crooks Botched Rifle Club Practice, Clearly Practiced Since</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/20/thomas-matthew-crooks-botched-rifle-team-club-practice-bad-shot-trump/</link><description>Thomas Matthew Crooks clearly put in serious practice at a gun range before trying to kill Donald Trump -- because now we know just how bad of a shot ...</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 23:38:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Investing in real estate isn’t all it’s cracked up to be</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/investing-in-real-estate-isnt-all-its-cracked-up-to-be-f8f97e8b?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>This asset class went 68 years with no net gain</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 21:07:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sugar Cream Pie (Hoosier Pie)</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/sugar-cream-pie/</link><description>Sugar cream pie, or Hoosier pie, is a creamy, delicious treat with deep roots in the Midwest, especially in Indiana.…</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In case you missed it: This week’s Top 5 stories on social media</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/in-case-you-missed-it-this-weeks-top-5-stories-on-social-media-20/</link><description>Check out a few of the most popular News Network stories on @mayoclinic social media this past week. Can you prevent cancer with lifestyle changes? Ne...</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Unpacking how Alphabet’s rumored Wiz acquisition could affect VC</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/20/unpacking-how-alphabets-rumored-wiz-acquisition-could-affect-vc/</link><description>Alphabet, the parent company of Google, is in advanced talks to acquire cybersecurity startup Wiz for $23 billion, the Wall Street Journal reported on...</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How and why to book Bluegreen Vacations resorts through Choice Hotels</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/bluegreen-vacations-choice-points/</link><description>Bluegreen Vacations, an American private vacation ownership brand owned by Hilton Grand Vacations, is best known for its timeshare properties. But you...</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 18:00:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dr. Fauci Plays Down Donald Trump's Injuries After Attempted Assassination</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/20/dr-anthony-fauci-downplays-donald-trump-injury-shooting-wolf-blitzer/</link><description>Donald Trump's former COVID czar Anthony Fauci doesn't think very much of the Republican presidential nominee's bullet wound that he suffered during h...</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 23:38:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to know if a financial planner is a good match or a mismatch for your money</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/youre-throwing-a-dart-in-the-dark-how-to-vet-financial-advisers-before-you-give-them-a-dime-5dba41b4?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Get the lowdown on a financial adviser before you give them a dime.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 20:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Boursin Pork Chops</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/boursin-pork-chops/</link><description>Boursin Pork Chops are savory, tender, and covered in a delicious cheesy cream sauce. This one-pan recipe is the perfect easy…</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Demystifying my diagnosis of autism</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/demystifying-my-diagnosis-of-autism/</link><description>After receiving a diagnosis of autism as an adult, a Mayo Clinic graduate student addressed her educational needs — and embarked on research to make t...</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Microsoft says 8.5M Windows devices were affected by CrowdStrike outage</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/20/microsoft-says-8-5m-windows-devices-were-affected-by-crowdstrike-outage/</link><description>Around 8.5 million devices — less than 1 percent Windows machines globally — were affected by the recent CrowdStrike outage, according to a Microsoft ...</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 19:01:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What it’s like to stay at The Caledonian Edinburgh, Curio Collection by Hilton</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/reviews/the-caledonian-edinburgh-hotel/</link><description>[circuit type=review circuit_id=”8748″] The Caledonian Edinburgh is a charming historic former railway hotel. Adjacent to the Princes Street Gardens, ...</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 15:00:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Drea de Matteo's 13-Year-Old Son Edits Her OnlyFans Content</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/20/drea-de-matteos-13-year-old-son-edits-her-onlyfans-content/</link><description>When it comes to business, Drea de Matteo's motto is ... you gotta keep it in the family. The "Sopranos" star revealed on the "Not Today, Pal" podcast...</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 23:38:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CrowdStrike outage affected 8.5 million Windows devices, Microsoft says</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/crowdstrike-outage-affected-8-5-million-windows-devices-microsoft-says-bfcf3dc1?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Microsoft said Saturday it estimates that worldwide about 8.5 million computers were disabled by the outage caused by an update from the Texas based c...</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 20:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sheet Pan Ratatouille with Crispy Baked Tofu</title><link>https://minimalistbaker.com/sheet-pan-ratatouille-with-crispy-baked-tofu/</link><description>What could be better than the saucy, savory goodness of classic ratatouille!? Answer: SHEET PAN ratatouille! Say “au revoir” to stovetop babysitting, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: Role of the larynx and how to protect it</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-role-of-the-larynx-and-how-to-protect-it/</link><description>A medical milestone at Mayo Clinic, a total larynx transplant performed on a patient with active cancer, has generated headlines recently in the medic...</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Some Black startup founders feel betrayed by Ben Horowitz’s support for Trump</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/20/some-black-startup-founders-feel-betrayed-by-ben-horowitzs-support-for-trump/</link><description>Trump is an advocate for a number of policies that could be harmful to people of color. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deal alert: Points and miles travel deals for July 2024</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/points-and-miles-travel-deals/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. Some of the below offers may be targeted. Citi is a TPG ad...</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 23:00:35 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>