<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 07:06:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>David Corenswet in Full Superman Costume, First On-Set Photos</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/24/david-corenswet-full-superman-costume-first-on-set-photos/</link><description>David Corenswet looks about ready to take flight on the set of the new 'Superman' flick ... 'cause he's out in full costume and looking real beefed up...</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 07:52:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Germany’s Merck Group shares drop 10% after scrapping trial of promising cancer drug</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/merck-shares-drop-10-as-pharma-giant-scraps-trial-of-promising-cancer-drug-a8c0188c?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Merck Group called off a Phase III trial of its promising cancer drug Xevinapant after an independent panel concluded it is unlikely to meet its goals</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 12:47:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Candied Pistachios (4 Ingredients!)</title><link>https://minimalistbaker.com/candied-pistachios/</link><description>Pistachios are good, but candied pistachios?! VERY good. They’re the ultimate sweet, nutty, versatile topping for everything from salads to sorbets (r...</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rain doesn’t have to mean a washout</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/rain-doesnt-have-to-mean-a-washout/</link><description>With all the rain of late, many people may be wondering if it's safe to embrace the weather and indulge in activities like playing or exercising in th...</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 18:09:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>EU accuses Microsoft of competition breach over Teams bundling</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/25/eu-accuses-microsoft-of-competition-breach-over-teams-bundling/</link><description>The European Union accused Microsoft of breaching competition rules Tuesday. In a formal statement of objections the bloc said it suspects the softwar...</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 12:30:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IHG promotions: Earn bonus points on stays and get discounts on reward nights this summer</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/ihg-bonus-points-promotion/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information. One of the most satisfying ways to earn hotel points is to leverage l...</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 23:30:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aaron Carter's Estate Valued at Six Figures For Now, More Items Pending</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/24/aaron-carter-estate-valued-six-figures-more-items-pending-appraisal/</link><description>Aaron Carter was worth a fair bit of money when he died -- and we're now getting a sense of just how much dough there was in his pot ... a 6-figure am...</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 07:52:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Copper Fever Is Breaking</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/why-copper-fever-is-breaking-45a45287?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>The energy-transition metal is still popular among investors, but bets on a looming supply crunch look less sure than they did a month ago.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 12:37:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zeppole (Italian Donuts)</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/zeppole-recipe/</link><description>Whip up a batch of these delightful zeppole, perfect for a sweet treat anytime! With a light, fluffy texture and…</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: What is hip preservation?</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-what-is-hip-preservation/</link><description>Hip issues are often thought of as an older person's problem. But the truth is, hip issues can be present at birth. While some of these conditions are...</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 16:17:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pooping on the Moon Is a Messy Business</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/pooping-on-the-moon-is-a-messy-business/</link><description>If humans are to return to the moon, space agencies and governments need to figure out the legal, ethical, and practical dimensions of extraterrestria...</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Allegiant to drop Austin as base in January, citing terminal closure</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/allegiant-ends-austin-crew-base/</link><description>Low-cost airline Allegiant Air is pulling back from a Texas airport that’s seen rapid growth over the last decade. The Las Vegas-based ultralow-cost c...</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 23:00:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jason Martin Recounts Kendrick Lamar 'Not Like Us' Video, Bobbi Althoff Cameo</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/24/jason-martin-kendrick-lamar-not-like-us-video-bobbi-althoff/</link><description>Kendrick Lamar's "Not Like Us" video went down in Compton over the weekend without a stitch of negativity ... and Jason Martin was there and witnessed...</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 07:52:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘She told my grandchildren lies about me so they would despise me’: I’m disinheriting my ungrateful and selfish daughter. Could she contest my will?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/she-told-my-grandchildren-lies-about-me-so-they-would-despise-me-im-disinheriting-my-ungrateful-and-selfish-daughter-could-she-contest-my-will-15096974?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>“I once complimented my daughter and her partner on a nice plant in their garage and they started laughing, and told me it was marijuana.”</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 12:10:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>S’mores Crack</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/smores-crack/</link><description>S’mores crack is a quick way to enjoy the classic s’more experience without a campfire. Featuring a buttery graham cracker…</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 02:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Can music help someone with Alzheimer’s disease?</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/consumer-health-can-music-help-someone-with-alzheimers-disease/</link><description>Alzheimer's disease is a progressive disorder that causes brain cells to waste away and die. Alzheimer's disease is the most common cause of dementia,...</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deepfake Creators Are Revictimizing GirlsDoPorn Sex Trafficking Survivors</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/girlsdoporn-deepfake-victim-videos/</link><description>The most notorious deepfake sexual abuse website is hosting altered videos originally published as part of the GirlsDoPorn operation. Experts say this...</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IHG’s Hotel Indigo brand on track for major global expansion</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/ihg-hotel-indigo-growth/</link><description>If all goes according to plan at IHG Hotels &amp; Resorts, there will be twice as many Hotel Indigo properties in the world. The lifestyle brand — the sec...</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 22:30:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jamie Lee Curtis and Lindsay Lohan Reunite on 'Freaky Friday 2' Set</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/24/jamie-lee-curtis-lindsay-lohan-reunite-freaky-friday-2-set/</link><description>Jamie Lee Curtis and Lindsay Lohan are finally filming the sequel to 'Freaky Friday' -- and yes, it's already looking every bit as epic as you might i...</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 07:52:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Something unusual is happening on Wall Street — and it likely bodes well for stocks</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/something-unusual-is-happening-on-wall-street-and-it-likely-bodes-well-for-stocks-b3f9779c?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Something unusual is happening on Wall Street that is helping to boost the confidence of stock-market bulls as the first half of 2024 comes to a close...</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Firecracker Meatballs</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/firecracker-meatballs/</link><description>Get ready to spice up your dinner with these firecracker meatballs! Juicy beef meatballs are baked to perfection and then…</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to improve communication with a loved one who has aphasia</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/how-to-improve-communication-with-a-loved-one-who-has-aphasia/</link><description>Editors note: June is National Aphasia Awareness Month Imagine being dropped off in a country where you aren't fluent in the local language Even when ...</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Snapchat introduces new safety features to limit bad actors from contacting users</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/25/snapchat-introduces-new-safety-features-to-limit-strangers-contacting-users/</link><description>Snapchat on Tuesday announced a new suite of safety features, including updates to its account blocking functionality and enhanced friending safeguard...</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>5 ways to ensure you have lounge access before your next flight</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/ensure-lounge-access-next-flight/</link><description>Airports can be stressful environments. Thousands of travelers are all heading in different directions, and you’re hearing boarding calls, paying for ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 22:00:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JJ Redick Ending LeBron James Podcast After Accepting Lakers Coaching Job</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/24/jj-redick-ending-lebron-james-podcast-after-accepting-lakers-coaching-job/</link><description>JJ Redick is a content creator no more -- the Los Angeles Lakers head coach just announced he's putting his podcasting career on hold after accepting ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 07:52:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Americans Chasing High Interest Rates Risk Falling Into a 'Cash Trap'</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/americans-chasing-high-interest-rates-risk-falling-into-a-cash-trap-f4282aee?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>Investors must decide whether to sit on their cash or redistribute it ahead of expected rate cuts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ground Beef and Broccoli</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/ground-beef-and-broccoli/</link><description>Get ready to enjoy a delicious and easy ground beef and broccoli stir-fry that’s perfect for a quick weeknight dinner.…</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In case you missed it: This week’s Top 5 stories on social media</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/in-case-you-missed-it-this-weeks-top-5-stories-on-social-media-16/</link><description>Check out a few of the most popular News Network stories on @mayoclinic social media this past week. Can cochlear implants slow dementia in older adul...</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 17:29:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rocketlane snags $24M to bring AI-led experiences for professional services teams</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/25/rocketlane-snags-24m-to-bring-ai-led-experiences-for-professional-services-teams/</link><description>Rocketlane initially aimed to support customer onboarding. However, it has broadened its scope and doubled down on addressing the needs of professiona...</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>American Airlines flight attendants move closer to strike as Alaska reaches deal</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/flight-attendants-strikes-american-alaska-airlines/</link><description>Flight attendants at Alaska Airlines reached a preliminary deal with the airline for a new contract on Friday, while cabin crew at American Airlines i...</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 21:30:24 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>