<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 06:54:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>'Naked &amp; Afraid: Last One Standing' Survivalists Eat Elephant Poop Seeds</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/21/naked-and-afraid-last-one-standing-survivalists-eat-elephant-poop-seeds/</link><description>"Naked and Afraid: Last One Standing" is back with its brown-out episode -- survivalists chowing down on elephant poop-covered seeds. TMZ snagged the ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 02:25:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Stock Market Rotation of Historic Proportions Is Taking Shape</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/a-stock-market-rotation-of-historic-proportions-is-taking-shape-da9b6546?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>The stock market has suddenly turned upside down. Few investors saw the shift coming, and many are puzzled by what is behind it.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 06:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Marry Me Shrimp Pasta</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/marry-me-shrimp-pasta/</link><description>Marry Me Shrimp Pasta dazzles with robust Italian flavors. It’s ready in just 30 minutes, and the creamy sauce, brimming…</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Caring for your psychological needs as an adolescent or young adult cancer survivor</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/caring-for-your-psychological-needs-as-an-adolescent-or-young-adult-cancer-survivor/</link><description>The burden of cancer is different for everyone, and life stages can play a role in how it affects people. For adolescents and young adults (AYAs) ages...</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Asus ROG Ally X Review: More Battery and Storage, Same Windows Problems</title><link>https://www.wired.com/review/asus-rog-ally-x/</link><description>I still can't stand Windows on a handheld gaming console. But if you can, the ROG Ally X is leagues better than its predecessor.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Capital One Quicksilver Secured credit card review: Earn 1.5% on all purchases and build credit</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/capital-one-quicksilver-secured-review/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. Capital One Quicksilver Secured overview The Capital One Q...</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bella Hadid Hires Legal Team to Sue Adidas After Munich Olympics-Themed Shoot</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/20/bella-hadid-hires-legal-team-sue-adidas-munich-olympics-photo-shoot/</link><description>Bella Hadid's readying for legal battle with Adidas ... with sources telling us she's hired legal counsel to take on the athleticwear giant. Sources f...</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 02:25:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stock futures inch higher, but Biden’s withdrawal adds to increasingly uncertain outlook for markets</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/stock-futures-inch-higher-but-bidens-withdrawal-adds-to-increasingly-uncertain-outlook-for-markets-88b001d0?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>President Joe Biden has officially dropped out of the race for president, injecting even more uncertainty into the outlook for markets at an increasin...</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 04:58:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tropical Smoothie</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/tropical-smoothie/</link><description>This refreshing tropical smoothie is bursting with tropical fruit flavors, making it the perfect treat for a hot day. Sip…</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pain relief for worn spinal disks</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/pain-relief-for-worn-spinal-disks/</link><description>The fluid-filled cushions between the bones in your spine are called disks. They provide flexibility, allow for spine movement like flexion and extens...</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Asus ROG Ally X turns PC gaming into a portable console</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/21/the-asus-rog-ally-x-turns-pc-gaming-into-a-portable-console/</link><description>A little more than a year after launching the ROG Ally, Asus is releasing a refined version of its portable device, the ROG Ally X. This Windows-based...</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>You can get a complimentary weekend night through InterContinental Ambassador: Here’s how</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/intercontinental-ambassador-free-night/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. The InterContinental Ambassador program effectively lets y...</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 19:00:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Esta TerBlanche, 'All My Children' Actress, Dead at 51</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/21/esta-terblanche-dead-dies-51-all-my-children/</link><description>Esta TerBlanche -- a star on the iconic soap "All My Children" -- has died at 51, her family tells TMZ. Barbie Ashley, her goddaughter, tells TMZ ... ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 02:25:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>China’s central bank cuts key policy rate in surprise move</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/china-pboc-cuts-key-policy-rate-2608ee35?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>China’s central bank unexpectedly cut a key policy rate to support the country’s ailing economy, just days after a flurry of data showed that a lopsid...</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 04:46:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Grilled Tri-Tip</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/grilled-tri-tip/</link><description>Grilled Tri-Tip is a flavorful, juicy steak that will be the star of your barbecue! It’s marinated in a simple,…</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: Preventing traveler’s diarrhea</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-preventing-travelers-diarrhea/</link><description>Traveler's diarrhea is a common and uncomfortable digestive tract disorder that can affect people when they travel to new environments. According to t...</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CIA AI director Lakshmi Raman claims the agency is taking a ‘thoughtful approach’ to AI</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/21/cia-ai-director-lakshmi-raman-claims-the-agency-is-taking-a-thoughtful-approach-to-ai/</link><description>As a part of TechCrunch’s ongoing Women in AI series, which seeks to give AI-focused women academics and others their well-deserved — and overdue — ti...</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Flight cancellations top 7,000 since IT snafu; Delta CEO apologies after weekend woes</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/sunday-flight-cancellations-it-outage/</link><description>Editor’s note: this story has been updated with new information Mass flight cancellations snarled U.S. airports for a third consecutive day Sunday, th...</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 17:50:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Hawk Tuah' Girl Appears at Jake Paul Fight, Slammed by Nick Kyrgios</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/21/nick-kyrgios-hawk-tuah-haliey-welch-jake-paul-fight-fame/</link><description>Tennis great Nick Kyrgios is bent out of shape that certain people -- AKA the "Hawk Tuah" chick -- are not getting famous the old-fashioned way. Kyrgi...</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 02:25:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nippon Steel hires Mike Pompeo as adviser to seal U.S. Steel deal</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/nippon-steel-hires-mike-pompeo-as-adviser-to-seal-u-s-steel-deal-98f386b1?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Nippon Steel has hired former U.S. Secretary of State Mike Pompeo as an adviser, as part of efforts to complete its plan to acquire U.S. Steel.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 03:46:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sugar Cream Pie (Hoosier Pie)</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/sugar-cream-pie/</link><description>Sugar cream pie, or Hoosier pie, is a creamy, delicious treat with deep roots in the Midwest, especially in Indiana.…</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In case you missed it: This week’s Top 5 stories on social media</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/in-case-you-missed-it-this-weeks-top-5-stories-on-social-media-20/</link><description>Check out a few of the most popular News Network stories on @mayoclinic social media this past week. Can you prevent cancer with lifestyle changes? Ne...</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Kamala Harris has said about AI, tech regulation, and more</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/21/what-kamala-harris-has-said-about-ai-tech-regulation-and-more/</link><description>With President Joe Biden dropping out of the race, Vice President Kamala Harris may become the Democrats’ new nominee. In announcing his plans, Biden ...</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 23:47:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>6 best Alaska cruises for families</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/best-alaska-cruises-for-families/</link><description>Adorable sled dog puppies, graceful whales, fascinating totem poles, lively lumberjacks and majestic glaciers — Alaska has much to offer families of a...</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 17:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jake Paul Defeats Mike Perry Via 6th-Round TKO</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/20/jake-paul-defeats-mike-perry-via-6th-round-tko/</link><description>Jake Paul outlasted "Platinum" Mike Perry on Saturday ... defeating the Bare Knuckle FC and former UFC fighter via sixth-round TKO. Jake handled Mike ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 02:25:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Here’s how stocks performed the last time a president ended a re-election bid — in 1968</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/heres-how-stocks-performed-the-last-time-a-president-ended-a-re-election-bid-in-1968-8b06a7c8?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Stocks rose after LBJ’s surprise announcement, but this time the market had already priced in Biden’s withdrawal.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 03:12:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Boursin Pork Chops</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/boursin-pork-chops/</link><description>Boursin Pork Chops are savory, tender, and covered in a delicious cheesy cream sauce. This one-pan recipe is the perfect easy…</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Demystifying my diagnosis of autism</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/demystifying-my-diagnosis-of-autism/</link><description>After receiving a diagnosis of autism as an adult, a Mayo Clinic graduate student addressed her educational needs — and embarked on research to make t...</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Staffers Were Told Biden Was Leaving Race in Email Telling Them to Check X</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/biden-campaign-staffers-leaving-race-email-x-post/</link><description>“Team, sharing with you the letter from President Biden that was released just now,” read an email that President Joe Biden’s campaign managers sent.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 22:58:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The first US hotel with flight simulators is opening this fall</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/us-hotel-flight-simulator-hotel-polaris/</link><description>Have you always dreamed of engaging in a virtual F-16 battle? Do you wish to play commercial airline captain for a day while attempting a landing at t...</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 15:00:50 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>