<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 07:35:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Donald Trump Assassination Attempt 'Total Failure' For Secret Service</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/28/donald-trump-assassination-attempt-total-failure-secret-service/</link><description>The Secret Service dropped the ball in spectacular fashion at Donald Trump's campaign rally where he was nearly killed by a would-be assassin ... so s...</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 08:27:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nvidia, AMD, Apple and other tech titans must prove that AI investment is boosting earnings</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/nvidia-amd-apple-and-other-tech-titans-must-prove-that-ai-investment-is-boosting-earnings-07735aa4?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Is Alphabet’s stock price drop — partially due to rising AI costs (and little income) — a sign of things to come?</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 13:21:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>One-Pan Lemon Chicken Orzo</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/lemon-chicken-orzo/</link><description>One-Pan Lemon Chicken Orzo is a comforting, well-rounded meal! Tender, juicy chicken pieces are joined with orzo pasta in a…</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Once a bariatric surgery patient, nurse now inspires others</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/once-a-bariatric-surgery-patient-nurse-now-inspires-others/</link><description>Eastern Caribbean or Western Caribbean, lounging on the ship or island hopping, Julie Pulmano's love language is "any vacation on a boat." The 60-year...</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>US border agents must get warrant before cell phone searches, federal court rules</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/29/us-border-agents-must-get-warrant-before-cell-phone-searches-federal-court-rules/</link><description>Critics have long argued that device searches at the U.S. border are unconstitutional and violate the Fourth Amendment. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 13:00:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Marriott and United elite members can use RewardsPlus to status match and convert rewards</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/marriott-united-rewardsplus/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information. Marriott Bonvoy and United MileagePlus have a partnership known as Re...</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 21:00:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coco Gauff's Tennis Teammates Bailed on Crowded Olympic Village for Hotels</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/28/coco-gauff-tennis-teammates-left-olympic-village-hotel-crowded-bathroom/</link><description>Coco Gauff was not just a flagbearer for Team USA for the opening ceremony of the Paris Olympics ... she was also the bearer of bad news ... the Olymp...</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 08:27:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Occidental unveils $970 million worth of asset sales as it works to reduce debt</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/occidental-agrees-to-sell-assets-in-texas-and-new-mexico-to-permian-resources-for-about-818-million-158918a1?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>The Warren Buffett-backed company is selling about 27,500 net acres in the Barilla Draw Field of the Texas Delaware Basin and about 2,000 net acres in the New Mexico Delaware Basin, with combined net fourth-quarter production estimated at about 15,000 barrels of oil equivalent a day.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 13:13:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Meal Plan #12</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/weekly-meal-plan-12/</link><description>This weekly meal plan has so many of my favorite recipes in it! It has meals that even my kiddos…</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>3D tattooing after breast reconstruction</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/3d-tattooing-after-breast-reconstruction/</link><description>Breast cancer is the most diagnosed cancer in U.S. women with about 1 in 8 women diagnosed over the course of their lifetime. In about 35% of cases, a...</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Back to BASIC—the Most Consequential Programming Language in the History of Computing</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/back-to-basic-the-most-consequential-programming-language/</link><description>Coding was a preserve of elites, until BASIC hit the streets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>American makes big cuts in Austin, brings flagship jet to Charlotte</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/american-cuts-austin-brings-777-300-to-charlotte/</link><description>It seems like Austin, Texas wasn’t as hot as American Airlines had expected. Over the weekend, the airline filed yet another major schedule change sur...</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 19:30:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ariana Grande, Tom Cruise and Other Celebrities Hit Up Olympics Women's Gymnastics</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/28/ariana-grande-tom-cruise-celebrities-paris-olympics-womens-gymnastics/</link><description>The Olympics may be struggling with Olympics fans venturing to Paris because it's so insanely expensive ... but for celebs where money is no object, t...</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 08:27:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Some $6 trillion of funds are about to shift — and here’s where they may end up</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/some-6-trillion-of-funds-are-about-to-shift-and-heres-where-they-may-end-up-d4857031?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Strategists at UBS led by Matthew Mish say corporate debt will benefit when fund flows begin to shift.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 13:12:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pita Pizza</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/pita-pizza/</link><description>Pita pizza is like having your own personalized mini-pizza! Grab some ready-made pitas, pile on your favorite toppings, and indulge…</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 02:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: How to jump-start your workout</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-how-to-jump-start-your-workout/</link><description>The Summer Olympics have started, which might inspire you to be more physically active. But jump-starting your workout routine can be challenging if y...</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 17:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TikTok Has a Nazi Problem</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/tiktok-nazi-content-moderation/</link><description>Not only is TikTok’s algorithm promoting Neo-Nazi content, extremist organizations are also using the platform to recruit new members and encourage real-world action.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is the Amex Gold worth the annual fee?</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/amex-gold-worth-annual-fee/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. The American Express® Gold Card gets a lot of attention fo...</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 19:00:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Robert Downey Jr. Will Reprise Role as Doctor Doom in 'Avengers' Sequel</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/28/robert-downey-jr-reprising-doctor-doom-avengers/</link><description>Robert Downey Jr. stunned fans of the Marvel Cinematic Universe when it was announced Saturday that he would play Doctor Doom in a new 'Avengers' film...</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 08:27:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘She’s a danger to herself’: Our late brother left us $3 million, but my sister is in hospital with schizophrenia. Should I take control of her finances?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/i-want-to-get-control-of-her-money-my-brother-left-my-sister-and-me-3-million-but-she-is-in-hospital-with-schizophrenia-will-this-inheritance-be-the-worst-thing-for-her-0f5cabe2?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>“At the moment, we are both in Florida, but the inheritance is in a California probate court.”</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 13:11:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Basil Vinaigrette</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/basil-vinaigrette/</link><description>Basil Vinaigrette is a versatile dressing made from a few fresh ingredients. It is bursting with flavor and can be…</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Preventing measles outbreaks in the US through vaccination</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/preventing-measles-outbreaks-in-the-us-through-vaccination/</link><description>The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention reports more than a dozen outbreaks of measles in the U.S., with more than 165 confirmed cases of the h...</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 16:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>UK’s Zapp EV plans to expand globally with an early start in India</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/28/uks-zapp-ev-plans-to-expand-globally-with-early-start-in-india/</link><description>Zapp is launching its urban electric two-wheeler in India in 2025 as it plans to expand globally. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 03:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>My (totally fun) vacation at Nashville International Airport</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/nashville-airport-hilton-guest-pass/</link><description>You may think you already spend too much time at airports. Most frequent flyers do. But the growing list of airports offering visitor passes to nontic...</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 17:00:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Love Island' Star Rob Rausch Hanging Out with YouTuber Tarayummy</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/28/rob-rausch-tarayummy-hang-out-los-angeles-matching-tattoos/</link><description>Rob Rausch -- the controversial player from the most recent "Love Island USA" season -- may have found a connection off-camera ... 'cause he's hanging...</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 08:27:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Abbott Labs, Reckitt see further stock-price pressure after $495 million jury award</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/baby-formula-settlement-drags-reckitt-down-after-495-million-jury-award-against-abbott-b74ca8a6?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>U.K. consumer-products giant Reckitt saw its share price slump after a jury awarded $495 million in a key baby-formula case.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 13:10:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chocolate Peanut Butter Ice Cream Bars (Vegan)</title><link>https://minimalistbaker.com/chocolate-peanut-butter-ice-cream-bars-vegan/</link><description>Welcome back, friends! We’ve returned to the magical land of chocolate + peanut butter (one of our favorite places). This timeless combo has won the d...</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In case you missed it: This week’s Top 5 stories on social media</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/in-case-you-missed-it-this-weeks-top-5-stories-on-social-media-21/</link><description>Check out a few of the most popular News Network stories on @mayoclinic social media this past week. Mayo Clinic Minute: Why skipping breakfast can be...</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 15:29:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dear Google, who wants an AI-written fan letter?</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/28/dear-google-who-wants-an-ai-written-fan-letter/</link><description>The first time I saw Google’s latest commercial, I wondered, “Is it just me, or is this kind of bad?” By the fourth or fifth time I saw it, I’d stopped wondering. It starts innocuously enough, with a father talking about how much his daughter loves Sydney McLaughlin-Levrone (she “might even be the world’s number […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 21:09:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>9 best South Pacific and Tahiti cruises for a once-in-a-lifetime trip</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/best-south-pacific-tahiti-cruises/</link><description>Cruising around the islands of the South Pacific is a once-in-a-lifetime trip for many travelers. While some of the island nations, like Fiji, are wel...</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 15:00:57 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>