<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 09:11:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Pete Buttigieg Shares How He'd Campaign as Kamala Harris' VP</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/24/pete-buttigieg-shares-how-hed-go-about-vice-president-campaign/</link><description>Pete Buttigieg is fully onboard with getting Vice President Kamala Harris elected to the White House ... whether or not she selects him as her running...</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 07:48:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Universal Music Group, a massive holding of Bill Ackman, sees stock-price tumble on streaming worries</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/universal-music-group-a-massive-holding-of-bill-ackman-sees-stock-price-tumble-on-streaming-worries-87df6805?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Shares in Universal Music Group, a big holding of Bill Ackman’s Pershing Square Capital Management, lost more than a quarter of its value on Thursday ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 12:44:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Basil Vinaigrette</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/basil-vinaigrette/</link><description>Basil Vinaigrette is a versatile dressing made from a few fresh ingredients. It is bursting with flavor and can be…</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New research discovers a new combination of therapy for people with a type of leukemia, leading them to live longer</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/new-research-discovers-a-new-combination-of-therapy-for-people-with-a-type-of-leukemia-leading-them-to-live-longer/</link><description>ROCHESTER, Minn. — In a new multicenter international study led by the Mayo Clinic Comprehensive Cancer Center, researchers found that people with the...</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 23:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Revolut receives long-awaited UK banking license</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/25/revolut-receives-much-awaited-uk-banking-license/</link><description>This is a significant milestone for the London-based fintech company, particularly since it has been trying to secure this license since 2021. © 2024 ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 12:08:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Southwest’s COO details new red-eye flights in TPG interview</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/southwest-airlines-redeye-flights-overnight/</link><description>Southwest Airlines is flying somewhere it’s never flown before: into the night. The airline plans to operate overnight flights for the first time in i...</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 12:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NBA Strikes Media Rights Deal With Amazon Prime Video, TNT Not Giving Up</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/24/nba-strikes-media-rights-deal-amazon-prime-video-ending-tnt-partnership/</link><description>2:45 PM PT -- TNT isn't going down without a fight ... saying it will take appropriate action after the league "grossly misinterpreted our contractual...</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 07:48:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Southwest Airlines to move ahead with assigned seating and premium seating options</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/southwest-airlines-to-move-ahead-with-assigned-seating-and-premium-seating-options-0891741b?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description></description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 12:38:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chocolate Peanut Butter Ice Cream Bars (Vegan)</title><link>https://minimalistbaker.com/chocolate-peanut-butter-ice-cream-bars-vegan/</link><description>Welcome back, friends! We’ve returned to the magical land of chocolate + peanut butter (one of our favorite places). This timeless combo has won the d...</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Detecting pancreatic cancer through changes in body composition and metabolism</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/detecting-pancreatic-cancer-through-changes-in-body-composition-and-metabolism/</link><description>Pancreatic cancer is a formidable disease, often diagnosed too late for effective treatment. However, new research from Mayo Clinic represents a promi...</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Soon Might the Atlantic Ocean Break? Two Sibling Scientists Found an Answer—and Shook the World</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/amoc-collapse-atlantic-ocean/</link><description>A gigantic, weather-defining current system could be headed to collapse. Peter and Susanne Ditlevsen had a simple yet controversial question: How much...</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JetBlue cuts or halts 24 routes, pulls out of 7 cities — but doubles down on New England</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/jetblue-network-shakeup/</link><description>JetBlue is pausing or cutting service on two dozen routes and pulling seven cities off its route map entirely as part of its latest network shakeup. T...</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 00:14:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prosecutors Cite Alleged Diddy Hit on Tupac, Try to Block Keefe D's Release</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/24/diddy-claim-alleged-hit-offer-money-kill-tupac-keefe-d-bond-opposition/</link><description>2:28 PM PT -- Law enforcement sources tell TMZ ... Diddy was never a suspect in the Tupac murder investigation, and that remains true today. In other ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 07:48:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Here’s the one factor that can douse the benefits of stock buybacks, according to Morgan Stanley</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/heres-the-one-factor-that-can-douse-the-benefits-of-stock-buybacks-according-to-morgan-stanley-9576f7a0?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>A Morgan Stanley fund crunched the numbers on companies that do buybacks while awarding employees stock</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 12:37:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Marry Me Shrimp Pasta</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/marry-me-shrimp-pasta/</link><description>Marry Me Shrimp Pasta dazzles with robust Italian flavors. It’s ready in just 30 minutes, and the creamy sauce, brimming…</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: Reducing thumb arthritis pain</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-reducing-thumb-arthritis-pain/</link><description>Thousands of Americans suffer from thumb arthritis. This disorder can greatly affect daily life and can make it a struggle to do simple things like op...</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 16:30:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oversight Board wants Meta to refine its policies around AI-generated explicit images</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/25/oversight-board-wants-meta-to-refine-its-policies-around-ai-generated-explicit-images/</link><description>The Board wants Meta to change the terminology it uses for labeling explicit, AI-generated images from "derogatory" to "non-consensual." © 2024 TechCr...</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Complete guide to airline status matches and challenges in 2024</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/airline-status-matches-challenges/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. While most loyalty programs do not offer a way to extend e...</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 23:30:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Dukes of Hazzard' Star John Schneider Marries Paul Sorvino's Widow Dee Dee</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/24/dukes-of-hazzard-john-schneider-paul-sorvino-widow-dee-dee/</link><description>John Schneider has found a new Duchess of Hazzard -- tying the knot with Dee Dee Sorvino, widow of the late Paul Sorvino ... about two years after his...</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 07:48:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oil prices fall after another China rate cut underlines demand worries</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/oil-prices-fall-after-another-china-rate-cut-underlines-demand-worries-59e91749?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Oil futures fell early Thursday after China’s central bank delivered another cut to rates, underlining worries about demand from the world’s second la...</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 12:36:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tropical Smoothie</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/tropical-smoothie/</link><description>This refreshing tropical smoothie is bursting with tropical fruit flavors, making it the perfect treat for a hot day. Sip…</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tomorrow’s Cure: How personalized vaccines combat cancer</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/tomorrows-cure-how-personalized-vaccines-combat-cancer/</link><description>The new episode of Tomorrow’s Cure highlights the efforts of research scientists who are equipping a vaccine with bits of proteins that redirect the i...</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Google Maps adds a slew of features to entice Indian drivers, commuters and travelers</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/25/google-maps-adds-features-to-improve-navigating-flyovers-and-narrow-roads-in-india/</link><description>Google Maps is improving navigation through flyovers and narrow roads in India through new feature updates. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. Fo...</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 09:30:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The best time to apply for these popular Citi credit cards, based on offer history</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/citi-best-welcome-offers/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. Citi is a TPG advertising partner. If you’re considering a...</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 23:15:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rockies Pitcher Ribs Reese McGuire Over Masturbation Arrest, Nearly Incites Brawl</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/24/rockies-pitcher-clowns-reese-mcguire-over-masturbation-bust-go-jack-off-in-a-parking-lot/</link><description>Rockies pitcher Cal Quantrill got so pissed at Reese McGuire during their game Wednesday, he shaded the Red Sox catcher for his past public masturbati...</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 07:48:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nestle and Unilever see share prices diverge on rival price hiking strategies</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/nestle-and-unilever-see-share-prices-diverge-on-rival-price-hiking-strategies-0b126203?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Nestle hiked its prices at a faster rate than its rival Unilever in a strategy that saw the Swiss firm’s revenue drop as its British competitor posted...</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 12:21:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Grilled Tri-Tip</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/grilled-tri-tip/</link><description>Grilled Tri-Tip is a flavorful, juicy steak that will be the star of your barbecue! It’s marinated in a simple,…</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What you need to know about listeria</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/what-you-need-to-know-about-listeria/</link><description>The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention has issued an alert after a listeria outbreak in several states. There have been at least two fatalitie...</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 19:54:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>bunch raises $15.5M for its platform that simplifies investment management for VCs</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/25/bunch-raises-15-5m-series-a-for-private-markets-platform-aimed-at-vc-funds/</link><description>Public market investors have a large variety of infrastructure and software that helps them keep track of, analyze and manage their investments, but t...</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 09:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amex will open its fourth Centurion Lounge in Mexico City</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/amex-centurion-lounge-mexico-city/</link><description>American Express is making big moves south of the border. The issuer announced on Wednesday that it will open its fourth Centurion Lounge at Mexico Ci...</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 23:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>