<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 08:05:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Marc Anthony's Dominican Republic House Catches Fire, Caught on Video</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/08/marc-anthony-house-fire/</link><description>Marc Anthony's house in the Dominican Republic went up in flames Thursday ... burning up part of the building -- and a local TV crew caught it all on ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 08:46:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Space stocks set to climb, boosted by Virgin Galactic and Rocket Lab results</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/space-stocks-set-to-climb-boosted-by-virgin-galactic-and-rocket-lab-results-df3b8128?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Rocket Lab reported a 71% revenue jump when it reported second-quarter results Thursday.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 13:32:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Croissant Bread</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/croissant-bread/</link><description>Croissant Bread is beautiful and fluffy with crispy, flaky layers on the outside. It’s also one of the most delicious…</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Start A Successful Health Coaching Business (Yes, You Can!)</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/4-tips-to-starting-successful-health-coaching-business</link><description>Start your journey helping people make life-changing health shifts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 11:27:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Hackers Extracted the ‘Keys to the Kingdom’ to Clone HID Keycards</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/hid-keycard-authentication-key-vulnerability/</link><description>A team of researchers have developed a method for extracting authentication keys out of HID encoders, which could allow hackers to clone the types of keycards used to secure offices and other areas worldwide.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Here’s why the Venture X and Amex Gold are the only 2 cards in my wallet</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/venture-x-amex-gold-best-combo/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. Like many TPGers, I’ve been sucked into credit cards with ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 11:00:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Donations Pour In For Lazar Dukic After CrossFit Games Drowning</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/08/drowning-crossfit-lazar-dukic-gofundme/</link><description>The CrossFit community is coming together to support Serbian athlete Lazar Dukic's family after he drowned at the 2024 CrossFit Games ... with hundred...</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 08:46:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eli Lilly Is Gaining on Novo Nordisk in the Obesity Race</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/eli-lilly-is-gaining-on-novo-nordisk-in-the-obesity-race-843bbfa9?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>Despite a late start, the advantage is shifting toward the U.S. company.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 13:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Boil Corn on the Cob</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/how-to-boil-corn-on-the-cob/</link><description>This is the BEST recipe for how to boil corn on the cob! Fresh summer corn gets boiled in a…</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>No Lie, This Supplement Is Like The Fountain Of Youth For Your Skin</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/how-each-mbg-best-skin-ingredient-benefits-aging-skin</link><description>Do you do your skin care routine morning and night? Great. But there's more you can do. Here's how to approach skin aging from the inside out.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 11:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Camo Hats Became an Instant Meme</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/camo-hats-harris-walz-instant-meme/</link><description>This week, Vice President Kamala Harris and Minnesota Governor Tim Walz cemented their bid for the White House with some camouflage caps. The headgear is on its way to red MAGA hat status.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>4 reasons someone in your family needs a United credit card</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/why-someone-in-your-family-needs-to-have-a-united-credit-card/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. Airline credit cards weren’t always super exciting, especi...</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 11:00:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chrisean Rock Mug Shot Surfaces In Oklahoma Drug Case</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/08/chrisean-rock-mug-shot-surfaces/</link><description>Chrisean Rock's newest mug shot shows her giant persona after the reality star's buzz was iced after her June arrest. According to her Craig County Sh...</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 08:46:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>20 stocks the bears can’t easily short — and that’s why you shouldn’t buy them</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/20-stocks-the-bears-cant-easily-short-and-thats-why-you-shouldnt-buy-them-473132db?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Companies that short-sellers struggle to bet against — like Super Micro Computer — are likely overvalued.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 13:21:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chocolate Cherry Protein Shake</title><link>https://minimalistbaker.com/chocolate-cherry-protein-shake/</link><description>Getting your protein in just got A LOT more delicious, friends! This chocolate cherry protein shake is thick, creamy, chocolaty, perfectly sweet, SO d...</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In A Financial Pinch? 7 Small Savings Tips That Add Up To Big Savings</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/small-savings-tips-that-add-up-to-big-savings</link><description>Don’t dismiss the power of baby steps, especially when it comes to saving money. Small money moves can add up to big savings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 21:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Olympics' Hostile Architecture Is a Preview of What's to Come</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/paris-los-angeles-olympics-hostile-architecture-homeless/</link><description>Under a bridge in Paris, a homeless encampment has been replaced with dozens of giant Lego-like bricks. Campaigners say things will likely get worse at the 2028 Games in LA.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to use your Amex Uber credits for rides and meals</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/amex-platinum-uber-cash-credit/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information. At first glance (and for the uninitiated), credit card annual fees ca...</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 11:00:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>College Students Hospitalized, Shocking Pic Shows Them Passed Out on Cancun Bar</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/08/college-students-hospitalized-cancun-bar/</link><description>College student Zara Hull is speaking out after she and her friend were apparently drugged at a swim-up bar in Cancun, Mexico ... sharing the harrowin...</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 08:46:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Perrigo voluntarily recalls 16,500 cans of baby formula because of excessive levels of vitamin D</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/perrigo-is-voluntarily-recalling-16-500-cans-of-baby-formula-because-of-high-levels-of-vitamin-d-9aa1a405?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>For most infants, short-term consumption of the affected formula is unlikely to cause harm. But in a small subset of infants, such as those with impaired renal function, there is “the potential that consumption of the recalled product could result in health complications,” a statement said.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 13:19:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Italian Corn Salad</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/italian-corn-salad/</link><description>This Italian Corn Salad is bursting with fresh flavors from sweet corn, juicy grape tomatoes, crisp green bell pepper, and…</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 02:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A 7-Week Plan To Master Pull-Ups (&amp; Why This Move Is A+ For Healthy Aging)</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/how-to-do-your-first-pull-up-7-week-beginner-plan</link><description>Pull-ups are way more than just a flex—they can actively boost longevity and health span.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 13:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Does Jewelry and Big Hair Slow Down Olympic Runners?</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/does-jewelry-slow-down-olympic-runners/</link><description>Even a little added weight and air drag can make a measurable difference. But WIRED's physics guru says, if it makes you feel strong, go for it!</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Does it make sense to hold an Amex Platinum and Amex Gold card?</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/amex-platinum-and-amex-gold-card/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. I know what you’re thinking: It doesn’t make much sense to...</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 11:00:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ariana Grande Details Conflicted Feelings About Music Leaks</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/08/ariana-grande-leaked-music-comments/</link><description>Ariana Grande is laying it all out about the "dehumanizing" impact of hackers leaking her music -- she says she’s got mixed feelings about the whole m...</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 08:46:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This strategist downgraded tech just before the summer swoon. Now he says buy and here’s why.</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/this-strategist-downgraded-tech-just-before-the-summer-swoon-now-he-says-buy-and-heres-why-14aa2e5c?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>This analyst downgraded tech before the slide and now he says buy</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 12:22:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cinnamon Roll Cheesecake</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/cinnamon-roll-cheesecake/</link><description>Rich and creamy Cinnamon Roll Cheesecake has the delicious flavor of a cinnamon roll in decadent cheesecake form. This irresistible…</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Creatine Supplements Bad For Your Kidneys? What's Fact vs. Fiction</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/are-creatine-supplements-bad-for-your-kidneys</link><description>Here's what you should know.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 12:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cambridge Audio Evo One Review: A Gorgeous High-End Speaker</title><link>https://www.wired.com/review/review-cambridge-audio-evo-one/</link><description>This superbly engineered all-in-one audio system will put a huge smile on your face.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 10:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Citi Prestige vs. Citi Strata Premier: Should you keep the Prestige or downgrade to the Strata Premier?</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/citi-prestige-vs-thankyou-premier/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. Citi is a TPG advertising partner. Citi’s flagship transfe...</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 11:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>