<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 07:33:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Bianca Censori Wears Nearly-Naked Look to Shop With Mom &amp; Sisters</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/19/bianca-censori-naked-outfit-shopping/</link><description>Bianca Censori seems like she's toning down her nearly-naked style lately ... but even wearing pants and a top, there's not much left to the imaginati...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 08:24:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oil prices edge higher after ending at nearly 2-week low</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/oil-prices-edge-higher-after-ending-at-nearly-2-week-low-560e3557?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Oil futures edged higher Tuesday morning, consolidating after ending the previous session at their lowest since Aug. 6 in response to hopes for a cease-fire between Israel and Hamas as well as concerns over China’s demand for crude.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 13:21:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kale Apple Slaw with Dijon Vinaigrette</title><link>https://minimalistbaker.com/kale-apple-slaw-with-dijon-vinaigrette/</link><description>When salad season and apple season collide, make this QUICK kale apple slaw! It’s sweet, crunchy, zippy, versatile, and comes together in just 10 minu...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Start A Successful Health Coaching Business (Yes, You Can!)</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/4-tips-to-starting-successful-health-coaching-business</link><description>Start your journey helping people make life-changing health shifts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 11:27:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Starpath accelerates moon water mining plans with $12M seed funding</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/20/starpath-accelerates-moon-water-mining-plans-with-12m-seed-funding/</link><description>NASA and the space industry are in agreement: if we want to establish a permanent human presence on the moon, we’ll need to make use of every native resource we can — and none are as important as water ice. Starpath Robotics is one of a handful of startups planning for this future. The startup […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FYI: You can bring (frozen) drinks through airport security</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/frozen-drinks-through-security/</link><description>Editor’s note: This post was updated with new information. Full-size liquids are among the items travelers most frequently forget to remove from their...</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 23:00:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TikTok Star Nicky Champa Files For Divorce From Pierre Boo</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/19/tiktok-couple-nicky-champa-pierre-boo-divorce/</link><description>TikTok star Nicky Champa is pulling the plug on his marriage ... he just filed for divorce from his famous partner. Nicky beelined it to court bright ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 08:24:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Harris and Trump promise us many financial benefits, but we need to know the costs</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/harris-and-trump-promise-us-many-financial-benefits-but-we-need-to-know-the-costs-6d0006ff?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>The Harris economic plan falls short, but Trump hasn’t offered a compelling alternative.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 13:20:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biscoff Cookies</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/biscoff-cookies/</link><description>Satisfy your sweet tooth with loaded Biscoff Cookies. They are soft and chewy and infused with the flavor of Biscoff…</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>No Lie, This Supplement Is Like The Fountain Of Youth For Your Skin</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/how-each-mbg-best-skin-ingredient-benefits-aging-skin</link><description>Do you do your skin care routine morning and night? Great. But there's more you can do. Here's how to approach skin aging from the inside out.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 11:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Reliant’s paper-scouring AI takes on science’s data drudgery</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/20/reliant-ai/</link><description>AI models have proven capable of many things, but what tasks do we actually want them doing? Preferably drudgery — and there’s plenty of that in research and academia. Reliant hopes to specialize in the kind of time-consuming data extraction work that’s currently a specialty of tired grad students and interns. “The best thing you […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 12:59:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Marriott Bonvoy program: How to redeem points for hotel stays, airfare and more</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/redeem-points-marriott-bonvoy-program/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with the latest information. Are you looking to maximize your Marriott Bonvoy points? Aside...</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 22:00:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shiloh Jolie Officially Drops Pitt From Last Name</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/19/shiloh-jolie-pitt-name-change-approved/</link><description>Shiloh Jolie has officially dropped dad Brad Pitt's surname from her moniker ... the 18-year-old has been granted a name change, TMZ has learned. In n...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 08:24:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘I don’t deserve this’: My abusive son only calls when he wants money. How do I put an end to his bullying and mooching?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/i-dont-deserve-this-my-abusive-son-only-calls-when-he-wants-money-how-do-i-put-an-end-to-his-bullying-and-mooching-8f82a81a?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>“It’s obvious that he doesn’t need me for anything except money.”</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 13:12:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cowboy Cornbread Casserole</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/cowboy-cornbread-casserole/</link><description>Cowboy Cornbread Casserole is a flavorful, comforting meal that’s so easy to make. Seasoned ground beef, corn, pinto beans, and…</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In A Financial Pinch? 7 Small Savings Tips That Add Up To Big Savings</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/small-savings-tips-that-add-up-to-big-savings</link><description>Don’t dismiss the power of baby steps, especially when it comes to saving money. Small money moves can add up to big savings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 21:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mike Lynch, recently acquitted in HP-Autonomy fraud case, is missing after yacht capsized off Sicily (updated)</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/20/mike-lynch-recently-acquitted-in-hp-autonomy-case-is-missing-after-yacht-capsized-off-sicily/</link><description>Update: Authorities have yet to access the inside of the sunken yacht, and Mike Lynch is still classified as missing. Other details have emerged in the interim. The accident appears to have been caused by a major storm and a resulting tornado-like water column that ensnared and damaged the yacht. Among the other six people […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 10:16:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Your vendor doesn’t accept credit cards — what now?</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/your-vendor-doesnt-accept-credit-cards-what-now/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. Small-business owners are constantly making payments to ve...</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 21:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sexyy Red Launches NSFW Lip Gloss Names</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/19/sexyy-red-nsfw-lip-gloss/</link><description>Sexyy Red is heating up summer with a new business venture ... a line of NSFW lip glosses, seemingly channeling her "Pound Town" anthem. The rapper re...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 08:24:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nvidia’s earnings could be noisy, but these bulls are still upbeat on the stock</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/nvidias-earnings-could-be-noisy-but-these-bulls-are-still-upbeat-on-the-stock-e21a7da3?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Analysts are curious about potential shipment delays for the new Blackwell chip but see plenty of reason to cheer Nvidia’s long-term opportunity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 13:09:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spaghetti alla Nerano (Stanley Tucci Zucchini Pasta)</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/spaghetti-alla-nerano/</link><description>Spaghetti alla Nerano is an unforgettable pasta dish packed with flavor! It has a rich and creamy zucchini sauce infused…</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A 7-Week Plan To Master Pull-Ups (&amp; Why This Move Is A+ For Healthy Aging)</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/how-to-do-your-first-pull-up-7-week-beginner-plan</link><description>Pull-ups are way more than just a flex—they can actively boost longevity and health span.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 13:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>US tech giants fight Indian telcos’ bid to regulate internet services, pay for network usage</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/20/us-tech-giants-fight-indian-telcos-bid-to-regulate-internet-services/</link><description>Global technology giants are pushing back against attempts by India’s telecom networks to bring internet services under stricter regulation, rejecting arguments that such measures are necessary to create a “level playing field” and address national security concerns. The Asia Internet Coalition (AIC), a powerful industry body that represents Amazon, Apple, Google, Meta, Microsoft, Netflix and […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 10:12:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Marriott rolls out new partnership with vacation rental platform Sonder</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/marriott-sonder-partnership/</link><description>The world’s largest hotel company continues to think outside the box of its traditional brands. Marriott International announced Monday morning a part...</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 20:30:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Flavor Flav Parties With USA Women's Water Polo Team In Vegas After Olympics</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/19/flavor-flav-parties-water-polo-team/</link><description>The USA women's water polo team took the party from Paris to Sin City this month -- jet-setting to Vegas following their run in the Olympics -- and th...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 08:24:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paramount’s stock boosted after report Edgar Bronfman Jr. has submitted $4.3 billion offer for Redstone’s National Amusements</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/paramounts-stock-boosted-after-report-edgar-bronfman-jr-has-submitted-4-3-billion-offer-for-redstones-national-amusements-b00c2ee9?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Media executive Edgar Bronfman Jr. has submitted a $4.3 billion offer for National Amusements in an attempt to upend a previous agreement to merge it with David Ellison’s Skydance Media, according to the Wall Street Journal.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 13:06:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Meal Plan #15</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/weekly-meal-plan-15/</link><description>This weekly meal plan has some classics with a twist that you are going to love! It gives you a…</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Creatine Supplements Bad For Your Kidneys? What's Fact vs. Fiction</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/are-creatine-supplements-bad-for-your-kidneys</link><description>Here's what you should know.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 12:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pakistan’s PostEx to enter new markets, starting with Saudi Arabia</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/19/pakistans-postex-to-enter-new-markets-starting-with-saudi-arabia/</link><description>Pakistani startup PostEx is entering Saudi Arabia as first global market after hitting $21 million ARR in the South Asian nation. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deal alert: Fly United business class from New York to Paris for only 60K miles</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/deals/star-alliance-paris-business-class/</link><description>If you’ve been dreaming of Paris during the holiday season, you’ll want to take advantage of this business-class bargain on United Airlines flights be...</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 20:00:33 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>