<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 07:19:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Melania Trump Responds to Trump Assassination Attempt</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/14/donald-trump-melania-responds-statement-assassination-attempt/</link><description>Melania Trump has just addressed the violent shooting that almost took her husband’s life Saturday. She explains how her and Barron’s life could have ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 07:52:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘It’s a very ugly American trait’: I cried foul when basic-economy passengers grabbed premium-economy seats. The airline has finally shown me respect.</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/its-a-very-ugly-american-trait-i-cried-foul-when-basic-economy-passengers-grabbed-premium-economy-seats-the-airline-has-finally-shown-me-respect-dad2e467?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>“That woman and her mother were selfish and self-interested, and believed that they were entitled to get those seats.”</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 12:35:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sushi Bowl</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/sushi-bowl/</link><description>This sushi bowl is a deconstructed California sushi roll loaded with irresistible flavor and all of the best sushi ingredients.…</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In the wake of thoracic outlet syndrome, an outdoors enthusiast triumphs</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/in-the-wake-of-thoracic-outlet-syndrome-an-outdoors-enthusiast-triumphs/</link><description>Johnathan Sederquist isn’t interested in taking it easy. The active 29-year-old likes to work out early in the morning, do landscaping and excavation ...</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Hidden Ties Between Google and Amazon’s Project Nimbus and Israel's Military</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/amazon-google-project-nimbus-israel-idf/</link><description>A WIRED investigation found public statements from officials detail a much closer link between Project Nimbus and Israel Defense Forces than previousl...</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is Hyatt Globalist status worth it?</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/hyatt-globalist-elite-status/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. Until I earned Hyatt Globalist status for the first time i...</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 22:00:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>First Photos of Donald Trump Shooter Surface</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/14/donald-trump-thomas-matthew-crooks-first-photos-shooter-surface/</link><description>The face of the gunman who tried to assassinate former President Donald Trump has now been unmasked -- and he looks like your average adolescent. Phot...</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 07:52:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why small-caps are the ‘most compelling investment case’ right now</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/why-small-caps-are-the-most-compelling-investment-case-right-now-46dfae3a?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>The obvious question for investors is whether the burst of interest in small-caps presages a longer up-trend for the sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 12:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Texas Twinkies</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/texas-twinkies/</link><description>Texas Twinkies are a major upgrade to your classic jalapeño poppers! They’re jalapeños filled with cream cheese, brisket, and shredded…</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How tapering maximizes your potential on marathon day</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/how-tapering-maximizes-your-potential-on-marathon-day/</link><description>The taper is an essential aspect of training that many new runners need to remember to incorporate into their training program. Tapering means reducin...</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How VanMoof’s new owners plan to win over its old customers</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/15/how-vanmoofs-new-owners-plan-to-win-over-its-old-customers/</link><description>When VanMoof declared bankruptcy last year, it left around 5,000 customers who had pre-ordered e-bikes in the lurch. Now VanMoof is up and running und...</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Western Mediterranean vs. Eastern Mediterranean cruises: Which itinerary will I like more?</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/western-vs-eastern-mediterranean-cruises/</link><description>The Mediterranean is the top cruising region in Europe, but ships rarely traverse the entire sea in a weeklong sailing. That means you have to choose ...</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 19:00:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Donald Trump Won't Delay Trip to Republican Convention Despite Assassination Attempt</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/14/donald-trump-will-not-delay-trip-republican-national-convention-assassination-attempt/</link><description>Donald Trump's travel plans aren't changing despite the attempt on his life Saturday ... with the former president saying he's still flying to Milwauk...</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 07:52:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rare-Earth Prices Are in the Doldrums. China Wants to Keep Them That Way.</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/rare-earth-prices-are-in-the-doldrums-china-wants-to-keep-them-that-way-bf0477da?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>China hasn’t been shy about using its dominance of supply chains to apply political pressure.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 12:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Meal Plan #11</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/weekly-meal-plan-11/</link><description>Weekly meal plan 11 is packed with so many delicious and vibrant flavors! With stir fry and tacos and a…</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: Keeping kids safe outside during summer play</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-keeping-kids-safe-outside-during-summer-play/</link><description>Summer vacation for kids is well underway. Finding activities to keep the kids busy and destinations to visit can be on many parents' list. There is o...</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 17:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mitti Labs aims to make rice farming less harmful to the climate, starting in India</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/14/mitti-labs-aims-to-make-rice-farming-less-harmful-to-the-climate-starting-in-india/</link><description>Mitti Labs aims to transform rice farming in India and other South Asian markets by reducing methane emissions by 50% and water consumption by 30%. © ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 06:30:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Luxury treehouses and fabulous food in the wilds of Montana: My stay at The Green-O</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/reviews/the-green-o-review/</link><description>[circuit type=review circuit_id=”9092″] Editor’s note: The Green-O provided TPG with a complimentary two-night stay so that we could get an inside loo...</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 15:00:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pennsylvania Officials Identify Victim in Trump Assassination Attempt</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/14/corey-comperatore-donald-trump-shooter-victim/</link><description>1:21 PM PT -- Authorities have released the names of two other people who were shot but are in stable condition ... David Dutch, 57, and James Copenha...</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 07:52:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are you wealthy, or just rich? Here’s how to tell, according to financial advisers.</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/are-you-wealthy-or-just-rich-heres-how-to-tell-according-to-financial-advisers-e4817bfc?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>“I know folks who make seven figures a year … but are a couple of missed paychecks away from bankruptcy,” one financial adviser says.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 12:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Baked Huli Huli Chicken</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/baked-huli-huli-chicken/</link><description>Baked Huli Huli chicken is a tried and true recipe now made in the oven! Tender chicken baked in a…</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Can you prevent cancer with lifestyle changes?</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/can-you-prevent-cancer-with-lifestyle-changes/</link><description>Nearly half of cancer deaths in the U.S. are associated with preventable risk factors — such as smoking and alcohol use — according to a new American ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 16:12:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to tell if your online accounts have been hacked</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/14/how-to-tell-if-your-online-accounts-have-been-hacked/</link><description>This is a guide on how to check whether someone compromised your online accounts. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to meet minimum spending on the Ink Business Preferred: $8,000 in 3 months</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/minimum-spend-ink-business-preferred/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. The Ink Business Preferred® Credit Card has long been tout...</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 23:00:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Country Singer Cody Johnson Speaks on Trump Shooting, Encourages People to Vote</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/14/cody-johnson-donald-trump-speaks-about-assassination-attempt-concert-patriotism/</link><description>Cody Johnson's got a message for his fans in the aftermath of the attempt on former President Donald Trump's life ... solve your problems with a ballo...</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 07:52:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘I want to get control of her money’: My brother left my sister and me $3 million, but she is in hospital with schizophrenia. Will this inheritance be the worst thing for her?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/i-want-to-get-control-of-her-money-my-brother-left-my-sister-and-me-3-million-but-she-is-in-hospital-with-schizophrenia-will-this-inheritance-be-the-worst-thing-for-her-0f5cabe2?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>“At the moment, we are both in Florida, but the inheritance is in a California probate court.”</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 11:35:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Baked Alaska</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/baked-alaska/</link><description>Impress everyone with this gorgeous Baked Alaska dessert! It’s surprisingly easy to make with just 5 ingredients. Layers of cake,…</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In case you missed it: This week’s Top 5 stories on social media</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/in-case-you-missed-it-this-weeks-top-5-stories-on-social-media-19/</link><description>Check out a few of the most popular News Network stories on @mayoclinic social media this past week. Mayo Clinic marks medical milestone with world's ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 14:51:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Influencers Are Racing to Profit From the Trump Shooting</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/trump-shooting-influencer-merchandise/</link><description>Niche celebrities and right-wing activists are already hawking merchandise featuring the image of a bloodied Donald Trump raising his fist in the air.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 21:43:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Your complete guide to the Choice Privileges hotel loyalty program</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/choice-privileges/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. Choice Privileges is the rewards program for Choice Hotels...</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 21:00:17 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>