<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 07:04:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Cardi B Announces She's Pregnant with Third Baby On Heels of Divorce News</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/01/cardi-b-pregnant-third-baby-after-filing-divorce-offset/</link><description>Cardi B is having another baby -- something she just announced online ... this hours after she filed for divorce from Offset. The rapper broke the new...</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 07:58:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stock market bulls are dangerously close to losing control to the bears</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/stock-market-bulls-are-dangerously-close-to-losing-control-to-the-bears-20cfb19f?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>S&amp;P 500’s critical support is 5,370.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 12:37:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Peach Lemonade</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/peach-lemonade/</link><description>This is the absolute BEST fresh peach lemonade recipe! Sweet juicy peaches combined with tart, tangy lemons make the most…</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Start A Successful Health Coaching Business (Yes, You Can!)</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/4-tips-to-starting-successful-health-coaching-business</link><description>Start your journey helping people make life-changing health shifts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 11:27:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tuariki Delamere’s Somersault Could Have Launched a New Era in the Olympic Long Jump</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/physics-of-the-banned-front-flip-long-jump/</link><description>The New Zealander came up with a better way to jump, using a front flip in midair. But the sport’s stodgy authorities shut him down before the 1975 Games.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 12:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Clear just increased its annual price for users by $10</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/price-increase-clear/</link><description>As of Aug. 1, the annual price of Clear is up $10 and will now cost $199, per a company spokesperson. The expedited airport security program is curren...</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 00:30:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Salma Hayek Rings In August With Bikini Thirst Trap</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/01/salma-hayek-bikini-thirst-trap-pool/</link><description>Salma Hayek is ringing in a new month with a good old-fashioned thirst trap ... and ya gotta see how she's looking these days in a two-piece swimsuit....</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 07:58:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘She makes seriously irresponsible choices’: We secretly transfer 20% of our 17-year-old daughter’s paycheck to a Roth IRA. Is this illegal?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/she-makes-seriously-irresponsible-choices-we-secretly-transfer-20-of-our-17-year-old-daughters-paycheck-to-a-roth-ira-is-this-illegal-ddd279af?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>“She spends all her money whenever she gets paid.”</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 12:34:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cookie in a Mug</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/cookie-in-a-mug/</link><description>This cookie in a mug recipe is the perfect way to satisfy your cookie craving. In just a few minutes,…</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 02:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>No Lie, This Supplement Is Like The Fountain Of Youth For Your Skin</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/how-each-mbg-best-skin-ingredient-benefits-aging-skin</link><description>Do you do your skin care routine morning and night? Great. But there's more you can do. Here's how to approach skin aging from the inside out.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 11:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How the ‘Slamming Door’ Sound Became Embedded in Hip-Hop History</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/korg-tribe-slam-sound-hip-hop-history/</link><description>If you’ve listened to any rap or pop music made in the 21st century, you’ve heard John Lehmkuhl’s most famous creation, a thwacking metallic percussion sample named “Tribe.”</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>United Airlines significantly improves basic economy fares with a key change</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/united-airlines-basic-economy-update/</link><description>Of all the major U.S. airlines, United Airlines’ basic economy fare is perhaps the most punitive. Travelers purchasing the cheapest basic economy fare...</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 00:24:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Swifties' Fundraiser for Families of UK Stabbing Victims Nears Half A Million</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/01/taylor-swift-fans-fundraiser-uk-stabbing-victims-families/</link><description>A fundraiser for the families of the 3 young girls who died at the Taylor Swift-themed dance party in Southport, England is picking up some major stea...</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 07:58:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Here’s the dividend-paying stock playbook for Fed rate cuts</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/heres-the-dividend-paying-stock-playbook-for-fed-rate-cuts-cf03ba84?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Bad news is bad news again. Time to consider defensive dividend payers</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 12:29:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sheet Pan Steak Fajitas</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/sheet-pan-steak-fajitas/</link><description>Sheet pan steak fajitas are beautiful and bursting with flavor. Easy to throw together on busy weeknights, they feature tender…</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 02:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In A Financial Pinch? 7 Small Savings Tips That Add Up To Big Savings</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/small-savings-tips-that-add-up-to-big-savings</link><description>Don’t dismiss the power of baby steps, especially when it comes to saving money. Small money moves can add up to big savings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 21:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Terraform Labs co-founder and crypto fugitive, Do Kwon, set for extradition to South Korea</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/02/terraform-labs-co-founder-and-crypto-fugitive-do-kwon-set-for-extradition-to-south-korea/</link><description>The Appellate Court of Montenegro ruled on Thursday that Terraform Labs co-founder, Do Kwon, should be returned to his home country, South Korea. The ruling confirmed an earlier decision in April from the High Court of Podgorica which rejected a request to extradite the crypto fugitive to the U.S. The extradition date for Kwon to […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 10:54:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bidding is open: Redeem Choice points for VIP college football experiences</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/redeem-choice-points-college-sports/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information. Attention, college football fans: Bidding is now open on the Choice P...</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 00:00:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kendall Jenner Says She's Cried Herself to Sleep Over Course of Modeling Career</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/01/kendall-jenner-remembers-loneliness-cried-herself-sleep-modeling/</link><description>Kendall Jenner's getting real about loneliness ... saying months of traveling around modeling left her in a dark place -- filled with tears just befor...</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 07:58:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Echoes of the dot-com bubble haunt U.S. stocks in 2024. Why investors shouldn’t worry too much about it.</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/echoes-of-the-dot-com-bubble-haunt-u-s-stocks-in-2024-why-investors-shouldnt-worry-too-much-about-it-24b9454b?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Jeremy Grantham’s GMO said it doesn’t make sense to draw a parallel between today’s so-called Magnificent Seven and their equivalents during the boom-and-bust cycle in the late-1990s.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 12:16:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>One-Pan Lemon Chicken Orzo</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/lemon-chicken-orzo/</link><description>One-Pan Lemon Chicken Orzo is a comforting, well-rounded meal! Tender, juicy chicken pieces are joined with orzo pasta in a…</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A 7-Week Plan To Master Pull-Ups (&amp; Why This Move Is A+ For Healthy Aging)</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/how-to-do-your-first-pull-up-7-week-beginner-plan</link><description>Pull-ups are way more than just a flex—they can actively boost longevity and health span.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 13:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meta’s Threads crosses 200 million active users</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/02/metas-threads-cross-200-million-active-users/</link><description>A day after Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg talked about his newest social media experiment Threads reaching “almost” 200 million users on the company’s Q2 2024 earnings call, the platform has touched the milestone. Instagram head Adam Mosseri confirmed that the Twitter rival has reached 200M active users in a post on Threads. Meta has taken […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 10:40:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>You can book The New York Edition for less than 50,000 points right now</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/new-york-edition-august-points-deal/</link><description>New York City hotels are notoriously expensive, but that doesn’t mean there aren’t good deals out there if you’re willing to be flexible. For a little...</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 23:30:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chris Paul Sells California Mansion For Over $15 Million, Saltwater Pool &amp; Home Theater!</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/01/chris-paul-california-mansion-house-sold/</link><description>Chris Paul unloaded his California mansion -- a massive estate with awesome amenities including a saltwater pool and home theater -- for over $15 mill...</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 07:58:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I retired comfortably on $100,000, so it’s not a myth – if you can handle the risk</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/i-retired-comfortably-on-100-000-so-its-not-a-myth-if-you-can-handle-the-risk-728897ea?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>A reader challenges the argument that you can’t have a happy retirement with a small nest egg</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 12:07:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Meal Plan #12</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/weekly-meal-plan-12/</link><description>This weekly meal plan has so many of my favorite recipes in it! It has meals that even my kiddos…</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Creatine Supplements Bad For Your Kidneys? What's Fact vs. Fiction</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/are-creatine-supplements-bad-for-your-kidneys</link><description>Here's what you should know.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 12:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Connect with Google Cloud, Aerospace, Qualcomm and more at Disrupt 2024</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/01/connect-with-google-cloud-aerospace-qualcomm-and-more-at-disrupt-2024/</link><description>TechCrunch Disrupt 2024 will be in San Francisco on October 28–30, and we’re already excited! Disrupt brings innovation for every stage of your startup journey, and we could not bring you this world-class event without our world-class partners. Take advantage of the opportunity to leverage the expertise and resources of some of tech’s leading companies. Their participation […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Virgin Hotels London-Shoreditch is now open</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/virgin-hotels-london-shoreditch/</link><description>In London, it’s out with the old and in with the new. The Mondrian Shoreditch, one of TPG’s best new hotels of 2021, has officially been reflagged as ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 23:00:58 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>