<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 12:09:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Deshaun Watson Grabs Model GF Jilly Anais' Butt On Baecation In Spain</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/02/deshaun-watson-jilly-anais-baecation-grab-butt-spain-cleveland-browns-nfl/</link><description>Deshaun Watson is having some fun in the sun with his model girlfriend Jilly Anais at one of the most picturesque places in the world ... before the s...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 09:55:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Koss surges as meme-stock chatter again swirls around the headphone maker</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/koss-surges-as-meme-stock-chatter-again-swirls-around-the-headphone-maker-3179a47e?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Shares of Koss Corp. were surging 18.4% in premarket trades Wednesday as the headphone maker resumed its rally amid a resurgence of interest in meme s...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Philly Cheesesteak Foil Packs</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/philly-cheesesteak-foil-packs/</link><description>Try these delicious Philly Cheesesteak Foil Packs, a fun new way to enjoy the flavors of the classic Philly Cheesesteak.…</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tomorrow’s Cure: How a lifetime of exposures impact health – exposome explained</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/tomorrows-cure-how-a-lifetime-of-exposures-impact-health-exposome-explained/</link><description>There is a study of the fascinating interplay between the cumulative effects of external exposures on a person's body and genes. It is called exposomi...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 13:21:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Everything You Need to Know About USB Ports and Speeds (2024)</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/usb-ports-speeds-generations-and-thunderbolt-explained/</link><description>USB-C was supposed to make everything simple. Instead, it’s more complicated than ever. So let's clear up the confusion.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fitness center or free breakfast? Here are the guaranteed offerings at midpriced Marriott brands</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/fitness-center-or-free-breakfast-here-are-the-guaranteed-offerings-at-midpriced-marriott-brands/</link><description>Sometimes, finding the right hotel for your needs and price point can feel as difficult as finding a needle in a haystack. If you are traveling with k...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:30:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bronny James Says No. 9 Jersey Is Tribute To Juice WRLD</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/02/bronny-james-says-no-9-jersey-number-tribute-juice-wrld/</link><description>Bronny James is opening up on his decision to rock No. 9 in the NBA ... confirming he chose it to honor late musician Juice WRLD. LeBron's eldest son ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 09:55:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>U.S. trade deficit jumps in May to highest level in 19 months</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/u-s-trade-deficit-jumps-in-may-to-highest-level-in-19-months-44fef50b?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Gap widens 0.8% to $75.1 billion</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:37:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tri Tip Marinade</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/tri-tip-marinade/</link><description>This tasty tri tip marinade is the best way to infuse your tri-tip steak with delicious flavor and make it…</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: Helping kids with anxiety through exposure therapy</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-helping-kids-with-anxiety-through-exposure-therapy/</link><description>It's normal for kids to feel anxious sometimes. When these feelings get too big and help is needed, experts often suggest cognitive behavioral therapy...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 16:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Get a Real ID License Before the Deadline</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-get-a-real-id-license-before-the-may-2025-deadline/</link><description>A new type of driver’s license will be required to board flights in the United States next year. Here’s how to update your license to the new Real ID ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 13:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New United app feature shows weather impacts with live radar and flight paths</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/united-app-feature-live-weather-delays/</link><description>United Airlines introduced a new tool in the United app Wednesday that can help travelers stay on top of weather delays during July Fourth — the holid...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:00:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Hawk Tuah' Girl Hailey Welch's Management Team Revealed</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/02/hawk-tuah-girl-hailey-welch-management-team-revealed/</link><description>Hailey Welch, who is best known for being the viral "Hawk Tuah" girl, is ready to extend her 15 minutes of fame ... as she's officially landed represe...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 09:55:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jobless claims — aka layoffs — rise to 238,000 and stay near one-year high</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/jobless-claims-rise-to-238-000-and-stay-near-one-year-high-c287346f?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Three states, New York, New Jersey and California, accounted for most of the increase</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:36:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Raspberry Fluff Salad</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/raspberry-fluff-salad/</link><description>Fresh and fruity Raspberry Fluff Salad is a sweet and creamy side or dessert with a mix of raspberries, vanilla…</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Drugs that kill “zombie” cells may benefit some older women, but not all, Mayo Clinic study finds</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/drugs-that-kill-zombie-cells-may-benefit-some-older-women-but-not-all-mayo-clinic-study-finds/</link><description>ROCHESTER, Minn. — Drugs that selectively kill senescent cells may benefit otherwise healthy older women but are not a "one-size-fits-all" remedy, May...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 13:26:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI Is Rewriting Meme History</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/ai-is-rewriting-meme-history/</link><description>TikTok’s latest trend involves videos of people traveling back in time to interrupt the viral memes of yore. The results are uncanny.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alaska Airlines ups Mexico service with new routes to La Paz and Monterrey</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/alaska-airlines-la-paz-monterrey-mexico-routes/</link><description>Alaska Airlines is bolstering its footprint in Mexico with two new nonstop flights launching for the winter season. In November, the Seattle-based car...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 23:30:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Murray the Magician Resigns From Academy of Magical Arts, Exposed Tricks</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/02/murray-the-magician-resigning-from-academy-of-magical-arts/</link><description>Murray The Magician is pulling a disappearing act on the Academy of Magical Arts -- this after having his fill of what he deems as the org's inconsist...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 09:55:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Trump trade war won’t be good for the stock market, warns Dr. Doom</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/a-trump-trade-war-wont-be-good-for-the-stock-market-warns-dr-doom-15e538ea?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Nouriel Roubini, the economist who is nicknamed “Dr. Doom” for his often-gloomy predictions, says a Trump win could spark a stock-damaging trade war.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Strawberry Cream Cheese Pie</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/strawberry-cream-cheese-pie/</link><description>This strawberry cream cheese pie has a smooth, creamy filling topped with sweet strawberries and held together by a crumbly…</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Celebrate safely: Use caution when using fireworks and sparklers</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/celebrate-safely-use-caution-when-using-fireworks-and-sparklers/</link><description>Americans everywhere will be celebrating Independence Day on July 4, and that often means fireworks and sparklers are involved. While exciting, firewo...</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Inside a16z’s Boot Camp for Crypto Startups</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/inside-a16zs-boot-camp-for-crypto-startups/</link><description>Andreessen Horowitz is betting the house on crypto. (Yes, really.) This spring, the VC firm schooled a new batch of founders that it hopes can prove t...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 12:36:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rosewood just opened a hotel in a 15th-century castle in Austria</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/rosewood-schloss-fuschl-austria/</link><description>Luxury hotel brand Rosewood has a picture-perfect new property outside of Salzburg, Austria, one of the best places to travel in July 2024. Called Ros...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 23:00:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Florida Woman Met With Instant Karma After Swinging At YouTuber, On Camera</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/02/florida-woman-swings-youtuber-fight-parking-lot-knocked-down/</link><description>A Florida woman got a taste of instant karma when she punched a YouTuber and ended up flat on the ground herself -- and the whole thing's on camera! A...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 09:55:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ADP says 150,000 private-sector jobs created in June, smallest gain in five months</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/adp-says-150-000-private-sector-job-screated-in-june-smallest-gain-in-five-months-f41a1a0c?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>U.S. businesses add a modest 150,000 new jobs in June, paycheck company ADP said, to mark the smallest increase in five months, possibly another sign ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:29:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sherbet Punch</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/sherbet-punch/</link><description>This bright sherbet punch is perfect for serving on any occasion! It has just the right balance of sweetness, zest,…</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: Tips from a gynecological surgeon on recovery from surgery</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-tips-from-a-gynecological-surgeon-on-recovery-from-surgery/</link><description>Every year, about 4 million gynecologic surgeries are performed in the U.S. Among these, hysterectomies are the most common, with over half a million ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDCX acquires BitOasis in international expansion push</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/03/coindcx-acquires-bitoasis-in-international-expansion-push/</link><description>CoinDCX, India’s leading cryptocurrency exchange, is expanding internationally through the acquisition of BitOasis, a digital asset platform in the Mi...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 12:31:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hurricane season is here: TPG’s storm guide for travelers</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/hurricane-season-travel-protection/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information. We’re only one month into hurricane season, and the Caribbean saw its...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 22:30:35 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>