<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 07:13:09 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Michael Rubin Confirms He Banned 'Not Like Us' at White Party For Drake's Sake</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/14/michael-rubin-banned-not-like-us-drake/</link><description>Michael Rubin's defending his decision to 86 Kendrick Lamar‘s megahit, “Not Like Us” during his annual All-White Party ... and admits it was all to pu...</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 07:56:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Three different factors could trigger the third wave of a stock market pullback, says strategist</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/three-different-factors-could-trigger-the-third-wave-of-a-stock-market-pullback-says-strategist-1225820b?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Dhaval Joshi, chief strategist of BCA Research’s Counterpoint service, says an analysis of the “price complexity” shows that the yen carry trade and the AI bubble are one and the same trade, and that any of three factors could torpedo it.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 12:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zucchini Roll-Ups</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/zucchini-roll-ups/</link><description>Zucchini Roll-Ups are a delicious, unique meal that the whole family will enjoy. Thin slices of zucchini are rolled around…</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Start A Successful Health Coaching Business (Yes, You Can!)</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/4-tips-to-starting-successful-health-coaching-business</link><description>Start your journey helping people make life-changing health shifts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 11:27:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Google Has Unleashed Its Legal Fury on Hackers and Scammers</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/google-affirmative-litigation-hacker-scammer-lawsuits/</link><description>The tech giant says its “affirmative litigation” deters and raises awareness of bad behavior. But skeptics wonder whether these suits are too small a gesture.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Goodbye sweet spot: Qatar Airways Privilege Club devalues American Airlines and Alaska Airlines award flights</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/qatar-airways-avios-american-alaska-devaluation/</link><description>Qatar Airways has devalued some Avios sweet spots for award flights on partner airlines including American Airlines and Alaska Airlines, as first repo...</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 01:22:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Poltergeist' House Listed for Sale, 1st Time in 45 Years</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/14/poltergeist-house-for-sale/</link><description>A piece of horror movie history could be yours ... as the famed haunted house from "Poltergeist" has officially hit the market. The home -- which serv...</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 07:56:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I have my RMD all figured out, except for one thing: Which investments should I take it from?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/i-have-my-rmd-all-figured-out-except-for-one-thing-which-investments-should-i-take-it-from-9e35bcf5?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>If you don’t specify exactly what you want to do, your bank may pull your required minimum distribution equally from all your holdings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 12:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Baking Soda vs Baking Powder (Baking Tips)</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/baking-soda-vs-baking-powder-baking-tips/</link><description>Baking soda vs baking powder….what is the difference? I’m here to teach you the basics of each so that you…</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>No Lie, This Supplement Is Like The Fountain Of Youth For Your Skin</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/how-each-mbg-best-skin-ingredient-benefits-aging-skin</link><description>Do you do your skin care routine morning and night? Great. But there's more you can do. Here's how to approach skin aging from the inside out.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 11:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Is the Most Detailed Map of Human Brain Connections Ever Made</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/this-is-the-most-detailed-map-of-brain-connections-ever-made-google-harvard/</link><description>In a world first, Harvard biologists worked with Google to diagram a cubic millimeter of human cerebral cortex at the subcellular level, paving the way for the next generation of brain science.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Remade and remodeled: First look at Lufthansa’s shiny new lounge at Newark Liberty</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/lufthansa-lounge-newark/</link><description>It’s a whole new concept in lounges from German carrier Lufthansa, and it just made its official debut at Newark Liberty International Airport (EWR). ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 00:28:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jonathan Owens Met With 'USA' Chants After Watching Simone Biles At Olympics</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/14/jonathan-owens-usa-chants-simone-biles-olympics/</link><description>Jonathan Owens' Chicago Bears teammates didn't have an issue with him missing part of training camp to watch his wife, Simone Biles, dominate at the O...</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 07:56:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>6 ways to build a successful retirement</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/6-ways-to-build-a-successful-retirement-3ec635b1?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>What people in their 50s, 60s and 70s should know about navigating life after work</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 12:25:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seedy Tahini Snack Bites (Nut-Free!)</title><link>https://minimalistbaker.com/seedy-tahini-snack-bites/</link><description>Nut-free friends, this one’s for you! We’re no strangers to energy bites (and cake bites… and cookie bites…), but a nut-free version of these snackabl...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In A Financial Pinch? 7 Small Savings Tips That Add Up To Big Savings</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/small-savings-tips-that-add-up-to-big-savings</link><description>Don’t dismiss the power of baby steps, especially when it comes to saving money. Small money moves can add up to big savings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 21:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Code Breaker Is Using AI to Decode the Heart’s Secret Rhythms</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/ai-doctor-roeland-decorte-future-industries/</link><description>Inspired by his expertise in breaking ancient codes, Roeland Decorte built a smartphone app that continuously listens for signs of disease hidden in our pulse.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spirit’s fare changes are live: Here’s how much you’ll pay</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/spirit-airlines-new-fares/</link><description>Two days earlier than planned, Spirit Airlines has rolled out sweeping changes to its booking channels. It’s offering four neat-and-tidy fare options,...</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 22:30:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Disney Wants Wrongful Death Suit Tossed, Claims Disney+ Loophole</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/14/disney-wrongful-death-streaming-loophole/</link><description>Disney's playing a stunning wild card in its face-off against a man suing over the death of his wife ... claiming the guy's Disney+ subscription preve...</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 07:56:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SEC approves fund that levers up MicroStrategy, which bets on bitcoin</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/sec-approves-fund-that-levers-up-microstrategy-which-bets-on-bitcoin-0b3eb34a?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Investors will now have the opportunity to buy a fund leveraged to a company that is leveraged to an asset that often is bought on leverage.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 11:58:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chocolate Pudding Cookies</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/pudding-cookies/</link><description>Chocolate Pudding Cookies are soft, chewy, and irresistibly delicious! They are quick and easy to bake and will be a…</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A 7-Week Plan To Master Pull-Ups (&amp; Why This Move Is A+ For Healthy Aging)</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/how-to-do-your-first-pull-up-7-week-beginner-plan</link><description>Pull-ups are way more than just a flex—they can actively boost longevity and health span.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 13:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Binance restarts services in India after seven-month regulatory halt</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/15/binance-restarts-services-in-india-after-seven-month-regulatory-halt/</link><description>Binance, the world’s largest cryptocurrency exchange, has resumed operations for users in India after a seven-month hiatus imposed by a local authority for operating “illegally” in the country. The exchange said Thursday it has registered as a reporting entity with India’s Financial Intelligence Unit (FIU), a government agency tasked with scrutinizing financial transactions. India blocked […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 09:12:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The top 11 credit cards with annual travel statement credits</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/credit-cards-best-annual-travel-statement-credits/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. Travel rewards credit cards entice new cardholders with fl...</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 22:00:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lil Pump Scraps Kamala Harris Diss in Favor of Donald Trump Rally Track</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/14/lil-pump-donald-trump-rally-song/</link><description>Lil Pump is scrapping his previously promised diss track aimed at Kamala Harris -- in exchange for an ode to Donald Trump!!! His reasoning? Spewing ha...</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 07:56:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘He called me a liar’: I will inherit a $650,000 house from my grandparents, but my husband says I’ll never have any money when I’m older. Is he right?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/he-called-me-a-liar-i-will-inherit-a-650-000-house-from-my-grandparents-but-my-husband-says-ill-never-have-any-money-when-im-older-is-he-right-7bf1a37e?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>“I plan to buy a second home as an investment property.”</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 11:29:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Raspberry Muffins</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/raspberry-muffins/</link><description>These raspberry muffins are moist and delicious, filled with plump fresh raspberries and topped with a sweet, crunchy streusel topping!…</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 02:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Creatine Supplements Bad For Your Kidneys? What's Fact vs. Fiction</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/are-creatine-supplements-bad-for-your-kidneys</link><description>Here's what you should know.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 12:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Video of Eric Schmidt blaming remote work for Google’s woes mysteriously vanishes</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/14/video-of-eric-schmidt-blaming-remote-work-for-googles-woes-mysteriously-vanishes/</link><description>Former Google CEO Eric Schmidt, who has since moved on to greener and perhaps more dangerous pastures, told an audience of Stanford students recently that “Google decided that work-life balance and going home early and working from home was more important than winning.” Evidently this hot take was not for wider consumption, as Stanford — […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 01:14:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>European airline launches new ‘All You Can Fly’ pass — but it comes with several catches</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/wizz-air-all-you-can-fly-pass-worth-it/</link><description>European budget airline Wizz Air recently launched the All You Can Fly pass, a subscription that offers passengers unlimited flights for an annual fee...</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 21:30:39 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>