<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 06:57:01 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Patrick Mahomes Says Taylor Swift is Behind Travis Kelce's New Bushy Hairdo</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/14/patrick-mahomes-taylor-swift-travis-kelce-long-hair-beard/</link><description>Taylor Swift is exerting her influence over her boyfriend Travis Kelce, especially when it comes to his appearance ... so says Patrick Mahomes. Mahome...</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 14:45:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘He does not manage his own bills’: My brother is about to take Social Security. Should we put his inheritance from our father’s estate into an annuity?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/he-does-not-manage-his-own-bills-my-brother-is-about-to-take-social-security-should-we-put-his-inheritance-from-our-fathers-estate-into-an-annuity-624944ae?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>“My other brother, who understands finances much better than me, says no one likes annuities.”</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 19:38:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zucchini Roll-Ups</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/zucchini-roll-ups/</link><description>Zucchini Roll-Ups are a delicious, unique meal that the whole family will enjoy. Thin slices of zucchini are rolled around…</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Start A Successful Health Coaching Business (Yes, You Can!)</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/4-tips-to-starting-successful-health-coaching-business</link><description>Start your journey helping people make life-changing health shifts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 11:27:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Palo Alto Networks CEO apologizes for happy hour display featuring women with lampshades on their heads</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/14/palo-alto-networks-ceo-apologies-for-happy-hour-display-featuring-women-with-lampshades-on-their-heads/</link><description>Cybersecurity giant Palo Alto Networks is getting a lot of grief for a recent trade show event in which two women posed with lampshades on their heads. The debacle — which unflatteringly recalls the CES booth babes of the early ’90s and 2000s — reportedly happened at a happy hour hosted by CyberRisk Collaborative and […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 19:37:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Get into 42 theme parks for less than $200 with this new season pass</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/cedar-fair-all-park-passport/</link><description>Just like gas and groceries, theme parks keep getting more expensive. We at TPG are always on the lookout for ways to help you save money when you vis...</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 19:45:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ángel Salazar Filming Indie 'Scarface' Spin-Off Before Death</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/14/scarface-angel-salazar-spin-off/</link><description>Ángel Salazar -- famous for playing Al Pacino's trusted sidekick "Chi Chi" in "Scarface" -- was filming an indie spin-off of the iconic gangster movie...</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 14:45:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Some hedge funds thought AI would help them beat the market. Then things got real.</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/some-hedge-funds-thought-ai-would-help-them-beat-the-market-then-things-got-real-e3aae97f?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>The Eurekahedge AI Hedge Fund Index has lagged the S&amp;P 500, proving that the machines aren’t learning from their investing mistakes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 19:36:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Baking Soda vs Baking Powder (Baking Tips)</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/baking-soda-vs-baking-powder-baking-tips/</link><description>Baking soda vs baking powder….what is the difference? I’m here to teach you the basics of each so that you…</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>No Lie, This Supplement Is Like The Fountain Of Youth For Your Skin</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/how-each-mbg-best-skin-ingredient-benefits-aging-skin</link><description>Do you do your skin care routine morning and night? Great. But there's more you can do. Here's how to approach skin aging from the inside out.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 11:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Week in AI: AI isn’t world-ending — but it’s still plenty harmful</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/14/this-week-in-ai-ai-isnt-world-ending-but-its-still-plenty-harmful/</link><description>Hiya, folks, welcome to TechCrunch’s regular AI newsletter. This week in AI, a new study shows that generative AI really isn’t all that harmful — at least not in the apocalyptic sense. In a paper submitted to the Association for Computational Linguistics’ annual conference, researchers from the University of Bath and University of Darmstadt argue […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 19:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Does adding an authorized user affect my credit score?</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/authorized-user-credit-score/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. Adding an authorized user to your credit card account can ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 19:00:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Simone Biles' Biological Mother Wants To Reconcile, 'Would Like To Make Amends'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/14/simone-biles-birth-mom-shanon-forgiveness/</link><description>Simone Biles' biological mother is ready to meet the Olympic hero face-to-face ... saying after decades of being out of her life, she wants to make th...</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 14:45:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘She’s now down to her last few dollars’: My friend quit her job, blew her inheritance and will take vacations using credit cards. Will she ever see sense?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/shes-now-down-to-her-last-few-dollars-my-friend-quit-her-job-blew-her-inheritance-and-will-take-vacations-using-credit-cards-will-she-ever-see-sense-f94bd271?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>“She has over $70,000 in her retirement fund, but says that’s for emergencies.”</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 19:35:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seedy Tahini Snack Bites (Nut-Free!)</title><link>https://minimalistbaker.com/seedy-tahini-snack-bites/</link><description>Nut-free friends, this one’s for you! We’re no strangers to energy bites (and cake bites… and cookie bites…), but a nut-free version of these snackabl...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In A Financial Pinch? 7 Small Savings Tips That Add Up To Big Savings</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/small-savings-tips-that-add-up-to-big-savings</link><description>Don’t dismiss the power of baby steps, especially when it comes to saving money. Small money moves can add up to big savings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 21:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Camera app Halide’s latest update adds an option for ‘zero-AI’ image processing</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/14/camera-app-halides-latest-update-adds-an-option-for-zero-ai-image-processing/</link><description>Popular iOS pro photography app Halide launched its new version today with a new feature called Process Zero, which does not use AI in image processing. Lux Optics, the company behind the Halide app, believes that this option can be a creative tool for photographers to take different kinds of snaps. The company previously allowed […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 24 best hotels in New York City</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/best-hotels-in-nyc/</link><description>Travelers headed to New York City are spoiled for choice when it comes to booking a hotel stay. After all, the city is home to an almost unfathomable ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 18:30:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Christopher Dorner's Gun Recovered During Arrest of Armed Robbery Suspects</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/13/christopher-dorner-gun-found/</link><description>A firearm registered to notorious cop killer Christopher Dorner was recovered during the arrest of two men suspected in the armed robbery of a $1 mill...</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 14:45:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘I only get Social Security’: I’m 72 with two adult children and live in a home for low-income seniors. Do I really need a will?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/everything-i-own-is-probably-worth-500-i-am-72-with-advanced-kidney-disease-and-live-in-a-home-for-low-income-seniors-do-i-need-to-make-a-will-dfc58e81?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>“Everything I own is probably only worth $500.”</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 19:25:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chocolate Pudding Cookies</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/pudding-cookies/</link><description>Chocolate Pudding Cookies are soft, chewy, and irresistibly delicious! They are quick and easy to bake and will be a…</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A 7-Week Plan To Master Pull-Ups (&amp; Why This Move Is A+ For Healthy Aging)</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/how-to-do-your-first-pull-up-7-week-beginner-plan</link><description>Pull-ups are way more than just a flex—they can actively boost longevity and health span.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 13:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Definity raises $4.5M as it looks to transform data application observability</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/14/definity-raises-4-5m-as-it-looks-to-transform-data-application-observability/</link><description>Definity focuses on the data transformation plane on top of a data lake or warehouse, not the data ingestion part of the pipeline. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 18:59:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>You can now finally earn miles, Loyalty Points from paid American Airlines upgrades</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/american-airlines-upgrades-earn-miles-loyalty-points/</link><description>The day is finally here. At long last, you can now earn American Airlines AAdvantage miles and Loyalty Points from upgrades purchased on American Airl...</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 18:00:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ex-MMA Fighter Lumumba Sayers Arrested, Allegedly Killed Man To Avenge Son's Death</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/14/lumumba-sayers-murder/</link><description>Former mixed martial artist Lumumba Sayers -- who once fought ex-UFC star Derek Brunson inside a cage -- was arrested for murder over the weekend ... ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 14:45:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>6 ways to build a successful retirement</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/6-ways-to-build-a-successful-retirement-3ec635b1?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>What people in their 50s, 60s and 70s should know about navigating life after work</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 18:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Raspberry Muffins</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/raspberry-muffins/</link><description>These raspberry muffins are moist and delicious, filled with plump fresh raspberries and topped with a sweet, crunchy streusel topping!…</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 02:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Creatine Supplements Bad For Your Kidneys? What's Fact vs. Fiction</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/are-creatine-supplements-bad-for-your-kidneys</link><description>Here's what you should know.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 12:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Databricks reportedly paid $2 billion in Tabular acquisition</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/14/databricks-reportedly-paid-2-billion-in-tabular-acquisition/</link><description>Analytics and AI giant Databricks reportedly paid nearly $2 billion when it acquired Tabular in June, a startup that was only doing $1 million in annual recurring revenue, according to Bloomberg. That’s a pretty outrageous exit multiple, and it was purportedly fueled by a battle between Databricks and Snowflake. Tabular had over $30 million in […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 18:44:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Delta debuts free Wi-Fi on long-haul flights with detailed rollout schedule</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/delta-air-lines-free-wifi-on-long-haul-flights/</link><description>Staying connected when flying on long-haul routes with Delta Air Lines is about to become much simpler. The Atlanta-based carrier announced this week ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 17:30:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>