<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 06:49:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Homeless Man Reportedly Shot &amp; Killed by Police Outside Republican National Convention</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/16/homeless-man-shot-killed-police-milwaukee-outside-republican-national-convention/</link><description>1:54 PM PT -- Sources with direct knowledge tell TMZ ... the shooting Tuesday was completely unrelated to the RNC -- and the reason Secret Service was...</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 08:24:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why a ‘do-nothing’ Congress is a winning vote for your stock portfolio</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/why-a-do-nothing-congress-is-a-winning-vote-for-your-stock-portfolio-ec12d985?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>The U.S. stock market on average has done better when Congress is not in session.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 13:20:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Boursin Pork Chops</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/boursin-pork-chops/</link><description>Boursin Pork Chops are savory, tender, and covered in a delicious cheesy cream sauce. This one-pan recipe is the perfect easy…</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic scientists define new type of memory loss in older adults</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-scientists-define-new-type-of-memory-loss-in-older-adults/</link><description>ROCHESTER, Minn. — Researchers at Mayo Clinic have established new criteria for a memory-loss syndrome in older adults that specifically impacts the b...</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 02:26:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RealPage Says Rental Pricing Tech Is Misunderstood, but Landlords Aren’t So Sure</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/realpage-says-rental-pricing-tech-is-misunderstood-but-landlords-arent-so-sure/</link><description>The software company has pushed back hard against claims that its algorithms helped make rent in the US too damn high. Property owners and managers ar...</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 13:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Avoid fees: How to change and cancel airline award tickets</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/award-ticket-change-cancellation-fees/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with the latest information. Compensation can be difficult when airlines cancel flights due...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 23:30:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MMA's Rener Gracie Demonstrates Safer 'SafeWrap' Restraining Method on TMZ Staffer</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/16/mma-rener-gracie-demonstrate-safer-safewrap-restraining-method-tmz-staffer/</link><description>Rener Gracie -- whose family is credited with creating Brazilian jiu-jitsu -- is teaching cops a new restraint that he says is safer than a chokehold,...</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 08:24:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Global stock investor Jim Rogers: ‘I’m waiting for something to go wrong.’</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/global-stock-investor-jim-rogers-im-waiting-for-something-to-go-wrong-8e3e44a4?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>‘Probably by the end of this year or next year, the bear market will have resumed in the U.S.,’ Quantum Fund co-founder says.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 13:11:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sheet Pan Ratatouille with Crispy Baked Tofu</title><link>https://minimalistbaker.com/sheet-pan-ratatouille-with-crispy-baked-tofu/</link><description>What could be better than the saucy, savory goodness of classic ratatouille!? Answer: SHEET PAN ratatouille! Say “au revoir” to stovetop babysitting, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic ranked No. 1 hospital in Florida by U.S. News &amp; World Report, makes leap in national rankings</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-ranked-no-1-hospital-in-florida-by-u-s-news-world-report-makes-leap-in-national-rankings/</link><description>JACKSONVILLE, Fla. — Mayo Clinic is again ranked the No. 1 hospital in Florida and the Jacksonville metro area in U.S. News &amp; World Report's "Best Hos...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 06:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kandji raises another $100M for Apple device management as valuation rises to $850M</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/17/kandji-raises-another-100m-for-apple-device-management-as-valuation-rises-to-850m/</link><description>At a time when many startups have struggled to raise money and keep their heads above water, Kandji, an Apple device management platform, has been an ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deal alert: Fly nonstop business class to Europe from various US cities from $1,779</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/deals/europe-business-class-nonstop-deals/</link><description>As TPG readers already know, the 2024 Summer Olympics aren’t generating a massive travel boom for Paris. Would-be visitors to Europe seem to be trying...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 23:00:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Lady of Rage Stars as Miss Cleo in Late Psychic Biopic</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/16/lady-of-rage-miss-cleo-rise-fall-psychic-biopic/</link><description>Veteran Death Row Records rapper The Lady of Rage has a new movie on the horizon, but any mind-reader worth their mettle already knows that ... as she...</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 08:24:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Temperature-controlled warehouse REIT Lineage sets terms for the biggest IPO of 2024</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/temperature-controlled-warehouse-reit-lineage-sets-terms-for-the-biggest-ipo-of-2024-a69094cd?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Company to raise up to $3.85 billion at a valuation of up to $19.2 billion</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 13:11:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Red Robin Campfire Sauce</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/red-robin-campfire-sauce/</link><description>Red Robin campfire sauce is the best pairing for your burgers, fries, and more. Whip it up in minutes with…</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic again earns top positions in U.S. News rankings, continues to transform healthcare for people everywhere</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-again-earns-top-positions-in-u-s-news-rankings-continues-to-transform-healthcare-for-people-everywhere/</link><description>ROCHESTER, Minn. — Mayo Clinic has once again been named a best hospital in the United States in U.S. News &amp; World Report's 2024-2025 "Best Hospitals"...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 06:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Real Problem With TikTok’s ‘Fruity’ Boy Trend</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/fruity-boys-prove-how-dating-apps-have-made-archetypes-of-us-all/</link><description>On TikTok and X, the “fruity” boyfriend has become a hot topic. But the trend exposes the real issues that arise when dating apps reduce everyone to a...</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple AirPods on sale at Amazon and Walmart</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/deals/apple-airpod-pro-amazon-sale/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. We’re currently seeing some great prices on Apple AirPods ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:30:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jonathan Majors Says He's Going to Propose to Meagan Good</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/16/jonathan-majors-meagan-good-propose-engagement-relationship/</link><description>Jonathan Majors is so smitten with Meagan Good, he’s openly saying he's ready to lock it down and put a ring on it! We caught up with the actor Tuesda...</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 08:24:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Leading Fed official says he still wants more data before supporting rate cut</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/leading-fed-official-says-he-still-wants-more-data-before-supporting-rate-cut-a86d2cac?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>A leading Federal Reserve official says he still needs a little more convincing before endorsing an interest-rate cut, a comment that all but rules ou...</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 13:11:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sushi Bowl</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/sushi-bowl/</link><description>This sushi bowl is a deconstructed California sushi roll loaded with irresistible flavor and all of the best sushi ingredients.…</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: Treatment and research of glioblastoma</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-treatment-and-research-of-glioblastoma/</link><description>Editor's note: Glioblastoma Awareness Day is July 17 Considered the most aggressive type of brain cancer, glioblastoma grows rapidly, destroying healt...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Matera raises $100M from Warburg Pincus to help the US catch up to Brazil in instant payments</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/17/matera-raises-100m-from-warburn-pincus-to-help-the-u-s-catch-up-to-brazil-in-instant-payments/</link><description>To say that Pix, the instant payment system created by the Central Bank of Brazil, has been a resounding success is an understatement. With Pix, money...</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amazon Prime Day deal: One of our favorite portable chargers is on sale for $16</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/deals/anker-portable-charger/</link><description>Editor’s note: Pricing and availability are accurate as of July 16. A portable charger is a must if you are a frequent traveler or always on the go. O...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:00:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Savannah Chrisley Set to Blast Justice Dept. at RNC After Parents' Conviction</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/16/savannah-chrisley-blasting-justice-dept-rnc-speech-after-parents-conviction/</link><description>Savannah Chrisley is all set to speak at the Republican National Convention Tuesday -- now, we have a sense of what she's gonna say ... her speech wil...</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 08:24:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>My adviser told me to take Social Security early — and save $2.5 million for our kids. But shouldn’t I delay as long as I can?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/my-adviser-told-me-to-take-social-security-early-and-save-2-5-million-for-our-kids-but-shouldnt-i-delay-as-long-as-i-can-41c2c80e?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>“Our kids and grandkids won’t get our Social Security if we pass away at a younger age.”</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 13:09:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Texas Twinkies</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/texas-twinkies/</link><description>Texas Twinkies are a major upgrade to your classic jalapeño poppers! They’re jalapeños filled with cream cheese, brisket, and shredded…</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A student’s approach in biomedical research aims to give others a voice</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/a-students-approach-in-biomedical-research-aims-to-give-others-a-voice/</link><description>Growing up as the child of a voice instructor, Emily Hardy developed a lifelong interest in singing. But the third-year student at Mayo Clinic Alix Sc...</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 17:10:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Use an eSIM for International Travel</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-use-buy-esim-international-travel-trips/</link><description>Setting up the eSIM feature on your smartphone and buying a cheap data plan is a great way to stay connected while on vacation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FuelRods on big discount for Prime Day — buy now if you’re going to Disney</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/fuel-rods-discount/</link><description>Amazon Prime Day is here again, so it’s a great time to snag a discount on things that you’ll use throughout the year. Sure, it’s a good idea to purch...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:00:24 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>