<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 07:00:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Blake Lively, Justin Baldoni's Heated Convo On Set, Source Says Not Sign of Feud</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/12/blake-lively-justin-baldoni-feud/</link><description>Blake Lively’s rumored feud with her "It Ends With Us" costar/director Justin Baldoni is all the buzz on social media -- and a video of them on-set is...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 13:43:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Traders see big drop in interest rates into 2025, at risk of underestimating inflation</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/traders-see-big-drop-in-interest-rates-into-2025-at-risk-of-underestimating-inflation-32dcffaa?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Cutting interest rates as many times as fed -funds traders currently expect would imply that policymakers are confident they could do so without reigniting inflation all over again.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 18:38:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Baking Soda vs Baking Powder (Baking Tips)</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/baking-soda-vs-baking-powder-baking-tips/</link><description>Baking soda vs baking powder….what is the difference? I’m here to teach you the basics of each so that you…</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Start A Successful Health Coaching Business (Yes, You Can!)</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/4-tips-to-starting-successful-health-coaching-business</link><description>Start your journey helping people make life-changing health shifts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 11:27:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Payoneer scoops up Skuad, Robinhood’s strong Q2, and X is making progress on payments</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/13/payoneer-scoops-up-skuad-robinhoods-strong-q2-and-x-is-making-progress-on-payments/</link><description>Welcome to TechCrunch Fintech! This week, we’re looking at Payoneer’s $61 million acquisition of Skuad, Robinhood and Dave’s second-quarter results, X’s progress on its payments and more. To get a roundup of TechCrunch’s biggest and most important fintech stories delivered to your inbox every Tuesday at 8:00 a.m. PT, subscribe here. The big story Last […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 18:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A day in Grand Cayman: What to do while your cruise is in port</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/grand-cayman-cruise-port/</link><description>The Cayman Islands are in the western Caribbean Sea, about 275 miles south of Cuba, and are made up of three islands: Grand Cayman, Cayman Brac and Li...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 18:00:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Katy Perry and Orlando Bloom Plunge From Helicopter Into Ocean in Sardinia</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/12/katy-perry-orlando-bloom-helicopter-jump/</link><description>Orlando Bloom can't get enough of jumping outta helicopters ... and this time he brought his fiancée Katy Perry along for a daring ocean plunge. The s...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 13:43:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stage set for mild increase in consumer prices as Fed readies rate cuts</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/dont-expect-inflation-to-take-a-turn-for-the-worse-in-ppi-and-cpi-reports-f79ba180?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Wholesale inflation was fairly tame in July, and most economists think consumer prices will show a similarly mild increase. If so, that would keep the Federal Reserve on track to cut interest rates next month.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 18:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seedy Tahini Snack Bites (Nut-Free!)</title><link>https://minimalistbaker.com/seedy-tahini-snack-bites/</link><description>Nut-free friends, this one’s for you! We’re no strangers to energy bites (and cake bites… and cookie bites…), but a nut-free version of these snackabl...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>No Lie, This Supplement Is Like The Fountain Of Youth For Your Skin</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/how-each-mbg-best-skin-ingredient-benefits-aging-skin</link><description>Do you do your skin care routine morning and night? Great. But there's more you can do. Here's how to approach skin aging from the inside out.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 11:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Encord lands new cash to grow its data labeling tools for AI</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/13/encord-lands-new-cash-to-grow-its-data-labeling-tools-for-ai/</link><description>Labeling and annotation platforms might not get the attention flashy new generative AI models do. But they’re essential. The data on which many models train must be labeled, or the models wouldn’t be able to interpret that data during the training process. Annotation is a vast undertaking, requiring thousands to millions of annotations for the […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Marriott Bonvoy: Complete guide to the hotel loyalty program</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/award-travelers-guide-to-marriott-bonvoy/</link><description>Marriott Bonvoy is a popular hotel loyalty program, especially among U.S. travelers. The program has changed significantly over the years — including ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:00:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Donald Trump Tells Elon Musk Illegal Immigration Saved His Life</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/12/elon-musk-donald-trump-interview-immigration/</link><description>Elon Musk and Donald Trump are finally chopping it up ... the former president is doing a live interview on Elon's social media platform, X, after a r...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 13:43:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Harley-Davidson dealers say the company is sending them too many motorcycles</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/harley-davidson-dealers-say-the-company-is-sending-them-too-many-motorcycles-2d0e6c8e?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Some of the famed motorcycle maker’s dealers reportedly complained about being sent too many bikes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 18:21:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chocolate Pudding Cookies</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/pudding-cookies/</link><description>Chocolate Pudding Cookies are soft, chewy, and irresistibly delicious! They are quick and easy to bake and will be a…</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In A Financial Pinch? 7 Small Savings Tips That Add Up To Big Savings</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/small-savings-tips-that-add-up-to-big-savings</link><description>Don’t dismiss the power of baby steps, especially when it comes to saving money. Small money moves can add up to big savings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 21:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Singaporean investment app Syfe pulls in $27M to hasten growth in Asia Pacific</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/13/singapores-investment-app-syfe-accelerates-growth-across-asia-pacific-with-27m/</link><description>The Asia Pacific region has long been an important market for wealth management firms with the plethora of developing economies and a burgeoning retail investment market. But there’s still a huge market to capture: About 40% to 45% of personal financial assets in the region are held in cash and deposits as of 2023, according […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:59:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What credit score do you need to get the Southwest Premier Credit Card?</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/credit-score-needed-for-southwest-premier-credit-card/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. To really succeed at the points and miles game, you need t...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 16:30:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stacy In 'Fast Times at Ridgemont High' 'Memba Her?!</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/13/stacy-in-fast-times-at-ridgemont-high-memba-her/</link><description>L.A. native and American actress Jennifer Jason Leigh was just 20 years old when she scored her breakout role, Stacy -- the sophomore at Ridgemont Hig...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 13:43:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Starbucks’ stock rallies on speculation of a turnaround under its new CEO — the head of Chipotle Mexican Grill</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/starbucks-names-new-ceo-the-head-of-chipotle-mexican-grill-80e547f8?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Brian Niccol will lead the 39,000-store coffee-shop giant after six years at Chipotle.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 18:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Raspberry Muffins</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/raspberry-muffins/</link><description>These raspberry muffins are moist and delicious, filled with plump fresh raspberries and topped with a sweet, crunchy streusel topping!…</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 02:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A 7-Week Plan To Master Pull-Ups (&amp; Why This Move Is A+ For Healthy Aging)</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/how-to-do-your-first-pull-up-7-week-beginner-plan</link><description>Pull-ups are way more than just a flex—they can actively boost longevity and health span.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 13:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Twitch rolls out video stories to challenge Instagram</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/13/twitch-rolls-out-video-stories-to-challenge-instagram/</link><description>After launching photo and text stories last year, Twitch is now introducing video stories. Streamers can now film 60-second videos in the Twitch mobile app or upload a video from their camera roll. Twitch sees the new feature as a way for streamers to take viewers with them when they’re on the go and away […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:07:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Budget airline turf war: Breeze adds 10 routes to New Haven, Avelo’s biggest stronghold</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/breeze-airways-new-haven-routes/</link><description>There’s a budget airline turf war heating up in Connecticut between the two newest U.S. airlines. For months, low-cost airline Avelo Airlines has stak...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 16:01:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TMZ TV Hot Takes: Kamala Harris, Miley Cyrus, Nyjah Huston</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/13/tmz-tv-hot-takes-kamala-harris-dnc-miley-cyrus-nyjah-huston/</link><description>Kamala Harris is being cautious with Hollywood influence, Miley Cyrus is getting emotional and Nyjah Huston is getting a new Olympic medal ... all thi...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 13:43:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Will Social Security be your only lifeline in retirement? Some people say yes.</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/will-social-security-be-your-only-lifeline-in-retirement-some-people-say-yes-473af550?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Almost a third of Americans will rely solely on Social Security and not on any retirement savings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Creamy Tuscan Dip (Marry Me Dip)</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/creamy-tuscan-dip/</link><description>There’s a new appetizer in town, and this creamy Tuscan dip won everyone’s hearts! The combination of cheeses, garlic, spinach,…</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Creatine Supplements Bad For Your Kidneys? What's Fact vs. Fiction</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/are-creatine-supplements-bad-for-your-kidneys</link><description>Here's what you should know.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 12:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>California AI bill SB 1047 aims to prevent AI disasters, but Silicon Valley warns it will cause one</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/13/california-ai-bill-sb-1047-aims-to-prevent-ai-disasters-but-silicon-valley-warns-it-will-cause-one/</link><description>SB 1047 has drawn the ire of Silicon Valley players large and small, including venture capitalists, big tech trade groups, researchers and startup founders. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Delta adds new Boston, NYC routes just weeks after JetBlue drops them</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/delta-air-lines-boston-new-york-new-routes/</link><description>Delta Air Lines is quickly moving to capture some of the territory that JetBlue Airways just retreated from. The Atlanta-based carrier filed plans ove...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 15:30:25 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>