<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 06:40:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Eminem Disses Diddy, References Cassie Hotel Attack On New Album</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/12/eminem-diddy-diss-antichrist-album-cassie-hotel-assault-antichrist-feul-lyrics/</link><description>Eminem made sure to shame Diddy on his new album, "Death of Slim Shady (Coup de Grâce)" -- he brings up Diddy's sexual assault allegations on multiple...</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 01:43:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Did hackers get your cellphone number from AT&amp;T? Be extra vigilant about these money-related scams.</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/did-hackers-get-your-cellphone-number-from-at-t-be-extra-vigilant-about-this-money-related-scam-f1270493?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>As “a general rule,” people should be on guard about unfamiliar senders and suspicious texts, AT&amp;T said.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 00:36:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Meal Plan #11</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/weekly-meal-plan-11/</link><description>Weekly meal plan 11 is packed with so many delicious and vibrant flavors! With stir fry and tacos and a…</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: Keeping kids safe outside during summer play</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-keeping-kids-safe-outside-during-summer-play/</link><description>Summer vacation for kids is well underway. Finding activities to keep the kids busy and destinations to visit can be on many parents' list. There is o...</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 17:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meta removes special restrictions for Trump’s account ahead of 2024 elections</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/12/meta-is-lifting-trumps-account-restrictions-ahead-of-2024-election/</link><description>Meta announced former President Donald Trump’s Facebook and Instagram accounts will no longer be subject to heightened suspension penalties, according...</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 00:49:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>9 Amazon Prime Day competitor deals for travelers</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/amazon-prime-day-competitor-deals-for-travelers/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. Availability was accurate as of 10 a.m. on July 12, 2024. ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 23:30:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Abraham Lincoln Documentary Claims He Had Sex with Men</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/12/abraham-lincoln-documentary-claims-secret-sex-men-gay/</link><description>Abraham Lincoln had sexual relations with other men before he was elected president ... at least according to a new documentary. Honest Abe's sex life...</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 01:43:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Summer Olympics are near — and you’ve got less than a week to save $2 on Peacock</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/the-summer-olympics-are-near-and-youve-got-less-than-a-week-to-save-2-on-peacock-211e1a2c?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Peacock, which will stream every Olympics event live, will raise prices by $2 a month starting July 18.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 00:19:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Baked Huli Huli Chicken</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/baked-huli-huli-chicken/</link><description>Baked Huli Huli chicken is a tried and true recipe now made in the oven! Tender chicken baked in a…</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Can you prevent cancer with lifestyle changes?</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/can-you-prevent-cancer-with-lifestyle-changes/</link><description>Nearly half of cancer deaths in the U.S. are associated with preventable risk factors — such as smoking and alcohol use — according to a new American ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 16:12:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Waymo cameras capture footage of person charged in alleged robotaxi tire slashings</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/12/waymo-cameras-capture-footage-of-man-charged-in-alleged-robotaxi-tire-slashings/</link><description>A Castro Valley resident was charged Thursday for allegedly slashing the tires of 17 Waymo robotaxis in San Francisco between June 24 and June 26, acc...</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 00:38:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deal alert: Points and miles travel deals for July 2024</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/points-and-miles-travel-deals/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. Some of the below offers may be targeted. Citi is a TPG ad...</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 23:00:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pregnant Margot Robbie Attends Wimbledon with Tom Ackerley</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/12/margot-robbie-pregnant-wimbledon-first-appearance-husband-tom-ackerley/</link><description>Margot Robbie's showing off her maternity fashion sense on the big stage -- making her first public appearance since revealing her pregnancy at Wimble...</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 01:43:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meta to lift restrictions on Trump’s social-media accounts ahead of election</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/meta-to-lift-penalties-on-trumps-accounts-ahead-of-election-d4f1a727?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Facebook and Instagram parent Meta Platforms Inc. on Friday said it would lift restrictions placed last year on the social-media accounts of former Pr...</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 23:46:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Baked Alaska</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/baked-alaska/</link><description>Impress everyone with this gorgeous Baked Alaska dessert! It’s surprisingly easy to make with just 5 ingredients. Layers of cake,…</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In case you missed it: This week’s Top 5 stories on social media</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/in-case-you-missed-it-this-weeks-top-5-stories-on-social-media-19/</link><description>Check out a few of the most popular News Network stories on @mayoclinic social media this past week. Mayo Clinic marks medical milestone with world's ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 14:51:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>21 Best Early Amazon Prime Day Deals (2024)</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-early-amazon-prime-day-deals-2024/</link><description>Prime Day falls on July 16 and 17, but we’ve handpicked deals on WIRED-tested products—from tech to blenders to hair straighteners—sitting at some of ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 22:28:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zoos, sporting events and movies: How I plan to max out the Q3 categories on my Freedom Flex</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/maximize-chase-freedom-entertainment/</link><description>Every three months, the Chase Freedom (no longer available to new applicants) and the Chase Freedom Flex® offer a set of new bonus categories that ear...</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 22:00:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Patrick &amp; Brittany Mahomes Expecting Baby No. 3</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/12/patrick-mahomes-brittany-pregnant-expecting-baby-no-3/</link><description>Patrick Mahomes and his wife, Brittany, are expecting another baby!! The Kansas City Chiefs superstar announced Friday morning Britt's pregnant with c...</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 01:43:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Postage rates are set to increase to 73 cents. Here’s why snail-mail loyalists don’t care.</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/postage-rates-are-set-to-increase-to-73-cents-heres-why-snail-mail-loyalists-dont-care-6aed778e?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>This marks the second rate hike the U.S. Postal Service has instituted this year alone.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 23:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Homemade Boursin Cheese</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/homemade-boursin-cheese/</link><description>Homemade Boursin Cheese is soft, creamy, and bursting with herbal flavor. Its texture is similar to cream cheese, making it…</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 02:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: Dangers of heat-related illnesses</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-dangers-of-heat-related-illnesses/</link><description>Scorching temperatures continue to blanket much of the U.S. in an ongoing summer heat wave. Prolonged exposure to both heat and humidity can lead to h...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Defending Russia’s EU neighbors</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/12/defending-russias-eu-neighbors/</link><description>Welcome to Startups Weekly — your weekly recap of everything you can’t miss from the world of startups. Sign up here to get it in your inbox every Fri...</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 21:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quick Points: Fly with a friend for almost free with the Southwest Companion Pass</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/quick-points-southwest-companion-pass/</link><description>Southwest Airlines remains a favorite for many flyers thanks to its generous ticket exchange policy, complimentary checked luggage and quirky boarding...</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 21:00:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lisa Rinna Posts Totally Nude Selfie on 61st Birthday</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/12/lisa-rinna-naked-selfie-birthday-real-housewives-beverly-hills/</link><description>Lisa Rinna's taking the phrase "birthday suit" pretty literally ... baring it all in honor of her 61st trip around the sun. The 'Real Housewives' star...</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 01:43:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Heard on the Street's Stock-Picking Contest</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/heard-on-the-streets-stock-picking-contest-bbb58f00?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>Read about our columnists’ favorite and least-favorite stocks and see how they have performed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 23:16:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Make Cheesecake (The Ultimate Guide)</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/how-to-make-cheesecake/</link><description>Cheesecake is my absolute FAVORITE dessert! I have perfected my method and I can’t wait to teach you how to…</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sports Safety Spotlight: Mayo advises teens on how to get back in the game safely after shoulder injury</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/sports-safety-spotlight-mayo-advises-teens-on-how-to-get-back-in-the-game-safely-after-shoulder-injury/</link><description>AUSTIN, Minn. ― For teens who love playing summer team sports, an injury that takes them out of the game can be devastating. Shoulder injuries are amo...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A VC told Keely Cat-Wells to get a male, non-disabled co-founder — she balked, nabbed a $2M pre-seed round</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/12/a-vc-told-keely-cat-wells-to-get-a-male-able-bodied-co-founder-she-balked-nabbed-a-2m-seed-round/</link><description>Cat-Wells said she started this platform because traditional hiring processes are exclusionary and often overlook skilled, talented disabled people. ©...</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is the Prime Visa credit card worth the cost?</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/is-amazon-prime-card-still-worth-it/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. Amazon is the giant in the room for easy, instant access t...</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 20:00:09 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>