<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 06:46:41 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Judge Sides with Courtney Clenney Over Laptop Evidence in Murder Trial</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/26/judge-sides-courtney-clenney-key-evidence-murder-trial/</link><description>The murder trial of OnlyFans model Courtney Clenney will not include key evidence prosecutors obtained from her mother's iCloud ... after a Miami-Dade...</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 13:05:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mortgage rates drop to a three-month low. ‘We expect rates to continue to come down over the summer months,’ Freddie Mac says.</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/mortgage-rates-drop-to-a-three-month-low-we-expect-rates-to-continue-to-come-down-over-the-summer-months-freddie-mac-says-efa36e2d?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>The 30-year mortgage rate is averaging at 6.86% Freddie Mac said in its latest weekly survey on Thursday.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>No-Bake Cookie Dough Cheesecake</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/no-bake-cookie-dough-cheesecake/</link><description>With the rich Oreo crust, creamy cheesecake filling, and edible cookie dough bites, this no-bake cookie dough cheesecake is something…</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sports Safety Spotlight: Mayo Clinic gives tips on staying active with joint pain</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/sports-safety-spotlight-mayo-clinic-gives-tips-on-staying-active-with-joint-pain/</link><description>EAU CLAIRE, Wis. ― When the weather has you enthused about fitness, the last thing you want is to be sidelined with joint pain. "People might associat...</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 17:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rondo Energy funding shows a new way across the climate startup ‘valley of death’</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/27/rondo-energy-funding-shows-a-new-way-across-the-climate-startup-valley-of-death/</link><description>Climate tech startups especially those building hardware, face a particular challenge when trying to move beyond the prototype or pilot phase and star...</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 17:40:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>6 reasons to choose Celebrity Edge for your Alaska cruise</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/celebrity-edge-alaska-cruise/</link><description>Heads up, cruisers, there’s a new cruise ship option in Alaska — and it’s a game changer. Travelers have long had plenty of choice in Alaska, with opt...</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:00:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Travis Scott Went Back to Miami Yacht for Forgotten Items Before Arrest</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/26/travis-scott-yacht-miami-beach-arrest-intoxication-left-belongings-argument/</link><description>Travis Scott could have avoided his arrest in Miami last week if he hadn't left some stuff behind on the yacht where the incident went down ... TMZ ha...</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 13:05:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Walgreens Boots Alliance’s stock headed for 27-year low after profit miss and lowered guidance</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/walgreens-boots-alliances-stock-slides-2-8-after-profit-miss-and-lowered-guidance-87496f7f?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Walgreens Boots Alliance Inc.’s stock fell 12% early Thursday, after the drugstore chain’s fiscal third-quarter profit fell short of estimates and it ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 17:53:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Easy Apricot Sorbet (No-Churn!)</title><link>https://minimalistbaker.com/easy-apricot-sorbet-no-churn/</link><description>Once upon a time, in the dark streets of San Francisco, a life-changing ice cream cone was enjoyed thanks to Garden Creamery. This apricot sorbet is i...</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: Fireworks safety tips</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-fireworks-safety-tips/</link><description>For many, the Fourth of July holiday is a time to celebrate with barbecues, parades and fireworks. But, experts say, when it comes to fireworks, it's ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amazon consolidates Amazon Clinic into the One Medical brand</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/27/amazon-one-medical-amazon-clinic-consolidation/</link><description>Amazon is folding its Amazon Clinic telehealth service into its primary care business One Medical, the company announced on Thursday. The company expl...</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 17:32:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This comeback cruise line just released details of 2 new luxury ships</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/crystal-cruise-new-luxury-ship-details/</link><description>Luxury cruise line Crystal is about to double the size of its oceangoing fleet by adding two new 690-passenger vessels, the first of which is set to d...</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 17:45:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bam Margera Pleads Guilty to Disorderly Conduct, Gets Probation</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/26/bam-margera-pleads-guilty-disorderly-conduct-probation-brother-kill-family/</link><description>Bam Margera's putting another legal issue behind him ... taking a plea deal before his assault trial kicked off. The "Jackass" star pled guilty to 2 c...</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 13:05:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘My mother is being catfished’: She fell ‘madly in love’ with a man over Facebook. How do I convince her that it’s a scam?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/my-mother-is-being-catfished-she-fell-madly-in-love-with-a-man-over-facebook-how-do-i-convince-her-that-its-a-scam-d3b90209?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>“My sister and I found loads of evidence online that this is a fake account. There are actually numerous fake accounts on various platforms that use t...</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 17:48:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Use an Air Fryer</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/how-to-use-an-air-fryer/</link><description>The air fryer is one of the most versatile appliances in today’s kitchen! Learn how to use an air fryer…</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>$20 million gift from Dwight and Dian Diercks to accelerate Mayo Clinic’s strategy for transformational healthcare AI and innovation</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/20-million-gift-from-dwight-and-dian-diercks-to-accelerate-mayo-clinics-strategy-for-transformational-healthcare-ai-and-innovation/</link><description>ROCHESTER, Minn. — A generous $20 million gift from Dwight and Dian Diercks will fuel key elements of Mayo Clinic’s vision for the future of healthcar...</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best Fire Pits to Get Your S'mores On This Summer (2024)</title><link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-fire-pits/</link><description>Turn your patio into a party with these burning rings of fire.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Now live: Etihad Guest makes changes to award redemptions, elite status and more</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/etihad-guest-2024-changes/</link><description>Etihad Airways has implemented a wide range of changes to its Etihad Guest loyalty program. Under the new system, there are some winners and losers. E...</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 17:30:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gavin Rossdale Goes Shirtless, Shows Off Abs in Thirst Trap</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/26/gavin-rossdale-thirst-trap-shirtless-photo/</link><description>Gavin Rossdale is like a fine wine ... he just keeps getting better with age, because he's 58 and still looking like an absolute hunk. The Bush frontm...</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 13:05:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Supreme Court gives emergency abortion care in Idaho a temporary reprieve</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/supreme-court-gives-emergency-abortion-care-in-idaho-a-temporary-reprieve-0ecb6324?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>The U.S. Supreme Court on Thursday allowed for provision of emergency abortion care in Idaho hospitals but avoided wading into the legal issues at the...</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 17:32:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Candied Pistachios (4 Ingredients!)</title><link>https://minimalistbaker.com/candied-pistachios/</link><description>Pistachios are good, but candied pistachios?! VERY good. They’re the ultimate sweet, nutty, versatile topping for everything from salads to sorbets. B...</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic expert discusses dengue fever amid CDC warning of increased risk</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/dengue-fever-a-mayo-clinic-expert-explains-the-mosquito-borne-infection/</link><description>The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) is warning of an increased risk of dengue fever in the U.S. Dengue fever is a potentially life-th...</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 18:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Just in time for the debates, Meta fixes bug impacting users’ political content settings on Instagram and Threads</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/27/meta-fixes-bug-that-seemed-to-reset-users-political-content-settings-on-instagram-and-threads/</link><description>Meta has fixed the bug that caused people to believe the company had adjusted their selections in a political content settings tool without their cons...</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 17:19:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Ritz-Carlton Yacht Collection will sail around Asia starting next year</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/ritz-carlton-yacht-luminara-asia/</link><description>It’s been only a few weeks since The Ritz-Carlton Yacht Collection shared images of Ilma, the second ship in its fleet. Now, the luxury sailing arm of...</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 17:00:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Guess Who This Boy In His Denim Jacket Turned Into!</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/27/guess-who-this-boy-in-his-denim-jacket-turned-into/</link><description>Before this boy with bleach blonde hair turned into a social media influencer and was swingin' behind the wrestling ring, he was just throwing on his ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 13:05:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Palo Alto Networks, Salesforce shares see big boosts as Nvidia stock rally cools</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/palo-alto-networks-salesforce-shares-see-big-boosts-as-nvidia-stock-rally-cools-f5d262db?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>A Mizuho analyst is intrigued by what he views to be a rotation into the software sector as the chip trade fades.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 17:09:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zeppole (Italian Donuts)</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/zeppole-recipe/</link><description>Whip up a batch of these delightful zeppole, perfect for a sweet treat anytime! With a light, fluffy texture and…</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How extreme heat and humidity affect your health</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/how-extreme-heat-and-humidity-affect-your-health/</link><description>Many parts of the U.S. continue to grapple with oppressive heat and humidity. This can prevent the body from cooling down, increasing the risk of heat...</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Mystery Ranch Coulee 30 is Everything You Need in Day Pack</title><link>https://www.wired.com/review/mystery-ranch-coulee-30/</link><description>A comfortable, well-design day pack capable of heavy loads with plenty of customization options.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Get them before they’re gone: Disneyland’s Oogie Boogie Bash tickets are on sale now</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/disney-halloween-party-tickets-on-sale/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. Even though Halloween is months away, this is the time of ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:45:26 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>