<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 06:54:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Matthew Perry Death, Charges Against 2 Doctors, 'Ketamine Queen' and Personal Assistant</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/15/matthew-perry-case-us-attorney/</link><description>5:57 PM PT -- Jasveen Sangha, AKA "The Ketamine Queen," and Dr. Salvador Plasencia appeared in court Thursday and pleaded not guilty. Sangha was jaile...</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 13:08:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Want to know your risk of chronic disease as you age? Don’t waste money trying to find out.</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/want-to-know-your-risk-of-chronic-disease-as-you-age-dont-waste-money-trying-to-find-out-0867df11?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>What you should know before you try genetic testing</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 18:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Meal Plan #15</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/weekly-meal-plan-15/</link><description>This weekly meal plan has some classics with a twist that you are going to love! It gives you a…</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Start A Successful Health Coaching Business (Yes, You Can!)</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/4-tips-to-starting-successful-health-coaching-business</link><description>Start your journey helping people make life-changing health shifts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 11:27:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TechCrunch Minute: Lockheed Martin rescues satellite manufacturer Terran Orbital</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/video/watch-lockheed-martin-rescues-satellite-manufacturer-terran-orbital/</link><description>Lockheed Martin is acquiring satellite manufacturer Terran Orbital, taking the smaller company private and potentially rescuing it from running out of cash while facing of serious debt. Although Terran Orbital itself wasn’t founded until 2013, its history goes back to the late ’90s, to the development of the CubeSat, which became the flagship in a […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>First look: Inside the new Banyan Tree Higashiyama Kyoto</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/banyan-tree-higashiyama-kyoto/</link><description>One of the best parts of travel is staying in incredible hotels full of personality, local charm and a true sense of place. In Japan, Accor just opene...</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 17:30:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Doctors In Matthew Perry Case Investigated By Medical Board, Still Have Licenses</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/15/doctors-matthew-perry-case-investigation-medical-licenses-active/</link><description>The two doctors charged in connection with Matthew Perry's death are being investigated by the Medical Board of California, but they haven't had their...</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 13:08:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gold Prices Set New Record on U.S. Rate-Cut Hopes, Geopolitical Concerns</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/gold-prices-set-new-record-on-u-s-rate-cut-hopes-geopolitical-concerns-4e982ed0?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>Continuous gold futures on the New York Mercantile Exchange reached as high as $2,538.7 earlier in the session, breaking the prior record of $2,522.5.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 18:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chocolate Whipped Cream</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/chocolate-whipped-cream/</link><description>Fluffy Chocolate Whipped Cream is a wonderful combination of chocolate and fresh whipped cream. It’s the perfect topping for fruit,…</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>No Lie, This Supplement Is Like The Fountain Of Youth For Your Skin</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/how-each-mbg-best-skin-ingredient-benefits-aging-skin</link><description>Do you do your skin care routine morning and night? Great. But there's more you can do. Here's how to approach skin aging from the inside out.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 11:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to See the Conjunction Between Mars, Jupiter, and the Moon</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-see-the-conjunction-between-mars-jupiter-and-the-moon-this-august/</link><description>On the 27th, the celestial bodies will form an unusual triangle in the sky just before dawn.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 17:53:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fall flight deals before Labor Day? School keeps starting earlier, and airlines are taking notice</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/school-starts-earlier-airlines-summer-schedules/</link><description>Summer isn’t over just yet: As much of the country scorches under stifling heat waves, two weeks still remain until Labor Day weekend marks the unoffi...</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 17:15:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Guess Who This Charming Kiddo Turned Into!</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/16/guess-who-charming-kiddo-turned-into/</link><description>Before this cool lil guy giving major side-eye and a smise turned into a broadcaster, he was just playing with his pet snake, Sam, and growing up with...</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 13:08:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>My ‘evil uncle’ asked me to pay $20,000 in legal fees for his late brother’s estate. How should I respond?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/my-evil-uncle-asked-me-to-sign-a-form-agreeing-to-pay-for-debt-taxes-and-20k-in-legal-fees-for-his-late-brothers-estate-can-he-sue-me-for-this-money-d165efd8?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>“His lawyer sent me a ‘refunding bond’ and ‘release form.’”</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 17:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zucchini Roll-Ups</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/zucchini-roll-ups/</link><description>Zucchini Roll-Ups are a delicious, unique meal that the whole family will enjoy. Thin slices of zucchini are rolled around…</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In A Financial Pinch? 7 Small Savings Tips That Add Up To Big Savings</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/small-savings-tips-that-add-up-to-big-savings</link><description>Don’t dismiss the power of baby steps, especially when it comes to saving money. Small money moves can add up to big savings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 21:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>African e-commerce company Jumia completes sale of secondary shares at $99.6M</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/16/african-e-commerce-company-jumia-completes-sale-of-secondary-shares-at-99-6m/</link><description>Almost two weeks ago, TechCrunch reported that African e-commerce giant Jumia was planning to sell 20 million American depositary shares (ADSs) and raise over $100 million, given its share price of around $5.70 at the time. The e-tailer has now completed the at-the-market transaction offering of 20,227,736 ADSs. Jumia sold the shares at an average […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 17:18:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>7 things to consider when choosing a credit card for large purchases</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/credit-cards-for-large-purchases/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. One of the first lessons I learned when I got into the poi...</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 17:00:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TMZ TV Hot Takes: Arrests In Matthew Perry Death Case, North West, Tom Brady</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/16/tmz-tv-hot-takes-matthew-perry-case-north-west-tom-brady/</link><description>There was a big break in the Matthew Perry death case, North West is twinning with her dog, and Tom Brady is showing off his arm ... all this on today...</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 13:08:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>B. Riley’s stock rallies 26% after founder offers to buy rest of troubled bank for $7 a share</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/b-rileys-stock-rallies-26-after-founder-offers-to-buy-rest-of-troubled-bank-for-7-a-share-af7e6e3c?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>B. Riley Financial Inc.’s stock rallied 26% on Friday after Bryant R. Riley, the founder, chairman, co-chief executive and largest shareholder of the troubled investment bank, made an offer to buy the stock he doesn’t already own for $7 a share.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Baking Soda vs Baking Powder (Baking Tips)</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/baking-soda-vs-baking-powder-baking-tips/</link><description>Baking soda vs baking powder….what is the difference? I’m here to teach you the basics of each so that you…</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A 7-Week Plan To Master Pull-Ups (&amp; Why This Move Is A+ For Healthy Aging)</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/how-to-do-your-first-pull-up-7-week-beginner-plan</link><description>Pull-ups are way more than just a flex—they can actively boost longevity and health span.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 13:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Only 7 days left to save on TechCrunch Disrupt 2024 tickets</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/16/only-7-days-left-to-save-on-disrupt-2024-tickets/</link><description>We’re entering the final week of discounted rates for TechCrunch Disrupt 2024. Save up to $600 on select individual ticket types until August 23. Join a dynamic crowd of over 10,000 attendees, startup founders and VC investors at Moscone West in San Francisco from October 28-30. Here are just a few big reasons to attend […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 20 best Hilton hotels in the world</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/best-hilton-hotels/</link><description>Hilton operates thousands of hotels in more than 120 countries and territories globally. So, how do you go about choosing the best of the best? How do...</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 16:30:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Olympian Alysha Newman Says OnlyFans Page Has Exploded Since Viral Twerk</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/16/alysha-newman-twerking-onlyfans-olympics/</link><description>Canadian pole vaulter Alysha Newman's twerking celebration in France has been great for her wallet ... she tells TMZ Sports the impromptu dance has le...</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 13:08:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Consumer sentiment picks up for first time in five months in August</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/consumer-sentiment-picks-up-for-first-time-in-five-months-in-august-d2bd37e5?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>“Consumers vote with their wallets, and household spending overall is still in solid shape,” one economist noted.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 17:23:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seedy Tahini Snack Bites (Nut-Free!)</title><link>https://minimalistbaker.com/seedy-tahini-snack-bites/</link><description>Nut-free friends, this one’s for you! We’re no strangers to energy bites (and cake bites… and cookie bites…), but a nut-free version of these snackabl...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Creatine Supplements Bad For Your Kidneys? What's Fact vs. Fiction</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/are-creatine-supplements-bad-for-your-kidneys</link><description>Here's what you should know.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 12:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best Field Recorders for Portable Audio</title><link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-field-recorders/</link><description>Tired of recording on your cell phone? These portable field recorders are fantastic for everything from interviews to concerts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 16:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Milestone credit card review: A bad choice for a credit-building card</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/milestone-credit-card-review/</link><description>Milestone Mastercard overview Building credit can be a challenge. The Bank of Missouri’s Milestone Mastercard® is one of many credit-building cards av...</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 16:00:28 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>