<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 06:56:01 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Jon Jones Pleads Not Guilty To Charges Stemming From Drug Test Incident</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/17/jon-jones-pleads-not-guilty-charges-drug-test-incident/</link><description>UFC heavyweight champion Jon Jones isn't tapping out in his ongoing legal battle ... entering a not-guilty plea for the two misdemeanor charges he's f...</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 07:49:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>China Investors' Newest Craze: Saudi Stocks</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/china-investors-newest-craze-saudi-stocks-e796fd0a?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>Chinese investors are piling into new funds tracking Saudi Arabian equities, a sign of the robust appetite for overseas exposure at a time when home m...</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 12:42:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sugar Cream Pie (Hoosier Pie)</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/sugar-cream-pie/</link><description>Sugar cream pie, or Hoosier pie, is a creamy, delicious treat with deep roots in the Midwest, especially in Indiana.…</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic study uncovers genetic cancer risks in 550 patients</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-study-uncovers-genetic-cancer-risks-in-550-patients/</link><description>PHOENIX — Current screening protocols fail to catch a notable number of people carrying genetic mutations associated with hereditary breast and ovaria...</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>India’s WazirX confirms security breach following a $230M ‘suspicious transfer’</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/18/indias-wazirx-confirms-security-breach-after-230-million-suspicious-transfer/</link><description>The Mumbai-based firm said one of its multisig wallets had suffered a security breach, and it was temporarily pausing all withdrawals from the platfor...</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 11:19:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alaska Airlines unveils big cabin retrofits, adding premium seats to Boeing 737s</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/alaska-airlines-boeing-737-retrofits-first-class-premium/</link><description>Premium demand is surging, and Alaska Airlines is betting that travelers will want to splurge for premium seats for the long haul. The Seattle-based c...</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 01:52:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bam Margera's Ex Was Never His Wife Despite Wedding, Court Tentatively Rules</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/17/bam-margera-never-married-ex-nikki-boyd-custody-dispute-judge-ruling/</link><description>Bam Margera and Nikki Boyd were never husband and wife in the eyes of the law, despite going through a wedding ceremony -- that's the word from the ju...</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 07:49:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tech selloff erases $1.1 trillion of ‘Magnificent Seven’ market cap in five days</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/tech-selloff-has-erased-1-1-trillion-of-magnificent-seven-market-cap-in-5-days-94745798?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>The seven Big Tech companies collectively shed more than $500 billion in market cap on Wednesday alone.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 12:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Boursin Pork Chops</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/boursin-pork-chops/</link><description>Boursin Pork Chops are savory, tender, and covered in a delicious cheesy cream sauce. This one-pan recipe is the perfect easy…</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paving the way for future larynx transplants through regenerative science</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/7-17paving-the-way-for-future-larynx-transplants-through-regenerative-science/</link><description>Surgeons at Mayo Clinic in Arizona perform a total larynx transplant Mayo Clinic envisions a day when regenerative science makes it possible to offer ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Samsung to acquire UK-based knowledge graph startup Oxford Semantic Technologies</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/18/samsung-to-acquire-uk-based-knowledge-graph-startup-oxford-semantic-technologies/</link><description>The Korean tech giant is acquiring Oxford Semantic Technologies, a U.K.-based knowledge graph startup that has built an AI reasoning engine. © 2024 Te...</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 11:14:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>American Airlines announces improvements to the AAdvantage Business program</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/american-airlines-aadvantage-business-changes/</link><description>Citi is a TPG advertising partner. AAdvantage Business, American Airlines’ corporate loyalty program, has announced several changes, which should be w...</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 23:30:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Thomas Matthew Crooks' Former Classmate Says He Was a Trump Hater</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/17/thomas-matthew-crooks-former-classmate-trump-hater/</link><description>Thomas Matthew Crooks wasn't a fan of Donald Trump years before attempting to assassinate the former Prez ... so says one of his former classmates. Vi...</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 07:49:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Infosys meets earnings estimate as sales edge past consensus</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/infosys-meets-earnings-estimate-as-sales-edge-past-consensus-bc4905ec?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Indian outsourcing giant Infosys reported growing profits as it forecast a slight pickup in sales growth for the year.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 12:37:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sheet Pan Ratatouille with Crispy Baked Tofu</title><link>https://minimalistbaker.com/sheet-pan-ratatouille-with-crispy-baked-tofu/</link><description>What could be better than the saucy, savory goodness of classic ratatouille!? Answer: SHEET PAN ratatouille! Say “au revoir” to stovetop babysitting, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tomorrow’s Cure: How nuclear medicine helps cancer patients</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/tomorrows-cure-how-nuclear-medicine-helps-cancer-patients/</link><description>Nuclear medicine therapy is sometimes the best option for people who no longer respond to other cancer treatments. It is often helpful for patients wi...</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Newly Discovered Moon Caves Could One Day House Astronauts</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/moon-tunnels-caves-astronauts-moon-colony/</link><description>Analysis of lunar imagery has ended a longstanding debate over whether there are accessible underground areas on the Moon; an emptied lava tube in the...</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Earn up to 90,000 points with these Choice Privileges Mastercard offers</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/new-wells-fargo-choice-privileges-card-launch/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information. Wells Fargo has two Choice Privileges credit cards. A no-annual-fee C...</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 23:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eric Trump Says 'Competent' Shooter Would've Hit Dad, Pissed at Security Lapses</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/17/eric-trump-competent-shooter-assassination-attempt-security-lapses-secret-service/</link><description>Eric Trump is furious with the security lapses leading up to the assassination attempt on his father ... and says a competent shooter wouldn't have mi...</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 07:49:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Slowdown in U.K. jobs market could pave way for BoE interest rate cut, Deutsche Bank says</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/slowdown-in-u-k-jobs-market-could-pave-way-for-boe-interest-rate-cut-deutsche-bank-says-bbc379d8?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>The Office for National Statistics data shows a slowdown in the U.K.’s labor market that could see the Bank of England cut interest rates at its upcom...</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 12:31:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Red Robin Campfire Sauce</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/red-robin-campfire-sauce/</link><description>Red Robin campfire sauce is the best pairing for your burgers, fries, and more. Whip it up in minutes with…</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic scientists define new type of memory loss in older adults</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-scientists-define-new-type-of-memory-loss-in-older-adults/</link><description>ROCHESTER, Minn. — Researchers at Mayo Clinic have established new criteria for a memory-loss syndrome in older adults that specifically impacts the b...</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 02:26:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Artificial Agency raises $16M to use AI to make NPCs feel more realistic in video games</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/18/artificial-agency-raises-video-game-npcs-ai/</link><description>A team of former Google DeepMind researchers are betting that their unique behavior engine for NPCs will make games more fun and dynamic. © 2024 TechC...</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Earn 50,000 miles and a discounted companion ticket with this Alaska Airlines card offer</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/current-alaska-card-offer/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. If you’re looking to boost your Alaska Airlines Mileage Pl...</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 22:00:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Salt-N-Pepa's Sandra Denton Says Southwest Airlines Treated Her Like a Criminal</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/17/salt-n-pepa-sandra-denton-southwest-airlines-treated-like-criminal/</link><description>Sandra "Pepa" Denton, 1/2 of Salt-N-Pepa, is still shaken and confused by her encounter with Southwest Airlines this week, when she says she got treat...</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 07:49:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘I’m not jealous — just genuinely curious’: How can a woman work from home and mind her 3-year-old child at the same time?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/im-not-jealous-just-genuinely-curious-how-can-a-woman-work-from-home-and-mind-her-3-year-old-child-at-the-same-time-14a9c311?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>“What do you all think about employees who work from home and have little kids to watch at the same time?”</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 12:23:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sushi Bowl</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/sushi-bowl/</link><description>This sushi bowl is a deconstructed California sushi roll loaded with irresistible flavor and all of the best sushi ingredients.…</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic ranked No. 1 hospital in Florida by U.S. News &amp; World Report, makes leap in national rankings</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-ranked-no-1-hospital-in-florida-by-u-s-news-world-report-makes-leap-in-national-rankings/</link><description>JACKSONVILLE, Fla. — Mayo Clinic is again ranked the No. 1 hospital in Florida and the Jacksonville metro area in U.S. News &amp; World Report's "Best Hos...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 06:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Israel’s startup scene shows reslience despite nine months of war</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/18/israels-startup-scene-shows-reslience-despite-nine-months-of-war/</link><description>When the war between Israel and Hamas broke out last October, we examined its potential impact on the tech ecosystems in Israel and Palestine. Nine mo...</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 09:12:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Park Hyatt London River Thames now accepting reservations</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/park-hyatt-london-river-thames/</link><description>Just in time for the fall and holiday travel season, one of the most anticipated hotels in London is almost ready to open its doors. According to the ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 21:30:20 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>