<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 12:07:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Slutty Vegan's Pinky Cole Calls Out Rival for Adding Meat to Menu</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/07/slutty-vegan-pinky-cole-calls-out-rival-adding-meat-to-menu/</link><description>Slutty Vegan founder Pinky Cole is weighing in on the controversy surrounding Sage Regenerative Kitchen &amp; Brewery ... calling out their vegan rival fo...</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 00:36:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PBOC to conduct temporary repo, reverse repo operations</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/china-pboc-to-conduct-temporary-repo-reverse-repo-operations-e901d2d9?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>China’s central bank has said that it will conduct temporary open market operations in the afternoon, on top of its traditional morning operations, in...</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 03:11:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tater Tot Nachos</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/tater-tot-nachos/</link><description>Tater Tot Nachos (Totchos) are made with crispy golden tater tots, topped with seasoned beef, scoops of refried beans, corn,…</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How a different mammogram experience led to lifesaving cancer diagnosis</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/how-a-different-mammogram-experience-led-to-lifesaving-cancer-diagnosis/</link><description>Melissa Neuman dreaded getting mammograms. Her small, dense breasts made the screening exceptionally uncomfortable and painful. So Melissa put off get...</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Investors chase wealthtech startups in India as affluent class grows</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/07/investors-chase-wealthtech-startups-in-india-as-affluent-class-grows/</link><description>Investors are betting on Indian wealthtech startups as a growing middle class turns to diversify investments and startups challenge traditional financ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 03:32:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How and why to register for Choice Hotels Personalized Weeknight Benefits</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/maximize-your-extras-choice-hotels/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information. Whether you frequently use the Choice Privileges program or are only ...</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 21:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cristina Pilo Stripes Down In Animal Print Bikini</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/07/cristina-pilo-stripes-down-in-animal-print-bikini/</link><description>This week's Summer Hot Shots feature is coming from an exotic green patch on a Virginia Key beach ... where wellness coach and IG hottie Cristina Pilo...</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 00:36:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paramount moves closer to finalizing merger with Skydance: reports</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/paramount-moves-closer-to-finalizing-merger-with-skydance-reports-a2d57781?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>The end of Paramount Global’s long and windy road to a sale appeared at hand Sunday, with multiple reports that a special committee had approved Skyda...</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 01:36:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Poke Sauce</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/poke-sauce/</link><description>The best Poke Sauce is easy to make with just a handful of simple ingredients! Whether you are using salmon…</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maximize memory function with a nutrient-rich diet</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/maximize-memory-function-with-a-nutrient-rich-diet/</link><description>Research suggests that the ability to maximize memory function may be related to what you eat. Following an eating plan that provides a healthier sele...</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seed VCs are turning to new ‘pro rata’ funds that help them compete with the big firms</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/07/pro-rata-seed-vcs-funds-venture-capital/</link><description>Three companies with new funds deploy capital to support seed and Series A VCs looking to exercise their pro rata rights. © 2024 TechCrunch. All right...</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amex EveryDay card review: Dip your toes into the world of Membership Rewards</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/amex-everyday-card-review/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. The Amex EveryDay® Credit Card from American Express is a ...</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 19:00:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Squaw Valley 1960 Winter Olympics Torch Up For Auction</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/07/squaw-valley-1960-winter-olympics-torch-for-sale-auction/</link><description>There's a super cool piece of sports history going up for sale ... one of the rarest Olympic torches ever made is hitting the auction block. Get a loa...</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 00:36:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How stock-market investors are making sense of Biden candidacy uncertainty</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/how-stock-market-investors-are-making-sense-of-biden-candidacy-uncertainty-b1fcde85?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Stock-market investors are taking uncertainty around President Joe Biden’s candidacy in stride, but analysts see volatility ahead.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 22:23:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Philly Cheesesteak Foil Packs</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/philly-cheesesteak-foil-packs/</link><description>Try these delicious Philly Cheesesteak Foil Packs, a fun new way to enjoy the flavors of the classic Philly Cheesesteak.…</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In case you missed it: This week’s Top 5 stories on social media</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/in-case-you-missed-it-this-weeks-top-5-stories-on-social-media-18/</link><description>Check out a few of the most popular News Network stories on @mayoclinic social media this past week. IBD Pride Clinic: Belonging while battling bowel ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 17:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>YouTube and LinkedIn have games now, and here’s how you can play them</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/07/youtube-and-linkedin-have-games-now-and-heres-how-you-can-play-them/</link><description>Here are the latest companies venturing into the gaming scene and details about each offering, including pricing, examples of titles and supported dev...</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bahamas cruise guide: Best itineraries, planning tips and things to do</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/bahamas-cruise-guide/</link><description>If you’ve cruised or are planning to cruise to someplace warm, it’s likely that the Bahamas will pop up on your itinerary — and for good reason. Found...</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 17:00:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trey Parker's Ex-Wife Boogie's L.A. House Broken Into, $500k Stolen Goods</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/07/trey-parker-baby-ex-wife-house-boogie-home-burglarized/</link><description>Trey Parker's ex-wife, Boogie Parker, is the latest victim in a string of burglaries hitting L.A. Law enforcement sources tell TMZ ... two burglars br...</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 00:36:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The rush to exit commercial real-estate funds is going mainstream</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/the-rush-to-exit-commercial-real-estate-funds-is-going-mainstream-ae178260?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>The plight of investors looking to pull money out of commercial real estate funds has gone mainstream.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 21:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tri Tip Marinade</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/tri-tip-marinade/</link><description>This tasty tri tip marinade is the best way to infuse your tri-tip steak with delicious flavor and make it…</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: Can energy drinks cause heart issues?</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-can-energy-drinks-cause-heart-issues/</link><description>In recent years, there's been a big boost in the beverage industry when it comes to the sale of energy drinks. Classified as dietary supplements, most...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 15:58:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CIOs’ concerns over generative AI echo those of the early days of cloud computing</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/07/cios-concerns-over-generative-ai-echo-those-of-the-early-days-of-cloud-computing/</link><description>CIOs trying to govern generative AI have the same concerns they had about cloud computing 15 years ago, but they've learned some things along the way....</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2 nights in the heart of the action: A review of the W Philadelphia</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/reviews/w-philadelphia/</link><description>[circuit type=review circuit_id=”20420181785″] Philadelphia is known for several things: serving sumptuous cheesesteaks (I’m looking at you, Barclay P...</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 15:00:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BKFC In Talks W/ Bam Margera, Looking To Add Ex-'Jackass' Star To Commentary Team</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/07/bam-margera-bkfc-in-talks-negotiating-deal-commentary-team-bare-knuckle/</link><description>Get used to seeing Bam Margera ringside at BKFC ... we've learned the former 'Jackass' star is negotiating with the promotion, and the aim is to bring...</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 00:36:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week’s U.S. inflation report could have serious implications for stocks</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/this-weeks-u-s-inflation-report-could-have-serious-implications-for-stocks-fc7bed2a?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Like all marquee economic releases, the June inflation numbers could have serious ramifications for markets. But investors will be paying especially c...</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 18:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Raspberry Fluff Salad</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/raspberry-fluff-salad/</link><description>Fresh and fruity Raspberry Fluff Salad is a sweet and creamy side or dessert with a mix of raspberries, vanilla…</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: Sunscreen has a shelf life and other facts to know</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-sunscreen-has-a-shelf-life-and-other-facts-to-know/</link><description>Did you know sunscreen has a shelf life and can expire? Or that too much heat or cold can ruin a new bottle? Protecting your skin from harmful sun ray...</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Epic Games CEO promises to ‘fight’ Apple over ‘absurd’ changes</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/07/epic-games-ceo-promises-to-fight-apple-over-absurd-changes/</link><description>It sounds like the latest dispute between Apple and Fortnite-maker Epic Games isn’t over. Epic has been fighting Apple for years over the company’s re...</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 17:23:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>21 new Hyatt hotels where you can get 500 extra points per night</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/hyatt-new-hotel-bonus/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. I stayed at the Hyatt House Johannesburg Sandton in South ...</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 21:00:40 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>