<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 06:57:07 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Hulk Hogan's Ex-Friend Is Willing to Work With Ben Affleck, Matt Damon on Gawker Film</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/12/bubba-love-sponge-help-sex-tape-movie/</link><description>Hulk Hogan's former close friend is not shying away from the upcoming Gawker movie ... instead he wants to collab with them ... and, he's got lots of ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 16:52:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How shunned China stocks could break out of a value trap</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/how-shunned-china-stocks-could-break-out-of-a-value-trap-56629b79?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Chinese stocks have gone nowhere fast, but may their time finally be arriving?</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 12:47:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Raspberry Muffins</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/raspberry-muffins/</link><description>These raspberry muffins are moist and delicious, filled with plump fresh raspberries and topped with a sweet, crunchy streusel topping!…</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 02:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Start A Successful Health Coaching Business (Yes, You Can!)</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/4-tips-to-starting-successful-health-coaching-business</link><description>Start your journey helping people make life-changing health shifts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 11:27:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Black Sororities and Fraternities Are Mobilizing Online and in Secret Chats for Voter Turnout</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/black-sororities-and-fraternities-mobilizing-online-voting/</link><description>Across the United States, members of Black Greek organizations are using everything from large social media accounts to secret group chats with the single aim of increasing turnout in November.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Disney World closing 2 classic attractions to make way for ‘Cars’ addition to Magic Kingdom</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/disney-world-closing-rides-cars-attractions/</link><description>On Saturday evening at the Disney Experiences Showcase during D23: The Ultimate Disney Fan Event, Disney Experiences Chairman Josh D’Amaro revealed do...</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 21:30:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sabrina Carpenter Freaks Out Onstage During Pyrotechnics Display</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/12/sabrina-carpenter-freaks-out-on-stage-fireworks-san-francisco-concert/</link><description>Sabrina Carpenter got quite a scare during her California concert over the weekend – she was filmed dashing away in terror after hearing exploding fir...</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 16:52:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Home Depot’s stock drops as higher rates hurt spending on home improvement</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/home-depots-stock-drops-as-earnings-beat-but-comparable-sales-missed-and-the-outlook-was-cut-fff23db7?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Home Depot’s stock was knocked lower in early Tuesday trading, after the home improvement retail giant reported fiscal second-quarter earnings that beat expectations but comparable sales that missed and provided a downbeat full-year outlook, citing a more pressured consumer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 12:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Creamy Tuscan Dip (Marry Me Dip)</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/creamy-tuscan-dip/</link><description>There’s a new appetizer in town, and this creamy Tuscan dip won everyone’s hearts! The combination of cheeses, garlic, spinach,…</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>No Lie, This Supplement Is Like The Fountain Of Youth For Your Skin</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/how-each-mbg-best-skin-ingredient-benefits-aging-skin</link><description>Do you do your skin care routine morning and night? Great. But there's more you can do. Here's how to approach skin aging from the inside out.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 11:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Made by Google Live Blog: New Pixel Phones, Smartwatches, Gemini, and More</title><link>https://www.wired.com/live/made-by-google-2024-live-blog/</link><description>We're live at the “Made by Google” event. We'll be bringing you up-to-the-minute news updates about the Pixel phones, watches, earbuds, and Google Gemini.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is Disney Lightning Lane worth it?</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/is-disney-lightning-lane-multi-pass-worth-it/</link><description>Want to save time and ride all the attractions at Walt Disney World and Disneyland while limiting how much time you spend in line? Assuming you’re not...</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 21:00:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Scarface' Actor Ángel Salazar Dead at 69</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/11/scarface-star-angel-salazar-dead-dies/</link><description>Ángel Salazar -- best known as Al Pacino's trusted sidekick "Chi Chi" in the iconic gangster film "Scarface" -- has died, TMZ has learned. Salazar's r...</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 16:52:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>My homeowners insurance in Tennessee went up 27% — and I’ve had no claims. What gives?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/my-homeowners-insurance-in-tennessee-went-up-27-and-ive-had-no-claims-what-gives-cb45ec2d?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>“I feel like I got punished with such a high increase.”</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 12:36:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tomato Toast</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/tomato-toast/</link><description>Vibrant Tomato Toast has sweet, juicy tomatoes, garlic, creamy ricotta, and fresh basil layered on a crusty slice of toasted bread. It’s…</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 02:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In A Financial Pinch? 7 Small Savings Tips That Add Up To Big Savings</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/small-savings-tips-that-add-up-to-big-savings</link><description>Don’t dismiss the power of baby steps, especially when it comes to saving money. Small money moves can add up to big savings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 21:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>She grew up a gearhead — now her startup has raised $4.3M to cut CO2 from trucking</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/13/she-grew-up-a-gearhead-now-her-startup-has-raised-4m-to-cut-co2-from-trucking/</link><description>The irony was not lost on her. Growing up the daughter of a family obsessed with car racing, Danielle Walsh had become — in her late 20s — the head of HSBC’s ‘Future Cities’ project, the global banking giant’s effort to serve clients’ climate change mandates. It was 2018, and she was reporting both into the […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:18:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Frontier slashes midweek flying and delays new jets but insists things are looking up</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/frontier-q2-earnings/</link><description>It seems Frontier Airlines CEO Barry Biffle has heard enough criticism of the U.S. ultra-low-cost airline industry — even as the carrier projects more...</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 20:30:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Colin Jost Calls Himself 'Leper' After Olympic Injuries and Infections</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/12/colin-jost-leper-injuries-infections-olympics-malta/</link><description>Colin Jost posted an alarming update on the injuries and illnesses he sustained during his harrowing -- and hilarious -- coverage in Tahiti as an Olym...</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 16:52:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>German economic expectations nosedive in August as global slowdown fears bite</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/german-economic-expectations-nosedive-as-global-slowdown-fears-bite-ea6654f4?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Economic sentiment in Germany slumped, as weakening views of the health of the global economy exacerbated an already gloomy outlook.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 12:14:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chicken Adobo</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/chicken-adobo/</link><description>Chicken Adobo is a tangy, salty, sweet, and spicy Filipino dish. It’s easy to make and requires just a few…</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A 7-Week Plan To Master Pull-Ups (&amp; Why This Move Is A+ For Healthy Aging)</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/how-to-do-your-first-pull-up-7-week-beginner-plan</link><description>Pull-ups are way more than just a flex—they can actively boost longevity and health span.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 13:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Best Teacher Discounts (2024): Deals on School Supplies and Tech</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-teacher-discounts/</link><description>Ace the school year with special perks—like cheap software, phone plans, and classroom supplies.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>22 best Hyatt hotels in the world</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/best-hyatt-hotels/</link><description>There’s a Hyatt brand and a Hyatt hotel for every budget, from labels like the casual new Caption all the way up to tony Park Hyatt. You might even be...</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 20:00:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Donald Trump Hits Impressive Golf Shot, Misses Hole-In-One By Inches</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/12/donald-trump-golf-misses-hole-in-one-inches/</link><description>Donald Trump's golf game has never looked better ... just a few weeks after he impressed LIV star Bryson DeChambeau with his on-the-course work, he ne...</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 16:52:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘There’s no way I’m giving into these vultures’: My friend, 86, is in a hospice but her ‘friends’ keep asking for her possessions</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/theres-no-way-im-giving-into-these-vultures-my-friend-86-is-in-a-hospice-but-her-friends-keep-asking-for-her-possessions-e916dcbe?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>‘I am a health-care and durable power of attorney. I am also the trustee of her trust and will be the executor of her estate’</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Meal Plan #14</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/weekly-meal-plan-14/</link><description>I love the recipes in this weekly meal plan! They are packed with flavor and you have options of using…</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Creatine Supplements Bad For Your Kidneys? What's Fact vs. Fiction</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/are-creatine-supplements-bad-for-your-kidneys</link><description>Here's what you should know.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 12:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Opera is releasing its redesigned browser on iOS</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/13/opera-is-releasing-its-redesigned-browser-on-ios/</link><description>Opera is releasing its redesigned Opera One browser on iOS as a stable release after testing it in the beta phase for weeks. The new browser has a bottom placed search bar for easy browsing, quick search suggestions while typing, and Aria AI assistant integration. While the placed search bar will be the default option, […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Heads up: Apple AirTags are on sale for lowest price we’ve seen</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/apple-airtags-sale/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. As of Monday, Apple AirTags are available at a discounted ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 19:30:13 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>