<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 06:55:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Barack Obama Daps Up Team USA With Hilarious 'Key &amp; Peele' Style Handshakes</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/11/barack-obama-daps-up-team-usa-key-and-peele-style-handshakes-nba-olympics/</link><description>Barack Obama's living in a 'Key &amp; Peele' skit ... the former President reenacted one of their most hilarious bits as #44 showed love to LeBron James a...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 17:43:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tesla’s stock falls on reported robotaxi delay, while Uber and Lyft shares rise</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/teslas-stock-falls-on-reported-robotaxi-delay-b8eea37e?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Tesla Inc.’s stock fell more than 8% on Thursday after a report said the electric-vehicle maker will delay its closely watched robotaxi debut by two m...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 22:32:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Baked Huli Huli Chicken</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/baked-huli-huli-chicken/</link><description>Baked Huli Huli chicken is a tried and true recipe now made in the oven! Tender chicken baked in a…</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: Dangers of heat-related illnesses</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-dangers-of-heat-related-illnesses/</link><description>Scorching temperatures continue to blanket much of the U.S. in an ongoing summer heat wave. Prolonged exposure to both heat and humidity can lead to h...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pressure Grows in Congress to Treat Crypto Investigator Tigran Gambaryan, Jailed in Nigeria, as a Hostage</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/tigran-gambaryan-us-congress-resolution-hostage-nigeria/</link><description>A new resolution echoes what 16 members of Congress have already said to the White House: It must do more to free one of the most storied crypto-focus...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 21:58:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TAP Air Portugal summer sale: One-way fares to Europe from $207</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/deals/tap-air-portugal-summer-sale-europe/</link><description>It’s not too late to book your summer vacation. TAP Air Portugal just dropped a new sale offering one-way fares to Europe for as low as $207 from the ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 22:32:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Uruguay's Darwin Núñez Brawls With Fans In Stands After Copa América Game</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/11/uruguay-darwin-nunez-brawls-fans-in-stands-after-copa-america-game/</link><description>The ending of the Uruguay vs. Colombia Copa América game took an ugly turn ... as Darwin Núñez was so furious with some opposing fans, he actually rus...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 17:43:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why slowing inflation may power bitcoin’s rally toward a record high</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/why-slowing-inflation-may-power-bitcoins-rally-toward-a-record-high-394b8c50?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>The consumer-price index data released on Thursday, which showed a slowing pace of inflation in the U.S., could provide an ideal setup for a turnaroun...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 22:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Baked Alaska</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/baked-alaska/</link><description>Impress everyone with this gorgeous Baked Alaska dessert! It’s surprisingly easy to make with just 5 ingredients. Layers of cake,…</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sports Safety Spotlight: Mayo advises teens on how to get back in the game safely after shoulder injury</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/sports-safety-spotlight-mayo-advises-teens-on-how-to-get-back-in-the-game-safely-after-shoulder-injury/</link><description>AUSTIN, Minn. ― For teens who love playing summer team sports, an injury that takes them out of the game can be devastating. Shoulder injuries are amo...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Data breach exposes millions of mSpy spyware customers</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/11/mspy-spyware-millions-customers-data-breach/</link><description>A huge batch of mSpy customer service emails dating back to 2014 were stolen in a May data breach. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For persona...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 21:15:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Current Hyatt promotions: Earn bonus points, double elite night credits and more</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/current-hyatt-promotions/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. Take a look at your account: World of Hyatt is running sev...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 22:00:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Barack Obama was Given Heads-Up about George Clooney's Biden Op-Ed</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/11/barack-obama-notified-george-clooney-new-york-times-step-down-joe-biden/</link><description>Barack Obama was notified beforehand George Clooney's shocking op-ed was going to be published in the New York Times, encouraging Joe Biden to drop ou...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 17:43:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Risky-Loan Trade Is Back</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/high-risk-corporate-loans-ea265256?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>Yields of 9% are drawing investors to leveraged loans, whose defaults have remained low.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 22:22:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Homemade Boursin Cheese</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/homemade-boursin-cheese/</link><description>Homemade Boursin Cheese is soft, creamy, and bursting with herbal flavor. Its texture is similar to cream cheese, making it…</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 02:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Expert alert: Procedure offers hope to patients living with physical changes from stroke, other conditions</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/expert-alert-procedure-offers-hope-to-patients-living-with-physical-changes-from-stroke-other-conditions/</link><description>World Brain Day is July 22 ROCHESTER, Minn. — Fifteen million people worldwide have a stroke each year. Of these, 5 million are left permanently disab...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shark Tank-backed Kudos raises another $3M for healthier, cotton-based disposable diapers</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/11/shark-tank-kudos-raises-3m-more-healthier-sustainable-disposable-diapers/</link><description>Kudos founder says her company makes a disposable diaper lined with 100% cotton, unlike the major competitors. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved....</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 21:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to get Nexus for fast-track entry to the US and Canada</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/nexus/</link><description>Trusted Traveler Programs help eligible travelers expedite their way through border security at U.S. airports and land and sea ports. There is a lesse...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 21:45:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Orlando Bloom Strips Down, Goes For A Swim at Italian Beach</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/11/orlando-bloom-strips-shirtless-beach-swim-italy-sardinia-photos-naked-katy-perry/</link><description>Orlando Bloom's getting an Italian tan ... soaking up rays in Sardiania without his fiancée Katy Perry -- who's on the island with him but skipped out...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 17:43:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘Our children have varying degrees of success’: My husband and I are in our 80s and have $300,000 to leave our 3 kids. Do we give more to our underemployed son?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/our-children-have-varying-degrees-of-success-my-husband-and-i-are-in-our-80s-and-have-300-000-to-leave-our-3-children-do-we-give-more-to-our-underemployed-son-3b4d1c61?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>“At 56, he has few prospects for his future.”</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 22:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Make Cheesecake (The Ultimate Guide)</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/how-to-make-cheesecake/</link><description>Cheesecake is my absolute FAVORITE dessert! I have perfected my method and I can’t wait to teach you how to…</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What is laryngeal chondrosarcoma?</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/what-is-laryngeal-chondrosarcoma/</link><description>You may have heard about a recent first at Mayo Clinic, a total larynx transplant. What you may not have heard was what precipitated that transplant. ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:25:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 39 Best Shows on Max (aka HBO Max) Right Now (July 2024)</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/hbo-max-best-shows-to-stream-right-now/</link><description>House of the Dragon, The Sopranos, and Fantasmas are just a few of the shows you need to be watching on Max this month.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fiji Airways plots big US expansion with a new longest route</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/fiji-airways-dfw-longest-route/</link><description>If Fiji is on your bucket list, there may soon be a new way to get there. Fiji Airways filed plans on Thursday to commence a new nonstop flight from D...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 21:15:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alleged Drunk Driver Smashes Through Nail Salon in Shocking Video</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/11/drunk-driver-slams-nail-salon-long-island-new-york-dead-kill/</link><description>An alleged drunk driver in New York careened through a nail salon at top speed ... and, the unbelievable moment was caught on video. The shocking clip...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 17:43:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cheetos Are the Latest Economic Red Flag</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/cheetos-are-the-latest-economic-red-flag-2fe6f00c?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>PepsiCo and Conagra are the latest in a long list of companies warning that shoppers are stretched.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 22:14:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Creamy Pesto Sauce (Dairy-Free)</title><link>https://minimalistbaker.com/creamy-pesto-sauce/</link><description>We’re throwing a pesto party, and you’re invited! With all the herby, savory goodness of traditional basil pesto, this CREAMY dairy-free pesto SAUCE i...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tomorrow’s Cure: How DNA guides cancer detection</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/tomorrows-cure-how-dna-guides-cancer-detection/</link><description>What if you knew you'd get sick before you ever felt symptoms? If it was a cold, that information is useful. In the case of cancer, it is lifesaving. ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 13:46:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘Wild Wild Space’ doc captures the risks and rivalries of the new space race</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/11/wild-wild-space-doc-captures-the-risks-and-rivalries-of-the-new-space-race/</link><description>Astra CEO Chris Kemp is already pulling out of a parking spot when he warns the person in the passenger seat that he doesn’t have a valid driver’s lic...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 20:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Capital One Savor vs. Capital One Quicksilver: Supercharge your leisure spending or flat cash back on everything?</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/credit-card-showdown-capital-one-savor-vs-capital-one-quicksilver/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. Travel rewards cards come in many forms. Some are cobrande...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 20:30:26 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>