<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 00:29:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Mike Rowe Says Lack of Patriotism Inspired New Doc 'Something to Stand For'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/04/mike-rowe-documentary-film-something-to-stand-for/</link><description>Mike Rowe's drumming up support for his new movie "Something to Stand For," urging Americans to rally around at least one thing -- feeling grateful fo...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 03:18:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is the big slowdown in hiring finally here? June U.S. jobs report not supposed to show it.</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/is-the-big-slowdown-in-hiring-finally-here-june-u-s-jobs-report-not-supposed-to-show-it-99c13c74?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>The U.S. economy wasn’t supposed to churn out so many new jobs this year, according to the experts. But lots of businesses have been hiring to underpi...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 07:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Philly Cheesesteak Foil Packs</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/philly-cheesesteak-foil-packs/</link><description>Try these delicious Philly Cheesesteak Foil Packs, a fun new way to enjoy the flavors of the classic Philly Cheesesteak.…</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: Sunscreen has a shelf life and other facts to know</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-sunscreen-has-a-shelf-life-and-other-facts-to-know/</link><description>Did you know sunscreen has a shelf life and can expire? Or that too much heat or cold can ruin a new bottle? Protecting your skin from harmful sun ray...</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 63 Best Movies on Disney+ Right Now (July 2024)</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-movies-disney-plus/</link><description>The Beach Boys, Taylor Swift: The Eras Tour (Taylor’s Version), and Fantastic Mr. Fox are just a few of the movies you should be watching on Disney+ t...</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>First look: Caesars Republic Scottsdale — the iconic brand’s first nongaming hotel</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/first-look-caesars-republic-scottsdale/</link><description>[circuit type=review circuit_id=”20420181899″] If you’ve been to Las Vegas, you probably associate the sound of slot machines with hotels — like the f...</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 23:00:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>American Flag Swimwear Guess Who!</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/04/american-flag-swimwear-guess-who/</link><description>Would ya take a good look at these spirited stars who've slipped into their finest American Flag swimsuits?! It's bikini babes galore and they are HOT...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 03:18:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Saudi Arabia cuts Asia oil prices for second straight month</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/saudi-arabia-cuts-oil-prices-for-asia-for-second-straight-month-7e03512c?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Looking at other importing regions, the oil producer instead increased its August prices for all grades for customers in northwest Europe and the Medi...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 07:33:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tri Tip Marinade</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/tri-tip-marinade/</link><description>This tasty tri tip marinade is the best way to infuse your tri-tip steak with delicious flavor and make it…</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>4 essential food safety tips for summertime gatherings</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/7-4-4-essential-food-safety-tips-for-summertime-gatherings/</link><description>Summer is a season of outdoor gatherings, barbecues and picnics, where food is often at the center of the festivities. However, the warm weather also ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spain’s exposure to climate change helps Madrid-based VC Seaya close €300M climate tech fund</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/04/spains-exposure-to-climate-change-helps-madrid-based-vc-seaya-close-e300m-climate-tech-fund/</link><description>According to a recent Dealroom report on the Spanish tech ecosystem, the combined enterprise value of Spanish startups surpassed €100 billion in 2023....</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 17:50:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>6 reasons to get the Citi AAdvantage Executive World Elite Mastercard</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/reviews/6-reasons-to-get-citi-aadvantage-executive-card/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. Citi is a TPG advertising partner. The Citi® / AAdvantage®...</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 22:00:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Genie Bouchard Splits With Longtime Boyfriend Jack Brinkley-Cook</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/04/genie-bouchard-splits-longtime-boyfriend-jack-brinkley-cook-breakup/</link><description>Genie Bouchard is single for the summer ... TMZ Sports has learned the tennis star and her longtime boyfriend, Jack Brinkley-Cook, have broken up. Our...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 03:18:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wall Street Bids Adieu to Its Biggest Bear</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/wall-street-bids-adieu-to-its-biggest-bear-93ed670e?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>JPMorgan’s Marko Kolanovic had a knack for making aggressive calls, but now the analyst is out after missing a roaring bull market.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 23:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Raspberry Fluff Salad</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/raspberry-fluff-salad/</link><description>Fresh and fruity Raspberry Fluff Salad is a sweet and creamy side or dessert with a mix of raspberries, vanilla…</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: A tick to blame for the alpha-gal, meat allergy</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-a-tick-to-blame-for-the-alpha-gal-meat-allergy/</link><description>You may have heard about alpha-gal syndrome also known as the meat allergy illness or tick bite meat allergy. The Centers for Disease Control and Prev...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 17:28:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Forestay, Europe’s newest $220M growth-stage VC fund, will focus on AI</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/04/forestay-europes-newest-220m-growth-stage-vc-fund-will-focus-on-ai/</link><description>Forestay, an emerging VC based out of Geneva, Switzerland, has been busy. This week it closed its second fund, Forestay Capital II, at a hard cap of $...</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 16:29:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to earn points with the Choice Privileges Eat &amp; Earn dining rewards program</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/choice-eat-and-earn-dining-program/</link><description>In 2022, Choice Hotels launched a new dining rewards program called Choice Privileges Eat &amp; Earn. The program lets you earn Choice Privileges points w...</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 21:00:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Marlon Wayans' L.A. Home Burglarized, Brother Keenen Home at the Time</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/04/marlon-wayans-home-burgled-safe-stolen-cash-keenen-ivory-wayans/</link><description>A not-so-funny situation for Marlon Wayans and his famously comedic family -- cops say his L.A.-area crib is the latest target of burglars. Law enforc...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 03:18:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘She told my grandchildren lies about me so they would despise me’: I’m disinheriting my ungrateful daughter. Could she contest my will?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/she-told-my-grandchildren-lies-about-me-so-they-would-despise-me-im-disinheriting-my-ungrateful-and-selfish-daughter-could-she-contest-my-will-15096974?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>“I once complimented my daughter and her partner on a nice plant in their garage and they started laughing, and told me it was marijuana.”</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 23:31:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Strawberry Cream Cheese Pie</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/strawberry-cream-cheese-pie/</link><description>This strawberry cream cheese pie has a smooth, creamy filling topped with sweet strawberries and held together by a crumbly…</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sports Safety Spotlight: Mayo Clinic touts advancements in hip, knee replacement to keep seniors active</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/sports-safety-spotlight-mayo-clinic-touts-advancements-in-hip-knee-replacement-to-keep-seniors-active/</link><description>MANKATO, Minn. ― The summer weather inspires people of all ages to head outside and play sports. For seniors, pickleball has become a popular option, ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 16:36:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best Sleeping Pads for Every Kind of Camping (2024)</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-sleeping-pads/</link><description>Whether you’re snoozing in a campground or schlepping up to an alpine valley, these are the best pads we’ve found for resting your weary bones.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 16:06:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eastern Caribbean vs. Western Caribbean cruises:  Which itinerary will I like more?</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/eastern-vs-western-caribbean-cruise/</link><description>Eastern Caribbean and Western Caribbean cruises might sound similar when you start researching them. Just about wherever you go, you’ll enjoy sunny da...</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 20:00:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shaquille O'Neal Gave 'Hawk Tuah' Girl Advice on How to Navigate Fame</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/04/shaquille-oneal-gave-hawk-tuah-girl-advice-navigate-fame/</link><description>Shaquille O'Neal is giving the "Hawk Tuah" girl some sage advice ... how to navigate her newfound celebrity status. Sources with direct knowledge tell...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 03:18:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Starmer’s Labour Party returns to power in the U.K. for the first time in 14 years: exit poll</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/starmers-labour-party-returns-to-power-in-the-u-k-for-the-first-time-in-14-years-exit-poll-aa3b32f1?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Keir Starmer’s Labour Party has vaulted back to power in the U.K. for the first time in 14 years, according to exit poll data released Thursday.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 23:10:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sherbet Punch</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/sherbet-punch/</link><description>This bright sherbet punch is perfect for serving on any occasion! It has just the right balance of sweetness, zest,…</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tomorrow’s Cure: How a lifetime of exposures impact health – exposome explained</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/tomorrows-cure-how-a-lifetime-of-exposures-impact-health-exposome-explained/</link><description>There is a study of the fascinating interplay between the cumulative effects of external exposures on a person's body and genes. It is called exposomi...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 13:21:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>16 Best Apple 3-in-1 Wireless Chargers for iPhones, AirPods, Apple Watches, Tested and Reviewed (2024)</title><link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-apple-3-in-1-wireless-chargers/</link><description>Keep your iPhone, Apple Watch, and AirPods topped up with these WIRED-tested docking systems.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to snag the best seats on Southwest Airlines</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/best-seats-southwest-airlines-boarding-process/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information. Few airlines command the customer devotion of Southwest Airlines, con...</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 19:00:18 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>