<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 06:50:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Steve Carell's 'Despicable Me 4' Smashes July 4th Weekend Box Office</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/07/despicable-me-4-steve-carell-smash-holiday-fourth-july-box-office/</link><description>Steve Carell might not be able to steal the moon ... but, his new movie's off to such a great start, the producers may be able to buy it when all is s...</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 13:07:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Airline stocks gain as daily travelers top 3 million, exceeding 2019 high</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/airline-stocks-gain-as-daily-travelers-top-3-million-exceeding-2019-high-ed117db8?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>The airline sector traded mostly higher Monday, after data showed there were more travelers at the end of the July 4 weekend than on any day last year...</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 18:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tater Tot Nachos</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/tater-tot-nachos/</link><description>Tater Tot Nachos (Totchos) are made with crispy golden tater tots, topped with seasoned beef, scoops of refried beans, corn,…</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: Misconceptions about how diet affects kidney stones</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-misconceptions-about-how-diet-affects-kidney-stones/</link><description>Kidney stones often have no definite, single cause, although several factors may increase someone's risk. While diet can be one of those factors, ther...</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:58:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TechCrunch Minute: How to protect yourself from AI scams</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/video/techcrunch-minute-how-to-protect-yourself-from-ai-scams/</link><description>You probably like to think of yourself as reasonably sophisticated when it comes to online scams — you’re not opening random email attachments or send...</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Boutique beachfront escape in Mexico: A review of the Mystique Holbox by Royalton</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/reviews/marriott-mystique-holbox-by-royalton/</link><description>[circuit type=review circuit_id=”20420182020″] Mystique Holbox by Royalton, A Tribute Portfolio Resort, is a small, contemporary beachfront resort ove...</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 18:00:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Margot Robbie Reportedly Pregnant with First Child</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/07/margot-robbie-pregnant-first-child-tom-ackerley/</link><description>Margot Robbie's about to give birth to her own little Barbie or Ken ... 'cause the megastar's pregnant according to reports! The actress and her husba...</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 13:07:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>As bitcoin keeps falling, an S&amp;P 500 correction could be close behind</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/as-bitcoin-keeps-falling-an-s-p-500-correction-could-be-close-behind-12b24c6e?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>The recent weakness of bitcoin could signal an imminent correction of the S&amp;P 500 in the summer, as the two assets often trade in tandem.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:56:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Poke Sauce</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/poke-sauce/</link><description>The best Poke Sauce is easy to make with just a handful of simple ingredients! Whether you are using salmon…</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How a different mammogram experience led to lifesaving cancer diagnosis</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/how-a-different-mammogram-experience-led-to-lifesaving-cancer-diagnosis/</link><description>Melissa Neuman dreaded getting mammograms. Her small, dense breasts made the screening exceptionally uncomfortable and painful. So Melissa put off get...</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tembo capitalizes on the database boom and lands new cash to expand</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/08/database-startup-tembo-lands-new-cash-to-expand/</link><description>One of the vendors to benefit from the database boom is Tembo, a startup creating a platform that lets developers deploy different flavors of Postgres...</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:33:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>U.S. Bank Altitude Reserve Visa Infinite Card review: Bonus points on mobile payments</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/reviews/it-pays-to-go-mobile-u-s-bank-altitude-reserve-visa-infinite-card-review/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. U.S. Bank Altitude Reserve Visa Infinite card overview The...</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:00:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Congressman Adam Schiff Says Biden's Age is Keeping Him From Beating Trump</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/07/adam-schiff-congressman-job-biden-donald-trump-age-kamala-harris/</link><description>Congressman Adam Schiff -- a prominent Democrat has added his voice to the growing number questioning Joe Biden's mental fitness. The California congr...</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 13:07:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paramount’s stock falls and bonds rally as company seals buyout deal with Skydance Media</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/paramounts-stock-and-bonds-sell-off-as-company-seals-buyout-deal-with-skydance-media-f52f9ee3?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>“It’s the old ‘buy the rumor, sell the news’ adage,” says a market source.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:51:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Philly Cheesesteak Foil Packs</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/philly-cheesesteak-foil-packs/</link><description>Try these delicious Philly Cheesesteak Foil Packs, a fun new way to enjoy the flavors of the classic Philly Cheesesteak.…</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maximize memory function with a nutrient-rich diet</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/maximize-memory-function-with-a-nutrient-rich-diet/</link><description>Research suggests that the ability to maximize memory function may be related to what you eat. Following an eating plan that provides a healthier sele...</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayfield’s Navin Chaddha is coming to TechCrunch Disrupt 2024</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/08/mayfields-navin-chaddha-is-coming-to-techcrunch-disrupt-2024/</link><description>TechCrunch Disrupt 2024 is set to welcome an impressive lineup of judges for the Startup Battlefield 200 competition, presented this year by Google Cl...</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What not to eat on a cruise</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/what-not-to-eat-cruise/</link><description>Some people consider a cruise vacation one of the most decadent ways to travel. On many cruises, food is practically always available — and most of it...</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 16:30:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Porn Star Jesse Jane Cause of Death Revealed</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/07/porn-star-jesse-jane-cause-death-drug-overdose-fentanyl/</link><description>Porn star Jesse Jane's official cause of death is an overdose ... TMZ has confirmed. TMZ has learned Jesse died of an accidental fentanyl and cocaine ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 13:07:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>S&amp;P 500 rally is ‘unusually strong’ in 2024. Here’s why stocks may keep rising.</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/s-p-500-rally-is-unusually-strong-in-2024-heres-why-stocks-may-keep-rising-4ca64121?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>The U.S. stock market’s rally is facing a test that begins this week with company earnings.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:25:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tri Tip Marinade</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/tri-tip-marinade/</link><description>This tasty tri tip marinade is the best way to infuse your tri-tip steak with delicious flavor and make it…</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In case you missed it: This week’s Top 5 stories on social media</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/in-case-you-missed-it-this-weeks-top-5-stories-on-social-media-18/</link><description>Check out a few of the most popular News Network stories on @mayoclinic social media this past week. IBD Pride Clinic: Belonging while battling bowel ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 17:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Art therapy app Scribble Journey lets you express emotions through doodles</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/08/art-therapy-app-scribble-journey/</link><description>Numerous concerns are weighing on the minds of many, whether it’s current global conflicts, climate change or the precarious state of the economy, it ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 16:49:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Top 5 reasons to get the United Quest Card: Perks galore with a reasonable annual fee</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/reasons-to-get-united-quest-card/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers The United Quest℠ Card was unveiled in 2021, giving United ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 16:00:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Billie Eilish Holds Lit Firework in Bikini for Fourth of July Weekend</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/07/billie-eilish-busty-display-bikini-pic-fourth-of-july/</link><description>Billie Eilish lit up the internet with her recent post ... posting a pic of herself holding a lit firework -- with just a bikini and towel covering he...</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 13:07:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What it’s like to be audited by the bigger, better-funded IRS. ‘They are pushing harder now.’</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/how-the-irs-is-using-a-bigger-budget-and-more-swagger-to-audit-more-rich-taxpayers-they-are-pushing-hard-now-b5f2f3b5?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>The Internal Revenue Service is showing more ‘swagger’ in audits of rich taxpayers, says one lawyer with ultra-wealthy clients</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:24:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Raspberry Fluff Salad</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/raspberry-fluff-salad/</link><description>Fresh and fruity Raspberry Fluff Salad is a sweet and creamy side or dessert with a mix of raspberries, vanilla…</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: Can energy drinks cause heart issues?</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-can-energy-drinks-cause-heart-issues/</link><description>In recent years, there's been a big boost in the beverage industry when it comes to the sale of energy drinks. Classified as dietary supplements, most...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 15:58:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pestle’s app can now save recipes from Reels using on-device AI</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/08/pestles-app-can-now-save-recipes-from-reels-using-on-device-ai/</link><description>Pestle addresses the common problem of finding recipes on the web. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 16:39:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Top tips from a flight attendant to avoid the worst of summer’s travel headaches</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/tips-flight-attendant-summer-travel/</link><description>Editor’s note: This post has been updated with new information. We’re off to a pretty decent start when it comes to flight delays and cancellations — ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:30:55 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>