<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 06:53:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Sexy Stars On Boats ... Feeling A Lil' Nauti!</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/05/sexy-stars-boats-feeling-little-nauti/</link><description>Land Ho! You'll be hopping on board in no time once you cast your eyes on these stars out on the open sea! Celebs never hold back on a boat ... It's n...</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 01:28:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>S&amp;P 500 scores record high as jobs data point to cooling ‘but not collapsing’ economy</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/s-p-500-scores-record-high-as-jobs-data-point-to-cooling-but-not-collapsing-economy-dce2581b?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>The U.S. stock market has extended its summer rally, with the S&amp;P 500 index climbing to yet another record peak Friday as investors weighed the latest...</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 00:47:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Philly Cheesesteak Foil Packs</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/philly-cheesesteak-foil-packs/</link><description>Try these delicious Philly Cheesesteak Foil Packs, a fun new way to enjoy the flavors of the classic Philly Cheesesteak.…</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In case you missed it: This week’s Top 5 stories on social media</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/in-case-you-missed-it-this-weeks-top-5-stories-on-social-media-18/</link><description>Check out a few of the most popular News Network stories on @mayoclinic social media this past week. IBD Pride Clinic: Belonging while battling bowel ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 17:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple approves Epic Games’ marketplace app after initial rejections</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/05/epic-games-calls-out-apple-for-rejecting-its-games-store-in-the-eu/</link><description>After multiple rejections, Apple has approved Fortnite maker Epic Games’ third-party app marketplace for launch in the EU. As now permitted by the EU’...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 23:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deal alert: Points and miles travel deals for July 2024</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/points-and-miles-travel-deals/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. Some of the below offers may be targeted. Citi is a TPG ad...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 23:00:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jake Paul Cops $650k Diamond Chain With New W Body Care Logo</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/05/jake-paul-cops-650k-diamond-chain-new-w-body-care-logo/</link><description>Jake Paul is celebrating the launch of his new W body care line in the flashiest way possible ... by getting a $650k diamond pendant and chain to rep ...</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 01:28:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘This is my big chance to secure my future’: I’m about to inherit $600,000. What should I do with all this lovely cash?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/this-is-my-big-chance-to-secure-my-future-im-about-to-inherit-600-000-what-should-i-do-with-all-this-lovely-cash-39ee7a9b?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>“Should I go for a high-yield account or a money-market for savings? I already have 401(k), IRA, and brokerage accounts, and laddered CDs.”</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 00:41:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tri Tip Marinade</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/tri-tip-marinade/</link><description>This tasty tri tip marinade is the best way to infuse your tri-tip steak with delicious flavor and make it…</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: Can energy drinks cause heart issues?</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-can-energy-drinks-cause-heart-issues/</link><description>In recent years, there's been a big boost in the beverage industry when it comes to the sale of energy drinks. Classified as dietary supplements, most...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 15:58:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OpenAI breach is a reminder that AI companies are treasure troves for hackers</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/05/openai-breach-is-a-reminder-that-ai-companies-are-treasure-troves-for-hackers/</link><description>There’s no need to worry that your secret ChatGPT conversations were obtained in a recently reported breach of OpenAI’s systems. The hack itself, whil...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 21:49:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When travelers should (and shouldn’t) tip hotel staff</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/tipping-hotel-staff-members/</link><description>Editor’s note: This post has been updated with new information. Tipping can be incredibly personal. Some people are willing to hand over cash regardle...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 22:00:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Crazy Town Singer Shifty Shellshock Talked Sobriety Months Before Fatal OD</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/05/crazy-town-singer-shifty-shellshock-seth-binzer-talked-sobriety-before-death-od/</link><description>Late Crazy Town frontman Shifty Shellshock was sober and happy a few months before his accidental drug overdose ... and seemed committed to staying on...</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 01:28:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘I’m watching every last cent’: For July 4, my friend booked an Airbnb on Cape Cod — and said I’m welcome to visit. Should I offer to pay half?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/im-watching-every-last-cent-for-july-4-my-friend-booked-an-airbnb-on-cape-cod-and-said-im-welcome-to-visit-should-i-offer-to-pay-half-07ae98ad?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>“This vacation is already nearly breaking my budget.”</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 00:41:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Raspberry Fluff Salad</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/raspberry-fluff-salad/</link><description>Fresh and fruity Raspberry Fluff Salad is a sweet and creamy side or dessert with a mix of raspberries, vanilla…</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: Sunscreen has a shelf life and other facts to know</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-sunscreen-has-a-shelf-life-and-other-facts-to-know/</link><description>Did you know sunscreen has a shelf life and can expire? Or that too much heat or cold can ruin a new bottle? Protecting your skin from harmful sun ray...</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Space for newcomers, biotech going mainstream, and more</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/05/space-for-newcomers-biotech-going-mainstream-and-more/</link><description>Welcome to Startups Weekly — TechCrunch’s weekly recap of everything you can’t miss from the world of startups. Sign up here to get it in your inbox e...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 21:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Which travel credits are the easiest to redeem?</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/travel-credits-easiest-to-redeem/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. It’s becoming increasingly common these days to see cards ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 21:00:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ex-'Howard Stern Show' Star Elisa Jordana Pleads Guilty To Battery</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/05/howard-stern-show-elisa-jordana-pleads-guilty-battery-mental-health-evaluation-ordered/</link><description>Elisa Jordana's putting her legal troubles behind her ... copping a plea in her battery case... but officials will take a look at her mental health as...</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 01:28:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘Our loyalty isn’t worth anything’: I paid $70 for a seat with more legroom, but two women grabbed similar empty seats for free. Is that fair?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/our-loyalty-isnt-worth-anything-i-paid-70-for-a-seat-with-more-legroom-but-two-women-grabbed-similar-empty-seats-for-free-is-that-fair-753493a4?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>“I wrote to the airline to explain what had happened and asked for a refund of my miles.”</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 00:38:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Strawberry Cream Cheese Pie</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/strawberry-cream-cheese-pie/</link><description>This strawberry cream cheese pie has a smooth, creamy filling topped with sweet strawberries and held together by a crumbly…</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>4 essential food safety tips for summertime gatherings</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/7-4-4-essential-food-safety-tips-for-summertime-gatherings/</link><description>Summer is a season of outdoor gatherings, barbecues and picnics, where food is often at the center of the festivities. However, the warm weather also ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>X plans to more deeply integrate Grok’s AI, app researcher finds</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/05/x-plans-to-more-deeply-integrate-groks-ai-app-researcher-finds/</link><description>Elon Musk’s X is exploring more ways to integrate xAI’s Grok into the social networking app. According to a series of recent discoveries, X is develop...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 20:31:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quick Points: Reserve premium economy seats for the price of a coach seat on select wide-body domestic routes</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/premium-economy-free/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. Although the “Big Three” U.S. carriers operate single-aisl...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 20:00:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Comedian Tony Knight Dead At 54</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/05/comedian-tony-knight-dead-at-54-tree-branch-france/</link><description>Comedian Tony Knight died following a freak accident ... when a large tree branch fell on top of him and several others at a festival in France. Knigh...</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 01:28:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘I’m appalled’: My grandfather co-signed his grandson’s student loan. After my grandfather died, my cousin skipped town. Will the estate have to pay the debt?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/im-appalled-my-grandfather-co-signed-his-grandsons-student-loan-after-my-grandfather-died-my-cousin-skipped-town-will-the-estate-have-to-pay-the-debt-40b78608?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>“The loan is now in default, and I have no idea where this grandson is.”</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 00:37:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sherbet Punch</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/sherbet-punch/</link><description>This bright sherbet punch is perfect for serving on any occasion! It has just the right balance of sweetness, zest,…</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: A tick to blame for the alpha-gal, meat allergy</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-a-tick-to-blame-for-the-alpha-gal-meat-allergy/</link><description>You may have heard about alpha-gal syndrome also known as the meat allergy illness or tick bite meat allergy. The Centers for Disease Control and Prev...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 17:28:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Saturday Night Live’ Writer Alex English Thinks Social Media Ruined the Art of Comedy</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/dial-up-saturday-night-live-alex-english/</link><description>Saturday Night Live writer and veteran stand-up comedian Alex English believes platforms like TikTok have changed the relationship a comic has to thei...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 20:17:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bahamas cruise packing list: What to pack for the islands</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/bahamas-cruise-packing-list/</link><description>Packing for a Bahamas cruise? Toss your swimsuits and tropical attire into your suitcase, and start channeling those relaxing island vibes. Even in wi...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 19:00:55 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>