<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 01:02:12 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Diddy's Ex Yung Miami Says He Never Abused Her During Relationship</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/08/diddy-ex-yung-miami-never-abusive/</link><description>Diddy's ex-girlfriend Yung Miami is speaking up about their relationship for the first time ... and she says he never got physical with her, unlike Ca...</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 16:50:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rocket Lab’s Archimedes engine test ‘a significant catalyst’ for new Neutron rocket, Cantor says</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/rocket-labs-archimedes-engine-test-a-significant-catalyst-for-new-neutron-rocket-cantor-says-33246374?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Rocket Lab reported a 71% second-quarter revenue hike after the market close Thursday. The company also said that it successfully fired its Archimedes engine for the first time. Rocket Lab shares are up 14.6% Friday.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 21:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Meal Plan #14</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/weekly-meal-plan-14/</link><description>I love the recipes in this weekly meal plan! They are packed with flavor and you have options of using…</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Start A Successful Health Coaching Business (Yes, You Can!)</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/4-tips-to-starting-successful-health-coaching-business</link><description>Start your journey helping people make life-changing health shifts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 11:27:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ATM Software Flaws Left Piles of Cash for Anyone Who Knew to Look</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/vss-atm-vulnerabilities-defcon-2024/</link><description>Six vulnerabilities in ATM-maker Diebold Nixdorf’s popular Vynamic Security Suite could have been exploited to control ATMs using “relatively simplistic attacks.”</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 20:37:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Marriott Bonvoy Brilliant American Express Credit Card review: Marriott’s most premium card</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/marriott-bonvoy-brilliant-amex-card-review/</link><description>Editor’s note: This post has been updated with new information and offers. Marriott Bonvoy Brilliant® American Express Card® overview The Marriott Bon...</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 21:00:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Travis Scott Arrested in Paris After Fighting Bodyguard</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/09/travis-scott-arrested-in-paris-after-hotel-fight-with-his-bodyguard-authorities-say/</link><description>Travis Scott has found himself in legal trouble once again ... the rapper was arrested in Paris after fighting his bodyguard in a hotel, TMZ has confi...</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 16:50:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oil prices snap streak of 4 straight losing weeks</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/oil-prices-on-track-to-snap-streak-of-4-straight-losing-weeks-91fa214e?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Worries over the U.S. economic outlook eased and traders braced for potential retaliatory strikes by Iran and its proxies against Israel after the assassination of a top Hamas official in Tehran last week.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 21:38:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chicken Adobo</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/chicken-adobo/</link><description>Chicken Adobo is a tangy, salty, sweet, and spicy Filipino dish. It’s easy to make and requires just a few…</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>No Lie, This Supplement Is Like The Fountain Of Youth For Your Skin</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/how-each-mbg-best-skin-ingredient-benefits-aging-skin</link><description>Do you do your skin care routine morning and night? Great. But there's more you can do. Here's how to approach skin aging from the inside out.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 11:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The X exodus that wasn’t</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/09/the-x-exodus-that-wasnt/</link><description>When digging into the data to determine how large the exodus everyone on Threads is talking about actually is, we oddly came up short. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 20:31:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Hoxton, Chicago review: Come to work and stay to socialize</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/reviews/the-hoxton-chicago/</link><description>Having lived in Chicago for two years, I’ve experienced the Hoxton on multiple occasions — from nights out with my girlfriends at Cabra and Lazy Bird ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 20:00:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Simone Biles and Snoop Dogg Collab to Give Ronald Biles a Birthday Gift</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/09/simone-biles-snoop-dogg-father-dad-birthday-gift-chain-paris-olympics/</link><description>Simone Biles and Snoop Dogg are now collaborating -- but it's not what you may think ... the two just gave SB's dad a very special birthday. The Olymp...</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 16:50:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Steak, dinner and more men: These have been keys to Sweetgreen’s recent growth</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/steak-dinner-and-more-men-these-have-been-keys-to-sweetgreens-recent-growth-910eb0ca?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Sweetgreen’s stock soars as a key sales-growth metric reaches its highest level in two years and new initiatives pay off.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 21:23:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Croissant Bread</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/croissant-bread/</link><description>Croissant Bread is beautiful and fluffy with crispy, flaky layers on the outside. It’s also one of the most delicious…</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In A Financial Pinch? 7 Small Savings Tips That Add Up To Big Savings</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/small-savings-tips-that-add-up-to-big-savings</link><description>Don’t dismiss the power of baby steps, especially when it comes to saving money. Small money moves can add up to big savings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 21:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>19 Best Back-to-School Deals (2024): Backpacks, Chargers, Laptops</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/back-to-school-deals-2024/</link><description>It's time to put away the pool noodles and get those butts back in seats. Save on backpacks, iPads, laptops, and more.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 20:00:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>All about Frontier Airlines’ all-you-can-fly passes for 2024-25</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/all-you-can-fly-frontier-airlines-gowild/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information. Few things get frequent flyers more excited than an all-you-can-fly p...</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 19:30:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wrestling Legend Kevin Sullivan Dead At 74</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/09/kevin-sullivan-dead-74-wrestling-wcw-wwe/</link><description>Wrestling legend Kevin Sullivan -- who was famously one of Hulk Hogan's biggest rivals in the 1990s -- has sadly passed away. The WWE confirmed his de...</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 16:50:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Boeing bondholders get defensive ahead of potential downgrade to junk</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/boeing-bondholders-get-defensive-ahead-of-potential-downgrade-to-junk-2ff5d84e?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Boeing’s bondholders have adopted a defensive trade in the last week of selling certain longer-dated notes and buying other, more recently issued bonds that will pay them more if the aerospace giant’s credit is downgraded.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 21:06:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Boil Corn on the Cob</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/how-to-boil-corn-on-the-cob/</link><description>This is the BEST recipe for how to boil corn on the cob! Fresh summer corn gets boiled in a…</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A 7-Week Plan To Master Pull-Ups (&amp; Why This Move Is A+ For Healthy Aging)</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/how-to-do-your-first-pull-up-7-week-beginner-plan</link><description>Pull-ups are way more than just a flex—they can actively boost longevity and health span.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 13:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Substack now lets anyone publish posts, even if they don’t have a newsletter</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/09/substack-now-lets-anyone-publish-posts-even-if-they-dont-have-a-newsletter/</link><description>Substack is opening up to more users with its recent announcement that anyone can now publish content on its platform without setting up a publication. With the change, Substack is likely looking to attract more types of writers and content creators, not just people who are interested in creating regularly distributed long-form written pieces. While […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 19:59:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cap One the final of the big 4 credit card issuers to increase Global Entry credit to $120</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/global-entry-fee-credit-card-raises/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. Applying for Global Entry is getting more expensive this O...</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 19:00:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Third Suspect Arrested in Vienna Over Taylor Swift Concert Terror Plot</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/09/taylor-swift-third-suspect-arrested-vienna-terror-plot/</link><description>Vienna State Police are moving swiftly to make arrests in the foiled Taylor Swift terrorist plot ... and they just busted a third suspect. The third w...</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 16:50:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elizabeth Warren probes student-loan transfer that tanked borrowers’ credit scores</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/warren-probes-student-loan-transfer-that-tanked-borrowers-credit-scores-1df9bad4?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>The letter to student-loan servicers and credit-reporting agencies is the latest example of scrutiny from the U.S. senator and consumer advocates.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 20:59:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chocolate Cherry Protein Shake</title><link>https://minimalistbaker.com/chocolate-cherry-protein-shake/</link><description>Getting your protein in just got A LOT more delicious, friends! This chocolate cherry protein shake is thick, creamy, chocolaty, perfectly sweet, SO d...</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Creatine Supplements Bad For Your Kidneys? What's Fact vs. Fiction</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/are-creatine-supplements-bad-for-your-kidneys</link><description>Here's what you should know.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 12:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>China’s autonomous vehicle startup WeRide prepares for a US IPO</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/09/chinas-autonomous-vehicle-startup-weride-prepares-for-a-us-ipo/</link><description>WeRide, a Chinese autonomous vehicle company, is officially gearing up for a U.S. public debut, over a year after China started easing its effective ban of foreign IPOs. WeRide registered 1 billion American Depository Receipts (ADRs) at a maximum price of $0.05, with the aggregate offering coming in at $50 million, per a Friday filing […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 19:15:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>United award sale: Fly to Hong Kong for 40K miles</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/deals/united-award-sale/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. United Airlines has been running an award sale all this we...</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 18:30:03 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>