<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 06:59:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Solange Rips Treatment Of Black Woman in U.S. After Sonya Massey Shooting</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/23/solange-sonya-massey-bodycam-police-shooting-outrage-america/</link><description>The fatal police shooting of Sonya Massey has saddened Solange Knowles like many Americans -- and she's making a nuanced point about this being a regu...</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 07:58:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AT&amp;T’s stock rises as earnings bring beats on these two key numbers</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/at-t-earnings-bring-beats-on-these-two-key-numbers-3279e8eb?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>AT&amp;T topped expectations on postpaid phone subscriber growth and free cash flow for the second quarter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 12:49:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Basil Vinaigrette</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/basil-vinaigrette/</link><description>Basil Vinaigrette is a versatile dressing made from a few fresh ingredients. It is bursting with flavor and can be…</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What you need to know about listeria</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/what-you-need-to-know-about-listeria/</link><description>The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention has issued an alert after a listeria outbreak in several states. There have been at least two fatalitie...</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 19:54:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 29 Best Shows on Apple TV+ Right Now (August 2024)</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-apple-tv-plus-shows/</link><description>Sunny, Constellation, and Presumed Innocent are among the best shows on Apple TV+ this month.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Last chance: Buy Hilton Honors points with up to a 100% bonus to make your stay cheaper</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/hilton-buy-points-promo/</link><description>You might be looking to redeem Hilton Honors points for an unforgettable stay at one of the best Hilton hotels in the world or one of the best Hilton ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 21:00:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gov. Wes Moore Says Democrats Will Win Election On Hope, Not Trump Fear</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/23/wes-moore-democrats-keys-election-hope-future-not-prosecuting-donald-trump/</link><description>Gov. Wes Moore says Democrats will hold the White House by selling voters on VP Kamala Harris' vision for the future -- and he explained why prosecuti...</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 07:58:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The lesson from 17 first cuts of the cycle are more sobering for the stock market than it appears</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/the-lesson-from-17-first-cuts-of-the-cycle-are-more-sobering-for-the-stock-market-than-it-appears-57b32b1d?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>The stock market usually goes up after the first cut, but the reason why might not be as helpful this time around.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 12:33:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chocolate Peanut Butter Ice Cream Bars (Vegan)</title><link>https://minimalistbaker.com/chocolate-peanut-butter-ice-cream-bars-vegan/</link><description>Welcome back, friends! We’ve returned to the magical land of chocolate + peanut butter (one of our favorite places). This timeless combo has won the d...</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: Why skipping breakfast can be bad for your heart</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-why-skipping-breakfast-can-be-bad-for-your-heart/</link><description>Some say that breakfast is the most important meal of the day. Is it really? That's up for debate. However, skipping the first meal is not the healthi...</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Silicon Valley Is Coconuts for Kamala Harris</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/silicon-valley-kamala-harris/</link><description>Prominent names in Big Tech are rallying behind Kamala Harris following Joe Biden's exit from the presidential race.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 20:57:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Current credit card transfer bonuses (July): 25% bonus when transferring Citi points to Flying Blue</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/current-transfer-bonuses/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers; some offers may be expired. Citi is a TPG advertising part...</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 20:45:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elon Musk Says 'Woke Mind Virus' Killed His Transgender Child, 'My Son Is Dead'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/23/elon-musk-transgender-daughter-killed-woke-mind-virus/</link><description>Elon Musk says his transgender daughter is dead in his eyes -- saying he feels she was brainwashed by the "woke mind virus." The Tesla chief did an in...</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 07:58:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gen X’s retirement woes may give rise to a generation of ‘silver squatters’</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/gen-xs-retirement-woes-may-give-rise-to-a-generation-of-silver-squatters-70523b8a?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>This generation will need more financial and housing support from family than older generations, study says.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 12:24:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Marry Me Shrimp Pasta</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/marry-me-shrimp-pasta/</link><description>Marry Me Shrimp Pasta dazzles with robust Italian flavors. It’s ready in just 30 minutes, and the creamy sauce, brimming…</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Researchers explore potential for AI to predict patients’ pain management support needs after surgery</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/ai-helps-predict-patient-need-for-opioid-refills-after-surgery/</link><description>A Mayo Clinic study explored the potential of artificial intelligence (AI) to predict a patient's need for additional pain management support after su...</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>There’s Another Chance to See the Northern Lights This Week</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/aurora-northern-lights-visible-summer-usa-europe-july-2024/</link><description>Don’t worry if you missed them in May—due to another geomagnetic storm, the northern lights might again be seen at lower latitudes across the US and E...</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 20:45:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Last chance: Earn a free night plus up to 130,000 bonus points with a new Hilton card</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/hilton-honors-amex-current-offers/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. From low-budget to ultra-luxury, there’s a Hilton property...</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 20:00:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sonya Massey Shooting, Ben Crump Claims Deputy Moved Closer For Better Shot</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/23/sonya-massey-ben-crump-deputy-moved-closer-better-shot/</link><description>The sheriff's deputy who shot and killed Sonya Massey claims he feared she was going to throw a pot of boiling water on him, but based on the horrifyi...</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 07:58:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Google Fails to 'Wow' as AI Bills Mount</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/google-fails-to-wow-as-ai-bills-mount-ef49399d?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>The advertising business faces tough growth comparisons, while AI spending continues to surge.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tropical Smoothie</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/tropical-smoothie/</link><description>This refreshing tropical smoothie is bursting with tropical fruit flavors, making it the perfect treat for a hot day. Sip…</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Back to basketball after seizure surgery</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/back-to-basketball-after-seizure-surgery/</link><description>Study shows advanced imaging, expert review improve diagnosis of encephaloceles The sound of a basketball bouncing, the squeak of shoes on a fast brea...</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 16:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OpenAI-backed legaltech startup Harvey raises $100M</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/23/openai-backed-legaltech-startup-harvey-raises-100m/</link><description>Harvey, a startup building what it describes as an AI-powered “copilot” for lawyers, has raised $100 million in a Series C round led by GV, Google’s c...</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 20:01:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hawaii cruise guide: Best itineraries, planning tips and things to do</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/hawaii-cruise-guide/</link><description>Hawaii and cruising seem like a match made in heaven. You can experience all the beaches, water sports, lush scenic areas and Polynesian culture witho...</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 19:00:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Francis Ngannou Opens Up On 15-Month Old Son's Death, 'What Do You Mean He's Gone?'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/23/francis-ngannou-opens-up-about-death-of-his-15-month-old-son-in-podcast-apperance/</link><description>Francis Ngannou is speaking into a mic for the first time since his 15-month-old son died suddenly back in March ... and his words are nothing short o...</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 07:58:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Xbox Players Are the Credit-Card Industry's Next Big Thing</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/xbox-players-are-the-credit-card-industrys-next-big-thing-a07bc2ae?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>Banks such as Barclays are seeking out customers in the $57 billion-a-year videogame industry.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 11:59:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Grilled Tri-Tip</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/grilled-tri-tip/</link><description>Grilled Tri-Tip is a flavorful, juicy steak that will be the star of your barbecue! It’s marinated in a simple,…</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Caring for your psychological needs as an adolescent or young adult cancer survivor</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/caring-for-your-psychological-needs-as-an-adolescent-or-young-adult-cancer-survivor/</link><description>The burden of cancer is different for everyone, and life stages can play a role in how it affects people. For adolescents and young adults (AYAs) ages...</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Digital banking startup Mercury abruptly shuttered service for startups in Ukraine, Nigeria, other countries</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/23/mercury-bank-fintech-sanctions-ukraine-nigeria/</link><description>Digital banking startup Mercury informed some founders that it is no longer serving customers in certain countries, including Ukraine. © 2024 TechCrun...</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 19:19:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Which card should replace my Amex Platinum? TPG’s top 6 picks</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/cards-to-replace-amex-platinum/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. The Platinum® Card from American Express, offers cardmembe...</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>