<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:17:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Kanye West's Former GF Julia Fox Reveals She's a Lesbian</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/09/julia-fox-lesbian-comes-out-kanye-west-tiktok/</link><description>Julia Fox -- the actress and ex-girlfriend of Kanye West -- just revealed she's a lesbian. Julia appeared Monday in a brief video posted to TikTok to ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 16:53:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Long-term Treasury yields rise for first time in five sessions after Powell expresses need for more ‘good’ inflation data</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/treasury-yields-steady-as-market-prepares-for-powell-testimony-1de667d2?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Yields on U.S. government debt finished modestly higher on Tuesday after Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell indicated that more improvement on inf...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 21:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Make Cheesecake (The Ultimate Guide)</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/how-to-make-cheesecake/</link><description>Cheesecake is my absolute FAVORITE dessert! I have perfected my method and I can’t wait to teach you how to…</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic marks medical milestone with world’s first known successful total larynx transplant performed in a patient with an active cancer as part of a clinical trial</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-marks-medical-milestone-with-worlds-first-known-successful-total-larynx-transplant-performed-in-a-patient-with-an-active-cancer-as-part-of-a-clinical-trial/</link><description>PHOENIX — Mayo Clinic announces a groundbreaking achievement in organ transplantation, offering hope to thousands who have lost their ability to speak...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 13:34:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bumble users can now report profiles that use AI-generated photos</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/09/bumble-reporting-option-ai-generated-profiles/</link><description>Bumble’s new reporting option arrives at a time when, unfortunately, AI-generated photos on dating apps are common © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reser...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 21:07:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deal alert: Fly nonstop to Amsterdam from Boston and New York City from $475</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/deals/amsterdam-netherlands-nonstop/</link><description>Considering a visit to Amsterdam? You should. With its world-class museums and iconic canals, the capital of the Netherlands is (rightfully) one of th...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 21:30:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Hears from The Lord Almighty Courtesy of Jon Stewart</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/09/biden-lord-almighty-jon-stewart-run-for-president/</link><description>President Joe Biden said the only one who could change his mind on running for re-election is The Lord Almighty ... well multiple Lords Almighty have ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 16:53:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oil prices finish lower after Hurricane Beryl leaves energy infrastructure largely unscathed</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/oil-prices-edge-lower-after-beryl-leaves-energy-infrastructure-largely-unscathed-4415a755?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Oil futures lost ground Tuesday, with U.S. benchmark prices settling at their lowest in nearly two weeks after Hurricane Beryl appeared to leave Texas...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 21:41:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Creamy Pesto Sauce (Dairy-Free)</title><link>https://minimalistbaker.com/creamy-pesto-sauce/</link><description>We’re throwing a pesto party, and you’re invited! With all the herby, savory goodness of traditional basil pesto, this CREAMY dairy-free pesto SAUCE i...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Breaking the silence: First known total larynx transplant on a patient with active cancer as part of landmark clinical trial</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/breaking-the-silence-first-known-total-larynx-transplant-on-a-patient-with-active-cancer-as-part-of-landmark-clinical-trial/</link><description>On Feb. 29, Marty Kedian made history by successfully undergoing a groundbreaking surgery at Mayo Clinic that is providing hope to thousands who have ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Talky social app Airchat gets a major overhaul, making it more like an asynchronous Clubhouse</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/09/talky-social-app-airchat-gets-a-major-overhaul-making-it-more-like-an-asynchronous-clubhouse/</link><description>The concept of Airchat is fun, especially if you're someone who loves to send voice memos instead of typing out long paragraphs on your phone keyboard...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 21:03:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The best time to apply for these popular Capital One credit cards based on offer history</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/capital-one-best-welcome-offers/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. If you’re considering applying for a credit card, you’re p...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 21:00:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bobbi Althoff Carried Out of Nashville Bar, Video Shows</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/09/bobbi-althoff-carried-out-nashville-barstool-bar-sean-murphy-bunting/</link><description>6:12 AM PT -- Bobbi Althoff took to her IG story this morning to address the alarming videos and thanked Sean Murphy-Bunting for looking out for her a...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 16:53:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prescription-drug middlemen face more pressure from FTC in new report</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/prescription-drug-middlemen-face-more-pressure-from-ftc-in-new-report-19062651?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>The Federal Trade Commission on Tuesday ramped up the pressure on prescription-drug middlemen who influence the accessibility and affordability of med...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 21:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tater Tot Nachos</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/tater-tot-nachos/</link><description>Tater Tot Nachos (Totchos) are made with crispy golden tater tots, topped with seasoned beef, scoops of refried beans, corn,…</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Preeclampsia’s lingering shadow</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/preeclampsias-lingering-shadow/</link><description>Researchers are searching for a cure for preeclampsia and have just uncovered some biomarkers that may lead to future treatments. The post Preeclampsi...</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 29 Best Movies on Max (aka HBO Max) Right Now (July 2024)</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-movies-hbo-max-right-now/</link><description>Quad Gods, Dune: Part Two, and Chinatown are just a few of the movies you should be watching on Max this month.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>France deal alert: Fly to the French Riviera from $366 round-trip</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/deals/french-riviera-france-beach/</link><description>Few travel destinations have the mystique of the French Riviera. The coastal region is legendary for being a haven for the rich, famous and fabulous a...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 20:30:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Joey Chestnut Devours 200 Boneless Wings In Under 38 Minutes</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/09/joey-chestnut-devours-200-boneless-wings-in-under-38-minutes/</link><description>Joey Chestnut didn't get much of a break following his Fourth of July hot dog feast ... the eating legend spent part of his Monday devouring boneless ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 16:53:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hopes for cooling inflation are stifled by Wall Street’s expectations for Trump 2.0</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/hopes-for-cooling-inflation-are-stifled-by-wall-streets-expectations-for-trump-2-0-baffd6ff?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Just as many investors and traders remain sanguine about the prospects of cooling U.S. inflation when Thursday’s consumer-price index for June comes o...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 21:07:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Poke Sauce</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/poke-sauce/</link><description>The best Poke Sauce is easy to make with just a handful of simple ingredients! Whether you are using salmon…</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: Misconceptions about how diet affects kidney stones</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-misconceptions-about-how-diet-affects-kidney-stones/</link><description>Kidney stones often have no definite, single cause, although several factors may increase someone's risk. While diet can be one of those factors, ther...</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:58:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nike Is Killing the App for Its $350 Self-Tying Sneakers</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/nike-kills-adapt-bb-app-self-tying-sneaker/</link><description>After August 6, you won't be able to download the app that controls the Adapt BB, and it won't be getting any more updates.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Another new ship? Disney Cruise Line will add a ninth vessel to its fleet in 2029</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/new-disney-cruise-ship-for-2029/</link><description>As if four new ships over the span of four years weren’t enough, Disney Cruise Line announced Tuesday that it plans to launch yet another new cruise s...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 20:15:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Twins' Joe Ryan Caught Powdering Nuts On Camera</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/09/twins-joe-ryan-caught-powdering-nuts-on-camera/</link><description>Minnesota Twins star Joe Ryan's crotch must've been on fire during Monday's game ... 'cause the pitcher couldn't help but douse his balls in baby powd...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 16:53:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>As Hurricane Beryl makes ‘explosive start’ to hurricane season, these disaster-recovery stocks are in the spotlight</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/as-hurricane-beryl-makes-explosive-start-to-hurricane-season-these-disaster-recovery-stocks-are-in-the-spotlight-df99a046?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Hurricane Beryl, which made landfall on the Texas coast Monday, is the first hurricane of what is expected to be an above-normal Atlantic hurricane se...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 20:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Philly Cheesesteak Foil Packs</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/philly-cheesesteak-foil-packs/</link><description>Try these delicious Philly Cheesesteak Foil Packs, a fun new way to enjoy the flavors of the classic Philly Cheesesteak.…</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How a different mammogram experience led to lifesaving cancer diagnosis</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/how-a-different-mammogram-experience-led-to-lifesaving-cancer-diagnosis/</link><description>Melissa Neuman dreaded getting mammograms. Her small, dense breasts made the screening exceptionally uncomfortable and painful. So Melissa put off get...</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The fall of EV startup Fisker: A comprehensive timeline</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/09/the-fall-of-ev-startup-fisker-a-comprehensive-timeline/</link><description>Here is a timeline of the events that led fledgling automaker Fisker to file for bankruptcy. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to redeem your points with the Southwest Rapid Rewards program</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/how-to-redeem-points-southwest-rapid-rewards/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with the latest information. Southwest Airlines is known for its generous ticket change and...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 20:00:08 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>