<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 05:22:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Village People Suing Disney for Allegedly Stiffing, Blackballing 'YMCA' Band</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/25/village-people-suing-disney-not-paying-breach-contract-blackballing-ymca/</link><description>Disney ain't gonna be singing "YMCA" anytime soon -- 'cause the wife of the most famous member of the Village People is taking the entertainment behem...</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 06:19:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘In a worst-case scenario, a stock-market bust could occur’: We are ‘healthy boomers’ in our 60s with a net worth of $4.2 million. Is it time to diversify?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/in-a-worst-case-scenario-a-stock-market-bust-could-occur-we-are-healthy-boomers-in-our-60s-with-a-net-worth-of-4-2-million-is-it-time-to-diversify-6a5c4fad?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>“We have no debt and live comfortably on $150,000 per year.”</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 11:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Easy Apricot Sorbet (No-Churn!)</title><link>https://minimalistbaker.com/easy-apricot-sorbet-no-churn/</link><description>Once upon a time, in the dark streets of San Francisco, a life-changing ice cream cone was enjoyed thanks to Garden Creamery. This apricot sorbet is i...</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: Know your status — the importance of HIV testing</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-know-your-status-the-importance-of-hiv-testing/</link><description>It's not making major news headlines like in the '80s, but HIV remains a significant health concern. About 38 million people are living with HIV, the ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rimac Verne Robotaxi: prices, availability, specs</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/rimacs-super-sleek-robotaxi-has-more-room-than-a-rolls-royce/</link><description>The group's new autonomous ride-hailing service has a 43-inch widescreen, 17-speaker audio system, and five-position reclining seats. But will it beat...</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 11:15:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why the Capital One Venture Rewards credit card still has a spot in our wallets</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/using-capital-one-venture-rewards-card/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information. When my family and I first landed the Capital One Venture Rewards Cre...</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 23:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WWE Hall of Famer Sika Anoa'i, Roman Reigns' Dad, Dead at 79</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/25/wwe-hall-of-famer-sika-anoai-roman-reigns-dad-dead-at-79/</link><description>WWE Hall of Famer Sika Anoa'i, the father of current WWE Superstar Roman Reigns, has died at the age of 79. One of Anoa'i's nephews, Jahrus Anoa'i, an...</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 06:19:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ken Griffin gets apology from IRS over leak of tax records</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/ken-griffin-gets-apology-from-irs-over-leak-of-tax-records-49701f90?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Citadel founder Ken Griffin received a rare public apology from the Internal Revenue Service after his tax records were leaked.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 11:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Use an Air Fryer</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/how-to-use-an-air-fryer/</link><description>The air fryer is one of the most versatile appliances in today’s kitchen! Learn how to use an air fryer…</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ready to Run: Mayo physician and runner suggests ways to beat the heat while running</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/ready-to-run-mayo-physician-and-runner-suggests-ways-to-beat-the-heat-while-running-this-spring/</link><description>MANKATO, Minn. — The heat is on, especially across the South, Southeast, and portions of the plains. The National Weather Service has issued several h...</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 15:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Opera’s browser adds AI-powered image generation and better multimedia controls</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/26/operas-new-version-of-the-browser-gets-better-multimedia-controls-and-ai-powered-image-generation/</link><description>Opera said today it is releasing Opera One’s second version in developer beta with features including new multimedia controls, split tabs, and new AI ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hilton free night reward redemptions: 10 best hotels in the world to use your award certificate</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/best-hilton-free-night-reward-redemptions/</link><description>Hilton Honors members can earn valuable Free Night Reward certificates — worth up to 150,000 points each — through two cobranded credit cards. The Hil...</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 23:00:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paul Mitchell's Son Angus Cause of Death Revealed, Accidental Pool Drowning</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/25/paul-mitchell-son-angus-cause-of-death-revealed-accidental-pool-drowning/</link><description>Paul Mitchell's son's death remains shrouded in mystery -- because even though we now know how he died ... it's still unclear exactly what led up to i...</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 06:19:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Get inspired by actress Christina Ricci’s charming L.A. home, just listed for $2.2 million</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/get-inspired-by-actress-christina-riccis-charming-l-a-home-just-listed-for-2-2-million-12bfd183?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>The serene, four-bedroom, four-bath luxury house is in a private, leafy enclave in the upscale Woodland Hills neighborhood.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Candied Pistachios (4 Ingredients!)</title><link>https://minimalistbaker.com/candied-pistachios/</link><description>Pistachios are good, but candied pistachios?! VERY good. They’re the ultimate sweet, nutty, versatile topping for everything from salads to sorbets (r...</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rain doesn’t have to mean a washout</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/rain-doesnt-have-to-mean-a-washout/</link><description>With all the rain of late, many people may be wondering if it's safe to embrace the weather and indulge in activities like playing or exercising in th...</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 18:09:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>With AI Tools, Scientists Can Crack the Code of Life</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/wired-health-pushmeet-kohli-deepmind-ai-google/</link><description>Google’s AI research lab DeepMind is steadily building knowledge of how genes and their products work inside the body—and how and why they sometimes g...</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Can a cruise ship leave without you?</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/cruise-ship-leave-without-you/</link><description>Let me tell you about the cruise passenger phenomenon of “pier runners.” These are folks who are in a port, enjoying the beach, off shopping or otherw...</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 22:00:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Notebook' Star Gena Rowlands Battling Alzheimer's After Onscreen Portrayal</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/25/notebook-gena-rowlands-battling-alzheimers-onscreen-portrayal-disease/</link><description>Gena Rowlands -- most famous from "The Notebook" -- is sadly battling Alzheimer's disease ... a heartbreaking update after she portrayed a key charact...</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 06:19:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘Freefall’? ‘Staggering losses’? Trump is doing a lot better right now than you might think.</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/freefall-staggering-losses-trump-is-doing-a-lot-better-right-now-than-you-might-think-86f7006d?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>If you’ve been casually following the news lately, you might think Donald Trump has suffered massive financial losses on the stock market since his re...</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 10:51:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zeppole (Italian Donuts)</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/zeppole-recipe/</link><description>Whip up a batch of these delightful zeppole, perfect for a sweet treat anytime! With a light, fluffy texture and…</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: What is hip preservation?</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-what-is-hip-preservation/</link><description>Hip issues are often thought of as an older person's problem. But the truth is, hip issues can be present at birth. While some of these conditions are...</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 16:17:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>EasyTranslate thinks augmenting LLMs with humans will give it an edge over pure AI translation services</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/26/easytranslate-thinks-augmenting-llms-with-humans-will-give-it-an-edge-over-pure-ai-translation-services/</link><description>EasyTranslate is headed in a new direction with a new, generative AI-driven platform that it calls HumanAI. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. Fo...</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Breeze adds 3 Florida routes from Northeast, including new nonstop from Long Island</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/breeze-new-florida-routes/</link><description>Breeze Airways is expanding its footprint in Florida. The Provo, Utah-based low-cost carrier announced three new nonstop routes Tuesday. Each will tou...</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 21:30:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Crazy Town Singer Shifty Shellshock Death Investigated As Possible Overdose</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/25/seth-binzer-crazy-town-singer-shifty-shellshock-death-investigation-possible-overdose-dead-dies/</link><description>Crazy Town frontman Shifty Shellshock's sudden death is under investigation ... and law enforcement sources tell us cops are looking into the possibil...</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 06:19:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deliveroo shares jump on report of DoorDash’s interest in takeover</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/deliveroo-shares-jump-on-report-of-doordashs-interest-in-takeover-d611206c?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>DoorDash reportedly approached Deliveroo last month before negotiations between the two companies broke down over disagreements about valuations</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 10:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>S’mores Crack</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/smores-crack/</link><description>S’mores crack is a quick way to enjoy the classic s’more experience without a campfire. Featuring a buttery graham cracker…</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 02:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Can music help someone with Alzheimer’s disease?</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/consumer-health-can-music-help-someone-with-alzheimers-disease/</link><description>Alzheimer's disease is a progressive disorder that causes brain cells to waste away and die. Alzheimer's disease is the most common cause of dementia,...</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple finally adds support for RCS in latest iOS 18 beta</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/26/apple-finally-adds-support-for-rcs-in-latest-ios-18-beta/</link><description>Apple has finally added support for Rich Communication Services (RCS) to its Messages app. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use on...</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 09:19:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>42 real-world family travel tips that actually work</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/top-family-travel-tips-with-kids/</link><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. Family travel is a whole other ballgame. The strategy, gea...</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 21:00:28 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>