<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 08:10:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The Insurance Industry Is Winning a Fight to Kill New Protections for Retirement Savers</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-insurance-industry-is-winning-a-fight-to-kill-new-protections-for-retirement-savers-54030e41?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>A Labor Department rule is forecast to curb commissions on annuities sharply. The products are sold as a way to convert retirement savings including an IRA into an often-guaranteed income stream that can carry hefty charges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 10:49:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘You’re not stupid enough to have to work in a place like this’: It’s time to give fast-food workers some respect. Could you do what they do?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/youre-not-stupid-enough-to-have-to-work-in-a-place-like-this-its-time-to-give-fast-food-workers-some-respect-could-you-do-what-they-do-b7f719d3?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>A 39-year-old woman in Parma, Ohio was sentenced to two months working in a fast-food restaurant after throwing a hot bowl in a Chipotle worker’s face.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 13:08:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Big Food Would Benefit from Private Ownership</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/big-food-would-benefit-from-private-ownership-11d5e478?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>Mars’s bid for Kellanova highlights the benefits of being out of public view.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 10:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘I fear a storm is coming’: I’m nervous about November’s election and another recession. Should I move my money to cash and gold?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/i-fear-a-storm-is-coming-im-nervous-about-novembers-election-and-another-recession-should-i-move-my-money-to-cash-and-gold-1318be33?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>“I’ve considered parking it all in a location such as Grand Cayman.”</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 13:06:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stocks Claw Back Losses After Global Selloff</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/global-stocks-markets-dow-news-08-06-2024-d73d9786?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>The Dow, S&amp;P 500 and Nasdaq advanced after the Nikkei jumped 10%.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 21:46:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CVS’s stock drops as the healthcare-benefits business continues to hurt profits</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/cvss-stock-drops-after-a-revenue-miss-and-lowered-profit-outlook-amid-challenges-in-health-care-benefits-f7041a28?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>CVS’s CEO said the company is “taking action” to address its challenges, including making leadership changes in some business segments.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:59:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>KKR Founders Sued for Allegedly Getting Giant Payday for No Work</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/kkr-founders-face-suit-alleging-they-got-giant-payday-for-no-work-97ab72d8?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>The lawsuit adds to legal scrutiny of arcane tax deals benefiting private-equity heavyweights.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:42:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Warner Music’s stock rises after profit matches estimates despite small revenue miss</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/warner-musics-stock-gains-after-profit-beat-offsets-small-revenue-miss-ce676e63?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Warner Music Group Corp.’s stock rose 3% premarket Wednesday, after the company matched profit estimates for the second quarter, offsetting a small revenue miss.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:59:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Everyone Needs a 'Digital Death-Cleaning' Plan</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/digital-death-cleaning-plan-f407cf27?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>Nobody wants to leave heirs a confusing collection of files they can’t open, accounts they can’t access and assets they can’t locate.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New York Times says new digital-only subscribers helped profit rise 41%</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/new-york-times-says-new-digital-only-subscribers-helped-profit-rise-41-c05b5e7c?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>News-media provider added 300,000 digital-only subscribers, bringing the number to a total of 10.84 million</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:49:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Google and Apple Can Afford to Play Long Game After Antitrust Ruling</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/google-and-apple-can-afford-to-play-long-game-after-antitrust-ruling-a9427aa7?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>They have a strong common cause to protect the billions of dollars Google pays Apple every year to keep its search engine on the iPhone, though the arrangement is looking a little more dicey.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 14:58:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IHOP parent Dine Brands’ stock falls after revenue miss and lowered sales guidance</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/ihop-parent-dine-brands-stock-up-premarket-as-profit-beat-offsets-small-revenue-miss-438fb67f?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>The parent of Applebee’s and IHOP had a better-than-expected profit in its latest quarter but revenue fell short.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:44:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Volatility Storm Is Buffeting Markets. When Will It Clear?</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/a-volatility-storm-is-buffeting-markets-when-will-it-clear-532e46c5?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>Though much of the stock selloff is likely caused by a reversal in speculative trades, rather than deeper problems, the market won’t immediately go back to normal.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 10:51:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>These sectors thrive in ‘deep recession’ scenario where yields fall and spreads widen, says Citigroup</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/these-sectors-thrive-in-deep-recession-scenario-where-yields-fall-and-spreads-widen-says-citigroup-c374fd2b?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>As recession fears build on Wall Street, Citigroup strategists have put together the sectors that would do best in such an environment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:42:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>China Evergrande Aims to Recover $6 Billion From Executives, Others</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/china-evergrande-aims-to-recover-6-billion-from-executives-others-5bd5620a?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>The heavily indebted Chinese developer said it is seeking to claw back the money from seven individuals, including founder Hui Ka Yan, his ex-wife, a former chief executive and a former chief financial officer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 05:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oil prices lifted as stocks extend bounce and traders eye Middle East tensions</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/oil-prices-lifted-as-stocks-extend-bounce-and-traders-eye-middle-east-tensions-fc9b90d2?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Oil futures rose Wednesday, finding support as the stock market continued its recovery from a global rout that had served to pull down commodity prices.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What to Do With Your Money if You're Worried About the Market</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/stock-market-selloff-portfolio-d47d4c59?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>The standard advice is to do nothing, but there are some exceptions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:49:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shopify’s stock soars as company bucks mixed spending signals with earnings beat</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/shopifys-stock-soars-as-company-bucks-mixed-spending-signals-with-earnings-beat-55261202?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Shopify posted a big beat on free cash flow for the second quarter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is This 1987 All Over Again? What's Driving the Market Meltdown?</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/is-this-1987-all-over-again-whats-driving-the-market-meltdown-4d107126?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>Monday’s wild day in markets showed that nervous investors were overextended.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:13:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>These stocks are likely to soar when the bull market rebounds</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/these-stocks-are-likely-to-soar-when-the-bull-market-rebounds-2dfccf20?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><description>Stocks that lose the most often make a strong recovery once market liquidity returns.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:25:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Unraveling Trades Fuel Global Market Rout</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/global-stocks-markets-dow-news-08-05-2024-35da4a74?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>The unwinding of some of Wall Street’s most popular trades intensified, sending stock indexes sharply lower and walloping tech shares. The Dow industrials fell more than 1,000 points.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 22:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Is the Yen Carry Trade?</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/what-is-the-yen-carry-trade-e5ab9670?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>The unwinding of a popular investment strategy is sending ripples through global markets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 22:26:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Outages Plague Trading Platforms During the Stock-Market Selloff</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/outages-plague-trading-platforms-during-the-stock-market-selloff-9f3b2330?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>Customers at Charles Schwab, Vanguard and Fidelity reported problems logging into accounts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 22:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stocks Are Crashing---That's a Great Reason to Sit Tight</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/stocks-are-crashingthats-a-great-reason-to-sit-tight-c48e5dee?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>There are some genuine concerns at the root of this market selloff. But many other factors seem to be at play too.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 17:31:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Japan's Nikkei Suffers Worst Day Since 1987, Hit by U.S. Concerns</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/japan-stocks-fall-sharply-after-weak-u-s-jobs-data-yen-strengthening-3903689f?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>Japan’s Nikkei Stock Average had its worst day since 1987, falling 12.4% in a frenzy of selling triggered by disappointing economic data in the U.S. and a surge in the Japanese yen.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 11:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Green-Energy Flops Revive Bets on Natural Gas</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/green-energy-flops-revive-bets-on-natural-gas-cb3d42b2?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>European energy giants Shell and BP are sticking to their core business as clean-energy investments make slow progress.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 10:36:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Banks Sweeping Dud Property Loans Under the Rug?</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/are-banks-sweeping-dud-property-loans-under-the-rug-61fd7029?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>New accounting rules should give investors an earlier warning, but surprises are cropping up and there could be more to come.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 10:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2024's Most Popular Trades Are Unraveling</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/2024s-most-popular-trades-are-unraveling-28f1fbef?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>Some on Wall Street worry the Fed waited too long to cut rates.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 09:19:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mars in Advanced Talks to Buy Cheez-It, Eggo Maker Kellanova</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/mars-in-advanced-talks-to-buy-cheez-it-maker-kellanova-44749cda?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>The deal would be one of the largest of the year and could come together imminently.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 02:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stock Funds Are Up 12.6% in 2024</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/stock-funds-up-july-2024-b2bbc46f?mod=rss_markets_main</link><description>It was another positive month for stock funds, but bond funds are drawing big-time cash. Also: A flashback to the 20th anniversary of the Google IPO.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>