<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:25:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>My Word for 2024:  Strong</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2024/05/21/my-word-for-2024-strong/</link><description>Before I begin, know that I fully recognize that it’s May. I selected my word of the year way back in December of 2023. After letting it marinade for ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 05:49:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I've Tried Every Topical &amp; Treatment Out There — Here's What Transformed My Skin</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/how-mindbodgyreens-best-skin-supplement-transformed-my-skin</link><description>If you have any aging skin care concerns, this one's for you.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 12:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In case you missed it: This week’s Top 5 stories on social media</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/in-case-you-missed-it-this-weeks-top-5-stories-on-social-media-15/</link><description>Check out a few of the most popular News Network stories on @mayoclinic social media this past week. Exercise timing conundrum: Optimal workout timing...</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Sound of Freedom</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/10/01/the-sound-of-freedom/</link><description>For a million years (more like 15,) I’ve been listening to a radio show: The Taylor Strecker Show. It’s a daily show that originated on SiriusXM and t...</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 21:26:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Spot Hidden Trauma Responses, From A Psychologist</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/3-ways-to-spot-trauma-stored-in-body-and-mind-from-psychologist</link><description>Trauma manifests in strange ways.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 10:26:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: Improvements in prostate surgery</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-improvements-in-prostate-surgery/</link><description>There will be approximately 299,010 new cases of prostate cancer diagnosed in 2024, according to the American Cancer Society. Treatments vary, includi...</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>That Time I Went to the Eras Tour [Part Two]</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/07/17/that-time-i-went-to-the-eras-tour-part-two/</link><description>To review part one of this adventure with Taylor Swift, click here. Click here to see all the Instagram highlight videos from Denver Night One. Mile H...</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 06:36:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Superfruit Extract Has Major Benefits For Aging Skin*</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/major-skin-care-benefits-of-blood-orange-extract</link><description>When I dug into the emerging research behind the skin care benefits of blood orange extract supplements, I loved what I found.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 10:27:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: Coping with cancer-related fatigue</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-coping-with-cancer-related-fatigue/</link><description>People can experience cancer-related fatigue before, during and after treatments. This is different from the typical tiredness. At times, your arms an...</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 16:09:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>That Time I Went to the Eras Tour [Part One]</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/07/16/that-time-i-went-to-the-eras-tour-part-one/</link><description>Do you ever have one of those experiences where you want to remember exactly how you felt? That’s how I feel about my experience at the Taylor Swift c...</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 05:17:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Want To Lower Your Resting Heart Rate? Get More Of This Nutrient</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/omega-3s-and-resting-heart-rate</link><description>You're likely falling below the recommended intake.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Removing skin cancer with Mohs surgery</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/removing-skin-cancer-with-mohs-surgery/</link><description>Skin cancer is the most common form of cancer. When treated early, it's also the most curable type of cancer. Mohs surgery is one of the most successf...</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 13:58:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jenny Craig Recipe Creation:  Turkey Philly Baguette</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/02/13/jenny-craig-recipe-creation-turkey-philly-baguette/</link><description>Special thanks to Jenny Craig for their sponsorship of this post. In honor of the Super Bowl this year, I decided to make a Philly to enjoy. Knowing t...</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:28:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>3 Easy Steps To Firmer, Smoother-Looking Legs According To A Beauty Editor</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/3-easy-steps-to-firmer-smoother-looking-legs</link><description>It's that time of the year when I start to think more and more about my legs. You too?</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 10:26:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Baseball’s best trade: Former ball player trains to become a cardiologist at Mayo Clinic</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/baseballs-best-trade-former-ball-player-trains-to-become-a-cardiologist-at-mayo-clinic/</link><description>Jimmy Howick, M.D., had embarked on a career as a professional baseball player. When the Houston Astros farm team released him, he went after another ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:30:33 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>