<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 09:40:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Charles Schwab total client assets dip 3% from previous month to $8.85 trillion during tax season</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/charles-schwab-total-client-assets-dip-3-from-previous-month-to-8-85-trillion-during-tax-season-a8a0b654?mod=mw_rss_marketpulse</link><image_url>https://www.marketwatch.com/rss/marketwatch.gif</image_url><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:07:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>White Bean Eggplant Caponata (1 Pan!)</title><link>https://minimalistbaker.com/white-bean-eggplant-caponata/</link><image_url>https://minimalistbaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Have you tried caponata? If not, let us introduce you! It’s a delicious Sicilian eggplant dish with sweet and savory flavor, and we ADORE it! While commonly served as an appetizer or side, it’s worthy of being a main when a little protein and fiber are added in. Introducing: white bean eggplant caponata! Made in 1 pan with just 10 ingredients , this is an effortless, plant-based entrée that pairs well with pasta, polenta, bread, or even mashed potatoes. White Bean Eggplant Caponata (1 Pan!) from Minimalist Baker →</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wood-Fired Pizza Dough</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/wood-fired-pizza-dough/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>This is the perfect beginner’s guide for making wood-fired pizza dough! Pizza expert, Chef Brandon Price, taught me how to…</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zipair economy vs. business class to Japan: Is the budget carrier worth it?</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/reviews/zipair-economy-vs-business-class/</link><image_url>https://thepointsguy.freetls.fastly.net/us/originals/2024/04/ZIPAIR-Economy-Cabin.jpg?fit=1280,960</image_url><description>Like many travelers prevented from visiting during years of coronavirus pandemic-related closures, I had been watching and waiting for a chance to travel to Japan. At long last, my family took the plunge and planned a weeklong trip to Tokyo last month. We scheduled our vacation for my children’s spring break — peak cherry blossom …</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:30:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lisbon’s 8 Top Rooftop Restaurants And Bars</title><link>https://thefoodellers.com/en/rooftop-restaurants-in-lisbon</link><image_url>https://thefoodellers.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/The-ART-INN.png</image_url><description>When you think of Lisbon, it’s hard not to picture the breathtaking views from its numerous hills. And it’s understandable – the city looks incredible from above, and the vistas are too captivating to ignore. Luckily, Lisbon is filled with spots to grab a bite or a drink with a view. That’s why we’ve rounded […] L'articolo Lisbon’s 8 Top Rooftop Restaurants And Bars proviene da The Foodellers .</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 15:19:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 13 Best Hair Dryers (2024): Blow-Dryers, Brushes, and Diffusers</title><link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-hair-dryers/</link><description>We tried blow-dryers, brushes, and a machine that sucks up your locks like a vacuum. These are our top tools to dry your do.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AWS CEO Adam Selipsky steps down</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/14/aws-ceo-adam-selipsky-steps-down/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Adam Selipsky is stepping down from his role as CEO of AWS. Amazon PR confirmed it to TechCrunch. In a memo shared internally by Amazon CEO Andy Jassy and published this morning to Amazon’s company blog, Jassy said that AWS sales chief Matt Garman will be promoted to CEO. Garman previously headed AWS’ EC2 cloud […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:34:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 7-Hour Itch: 3 Women With Eczema Describe the Ways They Combat Nighttime Flare-Ups</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/seven-hour-itch-women-eczema-combat-nighttime-flares?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Three women with eczema describe how they combat nighttime flare-ups.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 09:09:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NASA Visualizes What it Would Be Like to Plunge into a Black Hole – WATCH</title><link>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/nasa-visualizes-what-it-would-be-like-to-plunge-into-a-black-hole-watch/</link><image_url>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/cropped-GNN-Logo-Circles-2017-1-32x32.png</image_url><description>Relying on a supercomputer and the people with talent enough to use it, NASA scientists have produced a video illustration of what it would be like to float into a black hole if you were somehow invincible. Being that within the event horizon of a black hole, the laws of general relativity break down, it’s […] The post NASA Visualizes What it Would Be Like to Plunge into a Black Hole – WATCH appeared first on Good News Network .</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 12:00:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OPEC leaves forecast for demand-growth unchanged</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/opec-leaves-forecast-for-demand-growth-unchanged-127346d9?mod=mw_rss_marketpulse</link><image_url>https://www.marketwatch.com/rss/marketwatch.gif</image_url><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 12:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The BEST Gluten-Free Vanilla Cake (1 Bowl!)</title><link>https://minimalistbaker.com/the-best-gluten-free-vanilla-cake/</link><image_url>https://minimalistbaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Friends, meet the vanilla cake of your DREAMS! It’s super fluffy, perfectly moist, undetectably gluten-free (&amp; dairy-free), and seriously…the BEST. It’s impressive enough for a birthday or even a wedding! Bonus? It’s also SO easy to make, with simple methods, 1 bowl , and 9 ingredients . Preheat your oven. Let them eat cake! This cake could not be easier to make! Simply whisk, pour, bake, and enjoy your cake, for goodness sake! The BEST Gluten-Free Vanilla Cake (1 Bowl!) from Minimalist Baker →</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blueberry Lemon Upside-Down Cake</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/blueberry-lemon-upside-cake/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Be prepared to fall in love with this blueberry lemon upside-down cake! A delicious and moist lemon sponge cake bursting…</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Choosing the right bank as a traveler: Things to know about HSBC Premier checking</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/hsbc-premier-checking/</link><image_url>https://thepointsguy.freetls.fastly.net/us/originals/2021/07/Online-Shopping_martin-dm.jpg?fit=1280,960</image_url><description>When you travel, it’s obviously important to be able to pay for whatever it is you need whenever you need it. Sometimes, that’s going to be with the right credit card. Other times, especially in certain countries, you’ll find yourself in a cash-only situation. It’s important to have not only a good card that doesn’t …</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:00:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>7 Places For Brunch In Lisbon Not Just For Expats Or Tourists</title><link>https://thefoodellers.com/en/brunch-in-lisbon</link><image_url>https://thefoodellers.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Pipe-1024x825.jpg</image_url><description>While brunch might not be a traditional Portuguese meal, Lisbon has embraced this dining trend with open arms, offering various brunch options to suit diverse tastes. The concept of brunch in Lisbon varies, with some establishments serving American-style brunches, while others focus on Portuguese and European culinary traditions for their morning and midday menus. Brunch […] L'articolo 7 Places For Brunch In Lisbon Not Just For Expats Or Tourists proviene da The Foodellers .</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:58:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Movano Evie Ring Review: Running Out of Time</title><link>https://www.wired.com/review/movano-evie-ring/</link><description>For tracking women’s health, the Evie ring is still underbaked. Competitors like Samsung, Oura, and Apple may already have you covered.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>David Sacks reveals Glue, the AI company he’s been teasing on his All In podcast</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/14/david-sacks-glue-ai-slack-microsoft-teams-alternative/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>VC and podcaster David Sacks has revealed a new AI chat app called Glue that fixes "Slack channel fatigue," he says. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Mother’s Love: The Challenges of Parenting a Child With Eczema</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/mothers-love-challenges-parenting-child-eczema?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Two moms reveal the great lengths they went to in their determination to give their children relief and good health.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 09:18:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Good News in History, May 14</title><link>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/events060514/</link><image_url>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/cropped-GNN-Logo-Circles-2017-1-32x32.png</image_url><description>51 years ago today, Skylab was launched into orbit, the first and only space station to be entirely built and funded by the US. Occupied for about 24 weeks between May 1973 and February 1974, it was operated by three separate three-astronaut crews: Skylab 2, Skylab 3, and Skylab 4. Major operations included an orbital […] The post Good News in History, May 14 appeared first on Good News Network .</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Monster Beverage’s stock up 1.4% after company announces Dutch auction tender offer for up to $3 billion of its own stock</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/monster-beverages-stock-up-1-4-after-company-announces-dutch-auction-tender-offer-for-up-to-3-billion-of-its-own-stock-46178f45?mod=mw_rss_marketpulse</link><image_url>https://www.marketwatch.com/rss/marketwatch.gif</image_url><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 13:12:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Frozen Passion Fruit Mezcalita</title><link>https://minimalistbaker.com/frozen-passion-fruit-mezcalita/</link><image_url>https://minimalistbaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>We love a margarita, but a mezcalita? Do tell. A mezcalita has the familiar sweet and tart elements of a margarita, but with the added smoky complexity of mezcal. This frozen version is SO refreshing and bursting with passion fruit for a fun and fruity twist. Bonus? It’s (ridiculously) quick and easy with just 4 ingredients and 5 minutes required. Let us show you how it’s done! Frozen Passion Fruit Mezcalita from Minimalist Baker →</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cinnamon Roll Casserole</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/cinnamon-roll-casserole/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Get ready for a tasty treat with this easy cinnamon roll casserole! Using canned cinnamon rolls, this casserole is so…</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wyndham adds 9 all-inclusive resorts with bargain award redemption rates</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/wyndham-decameron-all-inclusive/</link><image_url>https://thepointsguy.freetls.fastly.net/us/originals/2024/05/Grand-Decameron-Cornwall-Beach-A-Trademark-All-Inclusive-1.png?fit=1280,960</image_url><description>Another day, another wave of all-inclusive resorts taking on major hotel loyalty affiliation. Wyndham Hotels &amp; Resorts continued its all-inclusive resort expansion Tuesday through a new partnership with Decameron All Inclusive Hotels &amp; Resorts, a Latin American all-inclusive resort operator. The partnership kicks off with nine resorts across Mexico, Panama and Jamaica, and it brings …</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 13:05:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Best Portuguese Desserts: 26 Must-Try Truly Local Treats</title><link>https://thefoodellers.com/en/portuguese-desserts</link><image_url>https://thefoodellers.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Queijada-1024x576.jpg</image_url><description>In Portuguese restaurants, one of the most familiar questions you’ll hear is, “Queres uma sobremesa e um café?” – “Do you want a sweet and a coffee?”. This question isn’t just a polite offer but an invitation to discover some of the most unforgettable desserts you’ll ever taste. These treats are so profoundly intertwined with […] L'articolo Best Portuguese Desserts: 26 Must-Try Truly Local Treats proviene da The Foodellers .</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 16:25:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tornado Cash Developer Found Guilty of Laundering $1.2 Billion of Crypto</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/tornado-cash-developer-found-guilty-of-laundering-crypto/</link><description>Alexey Pertsev, cofounder of the crypto-anonymizing tool, has been sentenced to more than five years behind bars.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 13:34:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>After surpassing $100M in ARR, Harness Labs grabs a $150M line of credit</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/14/after-surpassing-100m-in-arr-harness-labs-grabs-a-150m-line-of-credit/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Harness Lab isn’t founder Jyoti Bansal’s first startup. He sold AppDynamics to Cisco for $3.7 billion in 2017, the week it was supposed to go public. His latest venture has raised $425 million, per Crunchbase. On Tuesday, Harness announced $150 million in debt financing, essentially a line of credit that the company can draw on […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Working It Out: How to Minimize Eczema Flare-ups at the Gym and on the Job</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/minimize-eczema-flare-ups-gym-job?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Three keys to managing your eczema at the gym and then heading off to a productive and itch-free workday.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 07:30:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Town Saves the Threatened Bum-Breathing Punk Turtle–a 9lb Wonder Found Only in the Mary River</title><link>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/town-saves-the-threatened-bum-breathing-punk-turtle-a-9lb-wonder-found-only-in-the-mary-river/</link><image_url>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/cropped-GNN-Logo-Circles-2017-1-32x32.png</image_url><description>Australia is filled with wild and wonderful critters, but few surpass the novelty of the Mary River turtle—which was once one of the continent’s most endangered. Now however, the dedication of 800 residents in the town of Tiaro is seeing the turtle repopulate the river from which it draws its name, a point of pride […] The post Town Saves the Threatened Bum-Breathing Punk Turtle–a 9lb Wonder Found Only in the Mary River appeared first on Good News Network .</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 19:00:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cigna’s stock jumps 2.7% after earnings beat estimates and company raises guidance</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/cignas-stock-jumps-2-7-after-earnings-beat-estimates-and-company-raises-guidance-88cc8d33?mod=mw_rss_marketpulse</link><image_url>https://www.marketwatch.com/rss/marketwatch.gif</image_url><description></description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:14:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Simple Sun-Dried Tomato Hummus</title><link>https://minimalistbaker.com/simple-sun-dried-tomato-hummus/</link><image_url>https://minimalistbaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>If you love hummus and the rich flavor of tomatoes, you’ll ADORE this simple sun-dried tomato hummus. It’s SO versatile, creamy, easy to make, and adds instant flavor to just about everything. Enjoy it on pita, veggies, crackers, sandwiches, and more. It’s perfect for parties, picnics, meal prep, road trips, and everything in between! Just 15 minutes and a food processor or blender required. Let’s make hummus! This recipe is adapted from the Simple Sun-Dried Tomato Hummus in our cookbook! Simple Sun-Dried Tomato Hummus from Minimalist Baker →</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Thai Chicken Salad</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/thai-chicken-salad/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Crunchy and bright, this Thai Chicken Salad with creamy peanut dressing is bursting with flavor, texture and deliciousness! Prep it in…</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Holland America’s latest epic cruise is an Aussie lover’s dream</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/holland-america-grand-australia-cruise/</link><image_url>https://thepointsguy.freetls.fastly.net/us/originals/2023/05/HOLLAND-AMERICA-LINE-EXTERIOR_ZAANDAM.jpg?fit=1280,960</image_url><description>Looking for an easy and affordable way to see large swaths of Australia, New Zealand and the South Pacific in a single trip? Holland America is out with an epic new itinerary that will allow for just that. The only catch: You’ll need to set aside three months to do it. The “Grand Australia and …</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 13:00:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>40 Traditional Portuguese Foods To Eat While in Portugal</title><link>https://thefoodellers.com/en/traditional-portuguese-foods</link><image_url>https://thefoodellers.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/pasteis-1024x693.jpg</image_url><description>While maybe not as renowned as its Spanish neighbor, Portuguese cuisine offers a rich culinary experience. Many tourists primarily associate Portugal with pastel de nata and bacalhau, yet there’s much more to savor beyond these iconic dishes, which are undeniably essential. Having moved to Lisbon, we were acquainted with Portuguese cuisine but were unprepared for […] L'articolo 40 Traditional Portuguese Foods To Eat While in Portugal proviene da The Foodellers .</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 12:27:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Generative AI Is Totally Shameless. I Want to Be It</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/generative-ai-totally-shameless/</link><description>The best thing about brain-melting software like ChatGPT? It doesn’t feel remorse.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Waymo’s robotaxis under investigation after crashes and traffic mishaps</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/14/waymo-safety-probe-nhtsa-crashes-traffic-cones-construction/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The company's autonomous vehicles have had a number of misadventures lately, involving driving into construction sites. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 12:00:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cows Are Potential Spreaders of Bird Flu to Humans</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/food-recipes/food-poisoning/news/20240510/cows-are-potential-spreaders-bird-flu-humans?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Cow udders have the same receptors for flu viruses as humans and birds, raising concerns that cows could become “mixing vessels” that help the bird flu virus spread between people.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 19:36:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Teen Boy Translating Ancient Texts Turned a 4,000-Year-old Scribe From Egypt into Advice for Modern Age</title><link>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/teen-boy-translating-ancient-texts-turned-a-4000-year-old-scribe-from-egypt-into-advice-for-modern-age/</link><image_url>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/cropped-GNN-Logo-Circles-2017-1-32x32.png</image_url><description>Michael Hoffen is a new author, and like him, the protagonist of his book is a teenager. But there’s quite an age gap between them—about 4,000 years. That’s because Hoffen brought to life the story of a young Egyptian from ancient times named Pepi, whose father, Kheti, is intent on getting his son a job […] The post Teen Boy Translating Ancient Texts Turned a 4,000-Year-old Scribe From Egypt into Advice for Modern Age appeared first on Good News Network .</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 17:00:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dropbox says cybersecurity incident is unlikely to have a material impact on operations</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/dropbox-says-cybersecurity-incident-is-unlikely-to-have-a-material-impact-on-operations-eefac625?mod=mw_rss_marketpulse</link><image_url>https://www.marketwatch.com/rss/marketwatch.gif</image_url><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 22:58:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Meal Plan #4</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/weekly-menu-plan-4/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Take advantage of this weekly meal plan that has all the favorite recipes that families love! It is so easy…</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rakuten deal alert: Earn 15% to 20% cash back at major retailers when shopping online</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/bonus-rakuten-rewards/</link><image_url>https://thepointsguy.freetls.fastly.net/us/originals/2023/02/GettyImages-1346500027.jpg?fit=1280,960</image_url><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. If you’re looking to make some purchases before your summer travel plans, there’s a big online shopping event this week to maximize your spending. Plus, you can use these promotions to score some big deals and stack up the savings. Rakuten is …</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 22:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Travel Insurance Is Your Key To An Enjoyable Trip</title><link>https://thefoodellers.com/en/travel-insurance</link><image_url>https://thefoodellers.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Veru-Temple1-1024x768.jpg</image_url><description>It’s no secret that when we travel, we are at risk. From simple diseases (hello, food poisoning) to more serious accidents, the moment we step away from familiar places puts us at risk. That’s why having travel insurance is savage, regardless of whether you are going to use it or not: I think we’ve used […] L'articolo Why Travel Insurance Is Your Key To An Enjoyable Trip proviene da The Foodellers .</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:50:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>There’s Nothing Revolutionary About ‘Morning After the Revolution’</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/morning-after-the-revolution-nellie-bowles-book/</link><description>Former New York Times tech reporter and media entrepreneur Nellie Bowles’ book Morning After the Revolution bills itself as a bold contrarian missive but serves up lukewarm dogma.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sona, a frontline workforce management platform, raises $27.5M with eyes on US expansion</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/14/sona-a-frontline-workforce-management-platform-raises-27-5m-with-eyes-on-us-expansion/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Sona, a workforce management platform for frontline employees, has raised $27.5 million in a Series A round of funding. More than two-thirds of the U.S. workforce are reportedly in frontline jobs, which might be anything from customer service and healthcare to retail environments and hospitality. But managing this vast workforce, ensuring roles are filled and […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Age-Related Macular Degeneration: Putting a Hole in Our World</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/eye-health/news/20240510/age-related-macular-degeneration-putting-hole-our-world?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Estimates show that by 2040, age-related macular degeneration may affect nearly 300 million people worldwide. And we are very limited in our ability to treat or prevent it. Here's what to know.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 19:31:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Queensland Declared Drought Free for First Time in Decade: Colors Have Blossomed Out of the Brown</title><link>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/queensland-declared-drought-free-for-first-time-in-decade-colors-have-blossomed-out-of-the-brown/</link><image_url>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/cropped-GNN-Logo-Circles-2017-1-32x32.png</image_url><description>Incredible rains in Australia’s Queensland have turned the typical red of the outback soil into lush green terrain crisscrossed by swollen rivers, ending a decade-long drought. At its height, the drought affected 88% of the state. But after Diamantina and Bulloo shires had their drought status changed, it means the number has fallen to zero. […] The post Queensland Declared Drought Free for First Time in Decade: Colors Have Blossomed Out of the Brown appeared first on Good News Network .</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 16:00:57 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>