<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 06:59:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Business inventories drop 0.1% in March</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/business-inventories-drop-0-1-in-march-bc9aae3a?mod=mw_rss_marketpulse</link><image_url>https://www.marketwatch.com/rss/marketwatch.gif</image_url><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 15:13:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>White Bean Eggplant Caponata (1 Pan!)</title><link>https://minimalistbaker.com/white-bean-eggplant-caponata/</link><image_url>https://minimalistbaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Have you tried caponata? If not, let us introduce you! It’s a delicious Sicilian eggplant dish with sweet and savory flavor, and we ADORE it! While commonly served as an appetizer or side, it’s worthy of being a main when a little protein and fiber are added in. Introducing: white bean eggplant caponata! Made in 1 pan with just 10 ingredients , this is an effortless, plant-based entrée that pairs well with pasta, polenta, bread, or even mashed potatoes. White Bean Eggplant Caponata (1 Pan!) from Minimalist Baker →</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Easy Grilled Bourbon Chicken</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/grilled-bourbon-chicken/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>One bite of this grilled bourbon chicken and your tastebuds will be dancing with delight! It’s marinated in a flavorful…</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why I love the Amex Business Platinum’s Pay with Points perk</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/favorite-perk-amex-business-platinums-pay-with-points/</link><image_url>https://thepointsguy.freetls.fastly.net/us/originals/2020/01/ANA_777_New_Business_Class_The_Room_Zach_Griff_ZGriff-41.jpg?fit=1280,960</image_url><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. The Business Platinum Card® from American Express offers frequent travelers several ways to add elements of luxury to their travel plans. From flight discounts to hotel elite status and a comprehensive airport lounge access benefit, the Amex Business Platinum Card delivers unparalleled travel …</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 23:00:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lisbon’s 8 Top Rooftop Restaurants And Bars</title><link>https://thefoodellers.com/en/rooftop-restaurants-in-lisbon</link><image_url>https://thefoodellers.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/The-ART-INN.png</image_url><description>When you think of Lisbon, it’s hard not to picture the breathtaking views from its numerous hills. And it’s understandable – the city looks incredible from above, and the vistas are too captivating to ignore. Luckily, Lisbon is filled with spots to grab a bite or a drink with a view. That’s why we’ve rounded […] L'articolo Lisbon’s 8 Top Rooftop Restaurants And Bars proviene da The Foodellers .</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 15:19:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maven Is a New Social Network That Eliminates Followers—and Hopefully Stress</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/maven-social-network-that-eliminates-followers-and-stress/</link><description>Twitter cofounder Ev Williams is backing a new social network called Maven, which trades likes and follows for algorithms designed to foster serendipity and deep discussion.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>EU opens child safety probes of Facebook and Instagram, citing addictive design concerns</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/16/eu-opens-child-safety-probes-of-facebook-and-instagram-citing-addictive-design-concerns/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Facebook and Instagram are under formal investigation in the European Union over child protection concerns, the Commission announced Thursday. The proceedings follow a raft of requests for information to parent entity Meta since the bloc’s online governance regime, the Digital Services Act (DSA), started applying on it last August. The development could be significant as […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 11:35:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Personal Shopper: A Savvy Black Entrepreneur Guides You to Eczema-Friendly Clothes, Creams, Cosmetics, and More</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/savvy-black-entrepreneur-guides-eczema-friendly-clothes-creams-cosmetics?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>A savvy black entrepreneur guides you on an eczema-friendly shopping spree.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:54:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Good News in History, May 16</title><link>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/events060516/</link><image_url>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/cropped-GNN-Logo-Circles-2017-1-32x32.png</image_url><description>306 years ago today, Maria Agnesei was born in Milan. She is the first woman in the Western World ever to be appointed as a professor of mathematics at a university. She is credited with writing the first book discussing both differential and integral calculus. Her name is remembered most often today through her mathematical […] The post Good News in History, May 16 appeared first on Good News Network .</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OPEC leaves forecast for demand-growth unchanged</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/opec-leaves-forecast-for-demand-growth-unchanged-127346d9?mod=mw_rss_marketpulse</link><image_url>https://www.marketwatch.com/rss/marketwatch.gif</image_url><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 12:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The BEST Gluten-Free Vanilla Cake (1 Bowl!)</title><link>https://minimalistbaker.com/the-best-gluten-free-vanilla-cake/</link><image_url>https://minimalistbaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Friends, meet the vanilla cake of your DREAMS! It’s super fluffy, perfectly moist, undetectably gluten-free (&amp; dairy-free), and seriously…the BEST. It’s impressive enough for a birthday or even a wedding! Bonus? It’s also SO easy to make, with simple methods, 1 bowl , and 9 ingredients . Preheat your oven. Let them eat cake! This cake could not be easier to make! Simply whisk, pour, bake, and enjoy your cake, for goodness sake! The BEST Gluten-Free Vanilla Cake (1 Bowl!) from Minimalist Baker →</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wood-Fired Pizza Dough</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/wood-fired-pizza-dough/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>This is the perfect beginner’s guide for making wood-fired pizza dough! Pizza expert, Chef Brandon Price, taught me how to…</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How TPG’s points and miles experts maximize Chase Ultimate Rewards points</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/expert-chase-ultimate-rewards-redemptions/</link><image_url>https://thepointsguy.freetls.fastly.net/us/originals/2023/07/Best-September-2023_Vienna-Austria_CHUNYIP-WONG.jpg?fit=1280,960</image_url><description>There’s never been a better time to consider applying for one of the Chase Sapphire cards. Both cards are currently offering elevated welcome bonuses — the highest we have seen on these two popular cards in over a year. The Chase Sapphire Preferred® Card currently offers 75,000 bonus Ultimate Rewards points after you spend $4,000 on …</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 22:30:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>7 Places For Brunch In Lisbon Not Just For Expats Or Tourists</title><link>https://thefoodellers.com/en/brunch-in-lisbon</link><image_url>https://thefoodellers.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Pipe-1024x825.jpg</image_url><description>While brunch might not be a traditional Portuguese meal, Lisbon has embraced this dining trend with open arms, offering various brunch options to suit diverse tastes. The concept of brunch in Lisbon varies, with some establishments serving American-style brunches, while others focus on Portuguese and European culinary traditions for their morning and midday menus. Brunch […] L'articolo 7 Places For Brunch In Lisbon Not Just For Expats Or Tourists proviene da The Foodellers .</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:58:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>11 Best All-Clad Cookware Deals Right Now (Spring 2024)</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/all-clad-deals/</link><description>All-Clad makes some of the best—and priciest—cookware you can buy. These discounts will help you invest for less.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 00:14:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Forget EVs: Why Bedrock Materials is targeting gas-powered cars for its first sodium-ion batteries</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/16/forget-evs-why-bedrock-materials-is-targeting-gas-powered-cars-for-its-first-sodium-ion-batteries/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Bedrock Materials is developing a new type of sodium-ion battery, which promises to be dramatically cheaper than lithium-ion. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Behind the Spike in Colorectal Cancer Among Young Americans</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/colorectal-cancer/news/20240515/behind-the-spike-in-colorectal-cancer-cases?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Colorectal cancer cases increased a whopping 333% among 15- to 19-year-olds and 185% among 20- to 24-year-olds from 1999 to 2020.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:59:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Experimental Cancer Treatment Gives New Jersey Mom a Chance for A Second Baby: ‘I decided to go for it’</title><link>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/experimental-cancer-treatment-gives-new-jersey-mom-a-chance-for-a-second-baby-i-decided-to-go-for-it/</link><image_url>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/cropped-GNN-Logo-Circles-2017-1-32x32.png</image_url><description>After less than a year of treatment with an experimental new cancer drug, a young woman has seen her tumor vanish, along with her fears that she would never be able to carry another child. It should have been the happiest days of Kelly Spill’s life, until shortly after she delivered her first baby […] The post Experimental Cancer Treatment Gives New Jersey Mom a Chance for A Second Baby: ‘I decided to go for it’ appeared first on Good News Network .</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 19:30:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Monster Beverage’s stock up 1.4% after company announces Dutch auction tender offer for up to $3 billion of its own stock</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/monster-beverages-stock-up-1-4-after-company-announces-dutch-auction-tender-offer-for-up-to-3-billion-of-its-own-stock-46178f45?mod=mw_rss_marketpulse</link><image_url>https://www.marketwatch.com/rss/marketwatch.gif</image_url><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 13:12:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Frozen Passion Fruit Mezcalita</title><link>https://minimalistbaker.com/frozen-passion-fruit-mezcalita/</link><image_url>https://minimalistbaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>We love a margarita, but a mezcalita? Do tell. A mezcalita has the familiar sweet and tart elements of a margarita, but with the added smoky complexity of mezcal. This frozen version is SO refreshing and bursting with passion fruit for a fun and fruity twist. Bonus? It’s (ridiculously) quick and easy with just 4 ingredients and 5 minutes required. Let us show you how it’s done! Frozen Passion Fruit Mezcalita from Minimalist Baker →</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blueberry Lemon Upside-Down Cake</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/blueberry-lemon-upside-cake/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Be prepared to fall in love with this blueberry lemon upside-down cake! A delicious and moist lemon sponge cake bursting…</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>11 best hotels for nightlife — from popular nightclubs to swanky lounges</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/hotel-nightclubs-lounges-speakeasy/</link><image_url>https://thepointsguy.freetls.fastly.net/us/originals/2024/04/Golden-Hour_3-Credit_-Michael-Kleinberg.jpg?fit=1280,960</image_url><description>Sometimes you want to go to a hotel to rest and relax. Sometimes a hotel is just where you end up after a long day of traveling or for some conference for work. And then sometimes you go to a hotel for the nightlife — or, at least, you a pick a hotel wherever you’re …</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 22:00:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Best Portuguese Desserts: 26 Must-Try Truly Local Treats</title><link>https://thefoodellers.com/en/portuguese-desserts</link><image_url>https://thefoodellers.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Queijada-1024x576.jpg</image_url><description>In Portuguese restaurants, one of the most familiar questions you’ll hear is, “Queres uma sobremesa e um café?” – “Do you want a sweet and a coffee?”. This question isn’t just a polite offer but an invitation to discover some of the most unforgettable desserts you’ll ever taste. These treats are so profoundly intertwined with […] L'articolo Best Portuguese Desserts: 26 Must-Try Truly Local Treats proviene da The Foodellers .</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 16:25:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The US Election Threats Are Clear. What to Do About Them Is Anything But</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/election-threats-senate-hearing-ai-disinformation-deepfakes/</link><description>A Senate Intelligence Committee hearing today saw broad agreement on how AI and other threats loom ahead of the US election—and uncertainty about how to respond.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 00:05:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Thoma Bravo’s LogRhythm merges with Exabeam in more cybersecurity consolidation</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/16/thoma-bravos-logrhythm-merges-with-exabeam-in-more-cybersecurity-consolidation/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Private equity giant Thoma Bravo has announced that its security information and event management (SIEM) company LogRhythm will be merging with Exabeam, a rival cybersecurity company backed by the likes of Cisco and Lightspeed Venture Partners. SIEM is the business of using real-time data gleaned from servers, network devices, and applications to flag abnormal activity […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 11:19:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Build a Support Network for Schizophrenia Care</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/schizophrenia/features/choose-schizophrenia-care-team?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Schizophrenia caregiver support is essential to avoid burnout. Learn how to build a support network when you're a mental-health caregiver.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 14:20:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>11 Acres of Plant-infused Green Roofs Go ‘Blue’–Capturing Rainwater in Flood-Prone Amsterdam</title><link>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/11-acres-of-plant-infused-green-roofs-go-blue-capturing-rainwater-in-flood-prone-amsterdam/</link><image_url>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/cropped-GNN-Logo-Circles-2017-1-32x32.png</image_url><description>Amsterdam’s roofs have just been converted into a giant sponge that will make the city more climate resilient. The Dutch have always been famous for their ability to control water, born out of the necessity of their homeland, much of which is below sea level. Now, their expert water management skills are transforming the city […] The post 11 Acres of Plant-infused Green Roofs Go ‘Blue’–Capturing Rainwater in Flood-Prone Amsterdam appeared first on Good News Network .</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 16:00:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cigna’s stock jumps 2.7% after earnings beat estimates and company raises guidance</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/cignas-stock-jumps-2-7-after-earnings-beat-estimates-and-company-raises-guidance-88cc8d33?mod=mw_rss_marketpulse</link><image_url>https://www.marketwatch.com/rss/marketwatch.gif</image_url><description></description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:14:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Simple Sun-Dried Tomato Hummus</title><link>https://minimalistbaker.com/simple-sun-dried-tomato-hummus/</link><image_url>https://minimalistbaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>If you love hummus and the rich flavor of tomatoes, you’ll ADORE this simple sun-dried tomato hummus. It’s SO versatile, creamy, easy to make, and adds instant flavor to just about everything. Enjoy it on pita, veggies, crackers, sandwiches, and more. It’s perfect for parties, picnics, meal prep, road trips, and everything in between! Just 15 minutes and a food processor or blender required. Let’s make hummus! This recipe is adapted from the Simple Sun-Dried Tomato Hummus in our cookbook! Simple Sun-Dried Tomato Hummus from Minimalist Baker →</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cinnamon Roll Casserole</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/cinnamon-roll-casserole/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Get ready for a tasty treat with this easy cinnamon roll casserole! Using canned cinnamon rolls, this casserole is so…</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>9 things to do when you get the Amex Business Platinum Card</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/things-to-do-amex-business-platinum/</link><image_url>https://thepointsguy.freetls.fastly.net/us/originals/2021/09/20210927_Marriott-Le-Meridien_KGenter_walk-9.jpg?fit=1280,960</image_url><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. The Business Platinum Card® from American Express is unquestionably the best premium business card, thanks to its slew of perks and ability to earn flexible, valuable Membership Rewards points. You can earn an elevated 150,000 Membership Rewards points after spending $20,000 …</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 21:30:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>40 Traditional Portuguese Foods To Eat While in Portugal</title><link>https://thefoodellers.com/en/traditional-portuguese-foods</link><image_url>https://thefoodellers.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/pasteis-1024x693.jpg</image_url><description>While maybe not as renowned as its Spanish neighbor, Portuguese cuisine offers a rich culinary experience. Many tourists primarily associate Portugal with pastel de nata and bacalhau, yet there’s much more to savor beyond these iconic dishes, which are undeniably essential. Having moved to Lisbon, we were acquainted with Portuguese cuisine but were unprepared for […] L'articolo 40 Traditional Portuguese Foods To Eat While in Portugal proviene da The Foodellers .</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 12:27:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Best iPad to Buy (and Some to Avoid) in 2024</title><link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/the-best-ipad/</link><description>New iPads are here. We break down Apple’s current lineup to help you figure out which one of Apple's tablets is best for you.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 21:17:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Temu accused of breaching EU’s DSA in bundle of consumer complaints</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/15/temu-accused-of-breaching-eus-dsa-in-bundle-of-consumer-complaints/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Consumer protection groups around the European Union have filed coordinated complaints against Temu, accusing the Chinese-owned ultra low-cost e-commerce platform of a raft of breaches related to the bloc’s Digital Services Act (DSA). Temu only launched in the region about a year ago but recently reported blasting past 75 million monthly users. Penalties for confirmed […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 05:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Helping Someone Stick With Schizophrenia Treatment</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/schizophrenia/features/stay-on-schizophrenia-meds?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Schizophrenia treatment is tricky when your loved one resists it. Learn ways to help someone with schizophrenia stick with their treatment plan.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 14:20:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Diligent Planning Sees Teen Accepted into 231 Schools, Winning $14.7 Million in Scholarships</title><link>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/diligent-planning-sees-teen-accepted-into-231-schools-winning-14-7-million-in-scholarships/</link><image_url>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/cropped-GNN-Logo-Circles-2017-1-32x32.png</image_url><description>Maddison Crowell always knew she wanted to go to university, and her parents were all on board making it happen. Throughout her later high school years, they would regularly send admission applications to various schools, some nearer to their home in Liberty County, Georgia, some much farther away. When it came time to make the […] The post Diligent Planning Sees Teen Accepted into 231 Schools, Winning $14.7 Million in Scholarships appeared first on Good News Network .</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 14:00:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dropbox says cybersecurity incident is unlikely to have a material impact on operations</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/dropbox-says-cybersecurity-incident-is-unlikely-to-have-a-material-impact-on-operations-eefac625?mod=mw_rss_marketpulse</link><image_url>https://www.marketwatch.com/rss/marketwatch.gif</image_url><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 22:58:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Thai Chicken Salad</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/thai-chicken-salad/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Crunchy and bright, this Thai Chicken Salad with creamy peanut dressing is bursting with flavor, texture and deliciousness! Prep it in…</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why points and miles are a bad long-term investment</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/points-and-miles-bad-investment/</link><image_url>https://thepointsguy.freetls.fastly.net/us/originals/2023/12/Person-managing-home-finances-with-computer-and-smart-phone-calculator_hobo_018.jpg?fit=1280,960</image_url><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information. It’s easy to think of points and miles as a variant of Monopoly money. To some, they’re easy to throw around and spend nonchalantly; they can almost seem ethereal. To others, travel rewards can be easy to hoard. They are a form of currency, …</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 21:00:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Travel Insurance Is Your Key To An Enjoyable Trip</title><link>https://thefoodellers.com/en/travel-insurance</link><image_url>https://thefoodellers.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Veru-Temple1-1024x768.jpg</image_url><description>It’s no secret that when we travel, we are at risk. From simple diseases (hello, food poisoning) to more serious accidents, the moment we step away from familiar places puts us at risk. That’s why having travel insurance is savage, regardless of whether you are going to use it or not: I think we’ve used […] L'articolo Why Travel Insurance Is Your Key To An Enjoyable Trip proviene da The Foodellers .</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:50:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prepare to Get Manipulated by Emotionally Expressive Chatbots</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/prepare-to-get-manipulated-by-emotionally-expressive-chatbots/</link><description>The emotional mimicry of OpenAI’s new version of ChatGPT could lead AI assistants in some strange—even dangerous—directions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 20:56:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Google I/O 2024: Here’s everything Google just announced</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/15/google-i-o-2024-everything-announced-so-far/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Here are quick hits of the biggest news from the keynote as they are announced. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 23:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is It Time to Change Schizophrenia Treatments?</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/schizophrenia/features/caregiver-treatment-changes-schizophrenia?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Is it time for a change in your loved one's schizophrenia treatment? Learn the signs caregivers should watch for.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 14:20:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘Old age’ Starts Later Than Ever in the Eye of the Beholder and Beholden, Study Reveals</title><link>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/old-age-starts-later-than-ever-study-reveals/</link><image_url>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/cropped-GNN-Logo-Circles-2017-1-32x32.png</image_url><description>Middle-aged and older adults believe that old age begins later in life than their peers did decades ago according to a new study. It’s enough to put a bit of spring chicken back into the feet of a silver fox, and the study found that people tended to view being old as occurring later and […] The post ‘Old age’ Starts Later Than Ever in the Eye of the Beholder and Beholden, Study Reveals appeared first on Good News Network .</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 13:00:12 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>