<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 07:48:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Business inventories drop 0.1% in March</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/business-inventories-drop-0-1-in-march-bc9aae3a?mod=mw_rss_marketpulse</link><image_url>https://www.marketwatch.com/rss/marketwatch.gif</image_url><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 15:13:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>White Bean Eggplant Caponata (1 Pan!)</title><link>https://minimalistbaker.com/white-bean-eggplant-caponata/</link><image_url>https://minimalistbaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Have you tried caponata? If not, let us introduce you! It’s a delicious Sicilian eggplant dish with sweet and savory flavor, and we ADORE it! While commonly served as an appetizer or side, it’s worthy of being a main when a little protein and fiber are added in. Introducing: white bean eggplant caponata! Made in 1 pan with just 10 ingredients , this is an effortless, plant-based entrée that pairs well with pasta, polenta, bread, or even mashed potatoes. White Bean Eggplant Caponata (1 Pan!) from Minimalist Baker →</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best Swedish Meatballs</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/the-best-swedish-meatballs/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>These Swedish Meatballs are smothered in the most amazing rich and creamy gravy and packed with such delicious flavor. You…</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Act fast: Lie-flat business class to Europe as low as 45,00 miles each way</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/aer-lingus-business-class-miles/</link><image_url>https://thepointsguy.freetls.fastly.net/us/originals/2023/04/Planes-Zach-Griff1-1.jpg?fit=1280,960</image_url><description>It’s been a good week for business-class deal hunters. We saw incredible Air France Flying Blue business-class award space earlier this week and then stumbled upon first-class flights to Hawaii as low as 40,000 each way. But right now, you can fly up to four people to Europe in lie-flat business class as low as …</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 04:06:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lisbon’s 8 Top Rooftop Restaurants And Bars</title><link>https://thefoodellers.com/en/rooftop-restaurants-in-lisbon</link><image_url>https://thefoodellers.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/The-ART-INN.png</image_url><description>When you think of Lisbon, it’s hard not to picture the breathtaking views from its numerous hills. And it’s understandable – the city looks incredible from above, and the vistas are too captivating to ignore. Luckily, Lisbon is filled with spots to grab a bite or a drink with a view. That’s why we’ve rounded […] L'articolo Lisbon’s 8 Top Rooftop Restaurants And Bars proviene da The Foodellers .</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 15:19:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>25 Best REI Anniversary Sale Deals: Fitness Trackers, Tents, Sleeping Bags, Outdoor Apparel</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/rei-anniversary-sale-may-2024/</link><description>It’s the best time of the year to pick up all the tents, stoves, sleeping bags, and gear that you’ll need for summer fun.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A US Trustee wants troubled fintech Synapse to be liquidated via Chapter 7 bankruptcy, cites ‘gross mismanagement’</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/16/a-us-trustee-wants-troubled-fintech-synapse-to-be-liquidated-via-chapter-7-bankruptcy-cites-gross-mismanagement/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The prospects for troubled banking-as-a-service startup Synapse have gone from bad to worse this week after a United States Trustee filed an emergency motion on Wednesday. The trustee is asking to convert the company’s debt reorganization Chapter 11 bankruptcy into a liquidation Chapter 7, according to court documents. The trustee wrote that the need for […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:01:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Federal Experts Talk Bird Flu ‘What Ifs’ in WebMD Live Event</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/cold-and-flu/news/20240516/federal-experts-talk-bird-flu-what-ifs?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>WebMD brought together experts from four federal agencies to talk prevention, monitoring, and what the “what ifs” of bird flu might look like.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:50:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Good News in History, May 17</title><link>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/events060517/</link><image_url>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/cropped-GNN-Logo-Circles-2017-1-32x32.png</image_url><description>124 years ago today, L. Frank Baum’s first children’s novel The Wonderful Wizard of Oz was published in the US. The first edition was printed and bound by Baum himself for presentation to his sister, Mary Louise Baum Brewster. The first 10,000 copies sold out fast, and by 1938 over a million were sold. Telling the story […] The post Good News in History, May 17 appeared first on Good News Network .</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OPEC leaves forecast for demand-growth unchanged</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/opec-leaves-forecast-for-demand-growth-unchanged-127346d9?mod=mw_rss_marketpulse</link><image_url>https://www.marketwatch.com/rss/marketwatch.gif</image_url><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 12:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The BEST Gluten-Free Vanilla Cake (1 Bowl!)</title><link>https://minimalistbaker.com/the-best-gluten-free-vanilla-cake/</link><image_url>https://minimalistbaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Friends, meet the vanilla cake of your DREAMS! It’s super fluffy, perfectly moist, undetectably gluten-free (&amp; dairy-free), and seriously…the BEST. It’s impressive enough for a birthday or even a wedding! Bonus? It’s also SO easy to make, with simple methods, 1 bowl , and 9 ingredients . Preheat your oven. Let them eat cake! This cake could not be easier to make! Simply whisk, pour, bake, and enjoy your cake, for goodness sake! The BEST Gluten-Free Vanilla Cake (1 Bowl!) from Minimalist Baker →</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>No Bake Snickers Bar Pie</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/no-bake-snickers-bar-pie/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>No Bake Snickers Bar Pie is one of the easiest and most delicious no bake pies that you make. You…</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deal alert: Fly to Spain from Chicago, Miami and Washington, DC, from $371 round-trip</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/deals/spain-fare-sale-chicago-miami/</link><image_url>https://thepointsguy.freetls.fastly.net/us/originals/2022/04/GettyImages-Tenerife-beach.jpg?fit=1280,960</image_url><description>The deals for European travel keep coming. We’ve just been tipped off to a big sale on flights to a number of popular destinations in Spain, including Alicante, Barcelona, Bilbao, Madrid and Tenerife in the Canary Islands. Departure cities include Chicago, Houston, Miami, Newark and Washington, D.C. This sale’s travel window involves flights between September …</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 23:00:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>7 Places For Brunch In Lisbon Not Just For Expats Or Tourists</title><link>https://thefoodellers.com/en/brunch-in-lisbon</link><image_url>https://thefoodellers.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Pipe-1024x825.jpg</image_url><description>While brunch might not be a traditional Portuguese meal, Lisbon has embraced this dining trend with open arms, offering various brunch options to suit diverse tastes. The concept of brunch in Lisbon varies, with some establishments serving American-style brunches, while others focus on Portuguese and European culinary traditions for their morning and midday menus. Brunch […] L'articolo 7 Places For Brunch In Lisbon Not Just For Expats Or Tourists proviene da The Foodellers .</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:58:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Netflix Isn’t About Flicks Anymore</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/netflix-isnt-about-flicks-anymore/</link><description>And it's not just Netflix—Max, Disney+, and even YouTube are also turning their attention to series, sports, and shorts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seraphim’s latest space accelerator welcomes nine companies</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/16/seraphims-latest-space-accelerator-welcomes-nine-companies/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>U.K.-based Seraphim Space is spinning up its 13th accelerator program, with nine participating companies working on a range of tech from propulsion to in-space manufacturing and space situational awareness. The intense 12-week program is designed to get seed and Series A companies “investment ready,” the firm says, by providing specialist mentorship, networking opportunities and intensive […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 23:33:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What’s Next in Health Care for Older Adults: Questions and Answers With John Whyte, MD</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/blog-aging-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>As WebMD’s chief medical officer, John Whyte, MD, is in a unique position to see both the current state of medical care for America’s older adults and the way things are trending for the future. We asked him to share his insight on a few topics, along with a bit of advice.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:29:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Majestic Sei Whales Reappear in Argentine Waters After Nearly A Century</title><link>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/majestic-sei-whales-reappear-in-argentine-waters-after-nearly-a-century/</link><image_url>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/cropped-GNN-Logo-Circles-2017-1-32x32.png</image_url><description>GNN has reported several times over the last three years about large baleen whales returning to waters in which they haven’t been sighted for decades. Now again, news from Argentina shows that the benefits of the 1946 International Convention for the Regulation of Whaling are still compounding, with sei whales returning to the South American […] The post Majestic Sei Whales Reappear in Argentine Waters After Nearly A Century appeared first on Good News Network .</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 19:01:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Monster Beverage’s stock up 1.4% after company announces Dutch auction tender offer for up to $3 billion of its own stock</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/monster-beverages-stock-up-1-4-after-company-announces-dutch-auction-tender-offer-for-up-to-3-billion-of-its-own-stock-46178f45?mod=mw_rss_marketpulse</link><image_url>https://www.marketwatch.com/rss/marketwatch.gif</image_url><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 13:12:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Frozen Passion Fruit Mezcalita</title><link>https://minimalistbaker.com/frozen-passion-fruit-mezcalita/</link><image_url>https://minimalistbaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>We love a margarita, but a mezcalita? Do tell. A mezcalita has the familiar sweet and tart elements of a margarita, but with the added smoky complexity of mezcal. This frozen version is SO refreshing and bursting with passion fruit for a fun and fruity twist. Bonus? It’s (ridiculously) quick and easy with just 4 ingredients and 5 minutes required. Let us show you how it’s done! Frozen Passion Fruit Mezcalita from Minimalist Baker →</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Easy Grilled Bourbon Chicken</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/grilled-bourbon-chicken/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>One bite of this grilled bourbon chicken and your tastebuds will be dancing with delight! It’s marinated in a flavorful…</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>United cuts 2 Australia, New Zealand routes, tapping brakes on rapid Pacific growth</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/news/united-cuts-two-pacific-routes/</link><image_url>https://thepointsguy.freetls.fastly.net/us/originals/2024/03/Planes-Newark-Savannah-2.jpg?fit=1280,960</image_url><description>United Airlines is pulling back slightly on what’s been an ambitious expansion across the Pacific Ocean. The Chicago-based carrier plans to suspend its nonstop, seasonal service from Los Angeles to two destinations in Australia and New Zealand during the Northern Hemisphere’s winter, a spokesperson told TPG Thursday. As part of the network adjustment, United will …</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:30:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Best Portuguese Desserts: 26 Must-Try Truly Local Treats</title><link>https://thefoodellers.com/en/portuguese-desserts</link><image_url>https://thefoodellers.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Queijada-1024x576.jpg</image_url><description>In Portuguese restaurants, one of the most familiar questions you’ll hear is, “Queres uma sobremesa e um café?” – “Do you want a sweet and a coffee?”. This question isn’t just a polite offer but an invitation to discover some of the most unforgettable desserts you’ll ever taste. These treats are so profoundly intertwined with […] L'articolo Best Portuguese Desserts: 26 Must-Try Truly Local Treats proviene da The Foodellers .</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 16:25:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 11 Best Early Memorial Day 2024 Mattress Deals</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-mattress-deals/</link><description>Sleep starting to feel less like a luxury? It might be time for a new mattress, and they’re often discounted.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OpenAI inks deal to train AI on Reddit data</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/16/openai-inks-deal-to-train-ai-on-reddit-data/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>OpenAI has reached a deal with Reddit to use the social news site’s data for training AI models. In a blog post on OpenAI’s press relations site, the company said that the Reddit partnership will provide it access to “real-time, structured and unique content” — e.g. posts and replies — from Reddit, allowing its tools […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 23:04:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Get the Care You Need in a COVID-19 World</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/covid-senior-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>What to expect at the doctor’s office, hospitals, and long-term care facilities, the future of telemedicine, and how to get the best care during COVID-19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 19:50:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>13-year-old Successfully Undergoes World-First Treatment to Cure Rarer-Than-Rare Wild Syndrome</title><link>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/13-year-old-successfully-undergoes-world-first-treatment-to-cure-rarer-than-rare-wild-syndrome/</link><image_url>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/cropped-GNN-Logo-Circles-2017-1-32x32.png</image_url><description>The girl, pictured here third from right, is the first in world history to successfully undergo liver surgery for Wild Syndrome, a condition so rare it’s only been documented 21 times. After what seemed like an eternity in the hospital for 13-year-old Kai Xue and her mother Ning Chen, during which they traveled all over […] The post 13-year-old Successfully Undergoes World-First Treatment to Cure Rarer-Than-Rare Wild Syndrome appeared first on Good News Network .</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 16:00:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cigna’s stock jumps 2.7% after earnings beat estimates and company raises guidance</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/cignas-stock-jumps-2-7-after-earnings-beat-estimates-and-company-raises-guidance-88cc8d33?mod=mw_rss_marketpulse</link><image_url>https://www.marketwatch.com/rss/marketwatch.gif</image_url><description></description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:14:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Simple Sun-Dried Tomato Hummus</title><link>https://minimalistbaker.com/simple-sun-dried-tomato-hummus/</link><image_url>https://minimalistbaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>If you love hummus and the rich flavor of tomatoes, you’ll ADORE this simple sun-dried tomato hummus. It’s SO versatile, creamy, easy to make, and adds instant flavor to just about everything. Enjoy it on pita, veggies, crackers, sandwiches, and more. It’s perfect for parties, picnics, meal prep, road trips, and everything in between! Just 15 minutes and a food processor or blender required. Let’s make hummus! This recipe is adapted from the Simple Sun-Dried Tomato Hummus in our cookbook! Simple Sun-Dried Tomato Hummus from Minimalist Baker →</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wood-Fired Pizza Dough</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/wood-fired-pizza-dough/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>This is the perfect beginner’s guide for making wood-fired pizza dough! Pizza expert, Chef Brandon Price, taught me how to…</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to redeem Chase Ultimate Rewards points for maximum value</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/redeeming-chase-ultimate-rewards-maximum-value/</link><image_url>https://thepointsguy.freetls.fastly.net/us/originals/2023/11/Aerial-view-of-Easwt-End-St.-Jogn-US-Virgin-Islands_cdwheatley.jpg?fit=1280,960</image_url><description>You can never have too many Chase Ultimate Rewards points. This transferable points currency gives you access to some of the best hotel and airline transfer partners in the business, as well as the easy-to-use Chase Travel℠ portal, which allows you to cover a wide variety of different costs for your trip, including car rentals, …</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:00:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>40 Traditional Portuguese Foods To Eat While in Portugal</title><link>https://thefoodellers.com/en/traditional-portuguese-foods</link><image_url>https://thefoodellers.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/pasteis-1024x693.jpg</image_url><description>While maybe not as renowned as its Spanish neighbor, Portuguese cuisine offers a rich culinary experience. Many tourists primarily associate Portugal with pastel de nata and bacalhau, yet there’s much more to savor beyond these iconic dishes, which are undeniably essential. Having moved to Lisbon, we were acquainted with Portuguese cuisine but were unprepared for […] L'articolo 40 Traditional Portuguese Foods To Eat While in Portugal proviene da The Foodellers .</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 12:27:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amazon Is Hosting a Massive Book Sale</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/amazon-book-sale-spring-2024/</link><description>Ebooks, paperbacks, and hardcover editions are deeply discounted through May 20.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:56:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>X pushes more users to Communities</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/16/x-pushes-more-users-to-communities/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>X users will now be able to discover posts from new Communities that are trending directly from an Explore tab within the section. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:50:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Personal Shopper: A Savvy Black Entrepreneur Guides You to Eczema-Friendly Clothes, Creams, Cosmetics, and More</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/savvy-black-entrepreneur-guides-eczema-friendly-clothes-creams-cosmetics?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>A savvy black entrepreneur guides you on an eczema-friendly shopping spree.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:54:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Expert Believes He Has Solved Archaeological Mystery Surrounding Ancient Assyrian Symbols</title><link>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/expert-believes-he-has-solved-archaeological-mystery-surrounding-ancient-assyrian-symbol/</link><image_url>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/cropped-GNN-Logo-Circles-2017-1-32x32.png</image_url><description>An Assyriologist from Ireland believes he has discovered the meaning behind a series of symbols always presented together on the walls of the ancient Assyrian city of King Sargon II. His belief is that rather than being simple motifs or allegorical pieces, they were a way to imprint Sargon’s name in the stars themselves through […] The post Expert Believes He Has Solved Archaeological Mystery Surrounding Ancient Assyrian Symbols appeared first on Good News Network .</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 12:00:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dropbox says cybersecurity incident is unlikely to have a material impact on operations</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/dropbox-says-cybersecurity-incident-is-unlikely-to-have-a-material-impact-on-operations-eefac625?mod=mw_rss_marketpulse</link><image_url>https://www.marketwatch.com/rss/marketwatch.gif</image_url><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 22:58:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blueberry Lemon Upside-Down Cake</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/blueberry-lemon-upside-cake/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Be prepared to fall in love with this blueberry lemon upside-down cake! A delicious and moist lemon sponge cake bursting…</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>6 reasons why the Chase Sapphire Preferred is the perfect card for the average traveler</title><link>https://thepointsguy.com/guide/5-reasons-csp-best-card-average-traveler/</link><image_url>https://thepointsguy.freetls.fastly.net/us/originals/2023/05/Family-walking-through-airport-with-luggage_miniseries.jpg?fit=1280,960</image_url><description>Editor’s note: This is a recurring post, regularly updated with new information and offers. At TPG, we love the Chase Sapphire Preferred® Card. It was the first travel rewards credit card for many of us and remains one of the cards we can’t live without. We love that it earns versatile Chase Ultimate Rewards points …</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 21:30:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Travel Insurance Is Your Key To An Enjoyable Trip</title><link>https://thefoodellers.com/en/travel-insurance</link><image_url>https://thefoodellers.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Veru-Temple1-1024x768.jpg</image_url><description>It’s no secret that when we travel, we are at risk. From simple diseases (hello, food poisoning) to more serious accidents, the moment we step away from familiar places puts us at risk. That’s why having travel insurance is savage, regardless of whether you are going to use it or not: I think we’ve used […] L'articolo Why Travel Insurance Is Your Key To An Enjoyable Trip proviene da The Foodellers .</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 18:50:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Google’s AI Overviews Work, and How to Turn Them Off (You Can’t)</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/google-ai-overviews-how-to-use-how-to-turn-off/</link><description>Google’s new Gemini-powered search experience is rolling out to users in the US. Here’s some advice on how to navigate it. And if you want to turn AI Overviews off, too bad.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:42:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mark Zuckerberg’s makeover: Midlife crisis or carefully crafted rebrand?</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/16/mark-zuckerbergs-makeover-midlife-crisis-or-carefully-crafted-rebrand/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>For Mark Zuckerberg’s 40th birthday, his wife got him a photoshoot. Zuckerberg gives the camera a sly smile as he sits amid a carefully crafted re-creation of his childhood bedroom. It’s appropriately childish — a lava lamp, a participation trophy, a white stuffed dog — yet the surroundings foreshadow the culture-shifting, technological force Zuckerberg would […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 19:58:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Behind the Spike in Colorectal Cancer Among Young Americans</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/colorectal-cancer/news/20240515/behind-the-spike-in-colorectal-cancer-cases?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Colorectal cancer cases increased a whopping 333% among 15- to 19-year-olds and 185% among 20- to 24-year-olds from 1999 to 2020.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:59:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Good News in History, May 16</title><link>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/events060516/</link><image_url>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/cropped-GNN-Logo-Circles-2017-1-32x32.png</image_url><description>306 years ago today, Maria Agnesei was born in Milan. She is the first woman in the Western World ever to be appointed as a professor of mathematics at a university. She is credited with writing the first book discussing both differential and integral calculus. Her name is remembered most often today through her mathematical […] The post Good News in History, May 16 appeared first on Good News Network .</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>