<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 13:48:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>A Flaw in Windows Update Opens the Door to Zombie Exploits</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/windows-update-downdate-exploit/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent3.png</image_url><description>A researcher found a vulnerability that would let hackers strategically downgrade a target’s Windows version to reexpose patched vulnerabilities. Microsoft is working on fixes for the issue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 18:20:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Facebook creators have a new way to avoid ‘jail’</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/07/facebook-creators-have-a-new-way-to-avoid-jail/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent2.png</image_url><description>Facebook creators are being given a new option that will help them avoid jail — “Facebook jail,” that is — upon their first violation, and at various times after. In a revised policy, announced on Wednesday, social networking giant Meta said that creators who violate the company’s Community Standards for the first time will be […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 18:15:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>X Is Boosting the Far Right’s UK Riots as Telegram Scrambles for Control</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/telegram-is-blocking-the-far-right-from-boosting-the-uk-riots-x-is-emboldening-them/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent.png</image_url><description>Far-right protesters are trying to share violent rhetoric on social media. For the first time, Telegram is blocking them—while X is giving them a platform.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:43:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A comprehensive list of 2024 tech layoffs</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/07/tech-layoffs-2024-list/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent.png</image_url><description>The tech layoff wave is still going strong in 2024. Following significant workforce reductions in 2022 and 2023, this year has already seen 60,000 job cuts across 254 companies, according to independent layoffs tracker Layoffs.fyi. Companies like Tesla, Amazon, Google, TikTok, Snap and Microsoft have conducted sizable layoffs in the first months of 2024. Smaller-sized […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 18:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wildflower’s iPhone Cases Are Perfect for the Very Clumsy</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/wildflower-iphone-case-rave/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent3.png</image_url><description>Say goodbye to shattered displays, dreadful screen protectors, and worn-out phone cases.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 14:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Week in AI: OpenAI’s talent retention woes</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/07/this-week-in-ai-openais-talent-retention-woes/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent3.png</image_url><description>Hiya, folks, welcome to TechCrunch’s regular AI newsletter. This week in AI, OpenAI lost another co-founder. John Schulman, who played a pivotal role in the development of ChatGPT, OpenAI’s AI-powered chatbot platform, has left the company for rival Anthropic. Schulman announced the news on X, saying that his decision stemmed from a desire to deepen […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 18:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NBC’s Olympics Broadcast Isn’t Just Addictive. It’s a New Era of Streaming</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/nbc-peacock-2024-summer-olympics-coverage/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent3.png</image_url><description>With a big assist from Peacock, the 2024 Summer Olympics broadcast is fragmented in all the right ways.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nothing’s $399 Phone 2a Plus hits the US through a beta program</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/07/nothings-399-phone-2a-plus-hits-the-us-through-a-beta-program/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent3.png</image_url><description>As has been the case with Nothing's other handsets, there are a few hoops required to purchase the device in the U.S. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 18:03:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elon Musk Has Turned X Into His Personal Political Playground</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/musk-trump-support-x/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent2.png</image_url><description>Elon Musk accused Twitter’s leadership of tipping the scales politically. But now he’s doing just that with X.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mechanical Orchard, led by ex-Pivotal CEO, scores $50M round led by Alphabet’s GV</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/07/mechanical-orchard-led-by-ex-pivotal-ceo-scores-50-million-round-led-by-alphabets-gv/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent3.png</image_url><description>Digital transformation — the process of transforming outdated apps and processes with cloud technologies and digital workflows — can be a risky undertaking. In 2023, Harvard Business Review reported that while 89% of large companies have a digital and AI transformation underway, they’ve only captured 31% of the expected revenue uplift and 25% of anticipated […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 17:43:55 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>