<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 01:01:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Google Researchers Found Nearly a Dozen Flaws in Popular Qualcomm Software for Mobile GPUs</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/google-android-red-team-qualcomm-gpu-flaws/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>The vulnerabilities, which have been patched, may have novel appeal to attackers as an avenue to compromising phones.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 23:55:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Student raised security concerns in Mobile Guardian MDM weeks before cyberattack</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/09/student-raised-security-concerns-in-mobile-guardian-mdm-weeks-before-cyberattack/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>This is the second cyberattack targeting the school device management service Mobile Guardian this year. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 02:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The FDA Just Rejected a Bid for MDMA’s Approval to Treat PTSD</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/fda-rejects-mdma-ptsd-treatment/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>The agency has asked drugmaker Lykos Therapeutics to run an additional study on the use of the psychedelic drug in patients with post-traumatic stress disorder, pushing back its next proposal by years.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 23:50:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Smartwatches shipments see sharp decline in India</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/09/smartwatches-shipments-see-sharp-decline-in-india/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>India's wearable market declined in Q2, primarily because smartwatch are not attracting consumers. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Noah Lyles’ Olympic Run Is the New Normal for Living With Covid</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/noah-lyles-covid-olympics-new-normal/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Dozens of Olympic athletes competed with Covid as society increasingly treats it like the flu or the common cold. Public health experts warn that it's anything but.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 23:20:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anysphere, a GitHub Copilot rival, has raised $60M Series A at  $400M valuation from a16z, Thrive, sources say</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/09/anysphere-a-github-copilot-rival-has-raised-60m-series-a-at-400m-valuation-from-a16z-thrive-sources-say/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Anysphere, a two-year-old startup that’s developed an AI-powered coding assistant called Cursor, has raised over $60 million in a Series A financing at a $400 million post-money valuation, two sources familiar with the deal told TechCrunch. The round was co-led by Andreessen Horowitz and Thrive Capital. Patrick Collison, co-founder and CEO of Stripe, also participated […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 00:20:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ATM Software Flaws Left Piles of Cash for Anyone Who Knew to Look</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/vss-atm-vulnerabilities-defcon-2024/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Six vulnerabilities in ATM-maker Diebold Nixdorf’s popular Vynamic Security Suite could have been exploited to control ATMs using “relatively simplistic attacks.”</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 19:37:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to ask Google to remove deepfake porn results from Google Search</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/09/how-to-ask-google-to-remove-deepfake-porn-results-from-google-search/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>The internet is full of deepfakes — and most of them are nudes. According to a report from Home Security Heroes, deepfake porn makes up 98% of all deepfake videos online. Thanks to easy-to-use and freely available generative AI tools, the number of deepfakes online — many of which aren’t consensual — skyrocketed 550% from […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 22:00:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>19 Best Back-to-School Deals (2024): Backpacks, Chargers, Laptops</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/back-to-school-deals-2024/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>It's time to put away the pool noodles and get those butts back in seats. Save on backpacks, iPads, laptops, and more.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 19:00:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ecovacs home robots can be hacked to spy on their owners, researchers say</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/09/ecovacs-home-robots-can-be-hacked-to-spy-on-their-owners-researchers-say/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Researchers found flaws that could allow anyone to spy on the owners of Ecovacs home robots by hijacking their cameras and microphones. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>