<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 12:05:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The Best Fire Pits to Get Your S'mores On This Summer (2024)</title><link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-fire-pits/</link><description>Turn your patio into a party with these burning rings of fire.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rondo Energy funding shows a new way across the climate startup ‘valley of death’</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/27/rondo-energy-funding-shows-a-new-way-across-the-climate-startup-valley-of-death/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Climate tech startups especially those building hardware, face a particular challenge when trying to move beyond the prototype or pilot phase and star...</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:40:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Mystery Ranch Coulee 30 is Everything You Need in Day Pack</title><link>https://www.wired.com/review/mystery-ranch-coulee-30/</link><description>A comfortable, well-design day pack capable of heavy loads with plenty of customization options.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amazon consolidates Amazon Clinic into the One Medical brand</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/27/amazon-one-medical-amazon-clinic-consolidation/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Amazon is folding its Amazon Clinic telehealth service into its primary care business One Medical, the company announced on Thursday. The company expl...</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:32:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best Dyson Vacuums We've Tested and Reviewed: V15, V12, and More</title><link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-dyson-vacuums/</link><description>Feeling the pull of a clean machine? We’ll help you make sense of Dyson’s whirlwind vacuum lineup.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Just in time for the debates, Meta fixes bug impacting users’ political content settings on Instagram and Threads</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/27/meta-fixes-bug-that-seemed-to-reset-users-political-content-settings-on-instagram-and-threads/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Meta has fixed the bug that caused people to believe the company had adjusted their selections in a political content settings tool without their cons...</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:19:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tiptop Helps You Trade In Your Old Stuff to Pay for New Stuff</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/tiptop-trade-in-service-for-online-shopping/</link><description>One of Postmates’ founders is back with an ecommerce payment startup called Tiptop. The service lets you pay for online purchases by trading in someth...</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>YouTube Premium upgrade adds smart downloads and picture-in-picture mode for Shorts</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/27/youtube-premium-upgrade-adds-smart-downloads-and-picture-in-picture-mode-for-shorts/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>YouTube is adding several new features for Premium users, including smart downloads and support for picture-in-picture mode for Shorts, as well as a w...</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NASA Desperately Needs New Spacesuits. Private Firms Are Struggling to Make Them</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/nasas-commercial-spacesuit-program-just-hit-a-major-snag/</link><description>Collins Aerospace is expected to back out of a contract with NASA, while high interest rates and a difficult supply chain environment have affected Ax...</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 14:43:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TechCrunch Disrupt joins forces with Google Cloud for Startup Battlefield 200</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/27/techcrunch-disrupt-joins-forces-with-google-cloud-forstartup-battlefield-200/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>TechCrunch is joining forces with Google Cloud as its lead partner for Startup Battlefield 200. This event will highlight and support the most promisi...</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>