<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 06:56:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Why Did Samsung Take Control of My Banking App? Inside Android’s ‘Clobbering’ Dilemma</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/android-clobbering-app-store/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>A US judge is set to force Google to more widely open up Android phones to competing app stores. But as I found, app stores vying for supremacy could leave Android users confused and worried about security.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>UK neobank Revolut valued at $45B after secondary market sale</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/16/uk-neobank-revolut-valued-at-45b-after-secondary-market-sale/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Revolut has confirmed a new valuation of $45 billion via a secondary market share sale, shortly after the U.K.-based neobank secured its own banking license in the U.K. and in Mexico. The news positions Revolut as one of Europe’s most valuable private tech companies. Founded out of London in 2015, Revolut is one of numerous […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:47:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>EVs Are Losing Up to 50 Percent of Their Value in One Year</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/evs-are-losing-up-to-50-percent-of-their-value-in-one-year/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Some electric car brands are hemorrhaging value, with the worst losing as much as $600 a day. In this investigation, WIRED outlines the models to watch, why this is happening, and how you could game the market to your advantage.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ben Horowitz Declares War on Michael Moritz</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/15/ben-horowitz-declares-war-on-michael-moritz/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>A social media spat between billionaire tech investors is raising questions about the journalistic independence of three-year-old news outfit SF Standard, after a reporter representing the outlet reached out to sources for a story about VC Ben Horowitz and his wife Felicia. The Standard’s sole backer is another longtime VC, Michael Moritz, and on Thursday […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 05:31:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Mpox Outbreak Isn't Like the Last One</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/mpox-outbreak-global-public-health-emergency/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>The strain of mpox behind the current global health emergency is believed to be up to 10 times deadlier than the one that swept the globe in 2022.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 22:52:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>California AI bill SB 1047 aims to prevent AI disasters, but Silicon Valley warns it will cause one</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/15/california-ai-bill-sb-1047-aims-to-prevent-ai-disasters-but-silicon-valley-warns-it-will-cause-one/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>SB 1047 has drawn the ire of Silicon Valley players large and small, including venture capitalists, big tech trade groups, researchers and startup founders. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 00:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Uncertain Path Forward for Psychedelic Medicine</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/where-does-psychedelic-assisted-therapy-go-next-mdma-fda-lykos/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>After the FDA rejected its proposed MDMA treatment, Lykos Therapeutics is laying off 75 percent of its staff and its founder has left the company.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 22:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>California weakens bill to prevent AI disasters before final vote, taking advice from Anthropic</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/15/california-weakens-bill-to-prevent-ai-disasters-before-final-vote-taking-advice-from-anthropic/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>California’s bill to prevent AI disasters, SB 1047, has faced significant opposition from many parties in Silicon Valley. Today, California lawmakers bent slightly to that pressure, adding in several amendments suggested by AI firm Anthropic and other opponents. On Thursday the bill passed through California’s Appropriations Committee, a major step toward becoming law, with several […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 23:11:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Samsung Coupon and Promo Codes (August 2024)</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/samsung-promo-codes/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>WIRED has the best deals to save on your favorite Samsung products.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 20:25:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meta axed CrowdTangle, a tool for tracking disinformation. Critics claim its replacement has just ‘1% of the features’</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/15/meta-shut-down-crowdtangle-a-tool-for-tracking-disinformation-heres-how-its-replacement-compares/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Journalists, researchers and politicians are mourning Meta’s shutdown of CrowdTangle, which they used to track the spread of disinformation on Facebook and Instagram. In CrowdTangle’s place, Meta is offering its Content Library — but is limiting usage to people from “qualified academic or nonprofit institutions who are pursuing scientific or public interest research.” Many researchers […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 21:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>