<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 07:04:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The Limits of the AI-Generated 'Eyes on Rafah' Image</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/the-limits-of-the-ai-generated-eyes-on-rafah-image/</link><description>The “All Eyes on Rafah” image went viral on social media this week, with over 47 million shares on Instagram alone. It's bringing up tough questions a...</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spain bans Meta from launching election features on Facebook, Instagram over privacy fears</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/31/spain-bans-meta-from-launching-election-features-on-facebook-instagram-over-privacy-fears/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Meta has been banned from launching features on Facebook and Instagram that would have collected data on voters in Spain using the social networks ahe...</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 11:52:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple iPad Air (M2, 2024) Review: Bigger and Slightly Brighter</title><link>https://www.wired.com/review/apple-ipad-air-m2-2024/</link><description>Apple's lightweight tablet comes equipped with a faster processor, but it's the bigger screen that steals the spotlight.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stripe curbs India ambitions over regulatory changes</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/31/stripe-curbs-india-ambitions-over-regulatory-changes/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Stripe, the global fintech giant, said on Friday that it will temporarily move to an invite-only model for new account sign-ups in India, “a tough dec...</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 11:45:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Google Admits Its AI Overviews Search Feature Screwed Up</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/google-ai-overview-search-issues/</link><description>Liz Reid, Google’s head of search, said in a blog post that the company had made adjustments to its new AI search feature after screenshots of its err...</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 02:56:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Voice cloning of political figures is still easy as pie</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/31/voice-cloning-of-political-figures-is-still-easy-as-pie/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The 2024 election is likely to be the first in which faked audio and video of candidates is a serious factor. As campaigns warm up, voters should be a...</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 09:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump’s Online MAGA Army Calls Guilty Verdict a Declaration of War</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/trump-guilty-verdict-online-maga-fanbase-war/</link><description>Trump supporters, fringe extremists, right-wing pundits, and politicians have all posted incendiary rhetoric, including some calls for “war,” followin...</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 00:04:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OneScreen.ai brings startup ads to billboards and NYC’s subway</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/30/onescreen-ai-brings-startup-ads-to-billboards-and-nycs-subway/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>When Alex Ewing was a kid growing up in Purcell, Oklahoma, he knew how close he was to home based on which billboards he could see out the car window....</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 02:34:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Foreign Influence Campaigns Don’t Know How to Use AI Yet Either</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/openai-threat-report-china-russia-ai-propaganda/</link><description>OpenAI has released its first report, which details how bad actors in Russia, China, and beyond are using AI to spread propaganda. (Poorly.)</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 23:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SpaceX sent Starship to orbit — the next launch will try to bring it back</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/30/spacex-sent-starship-to-orbit-the-next-launch-will-try-to-bring-it-back/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>SpaceX’s massive Starship rocket could take to the skies for the fourth time on June 5, with the primary objective of evaluating the second stage’s re...</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 22:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>