<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 08:43:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Reid Hoffman Hasn't Given Up on Biden Just Yet</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/joe-biden-silicon-valley/</link><description>Some of the most prominent conservative venture capitalists have gotten louder about their support for Trump, but Reid Hoffman says not much has actua...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Medal raises $13M as it builds out a contextual AI assistant for desktop</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/11/medal-raises-13m-as-it-builds-out-a-new-ai-platform-for-desktop/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Medal, a startup that is better known for its video game clipping product, just announced that it has raised $13 million at a valuation of $333 millio...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 13:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘Death Occurs in the Dark’: Indie Video Game Devs Are Struggling to Survive</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/death-occurs-in-the-dark-indie-video-game-devs-are-struggling-to-stay-afloat/</link><description>Big video game makers like Epic Games and EA have gone through substantial layoffs in the past year. Amid the turmoil, many indie studios are getting ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alpine Space Ventures close first fund to grow the space economy on both sides of the pond</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/11/alpine-space-ventures-close-first-fund-to-grow-the-space-economy-on-both-sides-of-the-pond/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>When early SpaceX engineer Bulent Altan and long-time investor Joran Voelklein surveyed the European space sector at the end of the 2010s, they were s...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI's Energy Demands Are Out of Control. Welcome to the Internet's Hyper-Consumption Era</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/ai-energy-demands-water-impact-internet-hyper-consumption-era/</link><description>Generative artificial intelligence tools, now part of the everyday user experience online, are causing stress on local power grids and mass water evap...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Intel Capital backs AI construction startup that could boost Intel’s own manufacturing prospects</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/11/intel-capital-backs-ai-construction-startup-that-could-boost-intels-own-manufacturing-prospects/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Intel could be giving its burgeoning foundry ambitions a much-needed shot in the arm, as the chip giant’s venture capital arm today revealed that it’s...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Is the Moment RFK Jr. Has Been Waiting For</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/robert-f-kennedy-debate-tiktok/</link><description>Since the presidential debate, Robert F. Kennedy Jr.’s campaign has heavily leaned into X and TikTok as part of its strategy to get the third-party ca...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI-powered Regard nabs $61M to find missed illness, boost hospital revenue</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/11/ai-powered-regard-nabs-61m-to-find-missed-illness-boost-hospital-revenue/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>People in tech often say that data is the new oil. That phrase, coined by British mathematician Clive Humby, of course implies that data is valuable. ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Silicon Valley Hasn’t Embraced Trump. But It’s Wavering on Biden</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/silicon-valley-crypto-trump-biden-debate/</link><description>Venture capitalists on both sides of the aisle suggest Silicon Valley is more anti-Biden than it is pro-Trump.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 10:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>EU ends Apple Pay antitrust probe with binding commitments to open up contactless payments</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/11/eu-ends-apple-pay-antitrust-probe-with-binding-commitments-to-open-up-contactless-payments/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The European Union has accepted commitments from Apple over how it operates Apple Pay to settle a long running competition investigation. Commission E...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 11:04:25 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>