<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 08:10:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NBC’s Olympics Broadcast Isn’t Just Addictive. It’s a New Era of Streaming</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/nbc-peacock-2024-summer-olympics-coverage/</link><description>With a big assist from Peacock, the 2024 Summer Olympics broadcast is fragmented in all the right ways.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ex-Clubhouse employees take another swing at a social networking startup</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/07/ex-clubhouse-employees-take-another-swing-at-a-social-networking-startup/</link><description>The ex-Clubhouse, Netflix employees raised $1.65M for an app that combines social media, networking, and dating. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elon Musk Has Turned X Into His Personal Political Playground</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/musk-trump-support-x/</link><description>Elon Musk accused Twitter’s leadership of tipping the scales politically. But now he’s doing just that with X.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fintech Payoneer is buying 5-year-old global payroll startup Skuad for $61M in cash</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/07/payoneer-is-buying-5-year-old-global-payroll-startup-skaud-for-61m-cash/</link><description>New York-based fintech Payoneer has acquired Skuad, a Singapore-based global HR and payroll startup, for $61 million in cash, the company exclusively told TechCrunch. Payoneer said it could also pay up to another $10 million, contingent on if Skuad meets various performance goals within the first 18 months of the acquisition. Payoneer also committed to […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kamala Harris’ Campaign Is a Windfall for Influencers</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/harris-campaign-influencers/</link><description>The switch from Joe Biden to Kamala Harris atop the Democratic ticket has been a boon for the campaign—and content creators.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elon Musk’s X taken to court in Ireland for grabbing EU user data to train Grok without consent</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/07/elon-musks-x-taken-to-court-in-ireland-for-grabbing-eu-user-data-to-train-grok-without-consent/</link><description>Elon Musk's X is being taken to court in Ireland for using Europeans' data to train AI models without asking for their consent. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 11:02:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CrowdStrike Faces a Potential Tsunami of Lawsuits. Only the Fine Print Can Save It, Experts Say</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/crowdstrike-outage-microsoft-delta-lawsuits-analysis/</link><description>After crashing millions of computers and disrupting businesses across the globe, cybersecurity company CrowdStrike must protect itself against a flurry of legal activity that is already beginning. The devil will be in the details.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Automattic launches AI writing tool that aims to make WordPress blogs more readable and succinct</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/07/automattic-launches-ai-writing-tool-that-aims-to-make-wordpress-blogs-more-readable-and-succinct/</link><description>Automattic, the owner of WordPress.com, has launched a new AI tool designed to help bloggers write more clearly and succinctly. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 10:32:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>She’s the New Face of Climate Activism—and She’s Carrying a Pickax</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/climate-activism-radical-new-face-lena-lazare/</link><description>Sabotage. Property destruction. For Léna Lazare and her cohort, radicalized by years of inaction on the environmental crisis, these aren’t dirty words. They’re acts of joy.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>EQT takes a majority stake in cybersecurity firm Acronis at $3.5B+ valuation</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/07/eqt-takes-a-majority-stake-in-cybersecurity-firm-acronis-at-a-3-5b-valuation/</link><description>Cybersecurity remains a white-hot space for investors. In the latest example of that demand, EQT has bought a majority stake in Acronis, a security company that specializes in data protection, cloud and integrated security solutions for managed service providers (which resell services to consumers) and corporate IT teams. The size and value of the stake, […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 08:26:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A US Judge Ruled That Google Is an Illegal Monopolist. Here's What Might Come Next</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/google-search-monopoly-judge-amit-mehta-options/</link><description>Judge Amit Mehta’s ruling has triggered a potentially yearslong process to decide how to punish the company. For users, it could mean a future in which Google isn’t front and center everywhere.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 23:02:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>UK data watchdog to fine NHS vendor Advanced for security failures prior to LockBit ransomware attack</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/06/uk-data-watchdog-fines-nhs-vendor-advanced-for-security-failures-prior-to-lockbit-ransomware-attack/</link><description>The ICO issued the provisional fine in "failing to implement appropriate security measures prior to the attack." © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 00:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pack Your Bags With 8 Great Deals from Patagonia's Past-Season Sale</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/patagonias-past-season-sale-2024/</link><description>You still need a duffel bag and warm hoody on that last Labor Day trip. Pick one up for 40 percent off.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 22:42:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jumia plans to raise more than $100 million in secondary shares to drive stalled user growth</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/06/jumia-plans-to-raise-more-than-100-million-in-secondary-shares-to-drive-stalled-user-growth/</link><description>African e-commerce company Jumia is selling 20 million American depositary shares over the next couple of weeks, TechCrunch has learned. The at-the-market transaction is to take advantage of strong results despite a volatile market. Given Jumia’s share price of around $5.70 when the stock market opened on Tuesday, the e-commerce company could potentially raise approximately […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 00:00:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 30 Best Movies on Max (aka HBO Max) Right Now (August 2024)</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-movies-hbo-max-right-now/</link><description>Love Lies Bleeding, Dune: Part Two, and Beetlejuice are just a few of the movies you should be watching on Max this month.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Airbnb details plans to expand beyond short-term rentals, including co-hosting and relaunching ‘experiences’</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/06/airbnb-details-plans-to-expand-beyond-short-term-rentals-including-co-hosting-and-relaunching-experiences/</link><description>Airbnb CEO Brian Chesky suggested on Tuesday’s Q2 earnings call with investors that the company will soon expand into new products and services, including co-hosting, a relaunch of Airbnb’s “experiences,” guest services and more. The company positioned the upcoming offerings as a way for Airbnb to grow its revenue by becoming known for doing more […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 23:48:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Public Health Experts Want Coca-Cola and the Olympics to Break Up</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/public-health-experts-want-the-olympics-to-drop-its-oldest-sponsor/</link><description>Scientists, activists, and ordinary petitioners want the Olympics to break with Coca-Cola, comparing it to the tobacco companies that long sponsored the Games. They aren’t holding their breath.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:30:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Reddit to test AI-powered search result pages</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/06/reddit-ai-powered-search-results/</link><description>Reddit users will soon see AI-generated summaries at the top of search results. Reddit co-founder and CEO Steve Huffman told investors during its earnings call on Tuesday that the company plans to test AI-powered search result pages to “summarize and recommend content.” He noted this will help users “dive deeper” into content and discover new […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 23:10:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elon Musk’s X Sues Advertisers Over Alleged Boycott</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/elon-musk-x-twitter-rumble-sue-advertisers/</link><description>The platform's antitrust suit claims an alleged conspiracy to withhold advertising dollars. Right-wing video site Rumble filed a similar suit today.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 18:42:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rivian lost $1.46B in Q2 as it drives toward a VW-linked future</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/06/rivian-lost-1-46-billion-in-q2-as-it-drives-towards-a-vw-linked-future/</link><description>Rivian’s financial losses have crept up as it pushed out the last of its first-generation R1 trucks and SUVs in favor of newer, more cost-efficient versions — a sign of just how much the company could use the $5 billion it could get as part of a recently announced deal with Volkswagen Group. The company […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 23:07:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A New Plan to Break the Cycle of Destructive Critical Infrastructure Hacks</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/undisruptable27-us-critical-infrastructure-cybersecurity/</link><description>As digital threats against US water, food, health care, and other vital sectors loom large, a new project called UnDisruptable27 aims to help fix cybersecurity weaknesses where other efforts have failed.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 18:20:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Google Assistant lives to automate another day</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/06/google-assistant-lives-to-automate-another-day/</link><description>With new Pixel devices just over the horizon, Assistant’s days on Android may still be numbered. For the time being, however, it still has a place on the home. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 21:16:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI Is Heating the Olympic Pool</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/ai-is-heating-the-olympic-pool/</link><description>A data center in Paris has been hooked up to the energy system heating the Olympic pool. But critics say that projects recycling data centers’ excess heat are a distraction from the real environmental costs of AI.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 16:56:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amazon upgrades its AI image generator</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/06/amazon-upgrades-its-ai-image-generator/</link><description>Amazon has released an upgraded version of its in-house image-generating model, Titan Image Generator, for AWS customers using its Bedrock generative AI platform. Simply called Titan Image Generator v2, the new model brings with it several new capabilities, AWS principal developer advocate Channy Yun explains in a blog post. Users can “guide” the images they […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:43:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Google 4th-Gen Nest Learning Thermostat and Google TV Streamer: Specs, Features, Price, Release Date</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/google-nest-learning-thermostat-4th-gen-google-tv-streamer/</link><description>Nest’s connected thermostat gets a redesign and some AI smarts, while the brand-new iteration of the Chromecast serves as a hub for your smart home.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>X is getting closer to launching its payment service</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/06/x-twitter-payment-service-update/</link><description>X (formerly Twitter) appears to be making progress on its upcoming payments system, bringing it closer to Elon Musk’s vision of turning X into an “everything app.” According to a recent finding by app researcher Nima Owji, the company is working on adding a “Payments” button to the navigation bar under the bookmarks tab. Owji, […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:00:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Arturia AudioFuse 16Rig Audio Interface Review: So Many Inputs</title><link>https://www.wired.com/review/arturia-audiofuse-16rig/</link><description>This fancy audio interface makes plugging in all your synths a breeze.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:32:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dawn Aerospace’s rocket-propelled aircraft takes flight</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/06/dawn-aerospace/</link><description>Dawn Aerospace’s rocket-powered aircraft soared to new heights in its latest test campaign, as the company looks to build what could be the highest-performance aircraft to take off from a runway. The series of three flights, which were completed in late July, saw the Mk-II Aurora vehicle achieve a maximum speed of Mach 0.92 and […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best Climbing Gear for Beginners (2024): Shoes, Harnesses, and Ropes</title><link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-climbing-gear/</link><description>Whether you’re tempted by indoor climbing or want to take on the great outdoors, we’ve got the ropes, shoes, and harnesses to get you started.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Made by Google 2024: Pixel 9, Gemini, a new foldable and other things to expect from the event</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/06/made-by-google-2024-pixel-9-gemini-a-new-foldable-and-other-things-to-expect-from-the-event/</link><description>Google unveiled the Nest Learning Thermostat 4 and Google TV Streamer. It's expected to announce four Pixel devices, including the Pixel 9 and Pixel 9 Pro. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 18:58:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Go to Burning Man in an Extreme Climate and Feel Good About It</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-go-to-burning-man/</link><description>The worsening climate crisis and the changes in the culture may have you wondering if you should skip Burning Man. Veterans of the week-long festival, which begins August 25, have some advice.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Waymo expands robotaxi coverage in Los Angeles and San Francisco</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/06/waymo-expands-robotaxi-coverage-in-los-angeles-and-san-francisco/</link><description>Waymo, the Alphabet-owned self-driving car company, is adding another 10 square miles to its robotaxi service area to include cities surrounding San Francisco. The move, which adds Daly City, Broadmoor and Colma, pushes its total commercial service territory to about 55 square miles. Waymo said Tuesday it is also adding 16 square miles of new robotaxi […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 18:48:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elon Musk’s X Is Leaving San Francisco</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/elon-musk-x-twitter-leaving-san-francisco-office/</link><description>The office closure marks the end of an era for the site formerly known as Twitter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 22:37:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Europe’s most valuable fintech, and which startups became unicorns this year</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/06/europes-most-valuable-fintech-and-which-startups-became-unicorns-this-year/</link><description>Welcome to TechCrunch Fintech! This week, we’re looking at Revolut’s reported valuation hike, fintech unicorns, the Disrupt Fintech Stage, and more. To get a roundup of TechCrunch’s biggest and most important fintech stories delivered to your inbox every Tuesday at 8 a.m. PT, subscribe here. The big story Revolut reportedly told staff last week of […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 18:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Google Search Is an Illegal Monopoly, US Judge Rules</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/google-search-antitrust-monopoly-ruling/</link><description>Nearly a year after the US government took Google to trial, a judge has found that the tech giant violated antitrust laws. A new trial will determine how Google should be penalized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 20:52:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bluesky adds Techdirt founder Mike Masnick to its board</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/06/bluesky-adds-techdirt-founder-mike-masnick-to-its-board/</link><description>According to a company blog post, the team was already leaning on Masnick for advice, so adding him to the board is a "natural next step" in formalizing their relationship. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 17:57:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why People Are Mad About the 'House of the Dragon' Season 2 Finale</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/everyone-is-big-mad-about-the-house-of-the-dragon-season-2-finale/</link><description>“Did I just watch a 70 minute trailer for Season 3?” is just one of the reactions fans have posted online about the season's "disappointing and poorly executed" closer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 20:34:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amazon Music’s new AI feature lets you browse podcast episodes by topic</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/06/amazon-music-ai-feature-podcast-episodes-topics/</link><description>Amazon Music announced Tuesday the launch of its new AI-powered feature, “Topics,” which allows users to explore podcast episodes by specific topics discussed in the episode. When you visit the page of a podcast episode, look for new Topic tags below the episode description. You can tap on a tag to see a list of […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 17:24:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Controversial Kids Online Safety Act Faces an Uncertain Future</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/kids-online-safety-act-kosa-stalled-in-house/</link><description>While it easily passed the Senate, the House began a recess without bringing the bill—which critics say would keep young people from accessing vital information on topics like sexual health—to the floor for a vote.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 18:34:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple Intelligence’s writing tools stumble on swears and controversial topics</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/06/apple-intelligences-writing-tools-stumble-on-swears-and-controversial-topics/</link><description>Apple's Writing Tools feature will show a message notifying you that AI-generated suggestions might not be of the highest quality when tackling certain topics. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 17:00:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mountain Bikers Are Rewilding Land by Paying the Government to Do It</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/bike-park-wales-rewilding-private-sector-finance/</link><description>A new nature-restoration project in Wales is being funded by an unusual source: thrill-seeking downhill lovers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zoom Is Going After Google and Microsoft With AI-Driven Docs</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/zoom-is-going-after-google-and-microsoft-with-ai-driven-docs/</link><description>The video-conferencing app is trying to create an "everything workplace" app in a crowded market.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Are Color Gamuts and Color Spaces in TVs and Monitors, and Do They Matter?</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/what-are-color-gamuts-and-why-do-they-matter/</link><description>If you’re confused by all the jargon used to describe your new monitor, don’t worry. We’ve got you (and your color gamut) covered.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dacia Spring EV (2024) Review: Excellent Value for an Urban EV</title><link>https://www.wired.com/review/review-dacia-spring-2024/</link><description>This super-fun and likable urban all-electric runabout is packed with tech despite its rock-bottom price. Aside from the amazing value, it proves stateside EV makers need to up their game—fast.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jane Goodall Thinks It’s Not Too Late to Save the World</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/wired-czechia-jane-goodall-q-and-a-conservation/</link><description>The world, the famed primatologist says, isn’t what it used to be—but there’s still time to save it, if we treat crises like climate change, biodiversity loss, and poverty as one.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Project 2025 Would Put US Elections at Risk</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/project-2025-cisa-election-critical-infrastructure-security/</link><description>Experts say the “nonsensical” policy proposal, which largely aligns with Donald Trump’s agenda, would weaken the US agency tasked with protecting election integrity, critical infrastructure, and more.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JLab Hear OTC Hearing Aid Review: Super Affordable</title><link>https://www.wired.com/review/jlab-hear-otc-hearing-aid/</link><description>For the hearing-aid curious, these over-the-counter earbuds are amazingly affordable and effectively pull double duty.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 6 Best Cold Plunge Pools in 2024—I Spent Months Testing to Find the Best</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-cold-plunge-tubs/</link><description>Keen to try the latest wellness trend, I dipped out of my comfort zone. These are my favorite cold-water plunge pools for any budget.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 17:26:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Roku Pro Series TV Review: Bright and Easy to Use</title><link>https://www.wired.com/review/roku-pro-series-4k/</link><description>If you have a family with kids, post-lunch cartoons, and video games, you need this bright TV with an easy-to-navigate interface.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Logitech Combo Touch for iPad Pro (2024) Review: A Must-Have Keyboard Accessory</title><link>https://www.wired.com/review/logitech-combo-touch-ipad-pro-13-inch-keyboard-case/</link><description>Its protective, durable, and easy to swap between work and play.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>9 Best Action Cameras (2024): Underwater, 360, Compact, and More</title><link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-action-cameras/</link><description>Gearing up to shred the slopes or dive into the seas? These photography tools are made for danger.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>To Study Tornados, Bring an Apocalypse-Proof Truck. And Rocket Launchers</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/dominator-3-tornado-chaser/</link><description>A day of chasing storms with Reed Timmer's Dominator 3, the latest in extreme twister tech.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Best iPhone (2024): Which Model Should You Buy?</title><link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/iphone-buying-guide/</link><description>The iPhone 16 arrives in September. That means this is the worst moment to buy a new iPhone.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 12:09:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘Gem’ of a Proof Breaks 80-Year-Old Record, Offers New Insights Into Prime Numbers</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/sensational-proof-delivers-new-insights-into-prime-numbers/</link><description>The proof creates stricter limits on potential exceptions to the famous Riemann hypothesis.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>See the Perseids and Southern Delta Aquariids in a Stunning Double Meteor Shower</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/see-the-perseids-and-southern-delta-aquariids-in-a-stunning-double-meteor-shower/</link><description>Across the Northern Hemisphere, August will see beautiful displays of meteors. Here's everything you need to know to enjoy them.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>LCD, IPS, OLED, and Quantum Dots: All the Confusing Display Terms, Explained</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/lcd-ips-oled-and-quantum-dots-all-the-confusing-display-terms-explained/</link><description>Shopping for monitors can feel like swimming through alphabet soup. Learn what all these technical acronyms mean before you buy.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NASA Is ‘Evaluating All Options’ to Get the Boeing Starliner Crew Home</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/nasa-boeing-starliner-return-home-spacex/</link><description>Eight weeks after the Starliner spacecraft launched, NASA is still looking for possible answers to its technical issues—including the possibility of SpaceX lending a hand.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 13:36:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Control Android Auto or Apple CarPlay With Your Voice While Driving</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-use-your-voice-to-control-android-auto-or-apple-carplay/</link><description>Both smartphone platforms offer a number of ways to interact with your phone while keeping both hands on the wheel. Follow these tips to get the most out of in-car voice commands.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 13:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Stop Wildfire Smoke Damaging Your Health</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/wildfire-smoke-causes-long-term-health-problems-heres-how-to-protect-yourself/</link><description>Smoke from fires is linked to thousands of premature deaths every year, and is a growing health threat as widespread blazes becomes more common.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Insta360 Go 3S Review: Tiny, Fun, and 4K Footage</title><link>https://www.wired.com/review/insta360-go-3s-action-camera/</link><description>Insta360’s go-anywhere, wearable action camera hybrid gains smoother, sharper 4K video.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 49 Best Movies on Netflix Right Now (August 2024)</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/netflix-best-movies-this-week/</link><description>The Long Game, Leo, and Godzilla Minus One are just a few of the movies you should watch on Netflix this month.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 53 Best Shows on Netflix Right Now (August 2024)</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/netflix-best-shows-this-week/</link><description>Sweet Home, The Decameron, Star Trek Prodigy are just a few of the shows you need to watch on Netflix this month.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>US Hands Over Russian Cybercriminals in WSJ Reporter Prisoner Swap</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/russia-cybercriminal-us-prisoner-swap/</link><description>Plus: Meta pays $1.4 million in a historic privacy settlement, Microsoft blames a cyberattack for a major Azure outage, and an artist creates a face recognition system to reveal your NYPD “coppelganger.”</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Fight to Save Florida’s Oranges</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/the-fight-to-save-floridas-oranges-climate-change-farming-crop-shortages/</link><description>Once the leading producer of the citrus fruit in the US, Florida is being ground down by hurricanes, diseases, and drought—but its orange growers aren’t giving up yet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2024 Summer Olympics: A Self-Healing Pole Vault Pole Is One Great Leap for Sports Tech</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/a-self-healing-pole-vault-pole-is-one-great-leap-for-sports-tech/</link><description>Pole vaulting is a spectacular, dangerous sport. Modern poles could be drastically improved to make them more reliable, with healable tech being developed that could also be used in surfing and cycling.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TikTok Sued by US Justice Department for Alleged Violations of Kids’ Privacy</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/us-justice-department-sues-tiktok-kids-privacy/</link><description>The social media company, already fighting for its existence in the US, now has to contend with a potentially expensive penalty stemming from its policies toward users under 13.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 20:54:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>No, the Seine Cleanup Wasn’t a Failure</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/no-the-seine-cleanup-wasnt-a-failure/</link><description>The goal of the Seine-cleansing project is to produce swimmable conditions for the people of Paris for years to come—the Olympics was just a milestone in getting there.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 18:26:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sensitive Illinois Voter Data Exposed by Contractor’s Unsecured Databases</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/illinois-voter-databases-exposed/</link><description>Social Security numbers, death certificates, voter applications, and other personal data were accessible on the open internet, highlighting the ongoing challenges in election security.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 17:34:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A New Trick Could Block the Misuse of Open Source AI</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/center-for-ai-safety-open-source-llm-safeguards/</link><description>Researchers have developed a way to tamperproof open source large language models to prevent them from being coaxed into, say, explaining how to make a bomb.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 16:49:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Edifier Stax Spirit S5 Headphones Review: Great Sound, No Noise Canceling</title><link>https://www.wired.com/review/edifier-stax-spirit-s5/</link><description>These wireless planar magnetic headphones are the perfect way to maintain pristine audio quality on the go.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>