<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 12:07:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The Best Sheets for Every Body, Bed, and Budget (2024)</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-bedsheets/</link><description>Which material should you buy? Percale or linen? We tested dozens of sheets to find our favorites and break it all down.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TechCrunch Minute: How to protect yourself from AI scams</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/video/techcrunch-minute-how-to-protect-yourself-from-ai-scams/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>You probably like to think of yourself as reasonably sophisticated when it comes to online scams — you’re not opening random email attachments or send...</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DJI Mic 2 Review: A Powerful Lav Replacement</title><link>https://www.wired.com/review/dji-mic-2/</link><description>Convenient magnetic attachments, solid noise cancellation, and 32-bit float recording all add up to the perfect mic for location shoots.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 13:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tembo capitalizes on the database boom and lands new cash to expand</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/08/database-startup-tembo-lands-new-cash-to-expand/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>One of the vendors to benefit from the database boom is Tembo, a startup creating a platform that lets developers deploy different flavors of Postgres...</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 16:33:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why the Run-Up to Prime Day is the Worst Time To Shop on Amazon</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/amazon-prime-day-price-tracking-best-time-to-shop/</link><description>Retailers have historically jacked up prices right before big sales. Amazon is no different.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayfield’s Navin Chaddha is coming to TechCrunch Disrupt 2024</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/08/mayfields-navin-chaddha-is-coming-to-techcrunch-disrupt-2024/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>TechCrunch Disrupt 2024 is set to welcome an impressive lineup of judges for the Startup Battlefield 200 competition, presented this year by Google Cl...</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>His Galaxy Wolf Art Kept Getting Ripped Off. So He Sued—and Bought a Home</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/how-one-man-bought-a-home-by-suing-people-who-stole-his-galaxy-wolf-art/</link><description>When his galaxy wolf illustration was stolen by countless online stores, artist Jonas Jödicke decided to fight back.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Art therapy app Scribble Journey lets you express emotions through doodles</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/08/art-therapy-app-scribble-journey/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Numerous concerns are weighing on the minds of many, whether it’s current global conflicts, climate change or the precarious state of the economy, it ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:49:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Google’s Nonconsensual Explicit Images Problem Is Getting Worse</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/google-still-cant-quite-stop-explicit-deepfakes/</link><description>Reports of intimate images and video posted online without consent are growing, and deepfakes add a horrifying new dimension to the problem. Google in...</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 11:43:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pestle’s app can now save recipes from Reels using on-device AI</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/08/pestles-app-can-now-save-recipes-from-reels-using-on-device-ai/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Pestle addresses the common problem of finding recipes on the web. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:39:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>