<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 07:23:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The Best Early Labor Day Mattress Deals (2024)</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-early-labor-day-mattress-deals/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>It's one of the best times of the year to score a new mattress. Here are all the best deals (plus some exclusive sale codes) to snag ahead of the long weekend.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 22:04:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Starpath accelerates moon water mining plans with $12M seed funding</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/20/starpath-accelerates-moon-water-mining-plans-with-12m-seed-funding/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>NASA and the space industry are in agreement: if we want to establish a permanent human presence on the moon, we’ll need to make use of every native resource we can — and none are as important as water ice. Starpath Robotics is one of a handful of startups planning for this future. The startup […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Our 9 Favorite Pizza Ovens: Wood, Gas, and Electric (2024)</title><link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-backyard-pizza-ovens/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Craving carb-y comfort? We picked our favorite outdoor ovens for backyards, countertops, or camping.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 18:43:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Reliant’s paper-scouring AI takes on science’s data drudgery</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/20/reliant-ai/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>AI models have proven capable of many things, but what tasks do we actually want them doing? Preferably drudgery — and there’s plenty of that in research and academia. Reliant hopes to specialize in the kind of time-consuming data extraction work that’s currently a specialty of tired grad students and interns. “The best thing you […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 11:59:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best Hearing Aids of 2024, Reviewed by Experts</title><link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-hearing-aids/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>These WIRED-tested and audiologist-approved devices will help you hear sounds more clearly. Never miss out on a dinner conversation again.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 18:29:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mike Lynch, recently acquitted in HP-Autonomy fraud case, is missing after yacht capsized off Sicily (updated)</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/20/mike-lynch-recently-acquitted-in-hp-autonomy-case-is-missing-after-yacht-capsized-off-sicily/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Update: Authorities have yet to access the inside of the sunken yacht, and Mike Lynch is still classified as missing. Other details have emerged in the interim. The accident appears to have been caused by a major storm and a resulting tornado-like water column that ensnared and damaged the yacht. Among the other six people […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 09:16:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Climate Change’s Latest Deadly Threat: Lightning Strikes</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/thunder-lightning-strike-deaths-india/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>In rural India, stormy weather, a lack of knowledge, and scant protections are combining to kill thousands every year, with climate change likely to raise the threat as lightning becomes more common.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 17:51:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>US tech giants fight Indian telcos’ bid to regulate internet services, pay for network usage</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/20/us-tech-giants-fight-indian-telcos-bid-to-regulate-internet-services/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Global technology giants are pushing back against attempts by India’s telecom networks to bring internet services under stricter regulation, rejecting arguments that such measures are necessary to create a “level playing field” and address national security concerns. The Asia Internet Coalition (AIC), a powerful industry body that represents Amazon, Apple, Google, Meta, Microsoft, Netflix and […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 09:12:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Shares AI-Generated Images Claiming Swifties Are Supporting Him</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/trump-shares-ai-generated-taylor-swift/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>A week after falsely claiming Kamala Harris’ campaign used AI to inflate crowd sizes, Trump is now posting AI-generated photos of Taylor Swift fans endorsing him.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 16:38:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pakistan’s PostEx to enter new markets, starting with Saudi Arabia</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/19/pakistans-postex-to-enter-new-markets-starting-with-saudi-arabia/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Pakistani startup PostEx is entering Saudi Arabia as first global market after hitting $21 million ARR in the South Asian nation. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>