<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 06:49:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Newly Discovered Moon Caves Could One Day House Astronauts</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/moon-tunnels-caves-astronauts-moon-colony/</link><description>Analysis of lunar imagery has ended a longstanding debate over whether there are accessible underground areas on the Moon; an emptied lava tube in the...</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>India’s WazirX confirms security breach following a $230M ‘suspicious transfer’</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/18/indias-wazirx-confirms-security-breach-after-230-million-suspicious-transfer/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The Mumbai-based firm said one of its multisig wallets had suffered a security breach, and it was temporarily pausing all withdrawals from the platfor...</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 10:19:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>There's Still Time to Shop The 313 Absolute Best Prime Day Deals</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-prime-day-deals-2024-1/</link><description>We've been watching, and these deals are going fast. From laptops and tablets to Airpods and Echo dots, grab the best Prime Day deals before it's too ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 23:34:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Samsung to acquire UK-based knowledge graph startup Oxford Semantic Technologies</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/18/samsung-to-acquire-uk-based-knowledge-graph-startup-oxford-semantic-technologies/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The Korean tech giant is acquiring Oxford Semantic Technologies, a U.K.-based knowledge graph startup that has built an AI reasoning engine. © 2024 Te...</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 10:14:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alleged ‘Maniac Murder Cult’ Leader Indicted Over Plot to Kill Jews</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/commander-butcher-maniac-murder-cult-arrested/</link><description>US prosecutors have charged Michail Chkhikvishvili, also known as “Commander Butcher,” with a litany of crimes, including alleged attempts to poison J...</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 23:02:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Artificial Agency raises $16M to use AI to make NPCs feel more realistic in video games</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/18/artificial-agency-raises-video-game-npcs-ai/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>A team of former Google DeepMind researchers are betting that their unique behavior engine for NPCs will make games more fun and dynamic. © 2024 TechC...</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>There's Still Time to Shop the Best Prime Day TV Deals</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/top-5-tv-prime-day-deals-1/</link><description>Our favorite TV deals and home theater deals from Amazon’s big sales event. Find deals on TCL, Hisense, LG, Samsung, and more.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 22:03:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Israel’s startup scene shows reslience despite nine months of war</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/18/israels-startup-scene-shows-reslience-despite-nine-months-of-war/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>When the war between Israel and Hamas broke out last October, we examined its potential impact on the tech ecosystems in Israel and Palestine. Nine mo...</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 08:12:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I Can't Believe These Prime Day Outdoor Deals Aren't Sold Out</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-prime-day-deals-outdoor-gear-2024/</link><description>Less than 12 hours left to snag the best deals on water bottles, bikes, action cameras, and camping gear before I turn off your phone and make you go ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 21:31:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deel acquires Hofy to build its own IT device management service</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/18/deel-acquires-hofy-to-build-its-own-it-device-management-service/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Both of Hofy's co-founders, Sami Bouremoum and Michael Ginzo, along with the rest of the startup's leadership team and 120 employees, are joining Deel...</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>