<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 11:47:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Breville Paradice 16 Review: Doesn't Make the Cut</title><link>https://www.wired.com/review/breville-paradice-16/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Breville’s big food processor is an impressive machine, but its main feature doesn’t work well.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 16:32:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Waymo is now giving 100,000 robotaxi rides a week</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/20/waymo-is-now-giving-100000-robotaxi-rides-week/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Waymo disclosed Tuesday it’s now giving more than 100,000 paid robotaxi rides every week across its three main commercial markets in Los Angeles, San Francisco, and Phoenix. Those figures were shared by Waymo co-CEO Tekedra Mawakana in a social media post on X. The new 100,000 figure is double what the company has previously disclosed. […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 16:32:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>16 Best Paper Planners: Weekly, Daily, and Accessories (2024)</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-paper-planners/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Digital tools are not always superior. Here are some WIRED-tested agendas and notebooks to keep you on track.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 15:35:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Discover how founders and investors are saving the planet at TechCrunch Disrupt 2024</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/20/discover-how-founders-and-investors-are-saving-the-planet-at-techcrunch-disrupt-2024/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Until recently, saving the world usually didn’t involve turning a profit. But as the world has warmed, a range of startups and investors have emerged that have squared the circle, making a clear business case for reducing humanity’s impact on the planet. We’re excited that Rebecca Hu, co-founder and CEO of Glacier; Allison Wolff, co-founder […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Quest to Uncover the Secrets of Gold Hydrogen</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/researchers-head-to-greenland-to-uncover-the-secrets-of-gold-hydrogen/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Industries want to harvest naturally occurring hydrogen as soon as possible, but scientists warn of unforeseen consequences.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 15:34:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>4 days left to save big on TechCrunch Disrupt 2024 tickets</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/20/4-days-left-to-save-big-on-techcrunch-disrupt-2024-tickets/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>The countdown continues! You have 4 days left to lock in your TechCrunch Disrupt 2024 tickets at the discounted rate. Don’t miss the chance to save up to $600 — offer ends August 23 at 11:59 p.m. PT. Join 10,000+ enthusiastic startup leaders, founders, and investors from October 28-30 at Moscone West in San Francisco. […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Modular and Non-Modular PC Power Supply: What's the Difference?</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/pc-power-supply-explainer/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>If you’re in the process of building your desktop, here are all the things you need to know about choosing a power supply unit.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 15:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>US government accuses Iran of Trump campaign hack; Iran scoffs</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/20/us-government-accuses-iran-of-trump-campaign-hack-iran-scoffs/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>On Monday, the U.S. government formally accused Iran of hacking the Donald Trump campaign. In a joint statement issued by the FBI, the Office of the Director of National Intelligence (ODNI) and the Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA), the three agencies said that the intelligence community attributes the recently disclosed hack and leak against […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 15:42:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Back Up Your Slack Archive Before Slack Deletes It</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-move-slack-archive-to-discord/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>The app is going to delete older posts from free workspaces. Here’s how to archive everything—and, if you want to, move your community over to Discord.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 14:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Thirty-nine state AGs now support Live Nation-Ticketmaster lawsuit</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/20/thirty-nine-state-ags-now-support-live-nation-ticketmaster-lawsuit/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>The United States Department of Justice filed a major lawsuit against Live Nation-Ticketmaster in May, arguing that the entertainment giant is acting as a monopoly. An additional 10 state attorneys general joined the suit this week, bringing the total to 39 states and the District of Columbia. The plaintiffs also filed an amended complaint, making […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 15:01:43 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>