<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 06:49:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>How to Build a Hurricane-Proof House</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/hurricane-beryl-proof-housing/</link><description>In the face of longer hurricane seasons filled with more powerful storms, homeowners are turning to new designs and stronger materials to ensure the r...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 11:34:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nala to use $40M Series A to build B2B payments platform, scale remittance services</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/09/nala-series-a/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Nala, a remittance startup that is now widening its portfolio through a new B2B payments platform, has raised $40 million equity in a rare deal that b...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 09:04:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>17 Best Early Amazon Prime Day Deals (2024)</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-early-amazon-prime-day-deals-2024/</link><description>Prime Day falls on July 16 and 17, but we’ve handpicked deals on WIRED-tested products—from tech to blenders to hair straighteners—sitting at some of ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 22:36:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Byway is using AI to help travelers slow down and take the scenic route</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/09/byway-is-using-ai-to-help-travellers-slow-down-and-take-the-scenic-route/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Solo founder Cat Jones took the plunge on setting up a travel business right around the time the pandemic was hitting Europe in March 2020. Fast forwa...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Extreme Wildfires Have Doubled in Frequency and Intensity in the Past 20 Years</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/wild-fires-becoming-more-common-climate-change/</link><description>These findings align with other evidence that wildfires are getting worse—such as the total area burned each year ratcheting up.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 22:04:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Microsoft-owned adtech Xandr accused of EU privacy breaches</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/08/microsoft-owned-adtech-xandr-accused-of-eu-privacy-breaches/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>An adtech business owned by Microsoft is the target of a complaint backed by European privacy advocacy group, noyb — a nonprofit that punches far abov...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Far Right Is Already Demonizing Kamala Harris</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/far-right-attack-kamala-harris/</link><description>Social media platforms, far-right message boards, and extremist Telegram channels are full of misogynistic and racist hatred directed at the vice pres...</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 16:24:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quora’s Poe now lets users create and share web apps</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/08/quoras-poe-now-lets-users-create-and-share-web-apps/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Poe, Quora’s subscription-based, cross-platform aggregator for AI-powered chatbots like Anthropic’s Claude and OpenAI’s GPT-4o, has launched a feature...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 05:40:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best Sheets for Every Body, Bed, and Budget (2024)</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-bedsheets/</link><description>Which material should you buy? Percale or linen? We tested dozens of sheets to find our favorites and break it all down.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian game firms want to distance themselves from fantasy sports</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/08/indian-game-firms-want-to-distance-themselves-from-fantasy-sports/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>For over a decade, real-money gaming companies and fantasy sports startups have marketed themselves as video game companies. But as these businesses f...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:32:36 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>