<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 07:46:37 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>How Hackers Extracted the ‘Keys to the Kingdom’ to Clone HID Keycards</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/hid-keycard-authentication-key-vulnerability/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent3.png</image_url><description>A team of researchers have developed a method for extracting authentication keys out of HID encoders, which could allow hackers to clone the types of keycards used to secure offices and other areas worldwide.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ola Electric surges 20% in India’s biggest listing in two years</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/08/ola-electric-surges-in-indias-biggest-listing-in-two-years/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent2.png</image_url><description>Ola Electric, India’s largest electric two-wheeler maker, surged by 20% on its public debut on Friday, making it the biggest listing among Indian firms in two years. Shares of the Bengaluru-based firm, which counts SoftBank and Temasek among its backers, jumped to ₹91.20 (about $1.1) after starting to trade at ₹76, the higher end of […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 05:48:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Camo Hats Became an Instant Meme</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/camo-hats-harris-walz-instant-meme/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent2.png</image_url><description>This week, Vice President Kamala Harris and Minnesota Governor Tim Walz cemented their bid for the White House with some camouflage caps. The headgear is on its way to red MAGA hat status.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rocket Lab’s sunny outlook bodes well for future constellation plans</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/08/rocket-labs-sunny-outlook-bodes-well-for-future-constellation-plans/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent2.png</image_url><description>Rocket Lab surpassed $100 million in quarterly revenue for the first time, a 71% increase from the same quarter of last year. This is just one of several shiny accomplishments executives showed off to investors on Thursday — and a good omen for the space company’s medium-term ambitious plans. Executives continued to tease plans for […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 00:33:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Olympics' Hostile Architecture Is a Preview of What's to Come</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/paris-los-angeles-olympics-hostile-architecture-homeless/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent.png</image_url><description>Under a bridge in Paris, a homeless encampment has been replaced with dozens of giant Lego-like bricks. Campaigners say things will likely get worse at the 2028 Games in LA.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CloudPay, a payroll services provider, lands $120M in new funding</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/08/cloudpay-a-payroll-services-provider-lands-120m-in-new-funding/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent.png</image_url><description>In 1996, two companies, Patersons HR and Payroll Solutions, formed a venture called CloudPay to provide payroll and payments services to enterprise clients. CloudPay grew quietly over the next several decades, adding workflow automation features to maintain pace with upstart rivals. It’s still growing, CFO Andy Thomson assures TechCrunch. Thomson claims that CloudPay is handling […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 23:20:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Does Jewelry and Big Hair Slow Down Olympic Runners?</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/does-jewelry-slow-down-olympic-runners/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent2.png</image_url><description>Even a little added weight and air drag can make a measurable difference. But WIRED's physics guru says, if it makes you feel strong, go for it!</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Security bugs in ransomware leak sites helped save six companies from paying hefty ransoms</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/08/security-bugs-in-ransomware-leak-sites-helped-save-six-companies-from-paying-hefty-ransoms/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent3.png</image_url><description>The vulnerabilities allowed one security researcher to peek inside the leak sites without having to log in. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 23:20:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cambridge Audio Evo One Review: A Gorgeous High-End Speaker</title><link>https://www.wired.com/review/review-cambridge-audio-evo-one/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent.png</image_url><description>This superbly engineered all-in-one audio system will put a huge smile on your face.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 09:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A comprehensive list of 2024 tech layoffs</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/08/tech-layoffs-2024-list/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent.png</image_url><description>The tech layoff wave is still going strong in 2024. Following significant workforce reductions in 2022 and 2023, this year has already seen 60,000 job cuts across 254 companies, according to independent layoffs tracker Layoffs.fyi. Companies like Tesla, Amazon, Google, TikTok, Snap and Microsoft have conducted sizable layoffs in the first months of 2024. Smaller-sized […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>