<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 06:58:44 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Google’s AI Overview Search Results Copied My Original Work</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/google-ai-overview-search-results-copied-my-original-work/</link><description>Google’s AI feature bumped my article down on the results page, but the new AI Overview at the top still referenced it. What gives?</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SAP to acquire digital adoption platform WalkMe for $1.5B</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/05/sap-to-acquire-digital-adoption-platform-walkme-for-1-5b/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Enterprise software giant SAP is acquiring “digital adoption” platform provider WalkMe in an all-cash transaction worth $1.5 billion. SAP’s $14 per-sh...</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 10:18:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Age of the Drone Police Is Here</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/the-age-of-the-drone-police-is-here/</link><description>A WIRED investigation, based on more than 22 million flight coordinates, reveals the complicated truth about the first full-blown police drone program...</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Modi-led coalition’s election win signals policy continuity in India – but also spending cuts</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/04/modis-third-term-signals-policy-continuity-in-india-but-with-spending-cuts/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The National Democratic Alliance (NDA) has emerged victorious in India’s 2024 general election, but with a smaller majority compared to 2019. Accordin...</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 03:28:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>An American Company Enabled a North Korean Scam That Raised Money for WMDs</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/registered-agents-north-korean-scam-wmds/</link><description>Wyoming’s secretary of state has proposed ways of “preventing fraud and abuse of corporate filings by commercial registered agents” in the aftermath o...</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 10:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A comprehensive list of 2024 tech layoffs</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/04/tech-layoffs-2023-list/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The tech layoff wave is still going strong in 2024. Following significant workforce reductions in 2022 and 2023, this year has already seen 60,000 job...</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 21:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why the EU’s Vice President Isn’t Worried About Moon-Landing Conspiracies on YouTube</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/eu-vice-president-moon-landing-conspiracies-youtube/</link><description>During a tour of Silicon Valley, EU vice president Věra Jourová said she expects tech giants to prioritize stamping out content that could distort dem...</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What to expect from WWDC 2024: iOS 18, macOS 15 and so much AI</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/04/what-to-expect-from-wwdc-2024-ios-18-macos-15-and-so-much-ai/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Apple is hoping to make WWDC 2024 memorable as it finally spells out its generative AI plans. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use...</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 21:18:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>China Miéville Writes a Secret Novel With the Internet’s Boyfriend (It's Keanu Reeves)</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/china-mieville-writes-a-secret-novel-with-the-internets-boyfriend-keanu-reeves/</link><description>After nearly a decade of silence, the beloved sci-fi author opens up about loss, love, and a collaboration with Keanu Reeves. A WIRED exclusive.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The votes are in: Meet the Disrupt 2024 audience choice roundtable winners</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/04/the-votes-are-in-meet-the-disrupt-2024-audience-choice-roundtable-winners/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>We just announced the breakout session winners last week. Now meet the roundtable sessions that really “rounded” out the competition for this year’s D...</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>