<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 06:52:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The Pentagon Is Planning a Drone ‘Hellscape’ to Defend Taiwan</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/china-taiwan-pentagon-drone-hellscape/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>The US Defense Department’s grand strategy for protecting Taiwan from a massive Chinese military offensive involves flooding the zone with thousands of drones.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AMD to acquire infrastructure player ZT Systems for $4.9B to amp up its AI ecosystem play</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/19/amd-to-acquire-infrastructure-player-zt-systems-for-4-9b-to-amp-up-its-ai-ecosystem-play/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>AMD, the chipmaker hot on the heels of Nvidia in the AI computing race, today announced a big acquisition to boost its position as an “ecosystem” partner for companies building big artificial intelligence computing businesses: it announced that it will acquire ZT Systems, which provides compute design and infrastructure for so-called “hyperscalers” (the biggest technology […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 11:38:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>32 Best Family Board Games (2024): Catan, Labyrinth, Onitama</title><link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-family-board-games/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>From monsters to kittens to strategy games, these sets will liven things up on nights when everyone is tired of screens.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 09:36:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amazon considers moving Amazon Pay into a standalone app in India</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/19/amazon-considers-moving-amazon-pay-into-a-standalone-app-in-india/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Amazon is considering shifting its payments offerings in India into a standalone app, three sources familiar with the matter told TechCrunch, as the e-commerce giant aims to boost usage of Amazon Pay in the country. Amazon Pay is currently housed within the company’s primary e-commerce app in India, and lets users transfer money to individuals […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 09:56:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Watch the 2024 Summer Paralympics: Streaming Schedule, Free Options</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-watch-the-2024-paris-summer-paralympics/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>From uber-popular para swimming to “murderball” wheelchair rugby, this year’s Paralympics are full of exciting events. And thanks to a bevy of new streaming options, it’s easier than ever to tune in.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Waza comes out of stealth with $8M to power global trade for African businesses</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/19/waza-comes-out-of-stealth-with-8m-to-power-global-trade-for-african-businesses/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>In May, the African fintech processed up to $70 million in monthly payment volume. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 7 Best Projectors According to Our Reviewers (2024)</title><link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-projectors/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Whether you want a backyard presenter or a theater-quality behemoth, our projector picks will help you upgrade your movie nights.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 16:12:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>As CO2 emissions from supply chains come into focus, this startup is aiming at farms</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/19/as-co2-emissions-from-supply-chains-come-into-focus-this-startup-is-aiming-at-farms/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Root helps food and beverage companies collect primary data on their agricultural supply chains. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Catan: New Energies Review—Climate Crisis Across the Board</title><link>https://www.wired.com/review/catan-new-energies/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>This thoughtful twist on the classic board game illustrates fossil fuel impact on climate change, but it’s also fun.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 16:08:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Digitally resurrecting actors is still a terrible idea</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/18/digitally-resurrecting-actors-is-still-a-terrible-idea/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>This post contains spoilers for the movie “Alien: Romulus” In the long-running “Alien” movie franchise, the Weyland-Yutani Corporation can’t seem to let go of a terrible idea: It keeps trying to make a profit from xenomorphs — creatures with acid for blood and a penchant for violently bursting out of human hosts. The corporation is […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 23:01:17 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>