<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 15:49:40 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>ATM Software Flaws Left Piles of Cash for Anyone Who Knew to Look</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/vss-atm-vulnerabilities-defcon-2024/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Six vulnerabilities in ATM-maker Diebold Nixdorf’s popular Vynamic Security Suite could have been exploited to control ATMs using “relatively simplistic attacks.”</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 19:37:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The X exodus that wasn’t</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/09/the-x-exodus-that-wasnt/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>When digging into the data to determine how large the exodus everyone on Threads is talking about actually is, we oddly came up short. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 19:31:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>19 Best Back-to-School Deals (2024): Backpacks, Chargers, Laptops</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/back-to-school-deals-2024/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>It's time to put away the pool noodles and get those butts back in seats. Save on backpacks, iPads, laptops, and more.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 19:00:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Substack now lets anyone publish posts, even if they don’t have a newsletter</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/09/substack-now-lets-anyone-publish-posts-even-if-they-dont-have-a-newsletter/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Substack is opening up to more users with its recent announcement that anyone can now publish content on its platform without setting up a publication. With the change, Substack is likely looking to attract more types of writers and content creators, not just people who are interested in creating regularly distributed long-form written pieces. While […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 18:59:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 14 Best Amazon Echo and Alexa Speakers (2024): We've Tested Them All</title><link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-alexa-and-amazon-echo-speakers/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>We’ve rounded up our favorites, including third-party devices like the Sonos Era and a voice-enabled Yamaha soundbar.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 18:07:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>China’s autonomous vehicle startup WeRide prepares for a US IPO</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/09/chinas-autonomous-vehicle-startup-weride-prepares-for-a-us-ipo/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>WeRide, a Chinese autonomous vehicle company, is officially gearing up for a U.S. public debut, over a year after China started easing its effective ban of foreign IPOs. WeRide registered 1 billion American Depository Receipts (ADRs) at a maximum price of $0.05, with the aggregate offering coming in at $50 million, per a Friday filing […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 18:15:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Crush House' Is a Game For People Who Love Drama</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/crush-house-is-the-sims-for-people-who-like-drama/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>The “thirst person shooter” puts a dark spin on reality TV.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How a cybersecurity researcher befriended, then doxed, the leader of LockBit ransomware gang</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/09/how-a-cybersecurity-researcher-befriended-then-doxed-the-leader-of-lockbit-ransomware-gang/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Jon DiMaggio used sockpuppet accounts, then his own identity, to infiltrate LockBit and gain the trust of its alleged admin, Dmitry Khoroshev. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 18:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>He Started Out as the ‘Dear Abby’ of Grindr. Now Everyone Wants His Advice</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/dial-up-jp-brammer/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>With the advice column ¡Hola Papi!, JP Brammer tackles life’s most eccentric and heart-wrenching issues—like what to do after realizing your fiance is catfishing you.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 16:18:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI founders play musical chairs</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/09/ai-founders-play-musical-chairs/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Welcome to Startups Weekly — your weekly recap of everything you can’t miss from the world of startups. Want it in your inbox every Friday? Sign up here. This week we are looking at AI founders who are playing musical chairs, a massive defense tech investment, and more issues at Techstars. Let’s get into it. Most […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 18:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>