<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 01:36:07 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Thousands of Corporate Secrets Were Left Exposed. This Guy Found Them All</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/secret-hunting-bill-demirkapi/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Security researcher Bill Demirkapi found more than 15,000 hardcoded secrets and 66,000 vulnerable websites—all by searching overlooked data sources.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The tech world mourns Susan Wojcicki</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/10/the-tech-world-mourns-susan-wojcicki/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Susan Wojcicki, a longtime Googler who spent nearly a decade as the CEO of YouTube, passed away Friday after a two-year battle with non-small cell lung cancer. Wojcicki, who was 56, famously rented the garage of her Menlo Park home to Larry Page and Sergey Brin as they were starting Google. She then became one […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 22:10:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Hacker Who Hunts Video Game Speedrunning Cheaters</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/the-hacker-who-hunts-video-game-speedrunning-cheaters/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Allan “dwangoAC” has made it his mission to expose speedrunning phonies. At the Defcon hacker conference, he’ll challenge one record that's stood for 15 years.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 22:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>As Alexa turns 10, Amazon looks to generative AI</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/10/as-alexa-turns-10-amazon-looks-to-generative-ai/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>While Amazon has continued releasing Echo devices, including an upgraded Spot announced last month, the company has taken its foot off the gas. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple Prototypes and Corporate Secrets Are for Sale Online—If You Know Where to Look</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/apple-prototypes-corporate-data/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>On the hunt for corporate devices being sold secondhand, a researcher found a trove of Apple corporate data, a Mac Mini from the Foxconn assembly line, an iPhone 14 prototype, and more.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 20:35:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Redfin CEO promises to ‘drink our own urine’ if mortgage rates don’t fall</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/10/redfin-ceo-promises-to-drink-our-own-urine-if-mortgage-rates-dont-fall/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>He really said that: When asked about the company’s “Plan B” if mortgage rates don’t fall, Redfin CEO Glenn Kelman responded, “Plan B is to drink our own urine or our competitors’ blood, stay in the foxhole.” This wasn’t at some informal, off-the-record gathering. It was on Redfin’s second quarter earnings call, the kind of […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 21:58:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Former YouTube CEO Susan Wojcicki Dies at 56</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/susan-wojcicki-former-youtube-ceo-dies-at-56/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Susan Wojcicki is one of this era's great unsung executives—and was crucial to Google's trajectory from its very beginnings in her garage.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 18:47:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Turkey restores access to Instagram</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/10/turkey-restores-access-to-instagram/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Turkey appears to have restored access to Meta-owned Instagram, after blocking the app on August 2. Abdulkadir Uraloglu, the country’s minister of transport and infrastructure, posted today that the ban would be lifted at 9:30pm Turkish time. Cybersecurity monitor NetBlocks says, “Live metrics show that Instagram is being gradually restored on internet providers in #Turkey […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 21:26:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HexClad Cookware Review: Unjustifiably Expensive</title><link>https://www.wired.com/review/hexclad/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Want some of the benefits of two separate pans, combined into one pan? HexClad has you covered—sort-of.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 15:07:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tesla’s Dojo, a timeline</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/10/teslas-dojo-a-timeline/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Elon Musk doesn’t want Tesla to be just an automaker. He wants Tesla to be an AI company, one that’s figured out how to make cars drive themselves. Crucial to that mission is Dojo, Tesla’s custom-built supercomputer designed to train its Full Self-Driving (FSD) neural networks. FSD isn’t actually fully self-driving; it can perform some […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 19:59:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>