<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 08:55:40 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Everything You Need to Know About USB Ports and Speeds (2024)</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/usb-ports-speeds-generations-and-thunderbolt-explained/</link><description>USB-C was supposed to make everything simple. Instead, it’s more complicated than ever. So let's clear up the confusion.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CoinDCX acquires BitOasis in international expansion push</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/03/coindcx-acquires-bitoasis-in-international-expansion-push/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>CoinDCX, India’s leading cryptocurrency exchange, is expanding internationally through the acquisition of BitOasis, a digital asset platform in the Mi...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 11:31:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Get a Real ID License Before the Deadline</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-get-a-real-id-license-before-the-may-2025-deadline/</link><description>A new type of driver’s license will be required to board flights in the United States next year. Here’s how to update your license to the new Real ID ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In a major update, Proton adds privacy-safe document collaboration to Drive, its freemium E2EE cloud storage service</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/03/in-major-update-proton-adds-privacy-safe-document-collaboration-to-drive-its-freemium-e2ee-cloud-storage-service/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Collaborative document features are being made available inside Proton Drive, further extending the company's trademark pitch of robust security. © 20...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI Is Rewriting Meme History</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/ai-is-rewriting-meme-history/</link><description>TikTok’s latest trend involves videos of people traveling back in time to interrupt the viral memes of yore. The results are uncanny.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Telegram lets creators share paid content to channels</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/03/telegram-lets-creators-share-paid-content-to-channels/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Telegram launched a digital currency called Stars for in-app use last month. Now, the company is expanding its use cases to paid content. The chat app...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 10:47:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Inside a16z’s Boot Camp for Crypto Startups</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/inside-a16zs-boot-camp-for-crypto-startups/</link><description>Andreessen Horowitz is betting the house on crypto. (Yes, really.) This spring, the VC firm schooled a new batch of founders that it hopes can prove t...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 11:36:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Altrove uses AI models and lab automation to create new materials</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/03/altrove-uses-ai-models-and-lab-automation-to-create-new-materials/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>For the past couple of years, innovation has been accelerating in new materials development. And a new French startup called Altrove plans to play a r...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Proton Is Launching Encrypted Documents to Take On Google Docs</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/proton-docs-end-to-end-encryption-google-docs/</link><description>Proton is adding an end-to-end encrypted documents editor to its privacy tools, boosting its competition with Google’s suite of productivity apps.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian social network Koo is shutting down as buyout talks collapse</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/02/indian-social-network-koo-to-shut-down/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The Indian social media platform Koo, which positioned itself as a competitor to Elon Musk’s X, is ceasing operations after its last-resort acquisitio...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 07:56:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>