<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 06:47:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Amazfit Helio Review: Woefully Behind and Lacking Features</title><link>https://www.wired.com/review/amazfit-helio/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Amazfit’s fledgling smart ring pairs well with the company's smartwatches. But the ring is not ready to go it alone.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 11:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Conduit’s cross-border payments expand from LatAm into Africa with $6M round</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/12/conduits-cross-border-payments-expand-from-latam-into-africa-with-6m-round/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Cross-border payments for businesses in emerging markets remain significantly untapped, despite small to large businesses using banks and legacy fintechs to transact trillions of dollars in transaction volume annually. A report by Airwallex forecasts that the value of cross-border payments will grow by 60%, reaching $250 trillion by 2027. Between 2018 and 2022, the value […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 10:58:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Flush With Cash, Tether Has Got Microsoft, Google, and Amazon in Its Crosshairs</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/tether-ceo-paolo-ardoino-crypto-ai-interview/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Under new CEO Paolo Ardoino, the crypto company is spending heavily in a bid to muscle into an AI market dominated by the world’s largest tech firms.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharti will become BT’s biggest shareholder after buying a 25%, $4B stake from Altice</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/12/bharti-will-become-bts-biggest-shareholder-after-buying-a-25-4b-stake-from-altice/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>BT, the U.K.’s former incumbent telecoms carrier, is picking up a major new investor today as telecoms companies look for stronger footing in the rapidly-shifting technology and communications market. Bharti, the Indian tech and telecoms giant that owns Airtel, said it would purchase a 24.5% stake currently owned by Altice. Based on BT’s market cap […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 08:40:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Watch the Made by Google Pixel 9 Launch Event, and What to Expect</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/made-by-google-2024-pixel-9-launch-event-how-to-watch-what-to-expect/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>At its media event Tuesday, Google will unveil four new flagship Pixel handsets, new Pixel Watches, and new Pixel Buds. We can also expect a whole lot of Gemini. Here’s how to tune in.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elon Musk’s X targeted with nine privacy complaints after grabbing EU users’ data for training Grok</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/11/elon-musks-x-targeted-with-eight-privacy-complaints-after-grabbing-eu-users-data-for-training-grok/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>X, the social media platform owned by Elon Musk, has been targeted with a series of privacy complaints after it helped itself to the data of users in the European Union for training AI models without asking people’s consent. Late last month an eagle-eyed social media user spotted a setting indicating that X had quietly […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>29 Great Gifts for Mom: Ideas for the Mother in Your Life (2024)</title><link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/gifts-for-mom/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>There are many kinds of mothers, but these are our favorite picks for the WIRED mom in your life.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 16:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>India’s Kazam powers up to roll out EV charging in Southeast Asia</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/11/indias-kazam-powers-up-to-roll-out-ev-charging-in-southeast-asia/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Kazam, an Indian EV charging solution provider, has raised $8 million to expand its footprint in the country and enter Southeast Asian markets. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 05:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>13 Best USB Flash Drives (2024): Pen Drives, Thumb Drives, Memory Sticks</title><link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-usb-flash-drives/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>These WIRED-tested memory sticks are a virtual filing cabinet in your pocket.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 15:16:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Scott Painter is selling a beach house to start a new vehicle software company</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/11/scott-painter-autonomy-ads-vehicle-subscription-softwar/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Autonomy founder Scott Painter is spinning out a new company called Autonomy Data Services, or ADS, he tells TechCrunch in an exclusive interview. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>