<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 06:59:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Mill Food Recycler Review: Trendy and Spendy</title><link>https://www.wired.com/review/mill-food-recycler/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>This smart food-scrap trash can is not worth the hefty price tag.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 11:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nancy Pelosi criticizes California AI bill as ‘ill-informed’</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/17/nancy-pelosi-criticizes-california-ai-bill-as-ill-informed/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Congresswoman Nancy Pelosi issued a statement late yesterday laying out her opposition to SB 1047, a California bill that seeks to regulate AI. “The view of many of us in Congress is that SB 1047 is well-intentioned but ill-informed,” Pelosi said. She noted that other congresspeople from the Bay Area — Zoe Lofgren, Anna Eshoo, […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>13 Best Bluetooth Speakers Our Testers Jammed With in 2024</title><link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-bluetooth-speakers/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>These are our favorite portable speakers of all shapes and sizes, from clip-ons to a massive boom box.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 16:11:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Palantir CEO Alex Karp is ‘not going to apologize’ for military work</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/17/palantir-ceo-alex-karp-is-not-going-to-apologize-for-military-work/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Data analytics company Palantir has faced criticism and even protests over its work with the military, police, and U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement, but co-founder and CEO Alex Karp isn’t interested in “the apology show.” In a lengthy New York Times profile, Karp told writer Maureen Dowd that the company has “a consistently pro-Western view” […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 22:11:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 10 Best TVs We’ve Reviewed, Plus Buying Advice (2024)</title><link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-tvs/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>From LEDs to fancy OLED models, these are our favorite televisions at every price.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 15:31:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Porsche NA CEO Timo Resch is betting on ‘choice’ to survive the turbulent EV market</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/17/why-porsche-na-ceo-timo-resch-is-betting-on-choice-to-survive-the-turbulent-ev-market/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Timo Resch is basking in the sun. That’s literally true, as we speak on a gloriously clear California day at the Quail, one of Monterey Car Week’s most prestigious events. But it’s figuratively true as well, as Resch, who took the CEO role at Porsche Cars North America (PCNA) last November, is in a very […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 20:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The New Sonos App Is So Bad, the Company Might Bring Back the Old One</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/new-sonos-app-is-bad-company-considers-bringing-back-the-old-one/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Plus: Play Uno in your BMW, play Diablo on your browser, read The Onion in print again, and maybe don’t try to call people from your Starlink cell phone.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Google takes on OpenAI with Gemini Live</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/17/google-takes-on-openai-with-gemini-live/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Made by Google was this week, featuring a full range of reveals from Google’s biggest hardware event. Google unveiled its new lineup of Pixel 9 phones, including the $1,799 Pixel 9 Fold Pro; advanced AI-powered photo-editing tools; and the new Pixel Buds Pro 2, which are infused with Gemini AI. The company also announced Gemini […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 18:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Geofence Warrants Ruled Unconstitutional—but That’s Not the End of It</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/geofence-warrants-ruled-unconstitutional-tmobile-fine-deepfake-nudes-lawsuit/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Plus: US regulators fine T-Mobile $60 million for mishap with sensitive data, New Zealand approves Kim Dotcom’s US extradition, and San Francisco takes on deepfake porn.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OpenAI’s new voice mode let me talk with my phone, not to it</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/17/openais-new-voice-mode-let-me-talk-with-my-phone-not-to-it/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>I’ve been playing around with OpenAI’s Advanced Voice Mode for the last week, and it’s the most convincing taste I’ve had of an AI-powered future yet. This week, my phone laughed at jokes, made them back to me, asked me how my day was, and told me it’s having “a great time.” I was talking […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>