<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 06:55:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>We Asked AI to Take Us On a Tour of Our Cities. It Was Chaos</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/littlefoot-ai-chatbot-travel-planner/</link><description>We had a specialty chatbot to curate perfect days out in London and New York for under $100 each. We're still recovering from our journeys.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CrowdStrike update causes major IT outage, taking out banks, airlines and businesses across the world</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/19/banks-airlines-brokerage-houses-report-widespread-outages-across-the-globe/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Businesses across the world are reporting IT outages, including Windows “blue screen of death” errors on their computers, in what has already become o...</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 08:40:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Huge Microsoft Outage Linked to CrowdStrike Takes Down Computers Around the World</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/microsoft-windows-outage-crowdstrike-global-it-probems/</link><description>A software update from cybersecurity company CrowdStrike appears to have inadvertently disrupted IT systems globally.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 09:40:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paytm loss widens and revenue shrinks as it grapples with regulatory clampdown</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/18/paytm-loss-widens-and-revenue-shrinks-following-regulatory-clampdown/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Indian fintech Paytm’s struggles won’t seem to end. The company on Friday reported that its revenue declined by 36% and its loss more than doubled in ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 07:21:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 31 Best Movies on Hulu This Week (July 2024)</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-movies-hulu-right-now/</link><description>Ferrari, Perfect Days, and Get Out are just a few of the movies you need to watch on Hulu right now.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fandango founder dies in fall from Manhattan skyscraper</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/18/fandango-founder-dies-in-fall-from-manhattan-skyscraper/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>J. Michael Cline, the co-founder of Fandango and multiple other startups over his multi-decade career, died after falling from a Manhattan hotel, New ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 00:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>J.D. Vance Left His Venmo Public. Here’s What It Shows</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/jd-vance-venmo/</link><description>The Republican VP nominee's Venmo network reveals connections ranging from the architects of Project 2025 to enemies of Donald Trump—and the populist'...</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 18:02:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple Vision Pro debuts immersive content featuring NBA players, The Weeknd and more</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/18/apple-immersive-video-new-content-vision-pro/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Apple on Thursday announced its upcoming lineup of immersive video content for the Vision Pro. The list includes behind-the-scenes footage of the 2024...</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 21:14:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Missed Out on Prime Day? These 155 Deals Are Still Going Strong (2024)</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/leftover-prime-day-deals-2024/</link><description>You can still snag many of the same Prime Day deals on security cameras, hair straighteners, and iPads—though these discounts are quickly disappearing...</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 17:42:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elon Musk is now a villain in Joe Biden’s presidential campaign</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/18/elon-musk-is-now-a-villain-in-joe-bidens-presidential-campaign/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Biden centering Musk in his campaign is a notable escalation, considering he spent most of his presidency seemingly pretending the billionaire didn't ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 21:03:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>