<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 06:58:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Tuariki Delamere’s Somersault Could Have Launched a New Era in the Olympic Long Jump</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/physics-of-the-banned-front-flip-long-jump/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>The New Zealander came up with a better way to jump, using a front flip in midair. But the sport’s stodgy authorities shut him down before the 1975 Games.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 11:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Terraform Labs co-founder and crypto fugitive, Do Kwon, set for extradition to South Korea</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/02/terraform-labs-co-founder-and-crypto-fugitive-do-kwon-set-for-extradition-to-south-korea/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>&lt;p&gt;The Appellate Court of Montenegro ruled on Thursday that Terraform Labs co-founder, Do Kwon, should be returned to his home country, South Korea. The ruling confirmed an earlier decision in April from the High Court of Podgorica which rejected a request to extradite the crypto fugitive to the U.S. The extradition date for Kwon to [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 09:54:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How the ‘Slamming Door’ Sound Became Embedded in Hip-Hop History</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/korg-tribe-slam-sound-hip-hop-history/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>If you’ve listened to any rap or pop music made in the 21st century, you’ve heard John Lehmkuhl’s most famous creation, a thwacking metallic percussion sample named “Tribe.”</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meta’s Threads crosses 200 million active users</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/02/metas-threads-cross-200-million-active-users/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>&lt;p&gt;A day after Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg talked about his newest social media experiment Threads reaching &amp;#8220;almost&amp;#8221; 200 million users on the company&amp;#8217;s Q2 2024 earnings call, the platform has touched the milestone. Instagram head Adam Mosseri confirmed that the Twitter rival has reached 200M active users in a post on Threads. Meta has taken [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 09:40:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Intel Is Cutting More Than 15,000 Jobs Despite Getting Billions From the US Government</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/intel-job-cuts/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>The chipmaker, which has fallen behind competitors, is slashing 15 percent of its workforce.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 22:26:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Connect with Google Cloud, Aerospace, Qualcomm and more at Disrupt 2024</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/01/connect-with-google-cloud-aerospace-qualcomm-and-more-at-disrupt-2024/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>&lt;p&gt;TechCrunch Disrupt 2024 will be in San Francisco on October 28–30, and we’re already excited! Disrupt brings innovation for every stage of your startup journey, and we could not bring you this world-class event without our world-class partners. Take advantage of the opportunity to leverage the expertise and resources of some of tech’s leading companies. Their participation [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How 'World of Warcraft' Devs Launched One of the Biggest Unions in Video Games</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/world-of-warcraft-union-vidoe-games-labor/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>Microsoft’s acquisition of Activision Blizzard created an environment that helped workers. Amid layoffs and worries about AI, their efforts could be an indicator of the future of the industry.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 21:36:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A comprehensive list of 2024 tech layoffs</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/01/tech-layoffs-2024-list/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>&lt;p&gt;The tech layoff wave is still going strong in 2024. Following significant workforce reductions in 2022 and 2023, this year has already seen 60,000 job cuts across 254 companies, according to independent layoffs tracker Layoffs.fyi. Companies like Tesla, Amazon, Google, TikTok, Snap and Microsoft have conducted sizable layoffs in the first months of 2024. Smaller-sized [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 00:10:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Shameful Controversy Over Olympic Boxer Imane Khelif</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/imane-khelif-olympic-boxer-controversy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Imane Khelif has always defined herself as a woman, and has every right to compete.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 21:30:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Intel to lay off 15,000 employees</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/01/intel-to-lay-off-15000-employees/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>&lt;p&gt;Intel announced it would layoff more than 15% of its staff, or 15,000 employees, in a memo to employees on Thursday. The massive headcount is part of a large plan to reduce spending by $10 billion in 2025, following a dismal second quarter earnings report and outlook. &amp;#8220;Our revenues have not grown as expected – [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 00:05:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>