<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:09:37 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Our 9 Favorite Pizza Ovens: Wood, Gas, and Electric (2024)</title><link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-pizza-ovens-1/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Craving carb-y comfort? We picked our favorite outdoor ovens for backyards, countertops, or camping.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 17:07:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WeRide preps for an IPO, meet the man who built a startup pipeline at CNH and Waymo’s nightly honk-a-thon</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/15/weride-preps-for-an-ipo-meet-the-man-who-built-a-startup-pipeline-at-cnh-and-waymos-nightly-honk-a-thon/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Welcome back to TechCrunch Mobility — your central hub for news and insights on the future of transportation. Sign up here for free — just click TechCrunch Mobility! We brought you a Tesla Dojo explainer last week. Now we’re giving you a handy Dojo timeline that tracks the progress of Tesla’s AI supercomputer. The timeline […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Researchers Have Ranked AI Models Based on Risk—and Found a Wild Range</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/ai-models-risk-rank-studies/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Studies suggest that regulations could be tightened to head off AI misbehavior.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meta’s X rival Threads gains multiple drafts, audience insights and more</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/15/threads-starts-testing-multiple-drafts-says-posts-scheduling-coming-soon/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Meta’s X rival Threads announced a number of new features today, including the ability to store multiple drafts, a way to rearrange columns on the desktop, and insights into the user’s audience. Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg also mentioned that the company plans to add a post-scheduling feature soon. The company noted that these new features […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dyson OnTrac Headphones Review: A Solid, Visually Customizable Pair</title><link>https://www.wired.com/review/dyson-ontrac/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Dyson’s noise-canceling headphones look like vacuums but sound better than AirPods Max.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:16:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Geekbench releases AI benchmarking app</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/15/geekbench-releases-ai-benchmarking-app/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>It’s a successor to Geekbench ML. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best Cooling Sheets for Hot Summer Nights, Tested and Reviewed (2024)</title><link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-cooling-sheets/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Summer heat is here. Hop under these cooling sheets so that you can, you know, actually sleep.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 15:35:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Franki’s app rewards you for posting video reviews of local restaurants</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/15/franki-video-restaurant-review-app-rewards-program/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Franki is a social discovery and video-based review app where users can interact with a community of foodies, discover local dining spots, and create their own videos showing off their favorite restaurants. Franki recently underwent a brand refresh, which included the introduction of a new “Social Club” rewards program. This program rewards creators for posting […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 17:40:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Samsung S90D QD-OLED TV Review: Flagship Picture for Less</title><link>https://www.wired.com/review/samsung-s90d-qd-oled/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>This second-tier television is a colorful powerhouse loaded with value.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 15:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Announcing judges for the Startup Battlefield at TechCrunch Disrupt 2024</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/15/announcing-judges-for-the-startup-battlefield-at-techcrunch-disrupt-2024/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>The Startup Battlefield is one of the highlights of Disrupt, and we can’t wait to see which of the thousands of applicants will be selected to pitch to panels of top-tier VCs at TechCrunch Disrupt 2024, taking place on October 28–30 in San Francisco. It’s always epic, and every contender is on the road to making a […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>