<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 06:53:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The Run of Record-Breaking Heat Has Ended, for Now</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/13-month-heat-streak-ended-climate-change-global-warming-sea-surface-temperatures/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Air temperatures in July 2024 were fractionally cooler than in July 2023, probably because of a waning El Niño. But don’t expect things to be much cooler in coming years.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gogoro delays India plans due to policy uncertainty, launches bike-taxi pilot with Rapido</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/16/gogoro-delays-india-plans-due-to-policy-uncertainty-launches-bike-taxi-pilot-with-rapido/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Gogoro has deferred its India plans over delay in government incentives, but the Taiwanese company has partnered with Rapido for a bike-taxi pilot. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Slow-Burn Nightmare of the National Public Data Breach</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/national-public-data-breach-leak/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Social Security numbers, physical addresses, and more—all available online. After months of confusion, leaked information from a background-check firm underscores the long-term risks of data breaches.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 19:31:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A16z offers social media tips after its founder’s ‘attack’ tweet goes viral</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/16/a16z-offers-social-media-tips-after-its-founders-attack-tweet-goes-viral/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>On Friday, the venture firm Andreessen Horowitz tweeted out a link to its guide on how to “build your social media presence” which features advice for founders. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 23:59:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Is Gemini Live and How Do You Use It?</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/what-is-gemini-live/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Google is rolling out this new voice assistant, and now you can have real-time, natural conversations with its chatbot. Here’s what it’s like.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 17:56:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OpenAI shuts down election influence operation that used ChatGPT</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/16/openai-shuts-down-election-influence-operation-using-chatgpt/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>OpenAI has banned a cluster of ChatGPT accounts linked to an Iranian influence operation that was generating content about the U.S. presidential election, according to a blog post on Friday. The company says the operation created AI-generated articles and social media posts, though it doesn’t seem that it reached much of an audience. This is […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 21:09:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NASA Nears Decision Time on Boeing Starliner’s Fate</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/nasa-boeing-starliner-decision/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>There’s now a significant chance the spacecraft’s crew will have to return to Earth on a different one—and maybe not until next year.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 17:18:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple reportedly has ‘several hundred’ working on a robot arm with attached iPad</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/16/apple-reportedly-has-several-hundred-working-on-a-robot-arm-with-attached-ipad/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Apple is reportedly shifting into the world of home robots after the wheels came off its electric car. According to a new report from Bloomberg, a team of several hundred is working on its potential first product: a robotic arm with an “iPad-like” display attached. The home product would take a page out of Amazon’s […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 20:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to See the Conjunction Between Mars, Jupiter, and the Moon</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-see-the-conjunction-between-mars-jupiter-and-the-moon-this-august/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>On the 27th, the celestial bodies will form an unusual triangle in the sky just before dawn.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 16:53:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Another week in the circle of startup life</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/16/another-week-in-the-circle-of-startup-life/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Welcome to Startups Weekly — your weekly recap of everything you can’t miss from the world of startups. I’m Anna Heim from TechCrunch’s international team, and I’ll be writing this newsletter moving forward. Want it in your inbox every Friday? Sign up here. This week, we’re looking at some companies being created, funded, shut down and […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>