<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 12:07:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>How to See the Conjunction Between Mars, Jupiter, and the Moon</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-see-the-conjunction-between-mars-jupiter-and-the-moon-this-august/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>On the 27th, the celestial bodies will form an unusual triangle in the sky just before dawn.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 16:53:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TechCrunch Minute: Lockheed Martin rescues satellite manufacturer Terran Orbital</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/video/watch-lockheed-martin-rescues-satellite-manufacturer-terran-orbital/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Lockheed Martin is acquiring satellite manufacturer Terran Orbital, taking the smaller company private and potentially rescuing it from running out of cash while facing of serious debt. Although Terran Orbital itself wasn’t founded until 2013, its history goes back to the late ’90s, to the development of the CubeSat, which became the flagship in a […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best Field Recorders for Portable Audio</title><link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-field-recorders/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Tired of recording on your cell phone? These portable field recorders are fantastic for everything from interviews to concerts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 15:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>African e-commerce company Jumia completes sale of secondary shares at $99.6M</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/16/african-e-commerce-company-jumia-completes-sale-of-secondary-shares-at-99-6m/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Almost two weeks ago, TechCrunch reported that African e-commerce giant Jumia was planning to sell 20 million American depositary shares (ADSs) and raise over $100 million, given its share price of around $5.70 at the time. The e-tailer has now completed the at-the-market transaction offering of 20,227,736 ADSs. Jumia sold the shares at an average […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 16:18:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kamala Harris’ Brat Summer Is Almost Over. What’s Next?</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/kamala-harris-social-media-brat/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Writer and critic Hunter Harris has some thoughts on Kamala Harris’ social media strategy, and whether the vice president can sustain her moment in the online spotlight until November.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 14:47:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Only 7 days left to save on TechCrunch Disrupt 2024 tickets</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/16/only-7-days-left-to-save-on-disrupt-2024-tickets/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>We’re entering the final week of discounted rates for TechCrunch Disrupt 2024. Save up to $600 on select individual ticket types until August 23. Join a dynamic crowd of over 10,000 attendees, startup founders and VC investors at Moscone West in San Francisco from October 28-30. Here are just a few big reasons to attend […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elon Musk Is No Climate Hero</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/elon-musk-trump-climate-tesla/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>During a live interview with Republican presidential nominee Donald Trump, the former president literally said, “Drill, baby, drill.” Musk met the statement with … silence.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘Fortnite’ maker Epic Games launches its app store on iOS in the EU, worldwide on Android</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/16/fortnite-maker-epic-games-launches-its-app-store-on-ios-in-the-eu-worldwide-on-android/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Epic Games, the maker of Fortnite, announced on Friday that it has officially launched its rival iOS app store in the European Union. The Epic Games Store is also launching on Android worldwide. The app store is launching with games including Fortnite, Rocket League Sideswipe and Fall Guys. The company says it’s working with developers […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 14:39:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Set Up Your New Android Phone (2024)</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-set-up-your-new-android-phone/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Welcome to your shiny new Google-powered mobile device. It will be up and ready in no time with these handy tips.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 13:38:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Google is bringing AI overviews to India, Brazil, Japan, UK, Indonesia and Mexico</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/16/google-is-bringing-ai-overviews-to-india-brazil-japan-uk-indonesia-and-mexico/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>After bringing AI overviews to the U.S., Google is expanding the AI-powered search summaries to six more countries: India, Brazil, Japan, the U.K., Indonesia and Mexico. These markets will also get local language support for AI overviews. The search giant is rethinking how it displays source material links, as well. It’s adding a view on […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 14:36:13 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>