<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 16:16:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>War Crime Prosecutions Enter a New Digital Age</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/icc-investigation-digital-media/</link><description>A custom platform developed by SITU Research aided the International Criminal Court’s prosecution in a war crimes trial for the first time. It could c...</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 18:35:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sonia’s AI chatbot steps in for therapists</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/26/sonias-ai-chatbot-steps-in-for-therapists/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Can chatbots replace human therapists? Some startups — and patients — claim that they can. But it’s not exactly settled science. One study found that ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 21:12:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Shop Like a Pro During Amazon Prime Day - July 2024</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/amazon-prime-day-2024-tips-to-find-best-deals/</link><description>We’ve got tips to help you cut through the clutter to find real Amazon Prime Day deals.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 18:23:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dream Chaser spaceplane is off the manifest for ULA’s second Vulcan launch</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/26/dream-chaser-spaceplane-is-off-the-manifest-for-ulas-second-vulcan-launch/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Sierra Space said that despite the slip, its first Dream Chaser spaceplane is still on track for its maiden mission before the end of the year. © 2024...</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 20:48:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Russian Propaganda Network Is Promoting an AI-Manipulated Biden Video</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/russia-disinformation-network-ai-generated-biden-video/</link><description>Experts tell WIRED that Russian disinformation campaigns are using generative AI more and more.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 17:32:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Google improves search experience in the Chrome mobile app</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/26/google-chrome-mobile-app-updates-ios-android/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Facing new competition from startups like Arc, Google announced on Wednesday that it’s bringing five new features to the Chrome browser on mobile devi...</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 20:16:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Supreme Court Rules That US Government Can Continue Talking to Social Media Companies</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/scotus-us-government-talk-social-media-companies/</link><description>The SCOTUS ruling overturns an earlier injunction that prevented platforms from communicating with the government for more than a year.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 16:27:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Persona’s founders are certain the world can use another humanoid robot</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/26/personas-founders-are-certain-the-world-can-use-another-humanoid-robot/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>At this early stage, Persona’s pitch doesn’t stray far from the various humanoid firms with which it’s set to compete. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights r...</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 19:21:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best Hearing Aids of 2024, Reviewed by Experts</title><link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-hearing-aids/</link><description>These WIRED-tested and audiologist-approved devices will help you hear sounds more clearly. Never miss out on a dinner conversation again.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Week in AI: The fate of generative AI is in the courts’ hands</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/26/this-week-in-ai-the-fate-of-generative-ai-is-in-the-courts-hands/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Hiya, folks, and welcome to TechCrunch’s regular AI newsletter. This week in AI, music labels accused two startups developing AI-powered song generato...</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 18:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>