<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 07:26:08 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Elon Musk Has Turned X Into His Personal Political Playground</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/musk-trump-support-x/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>Elon Musk accused Twitter’s leadership of tipping the scales politically. But now he’s doing just that with X.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elon Musk’s X taken to court in Ireland for grabbing EU user data to train Grok without consent</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/07/elon-musks-x-taken-to-court-in-ireland-for-grabbing-eu-user-data-to-train-grok-without-consent/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk's X is being taken to court in Ireland for using Europeans' data to train AI models without asking for their consent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 11:02:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kamala Harris’ Campaign Is a Windfall for Influencers</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/harris-campaign-influencers/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>The switch from Joe Biden to Kamala Harris atop the Democratic ticket has been a boon for the campaign—and content creators.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Automattic launches AI writing tool that aims to make WordPress blogs more readable and succinct</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/07/automattic-launches-ai-writing-tool-that-aims-to-make-wordpress-blogs-more-readable-and-succinct/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>&lt;p&gt;Automattic, the owner of WordPress.com, has launched a new AI tool designed to help bloggers write more clearly and succinctly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 10:32:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CrowdStrike Faces a Potential Tsunami of Lawsuits. Only the Fine Print Can Save It, Experts Say</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/crowdstrike-outage-microsoft-delta-lawsuits-analysis/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>After crashing millions of computers and disrupting businesses across the globe, cybersecurity company CrowdStrike must protect itself against a flurry of legal activity that is already beginning. The devil will be in the details.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>EQT takes a majority stake in cybersecurity firm Acronis at $3.5B+ valuation</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/07/eqt-takes-a-majority-stake-in-cybersecurity-firm-acronis-at-a-3-5b-valuation/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>&lt;p&gt;Cybersecurity remains a white-hot space for investors. In the latest example of that demand, EQT has bought a majority stake in Acronis, a security company that specializes in data protection, cloud and integrated security solutions for managed service providers (which resell services to consumers) and corporate IT teams. The size and value of the stake, [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 08:26:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>She’s the New Face of Climate Activism—and She’s Carrying a Pickax</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/climate-activism-radical-new-face-lena-lazare/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>Sabotage. Property destruction. For Léna Lazare and her cohort, radicalized by years of inaction on the environmental crisis, these aren’t dirty words. They’re acts of joy.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>UK data watchdog to fine NHS vendor Advanced for security failures prior to LockBit ransomware attack</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/06/uk-data-watchdog-fines-nhs-vendor-advanced-for-security-failures-prior-to-lockbit-ransomware-attack/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>&lt;p&gt;The ICO issued the provisional fine in "failing to implement appropriate security measures prior to the attack."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 00:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A US Judge Ruled That Google Is an Illegal Monopolist. Here's What Might Come Next</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/google-search-monopoly-judge-amit-mehta-options/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>Judge Amit Mehta’s ruling has triggered a potentially yearslong process to decide how to punish the company. For users, it could mean a future in which Google isn’t front and center everywhere.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 23:02:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jumia plans to raise more than $100 million in secondary shares to drive stalled user growth</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/06/jumia-plans-to-raise-more-than-100-million-in-secondary-shares-to-drive-stalled-user-growth/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>&lt;p&gt;African e-commerce company Jumia is selling 20 million American depositary shares over the next couple of weeks, TechCrunch has learned. The at-the-market transaction is to take advantage of strong results despite a volatile market.&amp;#160; Given Jumia’s share price of around $5.70 when the stock market opened on Tuesday, the e-commerce company could potentially raise approximately [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 00:00:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>