<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:45:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Trump's Shooting Rattled QAnon Believers. Then They Doubled Down</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/trumps-shooting-rattled-qanon-believers-then-they-doubled-down/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>A month after the attempted assassination of Donald Trump, QAnon believers and their families are still stuck in a cycle of despair.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:54:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Palo Alto Networks CEO apologizes for happy hour display featuring women with lampshades on their heads</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/14/palo-alto-networks-ceo-apologies-for-happy-hour-display-featuring-women-with-lampshades-on-their-heads/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Cybersecurity giant Palo Alto Networks is getting a lot of grief for a recent trade show event in which two women posed with lampshades on their heads. The debacle — which unflatteringly recalls the CES booth babes of the early ’90s and 2000s — reportedly happened at a happy hour hosted by CyberRisk Collaborative and […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 18:37:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gamergate’s Aggrieved Men Still Haunt the Internet</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/gamergates-aggrieved-men-still-haunt-the-internet/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Ten years ago, much of the frustrations gamers were expressing came from anger over no longer being the target audience. Now those feelings are everywhere, from fandom to politics.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 14:29:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Week in AI: AI isn’t world-ending — but it’s still plenty harmful</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/14/this-week-in-ai-ai-isnt-world-ending-but-its-still-plenty-harmful/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Hiya, folks, welcome to TechCrunch’s regular AI newsletter. This week in AI, a new study shows that generative AI really isn’t all that harmful — at least not in the apocalyptic sense. In a paper submitted to the Association for Computational Linguistics’ annual conference, researchers from the University of Bath and University of Darmstadt argue […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 18:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nascar Pit Crews Are Using AI for the Perfect Pit Stop</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/lenovo-has-built-richard-childress-racing-its-own-nascar-pit-stop-ai/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>In a sport where speed is everything, Richard Childress Racing has embraced artificial intelligence to time its refueling down to the millisecond.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Camera app Halide’s latest update adds an option for ‘zero-AI’ image processing</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/14/camera-app-halides-latest-update-adds-an-option-for-zero-ai-image-processing/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Popular iOS pro photography app Halide launched its new version today with a new feature called Process Zero, which does not use AI in image processing. Lux Optics, the company behind the Halide app, believes that this option can be a creative tool for photographers to take different kinds of snaps. The company previously allowed […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Gargantuan Lab Simulates Blasting Satellites Into Space</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/national-satellite-testing-facility-uk-nstf/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>If you spend millions of dollars developing a satellite, you need to know it can handle the rigors of hurtling around the Earth at 17,000 mph. The UK's National Satellite Test Facility is here to help.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Definity raises $4.5M as it looks to transform data application observability</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/14/definity-raises-4-5m-as-it-looks-to-transform-data-application-observability/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Definity focuses on the data transformation plane on top of a data lake or warehouse, not the data ingestion part of the pipeline. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 17:59:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Supplements Companies Are Cashing In on the Ozempic Wave</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/the-ozempic-adjacent-supplement-gold-rush-is-just-getting-started/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>With demand for GLP-1 drugs sky-high, the supplement industry is elbowing into the market. Some products are meant to complement meds like Ozempic. Others are positioned as “natural” alternatives.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Databricks reportedly paid $2 billion in Tabular acquisition</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/14/databricks-reportedly-paid-2-billion-in-tabular-acquisition/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Analytics and AI giant Databricks reportedly paid nearly $2 billion when it acquired Tabular in June, a startup that was only doing $1 million in annual recurring revenue, according to Bloomberg. That’s a pretty outrageous exit multiple, and it was purportedly fueled by a battle between Databricks and Snowflake. Tabular had over $30 million in […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 17:44:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>