<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 06:55:52 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Black Sororities and Fraternities Are Mobilizing Online and in Secret Chats for Voter Turnout</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/black-sororities-and-fraternities-mobilizing-online-voting/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Across the United States, members of Black Greek organizations are using everything from large social media accounts to secret group chats with the single aim of increasing turnout in November.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>She grew up a gearhead — now her startup has raised $4.3M to cut CO2 from trucking</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/13/she-grew-up-a-gearhead-now-her-startup-has-raised-4m-to-cut-co2-from-trucking/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>The irony was not lost on her. Growing up the daughter of a family obsessed with car racing, Danielle Walsh had become — in her late 20s — the head of HSBC’s ‘Future Cities’ project, the global banking giant’s effort to serve clients’ climate change mandates. It was 2018, and she was reporting both into the […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:18:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Made by Google Live Blog: New Pixel Phones, Smartwatches, Gemini, and More</title><link>https://www.wired.com/live/made-by-google-2024-live-blog/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>We're live at the “Made by Google” event. We'll be bringing you up-to-the-minute news updates about the Pixel phones, watches, earbuds, and Google Gemini.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Opera is releasing its redesigned browser on iOS</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/13/opera-is-releasing-its-redesigned-browser-on-ios/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Opera is releasing its redesigned Opera One browser on iOS as a stable release after testing it in the beta phase for weeks. The new browser has a bottom placed search bar for easy browsing, quick search suggestions while typing, and Aria AI assistant integration. While the placed search bar will be the default option, […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Best Teacher Discounts (2024): Deals on School Supplies and Tech</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/best-teacher-discounts/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Ace the school year with special perks—like cheap software, phone plans, and classroom supplies.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The crypto founder who didn’t save Puerto Rico after all</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/12/the-crypto-founder-who-didnt-save-puerto-rico-after-all/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>In Puerto Rico, tax breaks enacted in 2012 aimed to juice the economy by encouraging mainland U.S. citizens to do business and live on the island, where they could apply to pay nothing in capital gains taxes. But the tech — and primarily crypto — entrepreneurs who showed up in droves to shield their wealth […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:10:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Donald Trump and Elon Musk's X Interview Took Forever to Start, Then Never Ended</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/donald-trump-elon-musks-x-space/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Musk laughed and agreed as Trump described a nation on the verge of the apocalypse—even where it put him at odds with the tycoon's own business interests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 03:53:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elon Musk and Donald Trump’s X Spaces event crashes</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/12/elon-musk-and-donald-trumps-x-spaces-crashes/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Elon Musk and Donald Trump’s joint X Spaces event appears to have crashed Monday afternoon. The conversation between the owner of X and the former President was scheduled for 5 pm PT, but users received an error message when joining at that time. “This Space is not available,” said a message on X when trying […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 02:00:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>He Made a Movie About Humans Rising Up Against AI. Now He’s Doing the Real Thing</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/hollywood-animators-fight-artificial-intelligence-labor-mike-rianda/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Mike Rianda’s The Mitchells vs. the Machines is a sci-fi comedy about a family fighting back against Silicon Valley tech. As animators gear up to battle Hollywood studios, it’s becoming a fable.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 19:44:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Antler doubles down on Southeast Asia with $72M second startup fund</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/12/antler-closes-72m-second-sea-fund-to-ramp-up-startup-investment-in-southeast-asia/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Antler, the Singapore VC that focuses on early-stage investments, just closed its second Southeast Asia fund. It’s raised $72 million to double down on startups in Singapore, Indonesia, Vietnam and Malaysia. This should be welcome news for startups. Like other regions, Southeast Asia has faced a persistent funding slump. Between January and July 2024, tech […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 01:59:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>