<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 02:03:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>2024 Summer Olympics: A Self-Healing Pole Vault Pole Is One Great Leap for Sports Tech</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/a-self-healing-pole-vault-pole-is-one-great-leap-for-sports-tech/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Pole vaulting is a spectacular, dangerous sport. Modern poles could be drastically improved to make them more reliable, with healable tech being developed that could also be used in surfing and cycling.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How the theft of 40M UK voter register records was entirely preventable</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/02/how-the-theft-of-40-million-uk-voter-register-records-was-entirely-preventable/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>&lt;p&gt;A scathing rebuke by the U.K. data protection watchdog reveals what led to the compromise of tens of millions of U.K. voters' information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TikTok Sued by US Justice Department for Alleged Violations of Kids’ Privacy</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/us-justice-department-sues-tiktok-kids-privacy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>The social media company, already fighting for its existence in the US, now has to contend with a potentially expensive penalty stemming from its policies toward users under 13.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 20:54:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Self-driving truck startup Aurora Innovation raises $483M in share sale ahead of commercial launch</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/02/self-driving-truck-startup-aurora-innovation-raises-483m-commercial-launch/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>&lt;p&gt;Self-driving technology company Aurora Innovation was hoping to raise hundreds of millions in additional capital as it races toward a driverless commercial launch by the end of 2024. The company, which had arranged to sell up to $420 million worth of shares, exceeded its goal and raised $483 million. The newly raised funds come a little [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 00:38:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>No, the Seine Cleanup Wasn’t a Failure</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/no-the-seine-cleanup-wasnt-a-failure/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>The goal of the Seine-cleansing project is to produce swimmable conditions for the people of Paris for years to come—the Olympics was just a milestone in getting there.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 18:26:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FTC and Justice Department sue TikTok over alleged child privacy violations</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/02/ftc-and-justice-department-sue-tiktok-over-alleged-child-privacy-violations/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>&lt;p&gt;The U.S. Federal Trade Commission and the Justice Department are suing TikTok and ByteDance, TikTok&amp;#8217;s parent company, with violating the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). The law requires digital platforms to notify and obtain parents&amp;#8217; consent before collecting and using personal data from children under the age of 13. In a press release issued [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 21:12:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sensitive Illinois Voter Data Exposed by Contractor’s Unsecured Databases</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/illinois-voter-databases-exposed/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>Social Security numbers, death certificates, voter applications, and other personal data were accessible on the open internet, highlighting the ongoing challenges in election security.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 17:34:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Acquiring AI talent wholesale</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/02/acquiring-ai-talent-wholesale/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to Startups Weekly — your weekly recap of everything you can’t miss from the world of startups.&amp;#160; This week we are looking at acquisitions of small startups, two new unicorns, wearable AI devices, and VCs who are supporting Kamala Harris. Let’s get into it. Most interesting startup stories from the week With the IPO [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 19:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A New Trick Could Block the Misuse of Open Source AI</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/center-for-ai-safety-open-source-llm-safeguards/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Researchers have developed a way to tamperproof open source large language models to prevent them from being coaxed into, say, explaining how to make a bomb.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 16:49:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Character.AI CEO Noam Shazeer returns to Google</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/02/character-ai-ceo-noam-shazeer-returns-to-google/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>&lt;p&gt;In a big move, Character.AI co-founder and CEO Noam Shazeer is returning to Google after leaving the company in October 2021 to found the a16z-backed chatbot startup. In his previous stint, Shazeer spearheaded the team of researchers that built LaMDA (Language Model for Dialogue Applications), a language model that was used for conversational AI tools. Character.AI co-founder Daniel [&amp;#8230;]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 18:52:09 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>