<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 06:53:01 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>How to Find the Best Eero Wi-Fi Mesh Router for You (2024)</title><link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-eero-wi-fi-mesh-router/</link><description>These popular systems are easy to use, but the product lineup is confusing. Here’s how to choose the right one for your home.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Waymo robotaxi pulled over by Phoenix police after driving into the wrong lane</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/06/waymo-robotaxi-pulled-over-by-phoenix-police-after-driving-into-the-wrong-lane/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>A police officer pulled over a self-driving Waymo vehicle in Phoenix after it ran a red light and pulled into a lane of oncoming traffic, according to...</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 22:10:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SteelSeries Arctis Nova 5X Wireless Review: The Best Universal Gaming Headset</title><link>https://www.wired.com/review/steelseries-arctis-nova-5x-wireless/</link><description>Universal console support, great battery life, and a powerful companion app make this one of the best gaming headsets I’ve tested in a while.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Figma pauses its new AI feature after Apple controversy</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/06/figma-pauses-its-new-ai-feature-after-apple-controversy/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Welcome back to TechCrunch’s Week in Review — TechCrunch’s newsletter recapping the week’s biggest news. Want it in your inbox every Saturday? Sign up...</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 21:16:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Choose the Right TV: Quantum Dots, HDR, and More in 2024</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-buy-the-right-tv/</link><description>How many ports do you need? What does 4K UHD even mean? Here's everything you need to know.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to set up parental controls on Facebook, Snapchat, TikTok and more popular sites</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/06/how-to-set-up-parental-controls-on-facebook-snapchat-tiktok-and-more-popular-sites/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>We’ve created this guide to help parents navigate the controls offered by popular social media companies. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For ...</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 20:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>T3 Aire 360 Air Styler Blowout Kit Review: Powerful and High-End</title><link>https://www.wired.com/review/t3-aire-360/</link><description>One of our favorite hair brands does it again, this time with an all-in-one blowout tool to rival Dyson.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>You could learn a lot from a CIO with a $17B IT budget</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/06/you-could-learn-a-lot-from-a-cio-with-a-15b-it-budget/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Lori Beer's work is a case study for every CIO out there, most of whom will never come close to JP Morgan Chase’s scale, but who can still learn from ...</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>We Flew, Drove, and Camped for Miles to Test the Best Luggage</title><link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-luggage/</link><description>We’ve traveled thousands of miles testing all kinds of luggage. These are our favorite suitcases, backpacks, duffels, and more.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 13:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tesla makes it onto Chinese government purchase list</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/06/tesla-makes-it-onto-chinese-government-purchase-list/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>For the first time, Chinese government workers will be able to purchase Tesla’s Model Y for official use. Specifically, officials in eastern China’s J...</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 18:43:48 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>