<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 13:53:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Google DeepMind’s Game-Playing AI Tackles a Chatbot Blind Spot</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/google-deepmind-alphaproof-ai-math/</link><description>Google’s new advance combines a large language model with a self-learning AI. The technique could address some shortcomings with AI—although there’s a...</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 16:30:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Uber, Lyft, DoorDash can continue to classify drivers as contractors in California</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/25/uber-lyft-doordash-can-continue-to-classify-drivers-as-contractors-in-california/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The California Supreme Court ruled Thursday that Proposition 22 – the ballot measure that passed in November 2020 and classified app-based gig workers...</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 18:35:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eminem’s New Album Prompted Gen X to Declare a TikTok ‘War’ on Gen Z</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/gen-x-has-declared-war-on-gen-z-eminem/</link><description>The release of Eminem’s new album The Death of Slim Shady has led to a series of viral shitposts from Gen X. Their targets, Gen Z, remain unbothered.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 15:33:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alphabet pours $5B into Waymo, Cruise scraps the Origin and Elon’s bet on autonomy</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/25/alphabet-pours-5b-into-waymo-cruise-scraps-the-origin-and-elons-bet-on-autonomy/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Welcome back to TechCrunch Mobility — your central hub for news and insights on the future of transportation. Sign up here for free — just click TechC...</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 18:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 7 Best Folding Phones We've Tested and Reviewed (2024)</title><link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-folding-phones/</link><description>Ready to move on from the traditional glass slab? Introduce a hinge into your life with these folding smartphones.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 15:27:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Archera helps customers access deep cloud discounts</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/25/archera-helps-customers-access-deep-cloud-discounts/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>In addition to insured commitments, Archera provides consulting services to help build purchasing strategies for customers to optimize their cloud usa...</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 17:49:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 13 Best Office Chairs in 2024, Tested and Reviewed</title><link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-office-chairs/</link><description>Sitting at a desk for hours? Upgrade your WFH setup and work in style with these comfy WIRED-tested seats.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 15:11:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Google makes its Gemini chatbot faster and more widely available</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/25/google-speeds-up-its-gemini-chatbot-and-brings-it-to-more-places/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>In its bid to maintain pace with generative AI rivals like Anthropic and OpenAI, Google is rolling out updates to the no-fee tier of Gemini, its AI-po...</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cars Are Now Rolling Computers, So How Long Will They Get Updates? Automakers Can’t Say</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/cars-are-now-rolling-computers-so-how-long-will-they-get-updates-automakers-cant-say/</link><description>Phones are supported well beyond their average ownership lifetime. In stark contrast, automakers are struggling to work out how long their “smartphone...</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TechCrunch Minute: Meta’s new ‘Imagine me’ feature lets you generate AI selfies</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/video/techcrunch-minute-metas-new-imagine-me-feature-lets-you-generate-ai-selfies/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Meta’s AI integrations into apps like Instagram and Facebook have felt pretty useless so far. If I’m just trying to find my friend’s Instagram, why do...</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>