<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 06:56:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Google Has Unleashed Its Legal Fury on Hackers and Scammers</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/google-affirmative-litigation-hacker-scammer-lawsuits/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>The tech giant says its “affirmative litigation” deters and raises awareness of bad behavior. But skeptics wonder whether these suits are too small a gesture.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Binance restarts services in India after seven-month regulatory halt</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/15/binance-restarts-services-in-india-after-seven-month-regulatory-halt/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Binance, the world’s largest cryptocurrency exchange, has resumed operations for users in India after a seven-month hiatus imposed by a local authority for operating “illegally” in the country. The exchange said Thursday it has registered as a reporting entity with India’s Financial Intelligence Unit (FIU), a government agency tasked with scrutinizing financial transactions. India blocked […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 08:12:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Is the Most Detailed Map of Human Brain Connections Ever Made</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/this-is-the-most-detailed-map-of-brain-connections-ever-made-google-harvard/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In a world first, Harvard biologists worked with Google to diagram a cubic millimeter of human cerebral cortex at the subcellular level, paving the way for the next generation of brain science.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Video of Eric Schmidt blaming remote work for Google’s woes mysteriously vanishes</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/14/video-of-eric-schmidt-blaming-remote-work-for-googles-woes-mysteriously-vanishes/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Former Google CEO Eric Schmidt, who has since moved on to greener and perhaps more dangerous pastures, told an audience of Stanford students recently that “Google decided that work-life balance and going home early and working from home was more important than winning.” Evidently this hot take was not for wider consumption, as Stanford — […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 00:14:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Code Breaker Is Using AI to Decode the Heart’s Secret Rhythms</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/ai-doctor-roeland-decorte-future-industries/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Inspired by his expertise in breaking ancient codes, Roeland Decorte built a smartphone app that continuously listens for signs of disease hidden in our pulse.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meet Black Forest Labs, the startup powering Elon Musk’s unhinged AI image generator</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/14/meet-black-forest-labs-the-startup-powering-elon-musks-unhinged-ai-image-generator/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Elon Musk’s Grok released a new AI image-generation feature on Tuesday night that, just like the AI chatbot, has very few safeguards. That means you can generate fake images of Donald Trump smoking marijuana on the Joe Rogan show, for example, and upload it straight to the X platform. But it’s not really Elon Musk’s […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 23:45:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Single Iranian Hacker Group Targeted Both Presidential Campaigns, Google Says</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/iran-apt42-trump-biden-harris-phishing-targeting/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>APT42, which is believed to work for Iran’s Revolutionary Guard Corps, targeted about a dozen people associated with both Trump’s and Biden’s campaigns this spring, according to Google’s Threat Analysis Group.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 23:27:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Filmmakers say AI will change the art — perhaps beyond recognition</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/14/filmmakers-say-ai-will-change-the-art-perhaps-beyond-recognition/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>One of the first topics tackled was the impractical nature of today's video generators. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 23:13:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Your Gym Locker May Be Hackable</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/electronic-locker-vulnerability/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Security researchers say they’ve extracted digital management keys from select electronic lockers and revealed how they could be cloned.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 18:59:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden tells creators they have something traditional media does not: ‘You’re trusted’</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/14/biden-tells-creators-they-have-something-traditional-media-does-not-youre-trusted/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>At the first ever White House Creator Economy Conference, the most popular man to drop by was not a TikTok superstar or a YouTube sensation. It was President Joe Biden, who emphasized social media creators’ role in shaping public opinion. “Until about three, four months ago, I didn’t pay very much attention, following you guys,” […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 22:32:54 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>