<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 13:57:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The End of ‘iPhone’</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/the-end-of-iphone/</link><description>Ken Segall is the reason so many Apple products start with “i.” Now he says it’s time to drop the prefix entirely.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 14:56:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SeekOut, a recruiting startup last valued at $1.2 billion, lays off 30% of its workforce</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/20/seekout-layoffs-30percent-talent-search-tigerglobal/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The company says it's refocusing and prioritizing fewer initiatives that will have the biggest impact on customers and add value to the business. © 20...</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 18:47:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WikiLeaks’ Julian Assange Can Appeal His Extradition to the US, British Court Says</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/julian-assange-court-hearing-appeal-extradition/</link><description>Two judges in London have ruled that WikiLeaks’ founder Julian Assange can appeal his extradition to the US on freedom of speech grounds.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 13:57:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>UK’s autonomous vehicle legislation becomes law, paving the way for first driverless cars by 2026</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/20/uks-autonomous-vehicle-legislation-becomes-law-paving-the-way-for-first-driverless-cars-by-2026/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The U.K.’s self-proclaimed “world-leading” regulations for self-driving cars are now official, after the Automated Vehicles (AV) Act received royal as...</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 17:39:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>7 Best Video Doorbell Cameras (2024): Smart, Battery, AI, Budget, and Subscription-Free</title><link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-video-doorbells/</link><description>Never miss a delivery. These WIRED-tested picks will help you keep tabs on your front door from anywhere.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ChatGPT: Everything you need to know about the AI-powered chatbot</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/20/chatgpt-everything-to-know-about-the-ai-chatbot/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>ChatGPT, OpenAI’s text-generating AI chatbot, has taken the world by storm. What started as a tool to hyper-charge productivity through writing essays...</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Craig Wright Lied About Creating Bitcoin and Faked Evidence, Judge Rules</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/craig-wright-lied-faked-evidence-bitcoin-judge-says/</link><description>A UK judge has determined that Craig Wright forged evidence in a campaign to prove he is Satoshi Nakamoto, creator of Bitcoin, in a move that prevents...</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 12:01:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fintech lender Solo Funds is being sued again by the government over its lending practices</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/20/solo-funds-lawsuit-cfpb/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>SoLo Funds CEO Travis Holoway: “Regulators seem driven by press releases when they should be motivated by true consumer protection and empowering equi...</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 17:14:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Remove Your Personal Info From Google’s Search Results</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/remove-personal-info-from-google-search-results/</link><description>Maybe you don’t want your phone number, email, home address, and other details out there for all the web to see. Here’s how to make them vanish.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rollup wants to be the hardware engineer’s workhorse</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/20/rollup-wants-to-be-the-hardware-engineers-workhorse/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Hard tech startups generate a lot of buzz, but there’s a growing cohort of companies building digital tools squarely focused on making hard tech devel...</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>