<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 00:28:36 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>'Saturday Night Live’ Writer Alex English Thinks Social Media Ruined the Art of Comedy</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/dial-up-saturday-night-live-alex-english/</link><description>Saturday Night Live writer and veteran stand-up comedian Alex English believes platforms like TikTok have changed the relationship a comic has to thei...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 19:17:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple approves Epic Games’ marketplace app after initial rejections</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/05/epic-games-calls-out-apple-for-rejecting-its-games-store-in-the-eu/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>After multiple rejections, Apple has approved Fortnite maker Epic Games’ third-party app marketplace for launch in the EU. As now permitted by the EU’...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 22:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Epic Games Lashes Out at Apple Over App Store Rejection</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/epic-games-lashes-out-at-apple-over-app-store-rejection/</link><description>Fortnite creator Epic Games says Apple rejected its App Store rival for being too similar to its own—a move it deemed “arbitrary, obstructive,” and in...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 16:10:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OpenAI breach is a reminder that AI companies are treasure troves for hackers</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/05/openai-breach-is-a-reminder-that-ai-companies-are-treasure-troves-for-hackers/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>There’s no need to worry that your secret ChatGPT conversations were obtained in a recently reported breach of OpenAI’s systems. The hack itself, whil...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 20:49:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Run on the Moon</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/running-on-the-moon-with-the-circle-of-death/</link><description>It’s hard to stay fit in low gravity. Here’s a simple solution, using Einsteinian physics and an old carnival stunt.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Space for newcomers, biotech going mainstream, and more</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/05/space-for-newcomers-biotech-going-mainstream-and-more/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Welcome to Startups Weekly — TechCrunch’s weekly recap of everything you can’t miss from the world of startups. Sign up here to get it in your inbox e...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 20:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>12 Best Tablets (2024): iPads, Androids, and More Tested and Compared</title><link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/the-best-tablets/</link><description>We’ve tested all the top slates, from Apple’s iPads to Android and Windows devices, and rounded up our favorite accessories.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 14:31:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>X plans to more deeply integrate Grok’s AI, app researcher finds</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/05/x-plans-to-more-deeply-integrate-groks-ai-app-researcher-finds/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Elon Musk’s X is exploring more ways to integrate xAI’s Grok into the social networking app. According to a series of recent discoveries, X is develop...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 19:31:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Shop for a Smart Lock (2024)</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/how-to-shop-for-a-smart-lock/</link><description>Here’s everything you need to know as you navigate the world of smart and digital locks for your front door.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meet Brex, Google Cloud, Aerospace and more at Disrupt 2024</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/05/meet-these-partners-at-disrupt-2024/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>We’re about four months away from TechCrunch Disrupt 2024, taking place October 28 to 30 in San Francisco! We could not bring you this world-class eve...</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>