<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:52:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>He Made a Movie About Humans Rising Up Against AI. Now He’s Doing the Real Thing</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/hollywood-animators-fight-artificial-intelligence-labor-mike-rianda/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Mike Rianda’s The Mitchells vs. the Machines is a sci-fi comedy about a family fighting back against Silicon Valley tech. As animators gear up to battle Hollywood studios, it’s becoming a fable.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 19:44:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The biggest data breaches in 2024: 1 billion stolen records and rising</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/12/2024-in-data-breaches-1-billion-stolen-records-and-rising/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Some of the largest, most damaging breaches of 2024 already account for over a billion stolen records. Plus, some special shoutouts. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 20:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NBC Sent 27 Creators to Paris. It Only Needed Snoop and Olympic Athletes</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/nbc-sent-creators-to-paris-it-only-needed-snoop-and-some-hip-athletes/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>In an attempt to lure in younger viewers, NBCUniversal sent dozens of social media influencers to the 2024 Paris Olympics. But the athletes and entertainers were the ones who went viral.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Euro VCs welcome Balderton’s fresh $1.3B but grumble about Europe’s AI misses</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/12/euro-vcs-welcome-baldertons-fresh-1-3b-but-grumble-about-europes-ai-misses/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>In the last 12 months, Balderton has announced 12 new investments. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 19:05:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>12 Best Sound Machines and White-Noise Machines, Tested and Reviewed (2024)</title><link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-sound-machines/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Help the whole family catch more z’s with soothing background noise from our favorite sound machines.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 14:11:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TikTok comes for messaging apps with the addition of group chats</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/12/tiktok-comes-for-messaging-apps-with-the-addition-of-group-chats/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>TikTok looks to be taking on popular messaging services like Meta’s WhatsApp and Apple’s Messages, as the company announced on Monday that it’s adding group chats to its platform. You can now create group chats with up to 32 people to chat and share content together. While people often share TikTok videos with each other […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 19:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>7 Best Chromebooks of 2024, Tested and Reviewed</title><link>https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-chromebooks/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Choosing the right Chromebook for your needs can be a tough decision. We can help with our favorite picks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 13:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What is AI good for anyway? Maybe not summarizing</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/12/what-is-ai-good-for-anyway-maybe-not-summarizing/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>There’s a fascinating look by John Herrman over at NYMag today at one of the big proposed uses of AI: summarizing content. We all need things summarized, right? Everybody’s too busy and overloaded with information. At least that’s what every tech company doing AI seems to be settling on. The problem is the summaries that […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 18:23:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Humans Are Going to the Moon’s South Pole. This Is How They’ll Drive There</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/artemis-v-lunar-terrain-vehicle-tires-wheels-design/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>As NASA gears up to send a lunar terrain vehicle to the moon, it has asked tire designers to make a set of wheels that can survive the harsh conditions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Waymo to begin testing driverless robotaxis on San Francisco freeways</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/12/waymo-to-begin-testing-driverless-robotaxis-on-san-francisco-freeways/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Waymo plans to start testing its fully autonomous vehicles with no human safety driver on freeways in the San Francisco Bay Area this week. Its employees will be the first guinea pigs, and initial testing will start outside rush hour with “less than a handful” of vehicles. For those who didn’t already know, Waymo got […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 17:58:33 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>