<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>briefUpdatesMainNLscienceAndDiscovery</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from briefUpdatesMainNLscienceAndDiscovery, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 11:37:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>New tools to identify and monitor cardiovascular disease</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/new-tools-identify-monitor-cardiovascular-disease</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Cardiovascular diseases cause one death every 33 seconds in America. Diagnosing these conditions, which account for approximately 20% of all deaths an...</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 14:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Huge sea-urchin populations are overwhelming Hawaii's coral reefs</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/05/250528150650.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>This study measured the growth rate of coral reefs in Honaunau Bay, Hawaii, using on-site data gathering and aerial imagery. Researchers found that th...</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 20:06:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A sweeping study of 7,000 years of monuments in South Arabia</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/05/250528150706.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>New research brings together 7,000 years of history in South Arabia to show how ancient pastoralists changed placement and construction of monuments o...</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 20:07:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nearly five million seized seahorses just 'tip of the iceberg' in global wildlife smuggling</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/05/250528132240.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Close to five million smuggled seahorses worth an estimated CAD$29 million were seized by authorities over a 10-year span, according to a new study th...</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 18:22:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Clearest-ever images of sun's corona captured with new optical technique</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/clearest-ever-images-suns-corona-captured-new-optical</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Using a new optical system, scientists at the U.S. National Science Foundation National Solar Observatory and the New Jersey Institute of Technology h...</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 19:36:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New AI tool reveals single-cell structure of chromosomes -- in 3D</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/05/250528131824.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>In a major leap forward for genetic and biomedical research, scientists have developed a powerful new artificial intelligence tool that can predict th...</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 18:18:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mid-air transformation helps flying, rolling robot to transition smoothly</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/05/250528150829.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Engineers have developed a real-life Transformer that has the 'brains' to morph in midair, allowing the drone-like robot to smoothly roll away and beg...</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 20:08:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Volcanic ash is critical to tracking changes in eruption behavior</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/volcanic-ash-critical-tracking-changes-eruption-behavior</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>U.S. National Science Foundation-funded researchers discovered that subtle changes in magma composition may drive tremors during volcanic eruptions, o...</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 14:24:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Preparing science educators to use and teach AI in the classroom</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/preparing-science-educators-use-teach-ai-classroom</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>An interdisciplinary team of researchers funded by the U.S. National Science Foundation has created a teacher-driven curriculum called Shark AI. This ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 19:32:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lab-synthesized botanical compound shows promise for fighting aggressive breast cancer</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/lab-synthesized-botanical-compound-shows-promise-fighting</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Chemists funded by the U.S. National Science Foundation have developed a new process to synthesize a plant-based compound that shows effectiveness aga...</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 14:18:24 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>