<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>briefUpdatesMainNLscienceAndDiscovery</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from briefUpdatesMainNLscienceAndDiscovery, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:56:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Hubble just captured a glittering star cluster like no other</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250911073620.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Hubble’s latest image captures a glittering star cluster inside the Large Magellanic Cloud, a dwarf galaxy about 160,000 light-years from Earth. This ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 12:36:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Your morning coffee could secretly be weakening antibiotics</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250911080113.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Researchers have discovered that everyday substances like caffeine can influence how bacteria such as E. coli respond to antibiotics. By examining 94 ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 13:12:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blocked blood flow makes cancer grow faster</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250910000311.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Researchers at NYU Langone Health discovered that cutting off blood flow accelerates cancer growth by prematurely aging the bone marrow and weakening ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 08:31:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This rare white dwarf looks normal, until Hubble shows its explosive secret</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250910233533.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Hubble has uncovered a rare ultra-massive white dwarf created in a violent star merger. Once thought to be ordinary, the star’s ultraviolet signature ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 04:43:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NASA’s celestial “Accident” unlocks secrets of Jupiter and Saturn</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250910000246.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Astronomers studying an oddball brown dwarf called “The Accident” have finally spotted silane, a long-predicted silicon molecule missing from Jupiter ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 04:31:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF National Quantum Virtual Laboratory speeds into the design phase</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-national-quantum-virtual-laboratory-speeds-design-phase</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation National Quantum Virtual Laboratory (NSF NQVL) is coming into sharper focus with the selection of the first four ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 15:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF announces funding to establish the National AI Research Resource Operations Center</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-funding-establish-national-ai-research</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation today announced a new solicitation to establish a National Artificial Intelligence Research Resource Operations C...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 15:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF expanding national AI infrastructure with new data systems and resources</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-expanding-national-ai-infrastructure-new-data-systems</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation today announced two major advancements in America's AI infrastructure: the launch of the Integrated Data Systems ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF announces new funding opportunities to advance AI education and build the STEM workforce of the future</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-new-funding-opportunities-advance-ai-education</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has announced two new Dear Colleague Letters (DCL) and one program solicitation that implement key elements of th...</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 20:03:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF and NVIDIA partnership enables Ai2 to develop fully open AI models to fuel U.S. scientific innovation</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-nvidia-partnership-enables-ai2-develop-fully-open-ai</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation announced a partnership with NVIDIA to develop a set of artificial intelligence models that will transform the ab...</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 13:07:12 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>