<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>briefUpdatesMainNLscienceAndDiscovery</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from briefUpdatesMainNLscienceAndDiscovery, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 11:12:22 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Only 3 years left: The carbon budget for 1. 5 °C is almost gone</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/06/250627021853.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>At current emission rates, we re just over three years away from blowing through the remaining carbon budget to limit warming to 1.5 C. This new inter...</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 15:46:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This breakthrough turns old tech into pure gold — No mercury, no cyanide, just light and salt</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/06/250626081540.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>At Flinders University, scientists have cracked a cleaner and greener way to extract gold—not just from ore, but also from our mounting piles of e-was...</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 07:02:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sex swap in seconds: The fish that takes charge and changes gender</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/06/250627095022.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Remove the top male spotty fish and, within minutes, the next-in-line female morphs into the tank s new tyrant charging and nipping rivals while her b...</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 15:36:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>These 545-million-year-old fossil trails just rewrote the story of evolution</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/06/250627021857.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>A groundbreaking study suggests that the famous Cambrian explosion—the dramatic burst of diverse animal life—might have actually started millions of y...</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 14:40:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tiny creatures, massive impact: How zooplankton store 65 million tonnes of carbon annually</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/06/250627021851.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Zooplankton like copepods aren’t just fish food—they’re carbon-hauling powerhouses. By diving deep into the ocean each winter, they’re secretly stashi...</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 13:51:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Superconducting material stabilized at everyday pressure, another step toward real-world applications</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/superconducting-material-stabilized-everyday-pressure</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>U.S. National Science Foundation-funded researchers have stabilized a composite material in a superconducting state at ambient or normal, everyday pre...</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 15:19:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chemical process more efficiently converts carbon dioxide to methanol, a chemical used in manufacturing and a potential fuel</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/chemical-process-more-efficiently-converts-carbon-dioxide</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>A new chemical process funded by the U.S. National Science Foundation has produced methanol — a type of alcohol essential for manufacturing many commo...</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 14:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF invests $25.5M in research to drive new U.S. manufacturing technologies and talent pipelines</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-invests-255m-research-drive-new-us-manufacturing</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has announced a $25.5 million investment to support fundamental research and workforce development aimed at enabl...</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 15:07:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF Graduate Research Fellow's work on light contributes to nanodot breakthrough</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-graduate-research-fellows-work-light-contributes-nanodot</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Americans spend a lot of time on their screens. The images on those screens are made of pixels — tiny dots that represent a single point of color. Sci...</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 13:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ever-changing universe revealed in first imagery from NSF-DOE Vera C. Rubin Observatory</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/first-imagery-nsf-doe-vera-c-rubin-observatory</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>The NSF-DOE Vera C. Rubin Observatory, a major new scientific facility jointly funded by the U.S. National Science Foundation and the U.S. Department ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 16:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>