<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>briefUpdatesMainNLscienceAndDiscovery</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from briefUpdatesMainNLscienceAndDiscovery, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 10:39:07 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>New ketamine study promises extended relief for depression</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/05/250522183206.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>For the nearly 30 percent of major depressive disorder patients who are resistant to treatment, ketamine provides some amount of normalcy, but it requ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 23:32:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Researchers make breakthrough in semiconductor technology set to supercharge 6G delivery</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/05/250522183216.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Self-driving cars which eliminate traffic jams, getting a healthcare diagnosis instantly without leaving your home, or feeling the touch of loved ones...</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 23:32:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A new approach could fractionate crude oil using much less energy</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/05/250522162533.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Engineers developed a membrane that filters the components of crude oil by their molecular size, an advance that could dramatically reduce the amount ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 21:25:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tapping into the World's largest gold reserves</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/05/250522133522.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Earth's largest gold reserves are not kept inside Fort Knox, the United States Bullion Depository. In fact, they are hidden much deeper in the ground ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:35:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists have figured out how extinct giant ground sloths got so big and where it all went wrong</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/05/250522162538.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Scientists have analyzed ancient DNA and compared more than 400 fossils from 17 natural history museums to figure out how and why extinct sloths got s...</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 21:25:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Preparing science educators to use and teach AI in the classroom</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/preparing-science-educators-use-teach-ai-classroom</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>An interdisciplinary team of researchers funded by the U.S. National Science Foundation has created a teacher-driven curriculum called Shark AI. This ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 19:32:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lab-synthesized botanical compound shows promise for fighting aggressive breast cancer</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/lab-synthesized-botanical-compound-shows-promise-fighting</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Chemists funded by the U.S. National Science Foundation have developed a new process to synthesize a plant-based compound that shows effectiveness aga...</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 14:18:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>4 planets discovered around Barnard's star, one of the closest stars to Earth</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/4-planets-discovered-around-barnards-star-one-closest-stars</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Researchers supported by the U.S. National Science Foundation have discovered four tiny exoplanets orbiting Barnard's star, a red dwarf at the center ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Using machine learning to speed up discovery for drug delivery and disease treatment</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/using-machine-learning-speed-discovery-drug-delivery-disease</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>A new computational tool developed with support from the U.S. National Science Foundation could greatly speed up determining the 3D structure of RNAs,...</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 16:00:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Leopard spots and protein nanoclusters: How pattern rules could advance muscular dystrophy treatment</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/leopard-spots-protein-nanoclusters-how-pattern-rules-could</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Although a leopard cannot change its spots, new research funded by the U.S. National Science Foundation uses the principles that govern patterns like ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 13:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>