<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>briefUpdatesMainNLscienceAndDiscovery</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from briefUpdatesMainNLscienceAndDiscovery, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 06:25:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Defying physics: This rare crystal cools itself using pure magnetism</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/07/250705084251.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Deep in Chile’s Atacama Desert, scientists studied a green crystal called atacamite—and discovered it can cool itself dramatically when placed in a ma...</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 07:49:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New tech tracks blood sodium without a single needle</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/07/250705084253.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Scientists have pioneered a new way to monitor sodium levels in the blood—without drawing a single drop. By combining terahertz radiation and optoacou...</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 09:16:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pregnancy’s 100-million-year secret: Inside the placenta’s evolutionary power play</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/07/250705084324.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>A group of scientists studying pregnancy across six different mammals—from humans to marsupials—uncovered how certain cells at the mother-baby boundar...</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 12:22:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Multisensory VR forest reboots your brain and lifts mood—study confirms</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/07/250705084325.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Immersing stressed volunteers in a 360° virtual Douglas-fir forest complete with sights, sounds and scents boosted their mood, sharpened short-term me...</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 13:17:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cough medicine turned brain protector? Ambroxol may slow Parkinson’s dementia</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/07/250706081848.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Ambroxol, long used for coughs in Europe, stabilized symptoms and brain-damage markers in Parkinson’s dementia patients over 12 months, whereas placeb...</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 14:01:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Superconducting material stabilized at everyday pressure, another step toward real-world applications</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/superconducting-material-stabilized-everyday-pressure</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>U.S. National Science Foundation-funded researchers have stabilized a composite material in a superconducting state at ambient or normal, everyday pre...</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 15:19:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chemical process more efficiently converts carbon dioxide to methanol, a chemical used in manufacturing and a potential fuel</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/chemical-process-more-efficiently-converts-carbon-dioxide</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>A new chemical process funded by the U.S. National Science Foundation has produced methanol — a type of alcohol essential for manufacturing many commo...</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 14:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF invests $25.5M in research to drive new U.S. manufacturing technologies and talent pipelines</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-invests-255m-research-drive-new-us-manufacturing</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has announced a $25.5 million investment to support fundamental research and workforce development aimed at enabl...</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 15:07:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF-funded researchers' work on light contributes to nanodot breakthrough</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-funded-researchers-work-light-contributes-nanodot</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Americans spend a lot of time on their screens. The images on those screens are made of pixels — tiny dots that represent a single point of color. Sci...</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 13:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ever-changing universe revealed in first imagery from NSF-DOE Vera C. Rubin Observatory</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/first-imagery-nsf-doe-vera-c-rubin-observatory</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>The NSF-DOE Vera C. Rubin Observatory, a major new scientific facility jointly funded by the U.S. National Science Foundation and the U.S. Department ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 16:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>