<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>briefUpdatesMainNLscienceAndDiscovery</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from briefUpdatesMainNLscienceAndDiscovery, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 06:36:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Overworked neurons burn out and fuel Parkinson’s disease</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250902085158.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Overactivation of dopamine neurons may directly drive their death, explaining why movement-controlling brain cells degenerate in Parkinson’s. Mice wit...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 09:57:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A simple metal could solve the world’s plastic recycling problem</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250902085150.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Scientists at Northwestern University have developed a groundbreaking nickel-based catalyst that could transform the way the world recycles plastic. I...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 08:02:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Alzheimer’s attacks the brain’s memory hub first</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250902085136.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Virginia Tech researchers are investigating how overloaded mitochondria in the brain’s memory circuits may spark early Alzheimer’s damage. Their work ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 04:28:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Central Asia’s last stable glaciers just started to collapse</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250902085147.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Snowfall shortages are now destabilizing some of the world’s last resilient glaciers, as shown by a new study in Tajikistan’s Pamir Mountains. Using a...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 07:36:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hidden viruses in our DNA could be medicine’s next big breakthrough</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250902085154.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Scientists have decoded the 3D structure of an ancient viral protein hidden in our DNA. The HERV-K Env protein, found on cancer and autoimmune cells, ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 08:54:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF expanding national AI infrastructure with new data systems and resources</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-expanding-national-ai-infrastructure-new-data-systems</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation today announced two major advancements in America's AI infrastructure: the launch of the Integrated Data Systems ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF announces new funding opportunities to advance AI education and build the STEM workforce of the future</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-new-funding-opportunities-advance-ai-education</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has announced two new Dear Colleague Letters (DCL) and one program solicitation that implement key elements of th...</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 20:03:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF and NVIDIA partnership enables Ai2 to develop fully open AI models to fuel U.S. scientific innovation</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-nvidia-partnership-enables-ai2-develop-fully-open-ai</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation announced a partnership with NVIDIA to develop a set of artificial intelligence models that will transform the ab...</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 13:07:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Podcast: Introducing AI to the future workforce</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/podcast-introducing-ai-future-workforce</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>A workforce fluent in AI techniques will be essential to ensure U.S. leadership in artificial intelligence continues. Jeremy Waisome, an assistant pro...</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 18:56:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF invests $29.2 million in EPSCoR Research Infrastructure collaborations for transformative impact across 11 jurisdictions</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-invests-292-million-epscor-research-infrastructure</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation (NSF) has announced six major awards through its EPSCoR Research Infrastructure Improvement Program: Focused EPSC...</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 14:55:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>