<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>briefUpdatesMainNLscienceAndDiscovery</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from briefUpdatesMainNLscienceAndDiscovery, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 06:32:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Antarctica’s frozen heart is warming fast, and models missed it</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250909031503.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>New research has revealed that East Antarctica’s vast and icy interior is heating up faster than its coasts, fueled by warm air carried from the South...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:45:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The ocean’s most abundant microbe is near its breaking point</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250909031505.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Tiny ocean microbes called Prochlorococcus, once thought to be climate survivors, may struggle as seas warm. These cyanobacteria drive 5% of Earth’s p...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 23:07:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why some plants are taking over the world</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250909031507.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Plants are spreading across the globe faster than ever, largely due to human activity, and new research shows that the very same traits that make plan...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 23:41:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hungry flathead catfish are changing everything in the Susquehanna</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250909031516.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Flathead catfish are rapidly reshaping the Susquehanna River’s ecosystem. Once introduced, these voracious predators climbed to the top of the food ch...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 23:54:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hit the wrong spot and an asteroid returns on a collision course</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250909031457.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Scientists caution that asteroid deflection must be precise, as striking the wrong spot risks sending it through a gravitational keyhole that sets up ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 10:23:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF National Quantum Virtual Laboratory speeds into the design phase</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-national-quantum-virtual-laboratory-speeds-design-phase</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation National Quantum Virtual Laboratory (NSF NQVL) is coming into sharper focus with the selection of the first four ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 15:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF announces funding to establish the National AI Research Resource Operations Center</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-funding-establish-national-ai-research</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation today announced a new solicitation to establish a National Artificial Intelligence Research Resource Operations C...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 15:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF expanding national AI infrastructure with new data systems and resources</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-expanding-national-ai-infrastructure-new-data-systems</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation today announced two major advancements in America's AI infrastructure: the launch of the Integrated Data Systems ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF announces new funding opportunities to advance AI education and build the STEM workforce of the future</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-new-funding-opportunities-advance-ai-education</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has announced two new Dear Colleague Letters (DCL) and one program solicitation that implement key elements of th...</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 20:03:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF and NVIDIA partnership enables Ai2 to develop fully open AI models to fuel U.S. scientific innovation</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-nvidia-partnership-enables-ai2-develop-fully-open-ai</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation announced a partnership with NVIDIA to develop a set of artificial intelligence models that will transform the ab...</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 13:07:12 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>