<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>briefUpdatesMainNLscienceAndDiscovery</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from briefUpdatesMainNLscienceAndDiscovery, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 16:03:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Scientists create biodegradable plastic stronger than PET</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250904014137.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>A Japanese research team successfully harnessed E. coli to produce PDCA, a strong, biodegradable plastic alternative. Their method avoids toxic byprod...</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 07:40:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A monster molecular cloud has been discovered in our galaxy – “No one had any idea this existed”</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250903075159.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Researchers spotted a colossal cloud of gas and dust in the Milky Way, filled with turbulent motion, newborn star seeds, and even a natural microwave ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 16:02:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fossil reveals a 310-million-year-old fish that ate with a hidden second jaw</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250904014143.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Scientists uncovered a 310-million-year-old fish fossil with a “tongue bite,” teeth on the roof and floor of its mouth that worked like a second jaw. ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 07:52:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A 3-minute brainwave test could spot Alzheimer’s years before symptoms</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250904014153.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Scientists at the University of Bath have developed a simple three-minute brainwave test called Fastball EEG that can detect memory problems years bef...</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 08:12:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists watch an atomic nucleus flip in real time</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250904014149.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Scientists at Delft University of Technology have managed to watch a single atomic nucleus flip its magnetic state in real time. Using a scanning tunn...</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 07:59:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF National Quantum Virtual Laboratory speeds into the design phase</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-national-quantum-virtual-laboratory-speeds-design-phase</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation National Quantum Virtual Laboratory (NSF NQVL) is coming into sharper focus with the selection of the first four ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 15:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF announces funding to establish the National AI Research Resource Operations Center</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-funding-establish-national-ai-research</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation today announced a new solicitation to establish a National Artificial Intelligence Research Resource Operations C...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 15:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF expanding national AI infrastructure with new data systems and resources</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-expanding-national-ai-infrastructure-new-data-systems</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation today announced two major advancements in America's AI infrastructure: the launch of the Integrated Data Systems ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF announces new funding opportunities to advance AI education and build the STEM workforce of the future</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-new-funding-opportunities-advance-ai-education</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has announced two new Dear Colleague Letters (DCL) and one program solicitation that implement key elements of th...</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 20:03:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF and NVIDIA partnership enables Ai2 to develop fully open AI models to fuel U.S. scientific innovation</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-nvidia-partnership-enables-ai2-develop-fully-open-ai</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation announced a partnership with NVIDIA to develop a set of artificial intelligence models that will transform the ab...</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 13:07:12 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>