<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>briefUpdatesMainNLscienceAndDiscovery</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from briefUpdatesMainNLscienceAndDiscovery, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:10:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Scientists reveal how breathwork unlocks psychedelic bliss in the brain</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250901104656.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>High-ventilation breathwork with music can evoke psychedelic-like states, shifting blood flow in the brain and reducing negative emotions. Participant...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 13:24:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NASA’s SPHEREx Captures Comet 3I/ATLAS, a Visitor From Beyond the Solar System</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250902084959.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>NASA’s SPHEREx joined Webb and Hubble in studying interstellar comet 3I/ATLAS, gathering data on its size, chemistry, and physical traits. While harml...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 15:03:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Distant suns covered in dark spots could shape the search for life</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250902085004.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>A new model called StarryStarryProcess lets scientists map star spots with precision, improving how exoplanets are studied. By factoring in both trans...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 15:25:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NASA’s Webb Space Telescope Reveals Secrets of Interstellar Comet 3I/ATLAS</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250902084955.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Webb, Hubble, and SPHEREx are joining forces to study the interstellar comet 3I/ATLAS, revealing details about its structure and chemistry. The comet ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 13:49:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Study finds cannabis improves sleep where other drugs fail</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250901104658.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>A long-term study following insomnia patients treated with cannabis-based medical products revealed sustained improvements in sleep quality, mood, and...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 13:42:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF expanding national AI infrastructure with new data systems and resources</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-expanding-national-ai-infrastructure-new-data-systems</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation today announced two major advancements in America's AI infrastructure: the launch of the Integrated Data Systems ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF announces new funding opportunities to advance AI education and build the STEM workforce of the future</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-new-funding-opportunities-advance-ai-education</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has announced two new Dear Colleague Letters (DCL) and one program solicitation that implement key elements of th...</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 20:03:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF and NVIDIA partnership enables Ai2 to develop fully open AI models to fuel U.S. scientific innovation</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-nvidia-partnership-enables-ai2-develop-fully-open-ai</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation announced a partnership with NVIDIA to develop a set of artificial intelligence models that will transform the ab...</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 13:07:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Podcast: Introducing AI to the future workforce</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/podcast-introducing-ai-future-workforce</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>A workforce fluent in AI techniques will be essential to ensure U.S. leadership in artificial intelligence continues. Jeremy Waisome, an assistant pro...</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 18:56:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF invests $29.2 million in EPSCoR Research Infrastructure collaborations for transformative impact across 11 jurisdictions</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-invests-292-million-epscor-research-infrastructure</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation (NSF) has announced six major awards through its EPSCoR Research Infrastructure Improvement Program: Focused EPSC...</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 14:55:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>