<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>briefUpdatesMainNLscienceAndDiscovery</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from briefUpdatesMainNLscienceAndDiscovery, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 15:59:44 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NSF announces new funding opportunities to advance AI education and build the STEM workforce of the future</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-new-funding-opportunities-advance-ai-education</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has announced two new Dear Colleague Letters (DCL) and one program solicitation that implement key elements of th...</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 20:03:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A star torn apart by a black hole lit up the Universe twice</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/08/250819072159.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Astronomers using AI have captured a once-in-a-lifetime cosmic event: a massive star’s violent death triggered by its black hole companion. The explos...</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 11:47:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists discover crystal that breathes oxygen like lungs</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/08/250821004248.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Researchers developed a crystal that inhales and exhales oxygen like lungs. It stays stable under real-world conditions and can be reused many times, ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 05:17:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hidden venom divide in Australia’s deadliest snake raises urgent treatment questions</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/08/250821094520.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Scientists have uncovered a startling split in the venom of Australia’s Eastern Brown Snake. In the south, bites cause rock-solid blood clots, while i...</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 07:17:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mysterious “little red dots” could reveal how the first black holes formed</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/08/250819072201.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Astronomers may have uncovered the origins of the mysterious “little red dots,” some of the strangest galaxies seen in the early universe. These tiny ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 12:35:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What came before the Big Bang? Supercomputers may hold the answer</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/08/250821094530.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Scientists are rethinking the universe’s deepest mysteries using numerical relativity, complex computer simulations of Einstein’s equations in extreme...</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 09:59:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF and NVIDIA partnership enables Ai2 to develop fully open AI models to fuel U.S. scientific innovation</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-nvidia-partnership-enables-ai2-develop-fully-open-ai</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation announced a partnership with NVIDIA to develop a set of artificial intelligence models that will transform the ab...</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 13:07:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Podcast: Introducing AI to the future workforce</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/podcast-introducing-ai-future-workforce</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>A workforce fluent in AI techniques will be essential to ensure U.S. leadership in artificial intelligence continues. Jeremy Waisome, an assistant pro...</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 18:56:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF invests $29.2 million in EPSCoR Research Infrastructure collaborations for transformative impact across 11 jurisdictions</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-invests-292-million-epscor-research-infrastructure</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation (NSF) has announced six major awards through its EPSCoR Research Infrastructure Improvement Program: Focused EPSC...</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 14:55:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF invests nearly $32M to accelerate novel AI-driven approaches in protein design, strengthening the U.S. bioeconomy</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-invests-nearly-32m-accelerate-novel-ai-driven-approaches</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation Directorate for Technology, Innovation and Partnerships (NSF TIP) announced an inaugural investment of nearly $32...</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 15:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>