<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:50:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Supreme Court hears arguments on Trump immunity case</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/politics/live-news/supreme-court-trump-immunity-04-25-24/index.html</link><image_url>https://cdn.cnn.com/cnnnext/dam/assets/240425091545-01-us-supreme-court-042524-super-169.jpg</image_url><description>The Supreme Court is hearing arguments Thursday in the blockbuster case over whether former President Donald Trump may claim immunity from prosecution in the federal election subversion case. Follow here for the latest live news updates, analysis and more.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:13:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gay actor's speech back on at Pennsylvania school after cancellation over his 'lifestyle'</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/wireStory/gay-actors-speech-back-pennsylvania-school-after-cancellation-109627867</link><description>A Pennsylvania school district has reversed the cancellation of an appearance by actor and children’s book author Maulik Pancholy</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:41:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>College protests over Gaza sweep across America. Hundreds arrested</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/business/live-news/columbia-usc-university-protests-04-25-24/index.html</link><image_url>https://cdn.cnn.com/cnnnext/dam/assets/240424152426-usc-protests-nick-watt-042424-super-169.jpg</image_url><description>Pro-Palestinian protests are taking place at major US universities, prompting some officials to take extraordinary steps to confront the growing crisis. Follow for live news updates.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 15:59:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FTC sends $5.6 million in refunds to Ring customers as part of video privacy settlement</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Business/wireStory/ftc-sends-56-million-refunds-ring-customers-part-109627889</link><description>The Federal Trade Commission is sending more than $5.6 million in refunds to consumers as part of a settlement with Amazon-owned Ring, which was charged with failing to protect private video footage from outside access</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:38:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Former tabloid executive continues testimony in Trump trial</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/politics/live-news/trump-hush-money-trial-04-25-24/index.html</link><image_url>https://cdn.cnn.com/cnnnext/dam/assets/240425095639-dle-donald-trump-042524-super-169.jpg</image_url><description>Witness testimony continues Thursday in Donald Trump's hush money criminal trial. Follow here for the latest live news updates from court, analysis and more.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 15:32:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>High schooler accused of killing fellow student on campus in Arlington, Texas</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/wireStory/high-schooler-accused-killing-fellow-student-campus-arlington-109628467</link><description>Police say a 17-year-old has been arrested on a murder warrant after fatally shooting a schoolmate on the campus of an Arlington, Texas, high school</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:37:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Venice entry fee tickets go on sale. Here's how they work</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/venice-entry-fee-explained/index.html</link><image_url>https://cdn.cnn.com/cnnnext/dam/assets/240116144435-04-venice-entry-fee-super-169.jpg</image_url><description>Venice's long awaited entry fee for day trippers launched on April 25. Here's how to pay, and how to claim an exemption if you're staying in the city.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 14:37:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump immunity case updates: Lawyer says assassinating rival could be 'official act'</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/live-updates/trump-immunity-supreme-court-arguments/?id=109581119</link><description>The Supreme Court is hearing a historic case on whether Trump has immunity or can be criminally prosecuted over his efforts to overturn his 2020 election loss</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:36:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kashmir Fast Facts</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2013/11/08/world/kashmir-fast-facts/index.html</link><image_url>https://cdn.cnn.com/cnnnext/dam/assets/161002225934-kashmir-militant-attack-kapur-live-00010629-super-169.jpg</image_url><description>Read CNN's Fast Facts about Kashmir, a region in the Himalayan and Karakoram mountain ranges. India, Pakistan and China all claim partial or complete ownership.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 13:39:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Harvey Weinstein's rape conviction overturned in New York; DA will attempt to retry</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/harvey-weinstein-conviction-overturned-new-york/story?id=109621776</link><description>The rape conviction of movie producer Harvey Weinstein has been overturned by New York's highest court.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:35:47 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>