<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 12:05:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>‘The Bear’ Is a Portrait of Food Culture Run Amok</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2024/06/27/opinion/the-bear-toxic-chefs.html</link><image_url>https://static01.nyt.com/images/misc/NYT_logo_rss_250x40.png</image_url><description>The celebrated show is both a product of our unhealthy obsession with toxic restaurant culture and a potential remedy for it.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:58:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Middle East Crisis: Israel Orders Evacuations as Strikes Pound Gaza City</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/live/2024/06/27/world/israel-gaza-war-hamas</link><image_url>https://static01.nyt.com/images/misc/NYT_logo_rss_250x40.png</image_url><description>The military had begun an operation against Hamas fighters who returned to an eastern part of Gaza’s biggest city, Israel’s public broadcaster reported.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:54:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sam’s Club is going after Costco through the hearts and wallets of Gen Z shoppers. ‘That generation believes it’s cool to save money,’ CEO says</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/06/27/sams-club-costco-gen-z-store-brand-kirkland/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/GettyImages-1410188362-e1719436491181.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The Walmart-owned retailer’s digital strategies and budget brands have struck a chord with tech-savvy and deal-driven Gen Z.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:58:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Boeing Sanctioned by NTSB Over Disclosures on 737 Max Investigation</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2024/06/27/business/boeing-737-max-ntsb.html</link><image_url>https://static01.nyt.com/images/2024/06/28/multimedia/27boeing-wcgh/27boeing-wcgh-mediumSquareAt3X.jpg</image_url><description>The National Transportation Safety Board said Boeing had improperly released information about the blowout of a panel on an Alaska Airlines flight.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:55:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Bird-watchers Paradise, Opened Up by Colombia’s Peace Deal</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/card/2024/06/25/world/americas/colombia-birdwatching</link><image_url>https://static01.nyt.com/images/misc/NYT_logo_rss_250x40.png</image_url><description>The 2016 peace treaty that ended a decades-long civil conflict has turned Colombia — home to more species of birds than any other country on Earth — into a birders’ delight, opening up forests that were once controlled by anti-government armed groups.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:54:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Doctors in Idaho can now provide emergency abortions, SCOTUS rules, after pregnant women were airlifted out of the state for emergency care</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/06/27/idaho-emergency-abortions-supreme-court/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/GettyImages-2149407061-e1719499809547.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The ruling came a day after an opinion was briefly posted on the court's website accidentally and quickly taken down, but not before it was obtained by Bloomberg News.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:51:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘A Personality Contest Is a Contest Trump May Lose’: Three Writers Preview the Biden-Trump Debate</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2024/06/27/opinion/trump-biden-debate-preview.html</link><image_url>https://static01.nyt.com/images/2024/06/27/opinion/27bruni-roundtable/27bruni-roundtable-mediumSquareAt3X.jpg</image_url><description>When Trump and Biden square off, we can expect disorientation, dizziness and much else.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:47:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>At Least 750,000 on Brink of Starvation and Death in Sudan, Experts Warn</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2024/06/27/world/africa/sudan-famine-starvation.html</link><image_url>https://static01.nyt.com/images/misc/NYT_logo_rss_250x40.png</image_url><description>A devastating civil war is pushing the country toward a full-blown famine, according to the international body that measures hunger.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:24:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ellevest’s founder went to Wall Street after being rejected by her first choice. Now her $2 billion empire is helping women build their own wealth</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/06/27/sallie-krawcheck-ellevest-ceo-secrets-to-success/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/Sallie-5.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The investing industry tends to look past women and mostly serve men, longtime Wall Street executive Sallie Krawcheck says. That's what led her to build Ellevest.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:50:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Two Killer Asteroids Are Flying by Earth, and You May Be Able to See One</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2024/06/27/science/asteroid-earth-nasa.html</link><image_url>https://static01.nyt.com/images/2024/06/27/multimedia/27sci-double-asteroids-bjkc/27sci-double-asteroids-bjkc-mediumSquareAt3X.jpg</image_url><description>The smaller of the pair was spotted only this month and could be visible with binoculars as it passes by our planet within the distance to the moon.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:33:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scaled-Back but Determined Protests in Kenya Call for President to Resign</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2024/06/27/world/africa/kenya-protests-taxes-president-ruto.html</link><image_url>https://static01.nyt.com/images/misc/NYT_logo_rss_250x40.png</image_url><description>The demonstrations were held despite his withdrawal of the tax bill that sparked days of protests. Some activists, fearing more bloodshed, warned people not to march to the president’s official residence.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:16:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Supreme Court just rejected a deal with the maker of OxyContin that would have shielded the billionaire Sackler family from liability—but provided billions of dollars to fight opioids</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/06/27/supreme-court-rejects-purdue-pharma-oxycontin-bankruptcy-settlement-sackler-family-opioid-epidemic/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/GettyImages-1824551962-e1719501501140.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Had the bankruptcy been approved, the Sacklers would have contributed up to $6 billion and given up ownership of the company but retained billions more.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:46:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>At Least 750,000 on Brink of Starvation and Death in Sudan, Experts Warn</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2024/06/27/world/africa/sudan-famine-starvation.html</link><image_url>https://static01.nyt.com/images/2024/06/27/multimedia/27sudan-1-zmkc/27sudan-1-zmkc-mediumSquareAt3X.jpg</image_url><description>A devastating civil war is pushing the country toward a full-blown famine, according to the international body that measures hunger.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:24:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Last Stand of the Woolly Mammoths</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2024/06/27/science/mammoth-genes-wrangel.html</link><image_url>https://static01.nyt.com/images/misc/NYT_logo_rss_250x40.png</image_url><description>The species survived on an island north of Siberia for thousands of years, scientists reported, but were most likely plagued by genetic abnormalities.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:13:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cybersecurity is now a ‘team sport’ amid a wave of generative AI-based attacks, say tech experts</title><link>https://fortune.com/asia/2024/06/27/cybersecurity-is-team-sport-amid-generative-ai-based-attacks-tech-experts-accenture/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/GettyImages-2022975324-e1719480883691.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>AI "is available to both our friends and foes," warned Maria Milosavljevic, group CISO at ANZ Banking Group, at a Fortune conversation Wednesday.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:45:58 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>