<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 08:10:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>German hotel partially collapses, killing 1 and trapping 8, police say</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/german-hotel-partially-collapses-killing-1-trapping-8/story?id=112633201</link><description>At least one person was killed and eight others remained trapped Wednesday after a hotel partially collapsed in the winemaking town of Kroev, Germany.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 10:07:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Romanian PM to boycott Olympics' closing ceremony after 'scandalous situation' in gymnastics ruling</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/romanian-pm-boycott-olympics-closing-152445637.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 16:24:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Belgian Olympian says virus got her sick, not E. coli from Seine River swim</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/claire-michel-belgian-olympian-sick-seine-river-swim-virus-not-e-coli/</link><description>Claire Michel, a Belgian triathlete who fell ill after a swim in the Seine River,says a virus that made her sick, not E. coli from the waterway.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:42:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CVS Health cuts its 2024 forecast a third time, dragged down by insurance struggles</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Business/wireStory/cvs-health-cuts-2024-forecast-time-dragged-health-112635354</link><description>CVS Health has chopped its 2024 forecast for a third time as the health care giant continues to struggle with high utilization in its health insurance business</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:42:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Insider Buying: CVRx President Bought US$251k Of Shares</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/insider-buying-cvrx-president-bought-112523922.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:25:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rocket fuel chemical is widespread in food, Consumer Reports finds</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/consumer-reports-chemical-rocket-fuel-perchlorate/</link><description>Perchlorate is found in a wide variety of foods, especially products popular with babies and kids, advocacy group says.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:34:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>4 hotel workers charged with felony murder in death of man captured being pinned down</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/d-vontaye-mitchell-death-murder-charges/story?id=112626265</link><description>The Milwaukee District Attorney's Office announced Tuesday it has filed a felony murder charge against four individuals related to D'Vontaye Mitchell's death.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:26:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BMW set to revolutionize EV range with new in-wheel motor: 'An exciting vision for the electric drive of the future'</title><link>https://autos.yahoo.com/bmw-set-revolutionize-ev-range-073000081.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 08:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Part of Germany hotel collapses, killing at least 2 people, trapping others</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/part-hotel-germany-mosel-river-collapses-people-dead-others-trapped/</link><description>Among those saved was a 2-year-old child pulled out unharmed and the child's mother, who was rescued with minor injuries. The child's father is still trapped.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 11:44:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Progressive Rep. Cori Bush loses high-stakes Democratic primary: AP projection</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/progressive-rep-cori-bush-loses-high-stakes-democratic/story?id=107328890</link><description>After a fiercely competitive primary race, the Associated Press projects that St. Louis County Prosecuting Attorney Wesley Bell has won the Democratic primary in MO.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 11:07:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Schwab, Fidelity, other online trading brokerages appear to go dark during huge market sell-off</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/schwab-fidelity-other-online-trading-151427448.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 16:14:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>U.K. mint extracts gold from e-waste: "What we're doing here is urban mining"</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/uk-royal-mint-extracting-gold-from-e-waste-urban-mining/</link><description>"We're taking a waste product that's being produced by society and we're mining the gold from that waste product and starting to see the value in that finite resource," a mint official says.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 11:35:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Woman charged in  Arizona 'fake elector' case pleads guilty, docket shows</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/woman-charged-arizona-fake-elector-case-pleads-guilty/story?id=112628710</link><description>One of former President Donald Trump's so-called "fake electors" has plead guilty to a single "reduced charge" in the Arizona's 2020 election case.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 04:38:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Archrock's (NYSE:AROC) Earnings Are Weaker Than They Seem</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/archrocks-nyse-aroc-earnings-weaker-110240444.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:02:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Green River Killer detective advances in race for Washington governor</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/green-river-killer-detective-dave-reichert-washington-state-attorney-general-bob-ferguson-advance-race-governor/</link><description>Bob Ferguson, a Democrat, will face Republican Dave Reichert, a former sheriff known for his work hunting down the notorious serial killer.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 11:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Body found during search for 5-year-old boy who wandered away from his birthday party</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/missing-boy-boise-idaho-matthew-glynn/story?id=112614805</link><description>Matthew Glynn was last seen by family members at his fifth birthday party Monday afternoon, Boise police said.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:51:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Debby tracker: See tropical storm's path as states brace for more rain, flooding</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/debby-tracker-see-tropical-storms-114416380.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:44:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Preliminary 5.2-magnitude earthquake strikes near Bakersfield, rattles LA County</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/preliminary-5-7-magnitude-earthquake-strikes-near-bakersfield-shakes-all-the-way-to-la-county/</link><description>A preliminary 5.2-magnitude earthquake struck near Bakersfield and shook all the way to Los Angeles County.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 06:42:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Microsoft hits back at Delta after the airline said last month's tech outage cost it $500 million</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Technology/wireStory/microsoft-hits-back-delta-after-airline-months-tech-112626969</link><description>Microsoft is joining cybersecurity firm CrowdStrike in fighting back against criticism from Delta Air Lines</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:19:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Utility company's proposal to rat out hidden marijuana operations to police raises privacy concerns</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/utility-companys-proposal-rat-hidden-042447520.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 05:24:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Slotkin, Rogers win Senate primaries in Michigan, CBS News projects</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/elissa-slotkin-mike-rogers-win-michigan-us-senate-primary-races/</link><description>Democratic Rep. Elissa Slotkin and former Republican Rep. Mike Rogers will face off in November for the seat held by Sen. Debbie Stabenow.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:08:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>American Cole Hocker pulls Olympic shocker in men's 1,500, leaving Kerr and Ingebrigtsen behind</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Sports/wireStory/hocker-pulls-olympic-shocker-mens-1500-leaving-kerr-112618966</link><description>American Cole Hocker pulled the upset of the Olympics on Tuesday night, outracing both favorites Jakob Ingebrigtsen and Josh Kerr to the finish line in the 1,500 meters</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:34:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Disney returns to profit in third quarter as streaming business starts making money for first time</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/disney-returns-profits-third-quarter-113518633.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:35:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>U.S. women's soccer team to play Brazil for Olympic gold medal</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/video/us-womens-soccer-team-to-play-brazil-olympic-gold-medal/</link><description>The U.S. women's soccer team advanced to the Olympic final with a 1-0 victory over Germany on Tuesday. The team will face Brazil in the gold medal match on Aug. 10. "CBS Saturday Morning" co-host and CBS News and sports correspondent Dana Jacobson has an Olympic recap from Paris.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 01:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>9 dead, including 6 children, after vehicle overturns in canal</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/4-dead-6-injured-after-vehicle-crashes-canal/story?id=112602308</link><description>Nine people are dead, including five juveniles, and one person was injured after a vehicle crashed into a canal in Palm Beach County, Florida, authorities said.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 01:46:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Buffalo man buys lemon from local used car lot, gets help from Erie Times-News</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/buffalo-man-buys-lemon-local-085633606.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 09:56:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Georgia, South Carolina and Florida work to clear Debby aftermath</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/video/georgia-south-carolina-florida-work-to-clear-debby-aftermath/</link><description>Tropical Storm Debby is moving north after dropping huge amounts of rain on parts of the Southeast. President Biden has authorized emergency declarations from the governors of Florida, Georgia and South Carolina. CBS News correspondent Cristian Benavides has the latest from Savannah, Georgia.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 01:52:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Kamala Harris decided on her running mate, Tim Walz</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/harris-decided-running-mate/story?id=112625017</link><description>Vice President Kamala Harris spent this past weekend interviewing the top contenders on her VP shortlist.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:28:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Reclusive tribe attacks loggers suspected of encroaching on their land in Peru's Amazon</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/reclusive-tribe-attacks-loggers-suspected-224401208.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:44:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Harris, Walz kick off tour of battleground states</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/video/harris-walz-kick-off-battleground-state-tour/</link><description>After weeks of speculation, Vice President Kamala Harris has selected Minnesota Gov. Tim Walz as her 2024 running mate. The two are now embarking on a tour of seven battleground states this week, starting with the rally in Philadelphia earlier Tuesday. Nidia Cavazos, CBS News campaign reporter, and Robby Mook, manager of Hillary Clinton's 2016 presidential campaign, join with more.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 01:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ex-deputy charged in Sonya Massey killing says he feared for his life, new docs show</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/deputy-charged-sonya-massey-killing-feared-life-new/story?id=112604944</link><description>The Sangamon County Sheriff’s Office (SCSO) released new documents in deputy-involved shooting death of Sonya Massey.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 21:27:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'I Almost Died of Liver Failure at Age 50—This Is the First Sign I Wish I'd Paid Attention To'</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/almost-died-liver-failure-age-232500054.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 00:25:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Calls for violence spiked online after Trump rally shooting</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/video/calls-for-violence-spiked-online-after-trump-rally-shooting/</link><description>Immediately following July's assassination attempt on former President Donald Trump, there was a significant spike in calls for violence across online platforms. The research firm Moonshot, which tracks domestic violent extremism online, found there were more than 1,500 calls for civil war the day after the shooting — up more than 600% from a normal day. Anna Schecter, senior coordinating producer for CBS News' crime and public safety unit, has the details.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 01:46:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elon Musk's X sues advertisers over alleged 'massive advertiser boycott' after Twitter takeover</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Business/wireStory/elon-musks-sues-advertisers-alleged-massive-advertiser-boycott-112613353</link><description>A "massive advertiser boycott" allegedly deprived X of billions of dollars.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 01:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The youngest Fortune 500 CFO was set up to run his family’s $21 billion chicken empire. His erratic behavior could change that</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/youngest-cfo-fortune-500-set-125759942.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 13:57:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hamas names mastermind of Oct. 7 attacks as political leader</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/video/hamas-names-mastermind-oct-7-attacks-political-leader/</link><description>Amid ongoing cease-fire and hostage negotiations, Hamas has named a key figure behind the Oct. 7 attacks on Israel as its new political leader following the assassination of Ismail Haniyeh in Iran. CBS News foreign correspondent Ramy Inocencio reports from Jerusalem.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 01:44:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Critics blast new VP nominee Tim Walz for 'massive' COVID-19 fraud 'under his watch'</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/critics-blast-new-vp-nominee-tim-walz-massive/story?id=112616260</link><description>As Tim Walz joins Kamala Harris on the Democratic presidential ticket, critics are blasting the governor for how he handled a massive COVID-19 fraud scheme in his state.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 10:27:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elon Musk's X sues advertisers over alleged 'massive advertiser boycott' after Twitter takeover</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musks-x-sues-advertisers-162213500.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 17:22:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How will Tim Walz impact the Harris campaign?</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/video/how-will-tim-walz-impact-harris-campaign/</link><description>Vice President Kamala Harris announced Minnesota Gov. Tim Walz as her 2024 running mate early Tuesday ahead of their first joint rally in the key state of Pennsylvania. CBS News senior White House and political correspondent Ed O'Keefe, Democratic strategist Joel Payne and CBS News campaign reporter Taurean Small join with more.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 01:42:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>LIVE:  ABC News Live</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Live/video/abcnews-live-41463246</link><description>24/7 coverage of breaking news and live events</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 23:58:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Georgia Aquarium CEO passes away; ‘limited operations’ as staff mourns loss</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/georgia-aquarium-ceo-passes-away-235626844.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 00:56:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Boeing questioned over mid-air door panel blowout</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/video/boeing-questioned-mid-air-door-panel-blowout/</link><description>Top Boeing officials faced tough questions from the National Transportation Safety Board on Tuesday over a mid-air door panel blowout on one of its planes earlier this year. The incident raised new questions about the company's aircraft safety. CBS News senior transportation correspondent Kris Van Cleave has the latest.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 01:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>California rocked by 5.3 magnitude earthquake centered near Bakersfield</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/southern-california-rocked-53-magnitude-earthquake-centered-bakersfield/story?id=112631691</link><description>California experienced a spate of earthquakes on Tuesday night.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 09:34:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>After Serena Williams Claimed That She And Her Kids Were Denied Entry To A Restaurant In Paris, A Staff Member Detailed What Apparently Went Down</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/restaurant-paris-responded-serena-williams-154945914.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 16:49:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Simone Biles says she has "no regrets" following Paris Olympics</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/video/simone-biles-says-she-has-no-regrets-following-paris-olympics/</link><description>Simone Biles is returning home from the Paris Olympic Games with three more gold medals to add to her collection. Jamie Yuccas spoke with the most decorated gymnast in history about her successes and disappointments.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 01:25:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WATCH:  1st new pandas to arrive in US in over 20 years are about to make their debut</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/GMA/Living/video/1st-new-pandas-arrive-us-20-years-make-112626154</link><description>Pandas Yun Chuan and Xin Bao will be available for public viewing at the San Diego Zoo starting Aug. 8.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 01:49:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hamas names Yahya Sinwar, mastermind of the Oct. 7 attacks, as its new leader in show of defiance</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/hamas-says-chosen-yahya-sinwar-181030234.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:10:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Need a pest control company? Here are 5 signs that you do</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/essentials/do-i-need-a-pest-control-company/</link><description>From creepy sounds to visible structural damage, these five signs mean it's time to call a professional pest control company.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 01:13:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WATCH:  Tornado wreaks havoc in Buffalo, New York</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/WNT/video/tornado-wreaks-havoc-buffalo-new-york-112595658</link><description>The rare weather event in the area tore roofs off buildings, left some without power and flipped over a car.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 01:27:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Newly released surveillance video shows D’Vontaye Mitchell’s last moments</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/newly-released-surveillance-video-shows-020553773.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 03:05:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Best back-to-school deals on smartwatches</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/essentials/smartwatch-deals/</link><description>Now's a great time to check out deals on smartwatches for back-to-school from Apple, Google, Samsung and more.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 01:08:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WATCH:  Football player has priceless reaction after sister wins gold at 2024 Olympics</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/GMA/Culture/video/football-player-priceless-reaction-after-sister-wins-gold-112571705</link><description>Thea LaFond’s brother Chreign LaFond couldn’t be prouder after finding out she won Dominica's first-ever gold medal in the triple jump finals in Paris.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 16:22:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>US woman found chained to tree in India tied herself, say police</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-woman-found-chained-tree-162048727.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 17:20:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The best laptops under $1,000 don't skimp on the features</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/essentials/best-laptops-under-1000/</link><description>Here's a roundup of laptops that cost $1,000 or less, but that can easily handle your everyday computing tasks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WATCH:  Bears tussle in California yard</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/video/bears-tussle-california-yard-112560117</link><description>Two bears were captured having a playful tussle in the yard of a home in South Lake Tahoe, California.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 18:47:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>US Supreme Court declines to halt Trump's sentencing in hush money case</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-supreme-court-declines-halt-184804444.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 19:48:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Samsung's 2024 Frame TV review: A great option for watching NFL football and more</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/essentials/samsungs-2024-frame-tv-review/</link><description>We got our hands on Samsung's 2024 65" Frame smart TV. And, yep, it's still worth every penny.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 00:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WATCH:  Humpback whale spotted swimming without tail</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/video/humpback-whale-spotted-swimming-tail-112560192</link><description>A humpback whale that was missing its tail and spotted in Washington state's inland waters likely lost its iconic flukes after becoming entangled, experts say.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 18:48:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Check your lottery tickets. A winning Mega Millions game was sold at a store in SC</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/check-lottery-tickets-winning-mega-163447474.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 17:34:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 6 best OLED TVs for 2024 offer unbeatable color and detail</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/essentials/best-oled-tvs/</link><description>Discover the best OLED TVs and why they're a great option for watching movies and sports, as well as for gaming.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 00:53:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WATCH:  President Biden welcomes Gershkovich, Whelan, Kurmasheva home</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/video/president-biden-welcomes-gershkovich-whelan-kurmasheva-home-112502375</link><description>BREAKING: Freed Americans Evan Gershkovich, Paul Whelan and Alsu Kurmasheva arrive in the U.S. after a historic prisoner swap with Russia.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 12:37:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cori Bush becomes second 'Squad' member to lose 2024 primary as Democrats split over Israel</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/cori-bush-becomes-second-squad-030104679.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 04:01:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Israel remains on edge ahead of anticipated Iran retaliation</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/video/israel-remains-on-edge-ahead-of-anticipated-iran-retaliation/</link><description>Iran and its proxies are still expected to retaliate against Israel following the assassinations of senior Hamas and Hezbollah leaders. Imtiaz Tyab has the latest.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 00:49:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WATCH:  Biden sings ‘Happy Birthday’ to daughter of freed prisoner</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/video/biden-sings-happy-birthday-daughter-freed-prisoner-112481986</link><description>The daughter of Alsu Kurmasheva, a Russian-American journalist released in the prisoner exchange, turns 13 on Friday.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 18:29:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fossils suggest even smaller ‘hobbits’ roamed an Indonesian island 700,000 years ago</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/fossils-suggest-even-smaller-hobbits-150225679.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 16:02:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Debby bringing record-breaking rain as it moves slowly up East Coast</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/video/debby-bringing-record-breaking-rain-as-it-moves-slowly-up-east-coast/</link><description>Tropical Storm Debby is dropping record amounts of rain and causing flooding as it moves slowly along the East Coast. The precipitation isn't forecast to let up, as the storm is expected to linger in the Southeast in the coming days. Manuel Bojorquez reports.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 00:49:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WATCH:  How a 4-eared cat is ‘bringing good luck’ to Tennessee animal shelter</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/GMA/Living/video/4-eared-cat-bringing-good-luck-tennessee-animal-112489737</link><description>Audio, a cat born with four ears, currently resides at True Rescue, an animal shelter in Mt. Juliet, Tennessee, as he awaits to be adopted.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 20:34:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Major Earth Systems on Track for Collapse, Scientists Find</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/major-earth-systems-track-collapse-223031664.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 23:30:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pakistani man charged in alleged murder-for-hire plot against Trump, U.S. officials</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/video/pakistani-man-charged-in-alleged-murder-for-hire-plot-against-trump-u-s-officials/</link><description>A Pakistani man with alleged ties to Iran is accused by the Justice Department of being part of a murder-for-hire plot against former President Trump and other U.S. officials. Nicole Sganga has the details.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 00:49:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WATCH:  Family of ducks photobomb beautiful sunset shot</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Lifestyle/video/family-ducks-photobomb-beautiful-sunset-shot-112463079</link><description>A piece of driftwood provided the perfect frame for a stunning sunset shot at a Michigan beach -- and the moment was made even more special when a family of ducks waddled into frame.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 04:19:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What is emphysema? David Lynch reveals impact of 'many years of smoking'</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/emphysema-smoking-lung-damage-symptoms-treatment-105506332.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 11:55:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A closer look at Tim Walz's background</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/video/a-closer-look-at-tim-walzs-background/</link><description>With Minnesota Gov. Tim Walz chosen as Vice President Kamala Harris' running mate, Ed O'Keefe takes a closer look at the background of the potential next vice president.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 00:48:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pakistani national charged with alleged plot to assassinate Trump, other officials</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/pakistani-national-charged-alleged-plot-assassinate-donald-trump/story?id=112617075</link><description>A Pakistani national with purported ties to Iran was arrested last month on charges he plotted to assassinate former President Donald Trump.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:47:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Citigroup whistleblower denied share of $400 million penalty</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/citigroup-whistleblower-denied-share-400-182857175.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:28:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Harris taps Minnesota Gov. Tim Walz for running mate</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/video/harris-taps-minnesota-gov-tim-walz-for-running-mate/</link><description>Vice President Kamala Harris has chosen Minnesota Gov. Tim Walz as her running mate. The two appeared at a campaign event in Philadelphia on Tuesday. Nancy Cordes has more on the pick.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 00:48:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>We now know when NC 540 will open across southern Wake County</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/now-know-nc-540-open-192539058.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:25:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>"CBS Evening News" headlines for Tuesday, Aug. 6, 2024</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/video/cbs-evening-news-headlines-for-tuesday-aug-6-2024/</link><description>Here's a look at the top stories making headlines on the "CBS Evening News" with Major Garrett.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 00:47:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Passengers narrowly escape disaster as plane’s tires burst during takeoff, shattering window</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/passengers-narrowly-escape-disaster-plane-095100869.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 10:51:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Democrats turn to influencers to help share their message on social media</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/influencer-social-media-politics/</link><description>Democrats have deployed a fleet of influencers to try to win over voters online – and match the hundreds of millions of dollars on similar efforts spent by the right.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 00:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Factbox-Deals signed by Italy and China after PM Meloni's trip</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/factbox-deals-signed-italy-china-145106849.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:51:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 6 best TVs for watching the 2024-5 NFL season</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/essentials/best-tvs-for-sports-nfl/</link><description>If you're looking to upgrade your TV to watch the 2024-5 NFL season, here are our top recommendations for watching live sports and other action.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 00:43:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New report warns that taxpayers could end up paying $3 billion for state's energy disaster — here's why</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/report-warns-taxpayers-could-end-150000035.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The best 32-inch TVs for college dorms are small but mighty</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/essentials/the-best-32-inch-tvs-for-dorms/</link><description>These 32-inch TVs are small yet mighty displays that work beautifully in compact living spaces.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 00:43:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I Did Everything 'Right' And I Still Got Herpes. Years Later, I'm Finally Making My Peace With That.</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/did-everything-still-got-herpes-130002159.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Milwaukee hotel workers charged with felony murder in death of Black man</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/dvontaye-mitchell-milwaukee-hotel-workers-charged-murder/</link><description>Cellphone video ​footage showed the four workers holding down D'Vontaye Mitchell on the hotel's driveway.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 00:42:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deputy who shot Sonya Massey thought her rebuke 'in the name of Jesus' indicated intent to kill him</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/deputy-shot-sonya-massey-thought-231338745.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 00:13:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Woman accused of stabbing worker in head following fight at Boston restaurant</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/woman-accused-stabbing-worker-head-112505957.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 12:25:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Warren Buffett's Unprecedented $132 Billion Warning to Wall Street Can't Be Ignored Any Longer</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/warren-buffetts-unprecedented-132-billion-080600021.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 09:06:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Russia warns Ukraine: peace terms will only get worse</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/russia-warns-ukraine-peace-terms-122512188.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 13:25:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trail cameras capture encouraging footage of one of the rarest large mammal species in the world — and it comes with a surprise</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trail-cameras-capture-encouraging-footage-020000209.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 03:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Watch: AC-130J gunship pummels Navy vessel during Rim of the Pacific</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/watch-ac-130j-gunship-pummels-183907269.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 19:39:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CrowdStrike is sued by fliers after massive outage disrupts air travel</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crowdstrike-sued-fliers-massive-outage-213238215.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 22:32:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CHP seeks public’s help in identifying Northern California hit-and-run suspect</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/chp-seeks-public-help-identifying-201900158.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 21:19:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FBI Raids Home of Rep Trying to Impeach Kamala Harris</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/fbi-raids-home-rep-trying-211751272.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 22:17:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mexico invites Putin to presidential inauguration, Russia's Izvestia newspaper says</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/mexico-invites-putin-presidential-inauguration-220611526.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 23:06:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>With Shares Down Nearly 30%, Is Now the Time to Buy This Software Stock?</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/shares-down-nearly-30-now-143900304.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 15:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump and Vance Roast Themselves With Accidentally Hilarious Signs</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-vance-roast-themselves-accidentally-131119968.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:11:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SpaceX Starship’s 2nd Flight Footage Released Under Freedom Of Information Act By NASA</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/spacex-starship-2nd-flight-footage-190320555.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian wrestling star Vinesh Phogat disqualified before gold medal bout after coming in 100 grams overweight</title><link>https://sports.yahoo.com/indian-wrestling-star-vinesh-phogat-070945837.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 09:53:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jinger Duggar Details Siblings’ Fear of Not Having ‘Enough’ Food Growing Up in Duggar House</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/jinger-duggar-details-siblings-fear-182108010.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 19:21:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Judge dismisses most claims in federal lawsuit filed by Black Texas student punished over hairstyle</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/judge-dismisses-most-claims-federal-011431465.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:14:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Big Powerball win at local Giant Eagle</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/winning-powerball-ticket-sold-local-095754637.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 10:57:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fox News host knocks Trump: ‘You either own the markets or you don’t’</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/fox-news-host-knocks-trump-133221737.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 14:32:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Intel is taking another of ASML's High NA tools, says CEO</title><link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/intel-taking-another-asmls-high-141533952.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 15:15:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ukraine Situation Report: Cross-Border Raid Shakes Russia’s Kursk Region</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/ukraine-situation-report-cross-border-002335679.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 01:23:35 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>