<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 06:57:39 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Devastation in Gaza as Israel wages war on Hamas</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/middleeast/live-news/israel-hamas-war-gaza-news-05-10-24/index.html</link><image_url>https://cdn.cnn.com/cnnnext/dam/assets/240509143110-rafah-super-169.jpg</image_url><description>Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu said Israel would fight with its "fingernails" if necessary after President Joe Biden's ultimatum that a major Israeli offensive in the Gazan city of Rafah would result in a shut-off of some US weapons. Follow for live updates.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:24:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Man sentenced to 27 years for stabbing 3 officers in Times Square on New Year's Eve</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/times-square-knife-attack-sentencing/story?id=110075248</link><description>Trevor Bickford was sentenced to 27 years in federal prison for a "brazen" 2022 New Year's Eve knife attack that seriously injured three NYPD officers, the DOJ said.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:48:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>May 9, 2024 Israel-Hamas war</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/middleeast/live-news/israel-hamas-war-gaza-news-05-09-24/index.html</link><image_url>https://cdn.cnn.com/cnnnext/dam/assets/240509153053-israeli-attacks-rafah-border-super-169.jpg</image_url><description>Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu said US President Joe Biden made a mistake after the US paused sending a shipment of bombs to Israel so that they would not used in an invasion of the southern Gaza city of Rafah.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 05:00:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prince Harry, Meghan arrive in Nigeria to champion the Invictus Games</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Entertainment/wireStory/prince-harry-meghan-arrive-nigeria-invictus-games-meet-110097991</link><description>Prince Harry and his wife Meghan have arrived in Nigeria to champion the Invictus Games, which he founded to aid the rehabilitation of wounded and sick servicemembers and veterans</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 10:50:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stormy Daniels wraps up testimony in Trump hush money trial</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/politics/live-news/trump-hush-money-trial-05-09-24/index.html</link><image_url>https://cdn.cnn.com/cnnnext/dam/assets/240509121650-sketch-tapper-02b-donald-trump-hush-money-trial-050924-super-169.jpg</image_url><description>The testimony of adult film actress Stormy Daniels, a central figure in the criminal case against Donald Trump, wrapped on Thursday after the former president's lawyers continued their attack on her credibility.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 00:29:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pope urges Italians to have babies as a measure of hope for future</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/pope-urges-italians-babies-measure-hope-future-110098340</link><description>Pope Francis has pressed his campaign to urge Italians to have children</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 10:47:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Today's news in 10 minutes</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2024/05/02/cnn10/ten-content-fri-5-10/index.html</link><description>May 10, 2024</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 17:21:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hopes fading for 44 workers still missing days after South Africa building collapse</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/hopes-fading-44-workers-missing-days-after-south-110098081</link><description>Hopes are fading for 44 construction workers buried for days in the rubble of a building that collapsed in South Africa</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 10:26:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2 men charged in connection with the fatal shooting of a 1-year-old boy in New York</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/06/us/one-year-old-death-new-york-charges/index.html</link><image_url>https://cdn.cnn.com/cnnnext/dam/assets/210506185532-01-one-year-old-death-new-york-charges-super-169.jpg</image_url><description>Dashawn Austin and Akeem Artis were two of 18 charged in a 63-count indictment for gang-related activity including multiple counts of murder and weapons charges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 15:23:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Air Vanuatu files for bankruptcy protection after canceling all international flights</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/air-vanuatu-files-bankruptcy-protection-after-canceling-20-110093132</link><description>Air Vanuatu has filed for bankruptcy protection a day after it cancelled all international flights, stranding thousands of travelers</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 06:02:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>