<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 22:38:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>At Trump Rally, Few Local Police Officers in Critical Area Before Shooting</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2024/07/20/us/politics/trump-rally-police-secret-service-shooting.html</link><image_url>https://static01.nyt.com/images/2024/07/20/multimedia/20dc-secret-service-glft/20dc-secret-service-glft-mediumSquareAt3X.jpg</image_url><description>Local law enforcement officials, present in abundance, said they were not assigned security duties around a warehouse used by a man who tried to kill former President Donald Trump.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 03:12:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dozens Dead or Missing After China Highway Collapse</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2024/07/20/world/asia/china-highway-collapse.html</link><image_url>https://static01.nyt.com/images/misc/NYT_logo_rss_250x40.png</image_url><description>It was the second such rain-related disaster in less than three months, as extreme weather challenges the country’s extensive network of newly built expressways.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 02:27:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Junk bonds are now in high demand as Wall Street bets on another Trump presidency</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/07/20/junk-bonds-donald-trump-trade-corporate-tax-cuts-tariffs-election/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/GettyImages-2162000451_2d93e9-e1721516063158.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>“US high yield is the trade. It is more domestic-focused and exposed to US economic activity.”</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 00:01:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Before the Alec Baldwin Trial’s End, 2 Jurors Had Doubts About His Guilt</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2024/07/20/arts/alec-baldwin-rust-jurors.html</link><image_url>https://static01.nyt.com/images/2024/07/20/multimedia/20baldwin-jurors1-tcgz/20baldwin-jurors1-tcgz-mediumSquareAt3X.jpg</image_url><description>When the judge threw out the case, the jurors said, they had doubts that Mr. Baldwin was guilty of involuntary manslaughter in the fatal shooting of the cinematographer on the set of the film “Rust.”</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 01:05:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Israeli Jets Bomb Sites in Yemen Linked to Iran-Backed Houthis</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2024/07/20/world/middleeast/israel-houthis-yemen.html</link><image_url>https://static01.nyt.com/images/misc/NYT_logo_rss_250x40.png</image_url><description>The strike was retaliation for a drone attack launched from Yemen a day earlier, which evaded Israel’s defenses and hit a building in Tel Aviv, killing one person.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 22:54:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The worst IT catastrophe ever hit less than 1% of all Microsoft Windows devices</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/07/20/crowdstrike-global-outage-less-than-1-percent-all-microsoft-windows-devices/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/GettyImages-2162656140-e1721515317401.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>A faulty software update from cybersecurity firm CrowdStrike affected 8.5 million devices globally that rely on the Microsoft Windows operating system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 23:49:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>After Fire at Sanctuary, First Baptist Dallas Church Mourns What’s Lost</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2024/07/20/us/first-baptist-dallas-fire.html</link><image_url>https://static01.nyt.com/images/2024/07/20/multimedia/20nat-dallas-church-kbmq/20nat-dallas-church-kbmq-mediumSquareAt3X.jpg</image_url><description>As officials work to determine the cause, many lament the damage at First Baptist Dallas, a church that grew along with the downtown around it.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 00:32:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Israeli Airstrikes Hit Houthi Targets in Yemen</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/video/world/middleeast/100000009583849/israeli-airstrikes-yemen-houthis.html</link><image_url>https://static01.nyt.com/images/misc/NYT_logo_rss_250x40.png</image_url><description>Israel struck the Yemeni port city of Hodeidah a day after the Houthis claimed responsibility for launching a drone at Tel Aviv that killed one person and wounded several others.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 21:43:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Phishing attempts rise as scam artists try to exploit the CrowdStrike global tech outage</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/07/20/crowdstrike-outage-phishing-attempts-scam-artists-microsoft-windows-cybersecurity/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/AP24202623575279-e1721514368759.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>“We know that adversaries and bad actors will try to exploit events like this,” CrowdStrike CEO George Kurtz said.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 23:34:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scams Tied to the CrowdStrike Crash Have Bloomed. Here’s How to Stay Safe</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2024/07/20/business/crowdstrike-tech-outage-scams.html</link><image_url>https://static01.nyt.com/images/2024/07/20/multimedia/20xp-scam-tvhb/20xp-scam-tvhb-mediumSquareAt3X.jpg</image_url><description>People posing as airline customer service representatives may be making fraudulent attempts to access your money or private data, experts warn.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 23:40:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Thomas Neff, Who Turned Soviet Warheads Into Electricity, Dies at 80</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2024/07/20/world/europe/thomas-l-neff-dead.html</link><image_url>https://static01.nyt.com/images/misc/NYT_logo_rss_250x40.png</image_url><description>An M.I.T. physicist, he engineered an East-West deal that reduced nuclear threats and produced one of the greatest peace dividends of all time.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 17:52:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gunman in Trump assassination attempt flew a drone over the rally site ahead of shooting, official says</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/07/20/trump-assassination-attempt-gunman-drone-campaign-rally-site-shooting/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/AP24198007342884-e1721513346169.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>More details about the investigation are expected to be made public in the coming week when FBI Director Chris Wray appears before the House Judiciary Committee.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 23:17:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Campaign Prepares Attack Plan for Harris in Case Biden Withdraws</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2024/07/20/us/politics/trump-harris-strategy.html</link><image_url>https://static01.nyt.com/images/2024/07/20/us/politics/20pol-trump-strategy-trump-top/20pol-trump-strategy-trump-top-mediumSquareAt3X.jpg</image_url><description>The effort, which includes expansive advertising and polling, assumes that the vice president would be the most likely candidate to replace the president at the top of the Democratic ticket.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 23:12:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>World Court Says Israel’s Occupation Violates International Law</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/video/world/middleeast/100000009582786/icj-opinion-israel-palestinian-territories-occupation.html</link><image_url>https://static01.nyt.com/images/misc/NYT_logo_rss_250x40.png</image_url><description>The International Court of Justice laid out it’s most sweeping stance on Israel’s occupation of the West Bank and East Jerusalem, and its settlements, calling for an end to Israel’s presence there. The advisory opinion, while not binding, carries legal weight.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 17:48:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘Black Swan’ investor warns the ‘greatest bubble in human history’ is about to pop and stocks could lose more than half their value</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/07/20/black-swan-investor-mark-spitznagel-greatest-bubble-human-history-stock-market-crash-recession/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/GettyImages-693466508-e1721506424565.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The federal government will have less capacity to respond, and the economy could enter a recession by the end of this year, Mark Spitznagel predicted.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 22:36:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>