<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 17:28:22 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>US pauses bomb shipments to Israel over Rafah concerns</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/middleeast/live-news/israel-hamas-war-gaza-news-05-08-24/index.html</link><image_url>https://cdn.cnn.com/cnnnext/dam/assets/240507094813-01-displaced-palestinian-rafah-0506-super-169.jpg</image_url><description>The United States paused a shipment of bombs to Israel amid concerns over their potential use in a ground operation in Rafah without a plan for civilians there, the US defense secretary confirmed. 
Follow for live updates.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:46:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Getting illicit pills as easy as ordering food delivery via app, DEA tells Congress</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/illicit-pills-easy-ordering-food-delivery-app-dea/story?id=110038067</link><description>A Drug Enforcement Administration official told Congress that illegal pills are being delivered to Americans' doorsteps "like Uber Eats."</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 22:14:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Congress grills liberal cities' school districts over antisemitism</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/us/live-news/antisemitism-hearing-05-08-24/index.html</link><image_url>https://cdn.cnn.com/cnnnext/dam/assets/230118162135-01-us-capitol-0104-super-169.jpg</image_url><description>Colleges and universities held graduation ceremonies over the weekend as pro-Palestinian protests continued on campuses across the US. Follow for live updates</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 18:10:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shohei Ohtani's interpreter to plead guilty to stealing millions from baseball star</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Sports/ippei-mizuhara-shohei-ohtanis-interpreter-pleads-guilty-stealing/story?id=110040916</link><description>Ippei Mizuhara, the former interpreter for MLB star Shohei Ohtani, has agreed to plead guilty to bank fraud in relation to stealing nearly $17 million from the player.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:51:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>May 7, 2024 Israel-Hamas war</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/middleeast/live-news/israel-hamas-war-gaza-news-05-07-24/index.html</link><image_url>https://cdn.cnn.com/cnnnext/dam/assets/240506115407-01-rafah-gaza-050524-super-169.jpg</image_url><description>Israeli airstrikes killed multiple people in Rafah early Tuesday, Palestinian officials said,</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 05:00:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>No hate crime charges filed against man who yelled racist slurs at Utah women's basketball team</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/wireStory/hate-crime-charges-filed-man-yelled-racist-slurs-110036007</link><description>A northern Idaho prosecutor won’t bring hate crime charges against an 18-year-old accused of shouting a racist slur at members of the Utah women’s basketball team while the team was in Idaho to attend the NCAA Tournament</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:38:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stormy Daniels testifies in Trump's hush money trial</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/politics/live-news/trump-hush-money-trial-05-07-24/index.html</link><image_url>https://cdn.cnn.com/cnnnext/dam/assets/240507132204-sketch-01-donald-trump-hush-money-trial-050724-super-169.jpg</image_url><description>Former President Donald Trump's hush money trial continued Tuesday in New York.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 00:27:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>9 of 10 wrongful death suits over Astroworld crowd surge have been settled: lawyer</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Entertainment/wireStory/9-10-wrongful-death-suits-deadly-astroworld-crowd-110025100</link><description>An attorney says nine of the 10 wrongful death lawsuits filed after the 2021 Astroworld music festival have been settled, including one that was set to go to trial this week</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:30:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deadly tornado reported in Oklahoma after barrage of destructive storms</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/weather/live-news/tornado-storms-forecast-oklahoma-kansas-05-06-24/index.html</link><image_url>https://cdn.cnn.com/cnnnext/dam/assets/240506094534-severe-outlook-05-06-24-super-169.jpg</image_url><description>Destructive storms and tornadoes hit the Central US on Monday and Tuesday, including at least one deadly tornado.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:34:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2 young children die after being swept away by fast-flowing California creek</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/wireStory/2-young-children-die-after-swept-fast-flowing-110026383</link><description>Two young siblings died after being swept away by a rapidly flowing creek in Southern California’s San Bernardino Mountains</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:29:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>