<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 06:58:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Tensions rise at college protests as Johnson calls for Columbia president to resign</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/business/live-news/columbia-usc-university-protests-04-25-24/index.html</link><image_url>https://cdn.cnn.com/cnnnext/dam/assets/240424152426-usc-protests-nick-watt-042424-super-169.jpg</image_url><description>Pro-Palestinian protests are taking place at major US universities, prompting some officials to take extraordinary steps to confront the growing crisis. Follow for live news updates.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:05:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Australia and New Zealand honor their war dead with dawn services on Anzac Day</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/australia-new-zealand-honor-war-dead-dawn-services-109596647</link><description>Hundreds of thousands of people have gathered across Australia and New Zealand for dawn services and street marches to commemorate their war dead on Anzac Day</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:54:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Witness testimony to continue in Trump's hush money trial</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/politics/live-news/trump-hush-money-trial-04-25-24/index.html</link><image_url>https://cdn.cnn.com/cnnnext/dam/assets/240423101045-lead-image-donald-trump-hush-money-042324-super-169.jpg</image_url><description>Witness testimony will continue Thursday in Donald Trump's hush money criminal trial. Follow here for the latest live news updates from court, analysis and more.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 10:48:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Giuliani, Meadows indicted in Arizona fake elector scheme</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/11-indicted-arizona-2020-election-probe/story?id=109509462</link><description>Several former and current key aides to former President Donald Trump appear to be among those charged by the Arizona State Attorney General.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:14:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>April 24, 2024 - US university protests</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/business/live-news/columbia-yale-university-protests-04-24-24/index.html</link><image_url>https://cdn.cnn.com/cnnnext/dam/assets/240423205704-05-columbia-protests-042324-super-169.jpg</image_url><description>Pro-Palestinian protests are taking place at major American universities, prompting some officials to take extraordinary steps to confront the growing crisis. Follow for live news updates.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 07:04:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>College encampments grow nationwide: What students are saying</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/150-arrested-new-york-university-amid-pro-palestinian/story?id=109525064</link><description>Protests calling for the divestment from Israeli military operations have continued to spread on college campuses throughout the country.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:09:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>April 24, 2024 - Israel-Hamas war</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/middleeast/live-news/israel-hamas-war-gaza-news-04-24-24/index.html</link><image_url>https://cdn.cnn.com/cnnnext/dam/assets/240418004344-gaza-bombardment-041624-super-169.jpg</image_url><description>Hamas released a video of Israeli-American hostage Hersh Goldberg-Polin, the first proof that he survived being badly wounded during his capture on October 7. He is shown in the undated video with part of his left arm missing.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 02:59:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Comparing Donald Trump's hush money trial to John Edwards, Bill Clinton cases</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/comparing-donald-trumps-hush-money-trial-john-edwards/story?id=109506871</link><description>Donald Trump's hush money trial is underway, and it's drawing attention to past high-profile litigation involving political stars and salacious affair allegations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:06:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Supreme Court hears case about emergency abortion care</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/politics/live-news/abortion-supreme-court-idaho-04-24-24/index.html</link><image_url>https://cdn.cnn.com/cnnnext/dam/assets/220222161930-scotus-exterior-0208-super-169.jpg</image_url><description>The Supreme Court heard oral arguments in another major abortion access case as it grapples with the aftermath of reversing Roe v. Wade. Follow here for live audio of the arguments, news updates, analysis and more.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:48:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Expanded so-called 'Don't Say Gay' education restrictions advance in Alabama</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/expanded-called-dont-gay-education-restrictions-advance-alabama/story?id=108746593</link><description>Alabama is on track to further restrict discussions of "gender identity or sexual orientation" in public schools in a new proposal of the so-called "Don't So Gay" law.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 02:10:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>