<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 06:57:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Pro-Palestinian protests disrupt colleges across the US</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/business/live-news/university-protests-palestine-04-29-24/index.html</link><image_url>https://cdn.cnn.com/cnnnext/dam/assets/240426211952-protestas-1-super-169.jpg</image_url><description>Pro-Palestinian protests are disrupting major US universities, and several schools have called police to remove demonstrators. Follow for live updates.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 11:02:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Likely attack by Yemen's Houthi rebels targets a vessel in the Red Sea</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/attack-yemens-houthi-rebels-targets-vessel-red-sea-109739373</link><description>A suspected missile attack by Yemen’s Houthi rebels targeted a container in the Red Sea, the latest assault in their campaign against international shipping in the crucial maritime route</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 11:54:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>April 28, 2024 - US university protests</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/business/live-news/university-protests-palestine-04-28-24/index.html</link><image_url>https://cdn.cnn.com/cnnnext/dam/assets/240426211952-protestas-1-super-169.jpg</image_url><description>Pro-Palestinian protests continue at major US universities, and several schools have called police to remove demonstrators.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 07:10:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>40 people die in western Kenya after a dam collapses</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/40-people-die-western-kenya-after-dam-collapses-109739096</link><description>Police in Kenya say at least 40 people have died after a dam collapsed in the country’s west</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 11:06:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>April 27, 2024 - Campus protest updates</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/business/live-news/university-protests-palestine-04-27-24/index.html</link><image_url>https://cdn.cnn.com/cnnnext/dam/assets/240426000842-01a-columbia-university-encampment-042524-super-169.jpg</image_url><description>Pro-Palestinian protests continue at major US universities, where several schools have called police on protesters, leading to the arrests of hundreds across the country. Follow for live updates.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 14:54:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>College protests live updates: Police crackdown leads to hundreds of arrests</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/live-updates/college-protests-israel-palestine-war/?id=109734946</link><description>Protests have broken out at colleges and universities across the country in connection with the war in Gaza.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 11:05:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>April 26, 2024 - Protests at Columbia and other schools escalate</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/business/live-news/columbia-university-palestine-protests-04-26-24/index.html</link><image_url>https://cdn.cnn.com/cnnnext/dam/assets/240426000842-01a-columbia-university-encampment-042524-super-169.jpg</image_url><description>Pro-Palestinian protests continue at major US universities where several schools have called police on protesters, leading to the arrests of hundreds across the country. Follow for live updates.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 15:46:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Teens plotted to buy guns, attack Jewish people after Sydney stabbing: police</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/teens-plotted-buy-guns-attack-jewish-people-after-109738228</link><description>Police allege in court documents that four teenagers plotted to buy guns and attack Jewish people days after a Christian bishop was stabbed in a Sydney church</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 10:18:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Day 8 of Trump New York hush money trial</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/politics/live-news/trump-hush-money-trial-04-26-24/index.html</link><image_url>https://cdn.cnn.com/cnnnext/dam/assets/240426095335-06-donald-trump-hush-money-trial-042624-super-169.jpg</image_url><description>Ex-tabloid publisher David Pecker and Donald Trump's former assistant Rhona Graff were among those who testifed Friday in the hush money trial.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 23:30:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tesla founder Elon Musk visits China as competitors show off new electric vehicles</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Business/wireStory/tesla-founder-elon-musk-visiting-china-competitors-show-109725360</link><description>Tesla founder and CEO Elon Musk has met with a top government leader in the Chinese capital, just as the nation’s carmakers are showing off their latest electric vehicle models at the Beijing auto show</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 04:58:34 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>