<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 07:11:32 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Google employees grill Sundar Pichai and CFO Ruth Porat on why they're not getting pay rises amid blowout earnings</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/09/google-employees-sundar-pichai-questioned-salaries-earnings/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2151466522-e1715249326531.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>“Despite the company’s stellar performance and record earnings, many Googlers have not received meaningful compensation increases,” one top-rated question began.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 12:02:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bank of England holds interest rates steady, but signals a cut is coming</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/09/bank-of-england-holds-interest-rates-steady-but-signals-that-a-cut-is-coming.html</link><description>The Bank of England confirmed a widely-expected hold in interest rates following its May meeting on Thursday.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 12:07:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AstraZeneca pulls its COVID-19 vaccine from European market after history of stumbles</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/09/astrazeneca-pulls-covid-19-vaccine-europe-market-history-stumbles/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1244086535-e1715252199595.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Partial results from its first major trial — which Britain used to authorize the vaccine — were clouded by a manufacturing mistake that researchers didn’t immediately acknowledge.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:57:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A rare hostile takeover bid in Europe's banking sector has shocked markets</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/09/spains-bbva-launches-rare-hostile-takeover-bid-for-rival-sabadell.html</link><description>Spanish bank BBVA caught markets by surprise after it announced a rare hostile takeover bid for domestic rival Banco Sabadell.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 12:04:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Norwegian wealth fund CEO converts a century-old grain silo into a $46 million art display to promote tourism in his hometown</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/09/norwegian-wealth-fund-ceo-nicolai-tangen-grain-silo-art-display-tourism-kristiansand/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2147055043-e1715249613225.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Once home to 15,000 tons of grain, Norges Bank CEO Nicolai Tangen's Kunstsilo is now a gallery of more than 5,000 artworks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:34:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Boeing cargo plane lands without front nose gear in Istanbul; investigation launched</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/09/boeing-cargo-plane-lands-without-front-nose-gear-in-istanbul-investigation-launched-.html</link><description>Boeing is in the midst of its latest safety and public relations crisis after a door plug blew out from one of its 737 Max 9 planes midair in early January.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:57:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I'm a founder struggling with mental-health issues. How can I step away from my startup?</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/09/ask-andy-mental-health-startups-growth-rate/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/DUNN-WEB.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Bonobos and Pie founder Andy Dunn answers questions about how a founder can address mental health challenges, and how fast is too fast to grow.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Long pauses between Fed actions are historically good for stocks</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/09/long-pauses-between-fed-actions-are-historically-good-for-stocks.html</link><description>Investors are deliberating when the Federal Reserve will start to lower rates, but the current pause could actually be a blessing in disguise for equities.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:46:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New York City’s watchdog investigates whether NYPD used official social media accounts to target public officials and private citizens</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/09/new-york-city-watchdog-investigates-nypd-official-social-media-accounts/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/AP24130014773668-e1715250374760.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The Department of Investigation confirmed the probe, saying it was prompted by recent requests from City Council Speaker Adrienne Adams and the Legal Aid Society.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:27:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chip designer Arm's shares plunge nearly 9% after lackluster revenue guidance</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/09/arm-stock-down-8percent-after-disappointing-sales-guidance.html</link><description>Shares of Arm fell almost 9% in premarket trading on Thursday, as lackluster revenue guidance from the firm clouded a positive sales quarter driven by AI demand.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>