<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 06:57:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Goldman Sachs has warned its staff about sneaking off to Paris during the Olympics—and leaving the bank to pick up the tab</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/29/goldman-sachs-paris-olympics-staff-warning/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/GettyImages-2149736103-e1714386683859.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>“In line with previous Olympic games, we have asked our people to effectively manage their spend and ensure coordination."</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 11:54:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Glass Lewis endorses 6 of activist Ancora's nominees for Norfolk Southern board</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/04/29/norfolk-southern-glass-lewis-endorses-6-ancora-nominees.html</link><description>Norfolk Southern shareholders should vote for activist Ancora's nominees, proxy advisor firm Glass Lewis recommended, a strong sign of support ahead of a May 9 meeting.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 11:21:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ryanair's Michael O'Leary, who is up for a $108 million bonus, doesn’t see high CEO pay as a problem: 'Footballers are getting half a million a week'</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/04/29/ryanair-michael-oleary-100-million-euros-bonus-ceo-pay-footballers-millions-a-week/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/GettyImages-2149388822-e1714385325946.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Michael O'Leary says that if football players and their managers can get paid in the multi-millions, why not him?</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 11:54:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Monday's analyst calls: Apple gets a big upgrade, headwinds seen for Lululemon and Tesla</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/04/29/mondays-analyst-calls-apple-gets-a-big-upgrade-headwinds-seen-for-lululemon.html</link><description>Monday's analyst calls included an upgrade to Apple and a move in the opposite direction for athleisure giant Lulu Lemon and electric car marker Tesla.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 11:21:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>EU's unwinnable EV price war: BYD cars 11 times more profitable in Europe than in China</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/04/29/eu-unwinnable-price-war-chinese-evs-byd-cars-11-times-more-profitable-in-europe-than-in-china/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/GettyImages-1926876968-e1714385648949.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Only a highly unlikely 50% import tariff would be enough to deter Chinese automakers from Europe, new research finds.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 11:48:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pedro Sanchez stays on as Spain's prime minister after weighing exit</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/04/29/spains-pedro-sanchez-stays-on-as-prime-minister-after-weighing-exit.html</link><description>Spain's Prime Minister Pedro Sanchez said on Monday he had decided to continue in office, days after abruptly announcing he was considering his future.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 11:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>McKinsey boss tries to boost staff morale amid layoffs by blasting Eminem, Bob Marley and Chumbawamba</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/29/mckinsey-boss-boost-staff-morale-layoffs-political-backlash-eminem-bob-marley-chumbawamba/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/GettyImages-1983628458-e1714386305325.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Global Managing Partner Bob Sternfels told his fellow partners at the mid-April event that McKinsey is expecting a good 2024 after its challenges of the past 18 months.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 11:34:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tesla jumps 8% in premarket trade after passing key hurdle to roll out full self-driving in China</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/04/29/tesla-tsla-stock-up-after-passing-hurdle-to-china-full-self-driving.html</link><description>Shares of Tesla rose sharply in U.S. premarket trading after the company passed a significant milestone to roll out its full self-driving technology in China.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 10:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Sam Bankman-Fried is turning against A-list FTX boosters—and what could happen to them</title><link>https://fortune.com/crypto/2024/04/29/sam-bankman-fried-ftx-endorsements-lawsuit-tom-brady-gisele-shaq-larry-david/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/Tom-Brady-Naomi-Osaka-Larry-David.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Some of the celebs who took money to tout SBF’s exchange may be in hotter water than others.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Philips shares rocket 46% as firm settles U.S. respiratory device case</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/04/29/philips-shares-rocket-33percent-as-firm-settles-us-respiratory-device-case.html</link><description>Philips shares soared Monday after the company agreed a $1.1 billion settlement in a U.S. case linked to the recall of some of its sleep apnea devices.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 09:07:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>