<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 06:37:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Uber stokes monopoly fears with plan to pay almost $1bn for its only major food delivery competitor in Taiwan</title><link>https://fortune.com/asia/2024/05/14/uber-monopoly-fears-pay-1bn-delivery-hero-food-delivery-competitor-taiwan/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1754862834-e1715680578250.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Uber, whose meal delivery business outperformed globally during the most recent quarter, aims to complete the all-cash deal by the first half of 2025.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 11:08:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 2024 CNBC Disruptor 50 full list: OpenAI becomes first back-to-back No. 1 company</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/14/these-are-the-2024-cnbc-disruptor-50-companies.html</link><description>CNBC reveals the 2024 Disruptor 50 list, AI-driven startups moving beyond the 'better, faster, cheaper' mantra that defined Silicon Valley's past.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 10:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Switzerland shouldn't follow Europe's lead on tax, says Roche CEO</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/14/switzerland-tax-europe-lead-roche-ceo-thomas-schinecker-compete-dubai-china-india/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1968671907-e1715678773771.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Europe is falling behind China and the U.S. in competitiveness, according to Thomas Schinecker, Roche CEO.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 10:42:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tuesday's analyst calls: Nvidia earnings preview, gym stock gets an upgrade</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/14/analyst-calls-all-the-market-moving-wall-street-chatter-from-tuesday.html</link><description>Nvidia and a major gym stock were among the biggest names talked about by analysts on Tuesday.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 10:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Emmanuel Macron woos Wall Street as he tries to position Paris as Europe’s top financial hub, calling Basel banking regulations 'a killer for risk taking'</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/14/paris-emmanuel-macron-wall-street-basel-regulations-europes-top-financial-hub/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2152250578-e1715677864499.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The push to lure more business to Paris has translated into more than 7,000 extra jobs in the financial sector between 2017 and 2022.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 10:37:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Home Depot misses on revenue, as high interest rates hurt sales</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/14/home-depot-hd-q1-2024-earnings-.html</link><description>Home Depot reported first-quarter earnings as it tries to grow sales with home professionals in a tough housing market.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 10:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BYD has been frozen out of the U.S. market so it’s debuting its first hybrid pickup truck in Mexico</title><link>https://fortune.com/asia/2024/05/14/byd-us-market-debuting-first-hybrid-pickup-truck-shark-mexico/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2152729589-e1715677641149.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>While BYD has said previously the Shark will be distributed globally, the automaker doesn’t have any plans to sell in the U.S. at the moment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 10:16:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Diamond giant De Beers faces spin-off as Anglo American takeover pressure mounts</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/14/anglo-american-to-spin-off-de-beers-as-bhp-takeover-pressure-mounts.html</link><description>Anglo American shares fell over 3% early Tuesday after it announced plans to spin off its highly prized De Beers diamond business.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 10:14:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vodafone turnaround: $11.9 billion earnings and a return to growth in Germany, but 'much more still needs to be done'</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/14/vodafone-turnaround-earnings-growth-germany/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2060423726-e1715675956407.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Vodafone is increasing its focus on the German market and exiting unprofitable ones, as part of CEO Della Valle’s turnaround strategy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 10:02:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden raises tariffs on $18 billion of Chinese imports: EVs, solar panels, batteries and more</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/14/biden-raises-china-tariffs-on-evs-solar-panels-batteries-.html</link><description>Biden Cabinet members like Janet Yellen, Gina Raimondo and Antony Blinken have all raised concerns about Chinese trade practices.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>