<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 13:41:30 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Postpartum PTSD: Right Diagnosis Can Help Mothers and Babies</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/mental-health/news/20240506/postpartum-ptsd-right-diagnosis-can-help-mothers-and-babies?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Many new mothers aren’t aware that postpartum PTSD even exists, but it’s far from rare. Here's what to know.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:19:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Sound of Freedom</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/10/01/the-sound-of-freedom/</link><description>For a million years (more like 15,) I’ve been listening to a radio show:  The Taylor Strecker Show. It’s a daily show that originated on SiriusXM and through a series of events became an independently broadcasted show on Patreon.  There’s something interesting that happens when you listen to a daily show.  You get to know...Read More</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 21:26:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Living With Major Depressive Disorder</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/depression/features/live-with-mdd?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>See how one person manages the ups and downs of major depressive disorder -- and how her depression inspired her career as a therapist.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:45:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>That Time I Went to the Eras Tour [Part Two]</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/07/17/that-time-i-went-to-the-eras-tour-part-two/</link><description>To review part one of this adventure with Taylor Swift, click here. Click here to see all the Instagram highlight videos from Denver Night One. Mile High Stadium was pink and sparkly from head to toe.  Never had I ever seen so many women in one place, nor so many generations piled into one venue. ...Read More</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 06:36:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Therapist’s Perspective</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/depression/features/mdd-therapists-perspective?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>A therapist talks about managing major depressive disorder (MDD): what to expect, strategies for dealing with setbacks, and when to talk to your therapist.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:45:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>That Time I Went to the Eras Tour [Part One]</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/07/16/that-time-i-went-to-the-eras-tour-part-one/</link><description>Do you ever have one of those experiences where you want to remember exactly how you felt?  That’s how I feel about my experience at the Taylor Swift concert this weekend.  Correction:  At the Eras Tour.  Saying it was a concert does not feel like enough to justify the magnitude of the event. Let’s talk about the...Read More</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 05:17:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Handling the Stigma</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/depression/features/mdd-stigma?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Learn from a mental health advocate how the stigma of depression is changing and how acceptance is the first step to managing major depressive disorder.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:44:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jenny Craig Recipe Creation:  Turkey Philly Baguette</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/02/13/jenny-craig-recipe-creation-turkey-philly-baguette/</link><description>Special thanks to Jenny Craig for their sponsorship of this post. In honor of the Super Bowl this year, I decided to make a Philly to enjoy. Knowing the Philadelphia Eagles were playing (and with no plans to watch the game), I let the City of Brotherly Love inspire this tasty dish.  I used the Jenny Craig...Read More</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:28:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How I Share About My Condition</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/depression/features/mdd-talk-about?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>A person with major depressive disorder shares how they talk about their condition with others.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:44:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jenny Craig Recipe Creation: Mexican Chicken and Rice Soup</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/01/23/jenny-craig-recipe-creation-mexican-chicken-and-rice-soup/</link><description>Special thanks to Jenny Craig for their sponsorship of this post. Over the past year, I’ve shared a TON of recipe ideas; however, most of them have been on social media – – specifically instagram. Knowing that I missed sharing many recipes with this blog-reading community and for all those who search the internet for creative ways...Read More</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 03:50:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>