<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 11:55:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>7 Most Effective Exercises</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/fitness-exercise/features/7-most-effective-exercises?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Not all exercises are created equal. Some are simply more efficient than others, whether they target multiple muscle groups, are suitable for a wide variety of fitness levels, or help you burn calories more effectively.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:55:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Sound of Freedom</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/10/01/the-sound-of-freedom/</link><description>For a million years (more like 15,) I’ve been listening to a radio show:  The Taylor Strecker Show. It’s a daily show that originated on SiriusXM and through a series of events became an independently broadcasted show on Patreon.  There’s something interesting that happens when you listen to a daily show.  You get to know...Read More</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 21:26:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>To Fast or to Feast?</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/ibd-crohns-disease/ulcerative-colitis/features/fast-feast-uc?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>These tips will help you enjoy the foods at social events when you have ulcerative colitis and still steer clear of a flare.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:52:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>That Time I Went to the Eras Tour [Part Two]</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/07/17/that-time-i-went-to-the-eras-tour-part-two/</link><description>To review part one of this adventure with Taylor Swift, click here. Click here to see all the Instagram highlight videos from Denver Night One. Mile High Stadium was pink and sparkly from head to toe.  Never had I ever seen so many women in one place, nor so many generations piled into one venue. ...Read More</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 06:36:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Can You Really Know What to Expect in the Long Haul?</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/ibd-crohns-disease/ulcerative-colitis/features/long-haul-expectations-uc?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Ulcerative colitis is a relapsing-remitting disease, so it’s hard to predict symptoms over time. Here’s what to expect and how to recognize remission.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 15:53:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>That Time I Went to the Eras Tour [Part One]</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/07/16/that-time-i-went-to-the-eras-tour-part-one/</link><description>Do you ever have one of those experiences where you want to remember exactly how you felt?  That’s how I feel about my experience at the Taylor Swift concert this weekend.  Correction:  At the Eras Tour.  Saying it was a concert does not feel like enough to justify the magnitude of the event. Let’s talk about the...Read More</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 05:17:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ulcerative Colitis: Social Relationships and Dating</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/ibd-crohns-disease/ulcerative-colitis/features/uc-relationships?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Friendship can be a good medicine when you have ulcerative colitis. Learn how to keep your social life going when you don’t always feel like going out.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 15:45:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jenny Craig Recipe Creation:  Turkey Philly Baguette</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/02/13/jenny-craig-recipe-creation-turkey-philly-baguette/</link><description>Special thanks to Jenny Craig for their sponsorship of this post. In honor of the Super Bowl this year, I decided to make a Philly to enjoy. Knowing the Philadelphia Eagles were playing (and with no plans to watch the game), I let the City of Brotherly Love inspire this tasty dish.  I used the Jenny Craig...Read More</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:28:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Normal Aging Process: Changes, Memory, Eyesight, Hearing, and More</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/normal-aging-changes-and-symptoms?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Curious if your body’s aging is normal? WebMD discusses healthy and normal signs of aging.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 14:30:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jenny Craig Recipe Creation: Mexican Chicken and Rice Soup</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/01/23/jenny-craig-recipe-creation-mexican-chicken-and-rice-soup/</link><description>Special thanks to Jenny Craig for their sponsorship of this post. Over the past year, I’ve shared a TON of recipe ideas; however, most of them have been on social media – – specifically instagram. Knowing that I missed sharing many recipes with this blog-reading community and for all those who search the internet for creative ways...Read More</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 03:50:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>