<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:30:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>A Healthy Lifestyle Can Add Years to Life, Despite 'Bad' Genes</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/balance/news/20240509/defeat-bad-genes-with-healthy-lifestyle?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Turn around those bad family genes with four lifestyle changes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 19:47:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Sound of Freedom</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/10/01/the-sound-of-freedom/</link><description>For a million years (more like 15,) I&#8217;ve been listening to a radio show: The Taylor Strecker Show. It&#8217;s a daily show that originated on SiriusXM and through a series of events became an independently broadcasted show on Patreon. There&#8217;s something interesting that happens when you listen to a daily show. You get to know... Read More</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 21:26:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Plateauing At The Gym? Women Share What's Finally Helping To Tone Their Muscles*</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/women-are-loving-this-supplement-for-staying-physically-and-mentally-stron</link><description>Emphasis on tone (not bulk).</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: When to seek care for pelvic pain</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-when-to-seek-care-for-pelvic-pain/</link><description>Editor's note: May is National Women's Health Month Pelvic pain is common, affecting 15% of women of reproductive age. Pinpointing its cause, whether it's endometriosis, ovarian cysts or musculoskeletal issues, can be a challenge. Dr. Megan Wasson, a gynecologic surgeon who specializes in minimally invasive procedures at Mayo Clinic, says it's important to seek medical [&#8230;] The post Mayo Clinic Minute: When to seek care for pelvic pain appeared first on Mayo Clinic News Network .</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 15:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Taking Racism out of the Kidney Disease Equation</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/a-to-z-guides/features/end-of-racist-kidney-math?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Kidney care in the U.S. is at a watershed moment of moving past a deeply entrenched, institutionally racist equation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 04:17:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>That Time I Went to the Eras Tour [Part Two]</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/07/17/that-time-i-went-to-the-eras-tour-part-two/</link><description>To review part one of this adventure with Taylor Swift, click here. Click here to see all the Instagram highlight videos from Denver Night One. Mile High Stadium was pink and sparkly from head to toe. Never had I ever seen so many women in one place, nor so many generations piled into one venue. ... Read More</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 06:36:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>These 2 Zodiac Signs Can Make For An Electrifying Relationship</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/taurus-gemini-compatibility</link><description>When done right, of course.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 13:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Melanoma in darker skin tones: Race and sex play a role, Mayo study finds</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/melanoma-in-darker-skin-tones-race-and-sex-play-a-role-mayo-study-finds/</link><description>A recent Mayo Clinic study reveals melanoma is often detected later in people with darker skin complexions. The post Melanoma in darker skin tones: Race and sex play a role, Mayo study finds appeared first on Mayo Clinic News Network .</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 14:13:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Plant-Powered Sleep: Vegan, Vegetarian Diets Unlock Extra ZZZs</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/sleep-disorders/news/20240508/plant-powered-sleep-vegan-vegetarian-diet-unlocks-extra-zzzs?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Vegans and vegetarians sleep around 30 more minutes per night than average and up to 90% of them report good or excellent sleep quality, according to a new survey published by the Sleep Foundation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 19:12:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>That Time I Went to the Eras Tour [Part One]</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/07/16/that-time-i-went-to-the-eras-tour-part-one/</link><description>Do you ever have one of those experiences where you want to remember exactly how you felt? That&#8217;s how I feel about my experience at the Taylor Swift concert this weekend. Correction: At the Eras Tour. Saying it was a concert does not feel like enough to justify the magnitude of the event. Let&#8217;s talk about the... Read More</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 05:17:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Cognition &amp; Longevity Expert's Favorite Herb For Optimal Brain Health</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/science-journalist-on-why-rosemary-is-for-brain-health</link><description>One particular herb tops the list.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 12:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: Treating breast cancer through surgery</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-treating-breast-cancer-through-surgery/</link><description>Editor&#8217;s Note: May is National Women&#8217;s Health Month Globally, 2.3 million women are diagnosed with breast cancer every year, according to the World Health Organization. Advances in treating breast cancer are improving care and quality of life. Watch: The Mayo Clinic Minute Journalists: Broadcast-quality video (1:00) is in the downloads at the end of this [&#8230;] The post Mayo Clinic Minute: Treating breast cancer through surgery appeared first on Mayo Clinic News Network .</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 15:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anorexia: The Body Neglected</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/mental-health/eating-disorders/anorexia-nervosa/features/anorexia-body-neglected?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>What, exactly, does anorexia nervosa do inside the human body? The heart and bones suffer the most.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jenny Craig Recipe Creation:  Turkey Philly Baguette</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/02/13/jenny-craig-recipe-creation-turkey-philly-baguette/</link><description>Special thanks to Jenny Craig for their sponsorship of this post. In honor of the Super Bowl this year, I decided to make a Philly to enjoy. Knowing the Philadelphia Eagles were playing (and with no plans to watch the game), I let the City of Brotherly Love inspire this tasty dish. I used the Jenny Craig... Read More</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:28:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Nongreasy Sunscreen Balances Your Skin &amp; Gives A Healthy Glow</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/eltamd-uv-tinted-broad-spectrum-spf</link><description>For the perfect protective glow.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:29:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo&#8217;s new &#8216;omics&#8217; strategy leaps into the future</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayos-new-omics-strategy-leaps-into-the-future/</link><description>Imagine a future where healthcare is tailored precisely for you, right down to the molecules deep inside your cells. Targeted treatments and preventive strategies are customized to your genome. Your personal medical roadmap outlines hereditary genetic variants, provides guidance on environmental risks and offers strategies for maintaining heart health and preventing cancer, making it as [&#8230;] The post Mayo&#8217;s new &#8216;omics&#8217; strategy leaps into the future appeared first on Mayo Clinic News Network .</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 12:40:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Postpartum PTSD: Right Diagnosis Can Help Mothers and Babies</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/mental-health/news/20240506/postpartum-ptsd-right-diagnosis-can-help-mothers-and-babies?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Many new mothers aren&#8217;t aware that postpartum PTSD even exists, but it&#8217;s far from rare. Here's what to know.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:19:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jenny Craig Recipe Creation: Mexican Chicken and Rice Soup</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/01/23/jenny-craig-recipe-creation-mexican-chicken-and-rice-soup/</link><description>Special thanks to Jenny Craig for their sponsorship of this post. Over the past year, I&#8217;ve shared a TON of recipe ideas; however, most of them have been on social media &#8211; &#8211; specifically instagram. Knowing that I missed sharing many recipes with this blog-reading community and for all those who search the internet for creative ways... Read More</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 03:50:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>My Headphones Were Constantly Falling Out During Long Runs, Until I Tried These</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/samsung-galaxy-buds2</link><description>Finally, headphones that don't fall out when I sweat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 10:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: Melanoma misconception &#8212; dark skin tones at risk, too</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-melanoma-misconception-dark-skin-tones-at-risk-too/</link><description>The myth that people with dark skin are immune to melanoma, a type of skin cancer, has persisted for many years. It's a dangerous misconception that has caused some people not to be diligent about protecting themselves against dangerous ultraviolet (UV) rays. Dr. Dawn Davis, a Mayo Clinic dermatologist, says people with darker skin tones [&#8230;] The post Mayo Clinic Minute: Melanoma misconception &#8212; dark skin tones at risk, too appeared first on Mayo Clinic News Network .</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>