<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 06:59:43 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>A lot of children are about to be born in Ukraine. Will the war affect them for life?</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/children/features/fetal-programming-ukraine?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Some of the most horrific images from the war so far have come from a maternity hospital in Mariupol bombed by Russian troops in mid-March. The upheaval spurs a troubling question: Could the stress and condition of war affect a fetus?</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 10:32:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Sound of Freedom</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/10/01/the-sound-of-freedom/</link><description>For a million years (more like 15,) I’ve been listening to a radio show:  The Taylor Strecker Show. It’s a daily show that originated on SiriusXM and through a series of events became an independently broadcasted show on Patreon.  There’s something interesting that happens when you listen to a daily show.  You get to know...Read More</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 21:26:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Trans Health Care for Minors Really Means</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/sex/features/trans-access-to-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>The meaning of gender-affirming care for young people, and what it looks like on the ground, isn’t always clear. The cloud of politics surrounding it has obscured the medical reality of how and when trans youth can get the treatments they seek.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 10:32:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>That Time I Went to the Eras Tour [Part Two]</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/07/17/that-time-i-went-to-the-eras-tour-part-two/</link><description>To review part one of this adventure with Taylor Swift, click here. Click here to see all the Instagram highlight videos from Denver Night One. Mile High Stadium was pink and sparkly from head to toe.  Never had I ever seen so many women in one place, nor so many generations piled into one venue. ...Read More</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 06:36:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Get the Care You Need in a COVID-19 World</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/covid-senior-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>What to expect at the doctor’s office, hospitals, and long-term care facilities, the future of telemedicine, and how to get the best care during COVID-19.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 07:31:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>That Time I Went to the Eras Tour [Part One]</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/07/16/that-time-i-went-to-the-eras-tour-part-one/</link><description>Do you ever have one of those experiences where you want to remember exactly how you felt?  That’s how I feel about my experience at the Taylor Swift concert this weekend.  Correction:  At the Eras Tour.  Saying it was a concert does not feel like enough to justify the magnitude of the event. Let’s talk about the...Read More</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 05:17:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What to Know About Your Health Insurer’s Formulary Drug List</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/health-insurance/features/formulary-list-medications?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>How do drug formularies work? Learn more about your health insurer's list of preferred drugs and how it can save you money.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 18:23:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jenny Craig Recipe Creation:  Turkey Philly Baguette</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/02/13/jenny-craig-recipe-creation-turkey-philly-baguette/</link><description>Special thanks to Jenny Craig for their sponsorship of this post. In honor of the Super Bowl this year, I decided to make a Philly to enjoy. Knowing the Philadelphia Eagles were playing (and with no plans to watch the game), I let the City of Brotherly Love inspire this tasty dish.  I used the Jenny Craig...Read More</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:28:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shop Around to Save on Drug Prices</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/health-insurance/features/medication-shop-around?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Should you shop around for prescription drugs? Learn ways to compare drug prices to find more affordable options.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 18:21:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jenny Craig Recipe Creation: Mexican Chicken and Rice Soup</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/01/23/jenny-craig-recipe-creation-mexican-chicken-and-rice-soup/</link><description>Special thanks to Jenny Craig for their sponsorship of this post. Over the past year, I’ve shared a TON of recipe ideas; however, most of them have been on social media – – specifically instagram. Knowing that I missed sharing many recipes with this blog-reading community and for all those who search the internet for creative ways...Read More</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 03:50:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>