<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 12:07:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>My Word for 2024:  Strong</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2024/05/21/my-word-for-2024-strong/</link><description>Before I begin, know that I fully recognize that it&#8217;s May. I selected my word of the year way back in December of 2023. After letting it marinade for a few days, I spent an hour looking for the perfect bracelet on Etsy that would display its letters each and every day. I also knew... Read More</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 05:49:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Start A Successful Health Coaching Business (Yes, You Can!)</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/4-tips-to-starting-successful-health-coaching-business</link><description>Start your journey helping people make life-changing health shifts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 10:27:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: Misconceptions about how diet affects kidney stones</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-misconceptions-about-how-diet-affects-kidney-stones/</link><description>Kidney stones often have no definite, single cause, although several factors may increase someone's risk. While diet can be one of those factors, there are several misconceptions about what foods and drinks to avoid or consume more of in order to prevent kidney stones. However, in this Mayo Clinic Minute, Dr. Aaron Potretzke, a Mayo [&#8230;] The post Mayo Clinic Minute: Misconceptions about how diet affects kidney stones appeared first on Mayo Clinic News Network .</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 14:58:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Sound of Freedom</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/10/01/the-sound-of-freedom/</link><description>For a million years (more like 15,) I&#8217;ve been listening to a radio show: The Taylor Strecker Show. It&#8217;s a daily show that originated on SiriusXM and through a series of events became an independently broadcasted show on Patreon. There&#8217;s something interesting that happens when you listen to a daily show. You get to know... Read More</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 21:26:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>No Lie, This Supplement Is Like The Fountain Of Youth For Your Skin</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/how-each-mbg-best-skin-ingredient-benefits-aging-skin</link><description>Do you do your skin care routine morning and night? Great. But there's more you can do. Here's how to approach skin aging from the inside out.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 10:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How a different mammogram experience led to lifesaving cancer diagnosis</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/how-a-different-mammogram-experience-led-to-lifesaving-cancer-diagnosis/</link><description>Melissa Neuman dreaded getting mammograms. Her small, dense breasts made the screening exceptionally uncomfortable and painful. So Melissa put off getting an annual mammogram until she felt she couldn't delay any longer. For about five years, Melissa had been plagued with a nagging pain just under her left breast. In February 2023, a recommendation from a friend [&#8230;] The post How a different mammogram experience led to lifesaving cancer diagnosis appeared first on Mayo Clinic News Network .</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>That Time I Went to the Eras Tour [Part Two]</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/07/17/that-time-i-went-to-the-eras-tour-part-two/</link><description>To review part one of this adventure with Taylor Swift, click here. Click here to see all the Instagram highlight videos from Denver Night One. Mile High Stadium was pink and sparkly from head to toe. Never had I ever seen so many women in one place, nor so many generations piled into one venue. ... Read More</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 06:36:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In A Financial Pinch? 7 Small Savings Tips That Add Up To Big Savings</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/small-savings-tips-that-add-up-to-big-savings</link><description>Don&#8217;t dismiss the power of baby steps, especially when it comes to saving money. Small money moves can add up to big savings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 20:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maximize memory function with a nutrient-rich diet</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/maximize-memory-function-with-a-nutrient-rich-diet/</link><description>Research suggests that the ability to maximize memory function may be related to what you eat. Following an eating plan that provides a healthier selection of dietary fats and a variety of plant foods rich in phytonutrients could positively affect your health. Phytonutrients are substances found in certain plants that are believed to be beneficial for human [&#8230;] The post Maximize memory function with a nutrient-rich diet appeared first on Mayo Clinic News Network .</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>That Time I Went to the Eras Tour [Part One]</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/07/16/that-time-i-went-to-the-eras-tour-part-one/</link><description>Do you ever have one of those experiences where you want to remember exactly how you felt? That&#8217;s how I feel about my experience at the Taylor Swift concert this weekend. Correction: At the Eras Tour. Saying it was a concert does not feel like enough to justify the magnitude of the event. Let&#8217;s talk about the... Read More</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 05:17:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A 7-Week Plan To Master Pull-Ups (&amp; Why This Move Is A+ For Healthy Aging)</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/how-to-do-your-first-pull-up-7-week-beginner-plan</link><description>Pull-ups are way more than just a flex&#8212;they can actively boost longevity and health span.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 12:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In case you missed it: This week&#8217;s Top 5 stories on social media</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/in-case-you-missed-it-this-weeks-top-5-stories-on-social-media-18/</link><description>Check out a few of the most popular News Network stories on @mayoclinic social media this past week. IBD Pride Clinic: Belonging while battling bowel disease In July 2022, Mayo Clinic was one of the first in the nation to open an Inflammatory Bowel Disease Pride Clinic. The clinic aims to create an affirming space [&#8230;] The post In case you missed it: This week&#8217;s Top 5 stories on social media appeared first on Mayo Clinic News Network .</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 16:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jenny Craig Recipe Creation:  Turkey Philly Baguette</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/02/13/jenny-craig-recipe-creation-turkey-philly-baguette/</link><description>Special thanks to Jenny Craig for their sponsorship of this post. In honor of the Super Bowl this year, I decided to make a Philly to enjoy. Knowing the Philadelphia Eagles were playing (and with no plans to watch the game), I let the City of Brotherly Love inspire this tasty dish. I used the Jenny Craig... Read More</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:28:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Creatine Supplements Bad For Your Kidneys? What's Fact vs. Fiction</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/are-creatine-supplements-bad-for-your-kidneys</link><description>Here's what you should know.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 11:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: Can energy drinks cause heart issues?</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-can-energy-drinks-cause-heart-issues/</link><description>In recent years, there's been a big boost in the beverage industry when it comes to the sale of energy drinks. Classified as dietary supplements, most of these drinks contain stimulating ingredients, in addition to high amounts of caffeine, that aren't regulated by the Food and Drug Administration. Researchers at Mayo Clinic recently published a [&#8230;] The post Mayo Clinic Minute: Can energy drinks cause heart issues? appeared first on Mayo Clinic News Network .</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 14:58:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>