<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 16:15:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Federal Experts Talk Bird Flu &#8216;What Ifs&#8217; in WebMD Live Event</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/cold-and-flu/news/20240516/federal-experts-talk-bird-flu-what-ifs?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>WebMD brought together experts from four federal agencies to talk prevention, monitoring, and what the &#8220;what ifs&#8221; of bird flu might look like.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:50:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>My Word for 2024:  Strong</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2024/05/21/my-word-for-2024-strong/</link><description>Before I begin, know that I fully recognize that it&#8217;s May. I selected my word of the year way back in December of 2023. After letting it marinade for a few days, I spent an hour looking for the perfect bracelet on Etsy that would display its letters each and every day. I also knew... Read More</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 05:49:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Superfruit Extract Has Major Benefits For Aging Skin*</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/major-skin-care-benefits-of-blood-orange-extract</link><description>When I dug into the emerging research behind the skin care benefits of blood orange extract supplements, I loved what I found.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 10:27:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: Coping with cancer-related fatigue</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-coping-with-cancer-related-fatigue/</link><description>People can experience cancer-related fatigue before, during and after treatments. This is different from the typical tiredness. At times, your arms and legs might feel heavy, making it hard to move. It may be challenging to even get out of bed in the morning. Cancer-related fatigue can take a toll mentally too. It can sometimes [&#8230;] The post Mayo Clinic Minute: Coping with cancer-related fatigue appeared first on Mayo Clinic News Network .</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 16:09:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What&#8217;s Next in Health Care for Older Adults: Questions and Answers With John Whyte, MD</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/blog-aging-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>As WebMD&#8217;s chief medical officer, John Whyte, MD, is in a unique position to see both the current state of medical care for America&#8217;s older adults and the way things are trending for the future. We asked him to share his insight on a few topics, along with a bit of advice.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:29:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Sound of Freedom</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/10/01/the-sound-of-freedom/</link><description>For a million years (more like 15,) I&#8217;ve been listening to a radio show: The Taylor Strecker Show. It&#8217;s a daily show that originated on SiriusXM and through a series of events became an independently broadcasted show on Patreon. There&#8217;s something interesting that happens when you listen to a daily show. You get to know... Read More</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 21:26:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Want To Lower Your Resting Heart Rate? Get More Of This Nutrient</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/omega-3s-and-resting-heart-rate</link><description>You're likely falling below the recommended intake.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 11:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Removing skin cancer with Mohs surgery</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/removing-skin-cancer-with-mohs-surgery/</link><description>Skin cancer is the most common form of cancer. When treated early, it's also the most curable type of cancer. Mohs surgery is one of the most successful surgical treatments for removing skin cancer. The abnormal growth of skin cells that leads to skin cancer develops most often on skin exposed to the sun, such as your [&#8230;] The post Removing skin cancer with Mohs surgery appeared first on Mayo Clinic News Network .</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 13:58:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Get the Care You Need in a COVID-19 World</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/covid-senior-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>What to expect at the doctor&#8217;s office, hospitals, and long-term care facilities, the future of telemedicine, and how to get the best care during COVID-19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 19:50:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>That Time I Went to the Eras Tour [Part Two]</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/07/17/that-time-i-went-to-the-eras-tour-part-two/</link><description>To review part one of this adventure with Taylor Swift, click here. Click here to see all the Instagram highlight videos from Denver Night One. Mile High Stadium was pink and sparkly from head to toe. Never had I ever seen so many women in one place, nor so many generations piled into one venue. ... Read More</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 06:36:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>3 Easy Steps To Firmer, Smoother-Looking Legs According To A Beauty Editor</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/3-easy-steps-to-firmer-smoother-looking-legs</link><description>It's that time of the year when I start to think more and more about my legs. You too?</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 10:26:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Baseball&#8217;s best trade: Former ball player trains to become a cardiologist at Mayo Clinic</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/baseballs-best-trade-former-ball-player-trains-to-become-a-cardiologist-at-mayo-clinic/</link><description>Jimmy Howick, M.D., had embarked on a career as a professional baseball player. When the Houston Astros farm team released him, he went after another dream: becoming a cardiologist at Mayo Clinic. The post Baseball&#8217;s best trade: Former ball player trains to become a cardiologist at Mayo Clinic appeared first on Mayo Clinic News Network .</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:30:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Personal Shopper: A Savvy Black Entrepreneur Guides You to Eczema-Friendly Clothes, Creams, Cosmetics, and More</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/savvy-black-entrepreneur-guides-eczema-friendly-clothes-creams-cosmetics?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>A savvy black entrepreneur guides you on an eczema-friendly shopping spree.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:54:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>That Time I Went to the Eras Tour [Part One]</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/07/16/that-time-i-went-to-the-eras-tour-part-one/</link><description>Do you ever have one of those experiences where you want to remember exactly how you felt? That&#8217;s how I feel about my experience at the Taylor Swift concert this weekend. Correction: At the Eras Tour. Saying it was a concert does not feel like enough to justify the magnitude of the event. Let&#8217;s talk about the... Read More</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 05:17:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Yes, Your Hormones Impact Your Social Battery &#8212; Here's How (&amp; What To Do)</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/how-your-cycle-impacts-your-social-battery-from-experts</link><description>From the experts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New elbow surgery technique developed at Mayo Clinic helps wrestler get back on the mat</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/new-elbow-surgery-technique-developed-at-mayo-clinic-helps-wrestler-get-back-on-the-mat/</link><description>Tommy John surgery is not just for baseball pitchers. Ask Kylie Donat of Bemidji, Minnesota. Kylie is an 18-year-old high school swimmer, track and field athlete, and wrestler. She has been wrestling since 2021, the first year that girls' wrestling was a sanctioned high school sport in Minnesota. By 2023, Kylie was favored to win [&#8230;] The post New elbow surgery technique developed at Mayo Clinic helps wrestler get back on the mat appeared first on Mayo Clinic News Network .</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 15:40:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Behind the Spike in Colorectal Cancer Among Young Americans</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/colorectal-cancer/news/20240515/behind-the-spike-in-colorectal-cancer-cases?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Colorectal cancer cases increased a whopping 333% among 15- to 19-year-olds and 185% among 20- to 24-year-olds from 1999 to 2020.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:59:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jenny Craig Recipe Creation:  Turkey Philly Baguette</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/02/13/jenny-craig-recipe-creation-turkey-philly-baguette/</link><description>Special thanks to Jenny Craig for their sponsorship of this post. In honor of the Super Bowl this year, I decided to make a Philly to enjoy. Knowing the Philadelphia Eagles were playing (and with no plans to watch the game), I let the City of Brotherly Love inspire this tasty dish. I used the Jenny Craig... Read More</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:28:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>These Are The 5 Healthiest Fish To Eat, According To A Registered Dietitian</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/im-registered-dietitian-and-these-are-healthiest-fish-to-eat</link><description>Clear your dinner plans; we're having seafood tonight!</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 10:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Empowering Lives: Navigating Parkinson&#8217;s disease with hope</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/empowering-lives-navigating-parkinsons-disease-with-hope/</link><description>LA CROSSE, Wis. &#8213; Parkinson's disease touches every aspect of a person's life, from the physical to the emotional, often leaving individuals feeling isolated and overwhelmed. However, amid the challenges, there is a beacon of hope&#8212;new treatments and simple lifestyle changes are making a significant difference, empowering those diagnosed to lead fuller, more vibrant lives. [&#8230;] The post Empowering Lives: Navigating Parkinson&#8217;s disease with hope appeared first on Mayo Clinic News Network .</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>