<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 06:37:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The 7-Hour Itch: 3 Women With Eczema Describe the Ways They Combat Nighttime Flare-Ups</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/seven-hour-itch-women-eczema-combat-nighttime-flares?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Three women with eczema describe how they combat nighttime flare-ups.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 09:09:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Sound of Freedom</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/10/01/the-sound-of-freedom/</link><description>For a million years (more like 15,) I&#8217;ve been listening to a radio show: The Taylor Strecker Show. It&#8217;s a daily show that originated on SiriusXM and through a series of events became an independently broadcasted show on Patreon. There&#8217;s something interesting that happens when you listen to a daily show. You get to know... Read More</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 21:26:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I'm A Neuroscientist: These Are The 3 Most Common Manifesting Mistakes</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/3-common-manifestation-mistakes-from-neuroscientist</link><description>There is a wrong way to manifest.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 10:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: Perimenopause and menopause</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-perimenopause-and-menopause/</link><description>Menopause marks a significant transition for women, yet understanding its precursor, perimenopause, and its symptoms can be complex. Dr. Stephanie Faubion, director of Mayo Clinic's Center for Women's Health and medical director of The Menopause Society, says experiencing perimenopause and menopause can be confusing for some. She says it is not only patients who may find it confusing, but medical providers as [&#8230;] The post Mayo Clinic Minute: Perimenopause and menopause appeared first on Mayo Clinic News Network .</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Mother&#8217;s Love: The Challenges of Parenting a Child With Eczema</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/mothers-love-challenges-parenting-child-eczema?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Two moms reveal the great lengths they went to in their determination to give their children relief and good health.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 09:18:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>That Time I Went to the Eras Tour [Part Two]</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/07/17/that-time-i-went-to-the-eras-tour-part-two/</link><description>To review part one of this adventure with Taylor Swift, click here. Click here to see all the Instagram highlight videos from Denver Night One. Mile High Stadium was pink and sparkly from head to toe. Never had I ever seen so many women in one place, nor so many generations piled into one venue. ... Read More</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 06:36:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>There Are 12 Hallmarks Of Aging &#8212; This Vitamin May Improve All Of Them</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/vitamin-d-and-the-hallmarks-of-aging</link><description>Hint: It has antioxidant properties.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 11:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Students&#8217; passion projects address big issues in healthcare</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/students-passion-projects-address-big-issues-in-healthcare/</link><description>Students from across Mayo Clinic College of Medicine and Science devote their spare hours to solving big biomedical problems. The post Students&#8217; passion projects address big issues in healthcare appeared first on Mayo Clinic News Network .</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 14:36:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Working It Out: How to Minimize Eczema Flare-ups at the Gym and on the Job</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/minimize-eczema-flare-ups-gym-job?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Three keys to managing your eczema at the gym and then heading off to a productive and itch-free workday.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 07:30:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>That Time I Went to the Eras Tour [Part One]</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/07/16/that-time-i-went-to-the-eras-tour-part-one/</link><description>Do you ever have one of those experiences where you want to remember exactly how you felt? That&#8217;s how I feel about my experience at the Taylor Swift concert this weekend. Correction: At the Eras Tour. Saying it was a concert does not feel like enough to justify the magnitude of the event. Let&#8217;s talk about the... Read More</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 05:17:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>3 Daily Gut Health Habits Recommended By A Gastroenterologist</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/3-gut-supporting-habits-gastroenterologist-recommends-daily</link><description>Three healthy habits, recommended by a gastroenterologist.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 10:29:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Timesaving tips for cooking healthy meals</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/timesaving-tips-for-cooking-healthy-meals/</link><description>Living a busy, fast-paced life can make it hard to find the motivation to cook a healthy meal at home. However, learning some shortcuts in the kitchen can keep your healthy eating goals on track and help you avoid grazing on unhealthy snacks, grabbing the first thing you see in the fridge or going out for fast food. Why cook [&#8230;] The post Timesaving tips for cooking healthy meals appeared first on Mayo Clinic News Network .</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cows Are Potential Spreaders of Bird Flu to Humans</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/food-recipes/food-poisoning/news/20240510/cows-are-potential-spreaders-bird-flu-humans?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Cow udders have the same receptors for flu viruses as humans and birds, raising concerns that cows could become &#8220;mixing vessels&#8221; that help the bird flu virus spread between people.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 19:36:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jenny Craig Recipe Creation:  Turkey Philly Baguette</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/02/13/jenny-craig-recipe-creation-turkey-philly-baguette/</link><description>Special thanks to Jenny Craig for their sponsorship of this post. In honor of the Super Bowl this year, I decided to make a Philly to enjoy. Knowing the Philadelphia Eagles were playing (and with no plans to watch the game), I let the City of Brotherly Love inspire this tasty dish. I used the Jenny Craig... Read More</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:28:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I Covered 100,000+ Steps In These Sandals On Vacation &amp; Didn't Get One Blister</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/pons-avarcas-editor-review</link><description>100,000 and counting</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 10:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Recovering from a stroke</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/consumer-health-recovering-from-a-stroke-2/</link><description>Editors Note: May is National Stroke Awareness Month. Stroke is one of the leading causes of death in the U.S. and a major cause of serious disability for adults. More than 795,000 people in the U.S. have a stroke each year, according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. Stroke risk increases with age, especially after [&#8230;] The post Recovering from a stroke appeared first on Mayo Clinic News Network .</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Age-Related Macular Degeneration: Putting a Hole in Our World</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/eye-health/news/20240510/age-related-macular-degeneration-putting-hole-our-world?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Estimates show that by 2040, age-related macular degeneration may affect nearly 300 million people worldwide. And we are very limited in our ability to treat or prevent it. Here's what to know.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 19:31:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jenny Craig Recipe Creation: Mexican Chicken and Rice Soup</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/01/23/jenny-craig-recipe-creation-mexican-chicken-and-rice-soup/</link><description>Special thanks to Jenny Craig for their sponsorship of this post. Over the past year, I&#8217;ve shared a TON of recipe ideas; however, most of them have been on social media &#8211; &#8211; specifically instagram. Knowing that I missed sharing many recipes with this blog-reading community and for all those who search the internet for creative ways... Read More</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 03:50:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Annual "Day Of Miracles" Is This Week&#8212;Here's Your Horoscope</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/weekly-horoscope-for-may-13-19-2024-from-astrotwins</link><description>The Taurus vibes are strong this week.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 12:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In case you missed it: This week&#8217;s Top 5 stories on social media</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/in-case-you-missed-it-this-weeks-top-5-stories-on-social-media-10/</link><description>Check out a few of the most popular News Network stories on @mayoclinic social media this past week. Hormone therapy: Four things a Mayo Clinic women&#8217;s health specialist wants you to know Hormone therapy is a treatment that uses medications containing hormones like estrogen or progesterone to replace those the body stops producing during menopause. [&#8230;] The post In case you missed it: This week&#8217;s Top 5 stories on social media appeared first on Mayo Clinic News Network .</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>