<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 13:51:36 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>My Word for 2024:  Strong</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2024/05/21/my-word-for-2024-strong/</link><description>Before I begin, know that I fully recognize that it&#8217;s May. I selected my word of the year way back in December of 2023. After letting it marinade for a few days, I spent an hour looking for the perfect bracelet on Etsy that would display its letters each and every day. I also knew... Read More</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 05:49:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Start A Successful Health Coaching Business (Yes, You Can!)</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/4-tips-to-starting-successful-health-coaching-business</link><description>Start your journey helping people make life-changing health shifts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 10:27:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: Keeping kids safe outside during summer play</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-keeping-kids-safe-outside-during-summer-play/</link><description>Summer vacation for kids is well underway. Finding activities to keep the kids busy and destinations to visit can be on many parents' list. There is one place Mayo Clinic's Dr. Steven Maher hopes they don't have to visit &#8212; and that's the emergency medicine department. From wearing bike helmets to keeping kids hydrated, Dr. [&#8230;] The post Mayo Clinic Minute: Keeping kids safe outside during summer play appeared first on Mayo Clinic News Network .</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 16:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Sound of Freedom</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/10/01/the-sound-of-freedom/</link><description>For a million years (more like 15,) I&#8217;ve been listening to a radio show: The Taylor Strecker Show. It&#8217;s a daily show that originated on SiriusXM and through a series of events became an independently broadcasted show on Patreon. There&#8217;s something interesting that happens when you listen to a daily show. You get to know... Read More</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 21:26:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>No Lie, This Supplement Is Like The Fountain Of Youth For Your Skin</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/how-each-mbg-best-skin-ingredient-benefits-aging-skin</link><description>Do you do your skin care routine morning and night? Great. But there's more you can do. Here's how to approach skin aging from the inside out.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 10:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Can you prevent cancer with lifestyle changes?</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/can-you-prevent-cancer-with-lifestyle-changes/</link><description>Nearly half of cancer deaths in the U.S. are associated with preventable risk factors &#8212; such as smoking and alcohol use &#8212; according to a new American Cancer Society study. Dr. Jon Ebbert, medical director of the Mayo Clinic Nicotine Dependence Center, says it's never too late to make lifestyle changes that can decrease your risk of [&#8230;] The post Can you prevent cancer with lifestyle changes? appeared first on Mayo Clinic News Network .</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 15:12:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>That Time I Went to the Eras Tour [Part Two]</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/07/17/that-time-i-went-to-the-eras-tour-part-two/</link><description>To review part one of this adventure with Taylor Swift, click here. Click here to see all the Instagram highlight videos from Denver Night One. Mile High Stadium was pink and sparkly from head to toe. Never had I ever seen so many women in one place, nor so many generations piled into one venue. ... Read More</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 06:36:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In A Financial Pinch? 7 Small Savings Tips That Add Up To Big Savings</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/small-savings-tips-that-add-up-to-big-savings</link><description>Don&#8217;t dismiss the power of baby steps, especially when it comes to saving money. Small money moves can add up to big savings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 20:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In case you missed it: This week&#8217;s Top 5 stories on social media</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/in-case-you-missed-it-this-weeks-top-5-stories-on-social-media-19/</link><description>Check out a few of the most popular News Network stories on @mayoclinic social media this past week. Mayo Clinic marks medical milestone with world's first known successful total larynx transplant performed in a patient with an active cancer as part of a clinical trial Mayo Clinic announces a groundbreaking achievement in organ transplantation, offering hope [&#8230;] The post In case you missed it: This week&#8217;s Top 5 stories on social media appeared first on Mayo Clinic News Network .</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 13:51:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>That Time I Went to the Eras Tour [Part One]</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/07/16/that-time-i-went-to-the-eras-tour-part-one/</link><description>Do you ever have one of those experiences where you want to remember exactly how you felt? That&#8217;s how I feel about my experience at the Taylor Swift concert this weekend. Correction: At the Eras Tour. Saying it was a concert does not feel like enough to justify the magnitude of the event. Let&#8217;s talk about the... Read More</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 05:17:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A 7-Week Plan To Master Pull-Ups (&amp; Why This Move Is A+ For Healthy Aging)</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/how-to-do-your-first-pull-up-7-week-beginner-plan</link><description>Pull-ups are way more than just a flex&#8212;they can actively boost longevity and health span.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 12:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayo Clinic Minute: Dangers of heat-related illnesses</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/mayo-clinic-minute-dangers-of-heat-related-illnesses/</link><description>Scorching temperatures continue to blanket much of the U.S. in an ongoing summer heat wave. Prolonged exposure to both heat and humidity can lead to heat-related illnesses &#8212; from heat cramps to exhaustion to life-threatening heatstroke. Dr. Jesse Bracamonte, a Mayo Clinic family physician, offers recommendations on what to do if you begin to feel ill. Watch: The Mayo [&#8230;] The post Mayo Clinic Minute: Dangers of heat-related illnesses appeared first on Mayo Clinic News Network .</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jenny Craig Recipe Creation:  Turkey Philly Baguette</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/02/13/jenny-craig-recipe-creation-turkey-philly-baguette/</link><description>Special thanks to Jenny Craig for their sponsorship of this post. In honor of the Super Bowl this year, I decided to make a Philly to enjoy. Knowing the Philadelphia Eagles were playing (and with no plans to watch the game), I let the City of Brotherly Love inspire this tasty dish. I used the Jenny Craig... Read More</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:28:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Creatine Supplements Bad For Your Kidneys? What's Fact vs. Fiction</title><link>https://www.mindbodygreen.com/articles/are-creatine-supplements-bad-for-your-kidneys</link><description>Here's what you should know.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 11:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sports Safety Spotlight: Mayo advises teens on how to get back in the game safely after shoulder injury</title><link>https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/sports-safety-spotlight-mayo-advises-teens-on-how-to-get-back-in-the-game-safely-after-shoulder-injury/</link><description>AUSTIN, Minn. &#8213; For teens who love playing summer team sports, an injury that takes them out of the game can be devastating. Shoulder injuries are among the most common for athletes who play volleyball, tennis, swimming, football and a variety of others. "The shoulder is an incredibly mobile joint that allows you to reach [&#8230;] The post Sports Safety Spotlight: Mayo advises teens on how to get back in the game safely after shoulder injury appeared first on Mayo Clinic News Network .</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>