<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 16:32:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>You Give Me (Spring) Fever</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/women/features/you-give-me-spring-fever?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>New Season Brings Boost of Energy, but Also Unplanned Pregnancies</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 16:57:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Sound of Freedom</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/10/01/the-sound-of-freedom/</link><description>For a million years (more like 15,) I’ve been listening to a radio show:  The Taylor Strecker Show. It’s a daily show that originated on SiriusXM and through a series of events became an independently broadcasted show on Patreon.  There’s something interesting that happens when you listen to a daily show.  You get to know...Read More</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 21:26:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Older Adults: 9 Nutrients You May Be Missing</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/missing-nutrients?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>With age, your body doesn’t absorb nutrients well, so every calorie you consume must be packed with nutrition. Here are 9 nutrients older adults often need more of.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 16:57:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>That Time I Went to the Eras Tour [Part Two]</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/07/17/that-time-i-went-to-the-eras-tour-part-two/</link><description>To review part one of this adventure with Taylor Swift, click here. Click here to see all the Instagram highlight videos from Denver Night One. Mile High Stadium was pink and sparkly from head to toe.  Never had I ever seen so many women in one place, nor so many generations piled into one venue. ...Read More</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 06:36:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Immunity Challenge: How aging affects your immune system</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/seniors-boost-immunity?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>How does getting older affect your immune system? How can you keep those effects to a minimum? Your answers are here.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 16:57:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>That Time I Went to the Eras Tour [Part One]</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/07/16/that-time-i-went-to-the-eras-tour-part-one/</link><description>Do you ever have one of those experiences where you want to remember exactly how you felt?  That’s how I feel about my experience at the Taylor Swift concert this weekend.  Correction:  At the Eras Tour.  Saying it was a concert does not feel like enough to justify the magnitude of the event. Let’s talk about the...Read More</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 05:17:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Helps When It’s Hard to Chew and Swallow?</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/eating-problems?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Trouble chewing and swallowing? WebMD shares six ways to make everything go down a little easier.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 16:57:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jenny Craig Recipe Creation:  Turkey Philly Baguette</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/02/13/jenny-craig-recipe-creation-turkey-philly-baguette/</link><description>Special thanks to Jenny Craig for their sponsorship of this post. In honor of the Super Bowl this year, I decided to make a Philly to enjoy. Knowing the Philadelphia Eagles were playing (and with no plans to watch the game), I let the City of Brotherly Love inspire this tasty dish.  I used the Jenny Craig...Read More</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:28:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Foods to Keep You Healthy as You Age</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/longevity-foods?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Staying healthy as you enter your golden years has a lot to do with your diet. Here are some foods that are good for your heart, your brain, your bones, and your muscles.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 16:57:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jenny Craig Recipe Creation: Mexican Chicken and Rice Soup</title><link>https://www.nothankstocake.com/2023/01/23/jenny-craig-recipe-creation-mexican-chicken-and-rice-soup/</link><description>Special thanks to Jenny Craig for their sponsorship of this post. Over the past year, I’ve shared a TON of recipe ideas; however, most of them have been on social media – – specifically instagram. Knowing that I missed sharing many recipes with this blog-reading community and for all those who search the internet for creative ways...Read More</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 03:50:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>