<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 07:27:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Kamala Harris Holds What Looks Michigan’s Largest Democratic Campaign Event In Years</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/08/07/kamala-harris-michigan-rally.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent2.png</image_url><description>Reporters on the scene are observing that the crowd for the Harris-Walz Michigan event is the biggest they've seen for a Democratic campaign since 2016.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 23:55:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oklahoma Knows You Can’t Manage What You Don’t Measure</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/08/07/oklahoma-knows-you-cant-manage-what-you-dont-measure/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent.png</image_url><description>Oklahoma’s Superintendent of the State Department of Education is asking Oklahoma school districts to get a handle on the number of illegal aliens occupying classrooms statewide “to find accurate and effective counting of the cost and burden that illegal immigration has.” To read the rest of the article click here The post Oklahoma Knows You Can’t Manage What You Don’t Measure appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:04:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Liz Cheney Just Totally Owned JD Vance</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/08/07/liz-cheney-just-totally-owned-jd-vance.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent.png</image_url><description>Former Rep. Liz Cheney responded to a picture of Vance at the airport today that summed up his failed campaign.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 21:39:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Massachusetts Migrant Housing Costs: Out of Orbit and Hard to Grasp</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/08/01/massachusetts-migrant-housing-costs-out-of-orbit-and-hard-to-grasp/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent3.png</image_url><description>Beyond a certain threshold, numbers become abstract and lose their meaningful context. A quick view of the national debt clock which adds $100,000 of national debt every two-and-a-half seconds to America’s current obligations of $35 trillion is virtually impossible to comprehend. To read the rest of the article click here The post Massachusetts Migrant Housing Costs: Out of Orbit and Hard to Grasp appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 17:55:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JD Vance Draws Hundreds In Michigan As Harris And Walz Pack Wisconsin</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/08/07/jd-vance-draws-hundreds-in-michigan-as-harris-and-walz-pack-wisconsin.html</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f4cd.png</image_url><description>Trump's running mate, JD Vance, drew hundreds for a campaign stop in Michigan, while Kamala Harris and Tim Walz have a crowd in the many thousands in Wisconsin.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 20:04:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>House Passes Resolution Condemning the Biden-Harris Administration’s Failure to Secure the Border</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/08/01/house-passes-resolution-condemning-the-biden-harris-administrations-failure-to-secure-the-border/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent2.png</image_url><description>On July 25, the House of Representatives passed H. Res. 1371, condemning President Biden and Vice President Kamala Harris’ failure to secure the border. The resolution passed the same week that President Biden announced he would not seek a second term. To read the rest of the article click here The post House Passes Resolution Condemning the Biden-Harris Administration’s Failure to Secure the Border appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 17:33:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Harris And Walz Draw A Gigantic Crowd In Wisconsin</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/08/07/harris-and-walz-draw-a-gigantic-crowd-in-wisconsin.html</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f4cd.png</image_url><description>A crowd of potentially tens of thousands has gathered in Wisconsin for Kamala Harris and running mate Tim Walz.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 19:31:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Disastrous Nexus of Biden-Harris Policies:  The Afghan Parole Program and Prohibition on Issuing Notices to Appear</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/31/a-disastrous-nexus-of-biden-harris-policies-the-afghan-parole-program-and-prohibition-on-issuing-notices-to-appear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent.png</image_url><description>On this date three years ago – July 31, 2021 – the first group of Afghan nationals arrived in the United States after the President Biden’s disastrous withdrawal of U.S. troops from the country. To read the rest of the article click here The post A Disastrous Nexus of Biden-Harris Policies: The Afghan Parole Program and Prohibition on Issuing Notices to Appear appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 16:02:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Now That He Is Not Winning Trump Wants To Debate</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/08/07/trump-wants-debate.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent.png</image_url><description>After several good weekend polls for Kamala Harris, Trump changed his tune on participating in a debate.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 18:56:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Human Smuggler Who Facilitated Illegal Entry of Thousands of Aliens Indicted</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/29/human-smuggler-who-facilitated-illegal-entry-of-thousands-of-aliens-indicted/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent2.png</image_url><description>On July 18, reports surfaced that Abdul Karim Conteh, a national from Sierra Leone, had been indicted and sanctioned in the United States and arrested in Tijuana, Mexico. Conteh ran a smuggling organization that facilitated the transport of thousands of illegal aliens to the United States through Mexico, including many from terrorism hot spots. To [...] The post Human Smuggler Who Facilitated Illegal Entry of Thousands of Aliens Indicted appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 20:17:26 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>