<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 16:01:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>It Seems Like Trump Is Trying To Weasel Out Of Debating Kamala Harris</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/23/donald-trump-debate-kamala-harris.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>In a call with reporters, Trump claimed that he wants to debate VP Kamala Harris, but he doesn't want the debate to be on ABC, which seems like Trump trying to change the network or get out of the debate.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 20:25:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Biden’s Border Crisis is Destroying Heartland America: A Look at Springfield, Ohio</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/19/how-bidens-border-crisis-is-destroying-heartland-america-a-look-at-springfield-ohio/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>You’ve seen the videos of migrants blatantly violating our immigration laws by illegally crossing the southern border, and you are probably one of the many Americans rightfully horrified by the recent stories of illegal alien crime. To read the rest of the article click here The post How Biden’s Border Crisis is Destroying Heartland America: A Look at Springfield, Ohio appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 21:58:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kamala Harris Has Taken The Lead Over Donald Trump In New Poll</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/23/kamala-harris-has-taken-the-lead-over-donald-trump-in-new-poll.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Vice President Kamala Harris has a lead over Trump that is within the margin of error in a two way race, but has a four point lead when RFK Jr. is included.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 19:56:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maryland Governor Wes Moore Says No to Statewide Immigration Policy</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/19/maryland-governor-wes-moore-says-no-to-statewide-immigration-policy/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>In a recent interview, Governor Wes Moore claimed that Maryland cannot establish a policy that dictates how the state interacts with U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE) because “it’s a federal agency.” To read the rest of the article click here The post Maryland Governor Wes Moore Says No to Statewide Immigration Policy appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 16:29:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bakari Sellers Says ‘Win with Black Men’ Raised Over over $1.3M for Kamala Harris</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/23/bakari-sellers-says-win-with-black-men-raised-over-over-1-3m-for-kamala-harris.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Fresh off of a Win with Black Men call that raised over $1.3M for VP Kamala Harris, Bakari Sellers said her campaign is "one of the most successful Democratic campaigns we've seen in a long time."</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 18:51:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DHS Extends Temporary Protected Status to Haitians, Encouraging More Illegal Immigration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/17/dhs-extends-temporary-protected-status-to-haitians-encouraging-more-illegal-immigration/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Extending and re-designating TPS to Haitian nationals, at a time of unprecedented illegal immigration to the United States, is yet another example of how the Biden administration’s open-border agenda prioritizes illegal aliens over American citizens. To read the rest of the article click here The post DHS Extends Temporary Protected Status to Haitians, Encouraging More Illegal Immigration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 21:34:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Just Outsmarted The GOP’s Netanyahu Stunt</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/23/biden-just-outsmarted-the-gops-netanyahu-stunt.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Israel Prime Minister Netanyahu's address to Congress will be upstaged by President Biden, who will give a national primetime address on his decision not to run for reelection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 18:19:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Voting Integrity Matters at the Federal AND Local Levels</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/16/voting-integrity-matters-at-the-federal-and-local-levels/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>University of Virginia political analyst Larry Sabato once said with intended obviousness, “every election is determined by the people who show up.” Yet now, in an era with endlessly increasing illegal immigration that risks undermining the electorate, the statement is woefully insufficient. What matters most to the integrity of America’s representative democracy is to ensure [...] The post Voting Integrity Matters at the Federal AND Local Levels appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 15:03:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kamala Harris Has Already Broken Trump</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/23/kamala-harris-has-broken-trump-as-he-claims-vp-got-him-shot.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Donald Trump's meltdown on his social media platform is ongoing as he is now claiming that Kamala Harris didn't protect him and got him shot.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 17:56:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Warning for New Yorkers: Moped-Riding Illegal Aliens Allegedly Robbing Outdoor Diners</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/12/warning-for-new-yorkers-moped-riding-illegal-aliens-allegedly-robbing-outdoor-diners/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Imagine this: you’re enjoying a warm summer evening in New York City, dining al fresco, proudly wearing the luxury watch you worked so hard to buy. Suddenly, a pair of armed, moped-riding bandits appear, robbing you of your prized possession. And it turns out these suspected criminals are reportedly newly-arrived illegal aliens. To read the [...] The post Warning for New Yorkers: Moped-Riding Illegal Aliens Allegedly Robbing Outdoor Diners appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 19:43:46 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>