<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:24:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>DOJ Tosses House Contempt Referral Of Merrick Garland In The Dumpster</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/14/doj-tosses-house-contempt-referral-of-merrick-garland-in-the-dumpster.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>The Department of Justice has notified Speaker Mike Johnson that it won't prosecute Attorney General Merrick Garland for contempt of Congress because Garland didn't commit a crime.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 20:09:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is That REALLY a Homeless Shelter for Needy Americans or…Illegal Alien Housing?</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/13/is-that-really-a-homeless-shelter-for-needy-americans-orillegal-alien-housing/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Promoting open border and amnesty policies is increasingly tricky business for the left. After all, illegal immigration is a major issue for most voters, a concern that’s apparently deepening as shown by a new CBS News poll revealing that 62 percent of Americans support, “in principle, a new government program to deport all undocumented immigrants [...] The post Is That REALLY a Homeless Shelter for Needy Americans or…Illegal Alien Housing? appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 14:49:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chuck Schumer Says Democrats Are Ready To Pass Bump Stock Ban After SCOTUS Overturn</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/14/chuck-schumer-says-democrats-are-ready-to-pass-bump-stock-ban-after-scotus-overturn.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Senate Majority Leader Chuck Schumer (D-NY) said that Democrats are to pass a bump stock ban, but it will be up to Republicans to supply additional votes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 18:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Crisis on NATO’s Eastern Border Shows How Anti-Western Regimes Weaponize Illegal Mass Migration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/12/crisis-on-natos-eastern-border-shows-how-anti-western-regimes-weaponize-illegal-mass-migration/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>A Polish soldier is dead, after being stabbed by an illegal migrant making an attempted incursion from the territory of neighboring Belarus. This incident represents a dangerous escalation of a “hybrid war” that has been ongoing on the eastern flank of NATO since 2021. To read the rest of the article click here The post Crisis on NATO’s Eastern Border Shows How Anti-Western Regimes Weaponize Illegal Mass Migration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 19:56:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Judge Orders Alex Jones’s Assets Sold To Pay Sandy Hook Families</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/14/judge-orders-alex-joness-assets-sold-to-pay-sandy-hook-families.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>A judge has ordered that Alex Jones's assets be liquidated and sold to pay the $1.5 billion that he owes Sandy Hook families for defamation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 17:39:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eight Illegal Aliens with Ties to ISIS Arrested Inside the U.S</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/12/eight-illegal-aliens-with-ties-to-isis-arrested-inside-the-u-s/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>In the latest alarming national security incident, eight suspected terrorists with ties to ISIS were arrested on immigration violations in a joint U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE) in conjunction with the FBI Joint Terrorism Task Force. To read the rest of the article click here The post Eight Illegal Aliens with Ties to ISIS Arrested Inside the U.S appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 18:36:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CEOs Offer Damning Assessment Of Trump’s Mental Decline</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/14/ceos-trump-mental-decline.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>CEOs who were described as Trumpish came away from a meeting with the ex-president concerned that he was meandering and couldn't keep a straight thought.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 16:30:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>House Committee Hears Testimony on Effects of the Border Crisis in North Dakota</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/11/house-committee-hears-testimony-on-effects-of-the-border-crisis-in-north-dakota/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>The House Judiciary Subcommittee on Immigration Integrity, Security, and Enforcement, recently held a field hearing to discuss the effects of the border crisis in North Dakota. To read the rest of the article click here The post House Committee Hears Testimony on Effects of the Border Crisis in North Dakota appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 19:51:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Clarence Thomas Corruption Bombshell: Senate Finds 3 New Undisclosed Trips</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/13/clarence-thomas-corruption-bombshell-senate-finds-3-new-undisclosed-trips.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>The Senate Judiciary Committee Democrats have uncovered three new trips that Justice Clarence Thomas received from Harlan Crow that he never disclosed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 22:50:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gun-Wielding Illegal Alien Allegedly Shoots Two NYPD Officers in Latest Migrant Crime Incident</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/05/gun-wielding-illegal-alien-allegedly-shoots-two-nypd-officers-in-latest-migrant-crime-incident/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>In the early hours of June 3, 2024, NYPD officers Christopher Abreu and Richard Yarusso were investigating a robbery when they encountered 19-year-old Bernardo Castro Mata, an illegal alien from Venezuela, driving a motorized scooter with no plates the wrong way down a street. To read the rest of the article click here The post Gun-Wielding Illegal Alien Allegedly Shoots Two NYPD Officers in Latest Migrant Crime Incident appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 18:21:58 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>