<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 08:43:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Biden DOE Investing $1.7 Billion to Support Auto Workers and EV Production</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/11/biden-doe-investing-1-7-billion-to-support-auto-workers-and-ev-production.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>"Building a clean energy economy can and should be a win-win for union autoworkers and automakers," President Biden said in a statement sent to PoliticusUSA. "This investment will create thousands of good-paying, union manufacturing jobs and retain even more."</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 10:00:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Illegal Aliens Aren’t the Only Ones Migrating. Americans are Too</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/10/illegal-aliens-arent-the-only-ones-migrating-americans-are-too/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>IRS data shows that American taxpayers are leaving sanctuary states for states that actually enforce the law. The negative impact of misguided sanctuary policies goes well beyond simply releasing dangerous criminals back onto the streets, it also impacts state economies and tax bases. To read the rest of the article click here The post Illegal Aliens Aren’t the Only Ones Migrating. Americans are Too appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:02:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pelosi Calls Out the New York Times for Making Up News</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/10/pelosi-calls-out-the-new-york-times-for-making-up-news.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Speaker Emerita Nancy Pelosi called out the New York Times for misrepresenting what she said about President Biden, “I don’t know what’s happened in New York Times that they make up news."</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 21:10:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Massachusetts Governor Maura Healey’s Charade at the Southern Border</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/02/massachusetts-governor-maura-healeys-charade-at-the-southern-border/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Things are pretty dire in the illegal alien sanctuary Bay State. As FAIR’s 2023 report showed, 393,000 illegal aliens and their U.S.-born children live in Massachusetts, costing taxpayers $2.9 billion annually for health care, education, criminal justice, and general welfare. To read the rest of the article click here The post Massachusetts Governor Maura Healey’s Charade at the Southern Border appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:51:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rep. Alexandria Ocasio Cortez’s Articles Of Impeachment Against Justices Alito And Thomas Are Devastating</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/10/rep-alexandria-ocasio-cortezs-articles-of-impeachment-against-justices-alito-and-thomas-are-devastating.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>The articles of impeachment introduced by Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez will be voted on in the House, and they are devastating for Justices Alito and Thomas.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 20:03:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayorkas Lies to the American People During Arizona Visit</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/01/mayorkas-lies-to-the-american-people-during-arizona-visit/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Recently impeached Department of Homeland Security Secretary Alejandro Mayorkas visited Tucson, Arizona, and attempted to sell President Biden’s recent executive action as having worked to reduce the number of illegal crossings at the southern border. To read the rest of the article click here The post Mayorkas Lies to the American People During Arizona Visit appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 19:31:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Report Finds Biden Debate Crisis Is A Bogus Media Creation</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/10/debate-crissi-report-bogus.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>A new multi-university research project found that the debate did nothing to change voter preferences and that Biden is actually doing a better job of holding on to his supporters after the debate than Trump.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:57:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sanctuary Politicians Need to Stop Lying and Admit the Obvious</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/28/sanctuary-politicians-need-to-stop-lying-and-admit-the-obvious/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Sanctuary politicians are getting nervous, and understandably so. The public is outraged over the surge of high-profile crimes allegedly committed by illegal aliens including the recent murder of 12-year old Jocelyn Nungaray in Houston, the sexual assault of a 13-year-old girl in New York City, and the Maryland rape and murder of Rachel Morin, mother [...] The post Sanctuary Politicians Need to Stop Lying and Admit the Obvious appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 17:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Leads The US And Mexico Deal To Stop China From Evading Steel Tariffs</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/10/biden-leads-the-us-and-mexico-deal-to-stop-china-from-evading-steel-tariffs.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>The Biden administration announced that the United States and Mexico are working together to prevent China from flooding the steel and aluminum markets.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 14:00:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>White House Leaves Out Key Fact in Statements on Alleged Murders of Americans by Illegal Aliens</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/27/white-house-leaves-out-key-fact-in-statements-on-alleged-murders-of-americans-by-illegal-aliens/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Over the past two weeks, Americans have seen numerous stories about horrific crimes allegedly committed by illegal aliens. The White House commented on two cases but failed to mention a key fact. To read the rest of the article click here The post White House Leaves Out Key Fact in Statements on Alleged Murders of Americans by Illegal Aliens appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 15:22:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>