<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 13:56:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Trump Appears To Be Spending Most Of His Day In Court Asleep</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/20/trump-appears-to-be-spending-most-of-his-day-in-court-asleep.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Donald Trump can't seem to stay awake during his trial, and multiple reporters have noted that Trump is asleep or has his eyes closed for long periods of time.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 18:45:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In Spite of Border Crisis Calls for Amnesty Continue</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/16/in-spite-of-border-crisis-calls-for-amnesty-continue/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>The border crisis and mass illegal migration have exceeded all historical records. In Fiscal Year 2023, over 3.2 million illegal aliens were encountered nationwide, and we are on track to exceed even that unprecedented annual figure this fiscal year. To read the rest of the article click here The post In Spite of Border Crisis Calls for Amnesty Continue appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 19:23:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Terrible News For Trump As Closing Arguments Delayed In Criminal Trial</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/20/terrible-news-for-trump-as-closing-arguments-delayed-in-criminal-trial.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Judge Merchan brought the parties into court early on Monday, and said that due to issues that have come up over the weekend closing arguments at the Trump criminal trial won't happen until after Memorial Day.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 14:06:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Border County Sees 5,000 Percent Increase in Prosecutions During Biden’s Border Crisis</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/16/border-county-sees-5000-percent-increase-in-prosecutions-during-bidens-border-crisis/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>In Kinney County, Texas, a stark example of the direct consequences of open-borders policies under the Biden administration is unfolding. To read the rest of the article click here The post Border County Sees 5,000 Percent Increase in Prosecutions During Biden’s Border Crisis appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 17:41:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Marco Rubio Melts Down As His Election Lies Get Debunked On Meet The Press</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/19/marco-rubio-melts-down-as-his-election-lies-get-debunked-on-meet-the-press.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Sen. Marco Rubio (R-FL) refused to commit to accepting the 2024 election results then melted down as NBC's Kristen Welker debunked his election lies.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 17:22:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This May Be the Most Far-Flung Argument Yet to Reward Illegal Aliens</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/15/this-may-be-the-most-far-flung-argument-yet-to-reward-illegal-aliens/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Illegal aliens can’t legally drive in Missouri. Legislation passed in 2009 specifies that applicants for driver’s licenses must be U.S. citizens, or have proof of lawful presence in the United States. Admirably, Missouri is holding fast against trends to the contrary. To read the rest of the article click here The post This May Be the Most Far-Flung Argument Yet to Reward Illegal Aliens appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 14:15:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rep. Jasmine Crockett Outs Marjorie Taylor Greene’s Racism On National TV</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/19/rep-jasmine-crockett-outs-marjorie-taylor-greenes-racism-on-national-tv.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Rep. Jasmine Crockett (D-TX) explained on CNN why Marjorie Taylor Greene's attack on her was racist and the racism of MAGA.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 15:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>UK Study Shows Mass Immigration Will NOT Help the Economy</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/14/uk-study-shows-mass-immigration-will-not-help-the-economy/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Supporters of open borders often claim there will be major economic gains from relaxed border and immigration policies. To read the rest of the article click here The post UK Study Shows Mass Immigration Will NOT Help the Economy appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:30:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SNL Takes Down Trump For Being Afraid To Testify</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/19/snl-trump-cold-open.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>SNL perfectly captured Trump's courthouse press conferences and why he hates court and is afraid to testify.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 06:04:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Do We Want? Everything! Migrants Send List of Demands to Denver City Officials</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/14/what-do-we-want-everything-migrants-send-list-of-demands-to-denver-city-officials/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>As the surge of illegal immigration began to unfold at the start of the Biden administration, the city of Denver, Colorado – or at least the politicians who run the city and state – decided that what most Americans see as a crisis would be a great opportunity for them to virtue signal. To read [...] The post What Do We Want? Everything! Migrants Send List of Demands to Denver City Officials appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 15:26:54 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>