<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 18:06:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The Jury Delivers A Devastating Message To Convicted Felon Donald Trump</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/30/the-jury-delivers-a-devastating-message-to-convicted-felon-donald-trump.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>By finding Trump guilty on all 34 felony counts, the jury sent a message to the nation and Donald Trump. Now it will be up to America to decide if they want a felon president.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 22:23:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Illegal Aliens Call Lyft Ride After Getting Sick of Waiting for Border Patrol to Pick them Up</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/30/illegal-aliens-call-lyft-ride-after-getting-sick-of-waiting-for-border-patrol-to-pick-them-up/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>In yet another alarming display of the Biden administration’s failure to secure our southern border, Fox News’s Bill Melugin caught a group of Colombian illegal aliens using a ride-hailing app, To read the rest of the article click here The post Illegal Aliens Call Lyft Ride After Getting Sick of Waiting for Border Patrol to Pick them Up appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 18:58:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump’s Mind Seems To Be Breaking As He Awaits Verdict</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/30/trumps-mind-seems-to-breaking-as-he-awaits-verdict.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Trump is both filled with rage and appears to be breaking as he posts on social media while awaiting the verdict at his criminal trial.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 19:15:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Two Illegal Aliens Attempt to Breach U.S. Military Base, Dangerous Trend Continues Under Biden</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/29/two-illegal-aliens-attempt-to-breach-u-s-military-base-dangerous-trend-continues-under-biden/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Two Jordanian illegal aliens are in ICE custody awaiting deportation proceedings after attempting to breach the Marine Corps base in Quantico, Virginia, earlier this month. To read the rest of the article click here The post Two Illegal Aliens Attempt to Breach U.S. Military Base, Dangerous Trend Continues Under Biden appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 21:01:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Poll Confirms That A Guilty Verdict Could Doom Trump</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/30/new-poll-confirms-that-a-guilty-verdict-could-doom-trump.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>The mainstream press is ignoring the part of the new NPR/PBS Newshour/Marist poll that shows that a guilty verdict would make 17% of voters less likely to vote for Trump.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 18:09:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Déjà Vu: Two Middle Eastern Illegal Aliens Attempt to Enter Secure Virginia Military Facility in a Box Truck</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/29/deja-vu-two-middle-eastern-illegal-aliens-attempt-to-enter-secure-virginia-military-facility-in-a-box-truck/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>On May 3, two Jordanian illegal aliens were apprehended as they attempted to enter the Marine Corps base in Quantico, Virginia, in a box truck. The two were posing as Amazon delivery drivers, although Amazon denies that they were employed by the company. To read the rest of the article click here The post Déjà Vu: Two Middle Eastern Illegal Aliens Attempt to Enter Secure Virginia Military Facility in a Box Truck appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 13:34:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Former Apprentice Producer Confirms Racist Trump Tapes</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/30/former-apprentice-producer-confirms-racist-trump-tapes.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>A former producer on The Apprentice has confirmed that there were tapes of Trump making racist and sexist comments on the NBC show.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 14:02:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tunisia Cracks Down on Africans Migrants: Outsourcing Border Security</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/28/tunisia-cracks-down-on-africans-migrants-outsourcing-border-security/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Tunisia is fighting a battle with illegal immigrants from other parts of Africa trying to use the country as a launch pad towards their ultimate destination, Europe. The North African country is close to the Italian coast and even closer to Italy’s smaller outlying islands. To read the rest of the article click here The post Tunisia Cracks Down on Africans Migrants: Outsourcing Border Security appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 20:02:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Senate Democrats Request DOJ Criminal Investigation Into The Oil Industry</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/30/senate-democrats-request-doj-investigation-into-the-oil-industry-for-price-fixing.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Twenty-three Senate Democrats have written to Attorney General Merrick Garland to request that the DOJ investigate the oil industry for violating the Sherman Antitrust Act.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 13:23:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Britain’s Migrant Boat Headache</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/23/britains-migrant-boat-headache/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Britain continues to see waves of boats landing on its coast carrying illegal immigrants. The sight of dinghies being towed to shore and migrant men disembarking has become a regular sight. To read the rest of the article click here The post Britain’s Migrant Boat Headache appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 18:14:23 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>