<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 06:52:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Rachel Maddow Shatters The Big Lie That Business Supports Trump</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/24/rachel-maddow-business-trump.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Rachel Maddow busted the Trump campaign for creating the false perception that business is supporting Donald Trump.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 04:57:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Isn’t the Solution to Police Staffing Shortages</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/19/this-isnt-the-solution-to-police-staffing-shortages/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Law enforcement agencies across the nation are suffering unprecedented staffing shortages so dire, that in some instances, entire departments have been forced to close. To read the rest of the article click here The post This Isn’t the Solution to Police Staffing Shortages appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 20:40:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Just Dropped A Massive Veto Hammer On House Republicans</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/24/biden-just-dropped-a-massive-veto-hammer-on-house-republicans.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>House Republicans will be voting on the bill to fund Homeland Security, but Biden has threatened to veto it because it violates the deal that he and Republicans agreed to on funding.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 23:56:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Administration Quietly Closes More than 350,000 Asylum Cases</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/19/biden-administration-quietly-closes-more-than-350000-asylum-cases/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Recent reports reveal that the Biden administration covertly closed over 350,000 asylum cases of illegal aliens since 2022, even as it attempts to convince the American public that it is cracking down on illegal immigration. To read the rest of the article click here The post Biden Administration Quietly Closes More than 350,000 Asylum Cases appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 19:12:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Republican Nightmare Grows As Abortion Is Top Motivating Voter Issue</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/24/republican-nightmare-grows-as-abortion-is-top-motivating-voter-issue.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>New polling reveals that abortion is the top motivating issue for voters in 67 battleground House districts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 23:19:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Illegal Alien Arrested in Brutal Rape and Murder of Mom of Five</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/18/illegal-alien-arrested-in-brutal-rape-and-murder-of-mom-of-five/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>The Ma &amp; Pa Trail in Bel Air, Maryland, is 1,800 miles from the southern border. It’s where Rachel Morin, a mom of five, was raped and murdered while on a hike. To read the rest of the article click here The post Illegal Alien Arrested in Brutal Rape and Murder of Mom of Five appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 14:35:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Adopts Loser Strategy Of Attacking CNN Moderators Before Debate</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/24/trump-loser-strategy-debate.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Donald Trump and his supporters are attacking CNN's Jake Tapper and Dana Bash before the presidential debate. It is a bad strategy that already failed in 2020.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 20:24:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>European Election Results Show Tide Turning in Germany</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/18/european-election-results-show-tide-turning-in-germany/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>European Elections held across the continent in early June have shown some remarkable victories for parties advocating immigration control. With the possible exception of France, nowhere were the results more dramatic than in Germany. To read the rest of the article click here The post European Election Results Show Tide Turning in Germany appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 14:29:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>These Are The 6 States That Biden Is Targeting To Win Reelection</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/24/these-are-the-6-states-that-biden-is-targeting-to-win-reelection.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>The Biden campaign believes that six swing states will decide the 2024 presidential election, and it is targeting each one for victory this fall.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 19:24:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is That REALLY a Homeless Shelter for Needy Americans or…Illegal Alien Housing?</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/13/is-that-really-a-homeless-shelter-for-needy-americans-orillegal-alien-housing/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Promoting open border and amnesty policies is increasingly tricky business for the left. After all, illegal immigration is a major issue for most voters, a concern that’s apparently deepening as shown by a new CBS News poll revealing that 62 percent of Americans support, “in principle, a new government program to deport all undocumented immigrants [...] The post Is That REALLY a Homeless Shelter for Needy Americans or…Illegal Alien Housing? appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 14:49:48 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>