<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 11:35:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Oklahoma Knows You Can’t Manage What You Don’t Measure</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/08/07/oklahoma-knows-you-cant-manage-what-you-dont-measure/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent2.png</image_url><description>Oklahoma’s Superintendent of the State Department of Education is asking Oklahoma school districts to get a handle on the number of illegal aliens occupying classrooms statewide “to find accurate and effective counting of the cost and burden that illegal immigration has.” To read the rest of the article click here The post Oklahoma Knows You Can’t Manage What You Don’t Measure appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:04:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Everything was going Kamala Harris’ way. Then came the market sell-off.</title><link>https://www.politico.com/news/2024/08/06/market-sell-off-democrats-harris-00172740</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent2.png</image_url><description>"We cannot win if people think we’re headed into a recession," one Democratic National Committee member said.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Massachusetts Migrant Housing Costs: Out of Orbit and Hard to Grasp</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/08/01/massachusetts-migrant-housing-costs-out-of-orbit-and-hard-to-grasp/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent.png</image_url><description>Beyond a certain threshold, numbers become abstract and lose their meaningful context. A quick view of the national debt clock which adds $100,000 of national debt every two-and-a-half seconds to America’s current obligations of $35 trillion is virtually impossible to comprehend. To read the rest of the article click here The post Massachusetts Migrant Housing Costs: Out of Orbit and Hard to Grasp appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 17:55:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JD Vance at RNC: Trump is the working class' 'last, best hope'</title><link>https://www.politico.com/video/2024/07/18/j-d-vance-at-rnc-trump-is-the-working-class-last-best-hope-1369100</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent2.png</image_url><description></description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 05:28:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>House Passes Resolution Condemning the Biden-Harris Administration’s Failure to Secure the Border</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/08/01/house-passes-resolution-condemning-the-biden-harris-administrations-failure-to-secure-the-border/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent2.png</image_url><description>On July 25, the House of Representatives passed H. Res. 1371, condemning President Biden and Vice President Kamala Harris’ failure to secure the border. The resolution passed the same week that President Biden announced he would not seek a second term. To read the rest of the article click here The post House Passes Resolution Condemning the Biden-Harris Administration’s Failure to Secure the Border appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 17:33:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>US added 206,000 jobs in June in a sign of continued economic strength</title><link>https://www.politico.com/news/2024/07/05/us-added-206-000-jobs-in-june-in-a-sign-of-continued-economic-strength-00166606</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent.png</image_url><description>Though hiring remains strong, voters blame President Joe Biden for persistent high prices.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 14:02:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Disastrous Nexus of Biden-Harris Policies:  The Afghan Parole Program and Prohibition on Issuing Notices to Appear</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/31/a-disastrous-nexus-of-biden-harris-policies-the-afghan-parole-program-and-prohibition-on-issuing-notices-to-appear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent.png</image_url><description>On this date three years ago – July 31, 2021 – the first group of Afghan nationals arrived in the United States after the President Biden’s disastrous withdrawal of U.S. troops from the country. To read the rest of the article click here The post A Disastrous Nexus of Biden-Harris Policies: The Afghan Parole Program and Prohibition on Issuing Notices to Appear appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 16:02:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dems to Biden: You must out-populist Trump at the debate</title><link>https://www.politico.com/news/2024/06/26/biden-debate-anti-corporate-billionaires-00165178</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent2.png</image_url><description>The president has a compelling antimonopoly record. But he doesn’t always lean into it. And voters don’t really know of it. The debate could change that.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:48:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Human Smuggler Who Facilitated Illegal Entry of Thousands of Aliens Indicted</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/29/human-smuggler-who-facilitated-illegal-entry-of-thousands-of-aliens-indicted/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent3.png</image_url><description>On July 18, reports surfaced that Abdul Karim Conteh, a national from Sierra Leone, had been indicted and sanctioned in the United States and arrested in Tijuana, Mexico. Conteh ran a smuggling organization that facilitated the transport of thousands of illegal aliens to the United States through Mexico, including many from terrorism hot spots. To [...] The post Human Smuggler Who Facilitated Illegal Entry of Thousands of Aliens Indicted appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 20:17:26 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>