<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 07:26:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Trump Is Melting Down After Tim Walz Joined The Ticket</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/08/06/trump-is-melting-down-after-tim-walz-joined-the-ticket.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>Forget the Republican spin. Donald Trump responded to Tim Walz joining the ticket by trying to get Joe Biden back into the race.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 21:51:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Massachusetts Migrant Housing Costs: Out of Orbit and Hard to Grasp</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/08/01/massachusetts-migrant-housing-costs-out-of-orbit-and-hard-to-grasp/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Beyond a certain threshold, numbers become abstract and lose their meaningful context. A quick view of the national debt clock which adds $100,000 of national debt every two-and-a-half seconds to America’s current obligations of $35 trillion is virtually impossible to comprehend. To read the rest of the article click here The post Massachusetts Migrant Housing Costs: Out of Orbit and Hard to Grasp appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 17:55:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Is Going To Be Terrified As Thousands Wait In The Rain To Get Into Harris-Walz Rally</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/08/06/harris-walz-philadelphia-rally-trump.html</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f4cd.png</image_url><description>The line stretches for more than six city blocks as thousands wait for entry into the first Harris-Walz rally in Philadelphia.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 21:11:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>House Passes Resolution Condemning the Biden-Harris Administration’s Failure to Secure the Border</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/08/01/house-passes-resolution-condemning-the-biden-harris-administrations-failure-to-secure-the-border/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>On July 25, the House of Representatives passed H. Res. 1371, condemning President Biden and Vice President Kamala Harris’ failure to secure the border. The resolution passed the same week that President Biden announced he would not seek a second term. To read the rest of the article click here The post House Passes Resolution Condemning the Biden-Harris Administration’s Failure to Secure the Border appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 17:33:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Congressman Trying To Impeach Kamala Harris Was Searched By The FBI</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/08/06/the-congressman-trying-to-impeach-kamala-harris-was-searched-by-the-fbi.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>Rep. Andy Ogles (R-TN) is trying to impeach Vice President Kamala Harris was searched by the FBI in relation to a fraudulent campaign finance report.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:34:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Disastrous Nexus of Biden-Harris Policies:  The Afghan Parole Program and Prohibition on Issuing Notices to Appear</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/31/a-disastrous-nexus-of-biden-harris-policies-the-afghan-parole-program-and-prohibition-on-issuing-notices-to-appear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>On this date three years ago – July 31, 2021 – the first group of Afghan nationals arrived in the United States after the President Biden’s disastrous withdrawal of U.S. troops from the country. To read the rest of the article click here The post A Disastrous Nexus of Biden-Harris Policies: The Afghan Parole Program and Prohibition on Issuing Notices to Appear appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 16:02:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fox News Explains Why Trump Should Fear Tim Walz</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/08/06/fox-news-explains-why-trump-should-fear-tim-walz.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Even Fox News says that Tim Walz understands rural America in a way that Trump doesn't.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:02:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Human Smuggler Who Facilitated Illegal Entry of Thousands of Aliens Indicted</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/29/human-smuggler-who-facilitated-illegal-entry-of-thousands-of-aliens-indicted/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>On July 18, reports surfaced that Abdul Karim Conteh, a national from Sierra Leone, had been indicted and sanctioned in the United States and arrested in Tijuana, Mexico. Conteh ran a smuggling organization that facilitated the transport of thousands of illegal aliens to the United States through Mexico, including many from terrorism hot spots. To [...] The post Human Smuggler Who Facilitated Illegal Entry of Thousands of Aliens Indicted appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 20:17:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Republicans Should Be Very Worried As Harris-Walz Release Barnburner Video</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/08/06/republicans-should-be-very-worried-as-harris-walz-release-barnburner-video.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>The new Harris-Walz ticket released its first campaign video and it should have Trump and the Republicans worried.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:45:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Did Biden Really Say Our Borders are More Secure than When He Took Office?</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/26/did-biden-really-say-our-borders-are-more-secure-than-when-he-took-office/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Every politician is prone to exaggerating their accomplishments in an attempt to define their legacy in the most positive possible terms. President Biden is certainly no exception. In his address to the nation on Wednesday evening, after he announced his decision to abandon his 2024 reelection bid, the president ticked off a long list of [...] The post Did Biden Really Say Our Borders are More Secure than When He Took Office? appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 21:24:59 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>