<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 06:54:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Rally To Protest Trump Felony Conviction Flops</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/02/rally-to-protest-trump-felony-conviction-flops.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>A seemingly small crowd assembled on Staten Island, NY to protest the felony conviction of Donald Trump.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 23:30:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Massachusetts Response to its Migrant Crisis: Offer Even More Benefits</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/31/massachusetts-response-to-its-migrant-crisis-offer-even-more-benefits/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>If any state in America proves the axiom that “things in motion stay in motion” it’s Massachusetts. What else but perpetual motion physics can explain the logic behind the Bay State’s non-stop granting of benefits to illegal aliens? To read the rest of the article click here The post Massachusetts Response to its Migrant Crisis: Offer Even More Benefits appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 21:12:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Embarrasses Himself By Claiming Rising Seas Create Beachfront Property</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/02/trump-embarrasses-himself-by-claiming-rising-seas-create-beachfront-property.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Trump claimed on Sunday that he supports climate change because rising seas create more beachfront property.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 22:55:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Illegal Aliens Call Lyft Ride After Getting Sick of Waiting for Border Patrol to Pick them Up</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/30/illegal-aliens-call-lyft-ride-after-getting-sick-of-waiting-for-border-patrol-to-pick-them-up/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>In yet another alarming display of the Biden administration’s failure to secure our southern border, Fox News’s Bill Melugin caught a group of Colombian illegal aliens using a ride-hailing app, To read the rest of the article click here The post Illegal Aliens Call Lyft Ride After Getting Sick of Waiting for Border Patrol to Pick them Up appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 18:58:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Video Catches Trump Waving To Imaginary Supporters</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/02/video-catches-trump-waving-to-imaginary-supporters.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>A video of Trump leaving Trump Tower catches him waving to a crowd of supporters that doesn't exist as he exits the building.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 20:49:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Two Illegal Aliens Attempt to Breach U.S. Military Base, Dangerous Trend Continues Under Biden</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/29/two-illegal-aliens-attempt-to-breach-u-s-military-base-dangerous-trend-continues-under-biden/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Two Jordanian illegal aliens are in ICE custody awaiting deportation proceedings after attempting to breach the Marine Corps base in Quantico, Virginia, earlier this month. To read the rest of the article click here The post Two Illegal Aliens Attempt to Breach U.S. Military Base, Dangerous Trend Continues Under Biden appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 21:01:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>James Comey Says Locking Up Trump Is Doable</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/02/james-comey-trump-lock-up.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Former FBI Director James Comey explained how easily doable it would be to lock up Donald Trump if he were sentenced to jail time.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 19:58:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Déjà Vu: Two Middle Eastern Illegal Aliens Attempt to Enter Secure Virginia Military Facility in a Box Truck</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/29/deja-vu-two-middle-eastern-illegal-aliens-attempt-to-enter-secure-virginia-military-facility-in-a-box-truck/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>On May 3, two Jordanian illegal aliens were apprehended as they attempted to enter the Marine Corps base in Quantico, Virginia, in a box truck. The two were posing as Amazon delivery drivers, although Amazon denies that they were employed by the company. To read the rest of the article click here The post Déjà Vu: Two Middle Eastern Illegal Aliens Attempt to Enter Secure Virginia Military Facility in a Box Truck appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 13:34:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Threatens America If He’s Sentenced To House Arrest</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/02/trump-threatens-america-if-hes-sentenced-to-house-arrest.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Trump claimed in an interview on Fox that locking him up, even with house arrest, would be a breaking point for the American people.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 19:11:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tunisia Cracks Down on Africans Migrants: Outsourcing Border Security</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/28/tunisia-cracks-down-on-africans-migrants-outsourcing-border-security/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Tunisia is fighting a battle with illegal immigrants from other parts of Africa trying to use the country as a launch pad towards their ultimate destination, Europe. The North African country is close to the Italian coast and even closer to Italy’s smaller outlying islands. To read the rest of the article click here The post Tunisia Cracks Down on Africans Migrants: Outsourcing Border Security appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 20:02:35 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>