<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 00:44:09 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Jim Jordan Humiliates Himself Trying To Get Alvin Bragg To Testify</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/31/jim-jordan-alvin-bragg-testify.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>House Judiciary Committee Chair Jim Jordan (R-OH) has embarrassed himself by trying to get Alvin Bragg to testify before his Weaponization of Government Committee.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 00:06:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Massachusetts Response to its Migrant Crisis: Offer Even More Benefits</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/31/massachusetts-response-to-its-migrant-crisis-offer-even-more-benefits/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>If any state in America proves the axiom that “things in motion stay in motion” it’s Massachusetts. What else but perpetual motion physics can explain the logic behind the Bay State’s non-stop granting of benefits to illegal aliens? To read the rest of the article click here The post Massachusetts Response to its Migrant Crisis: Offer Even More Benefits appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 21:12:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Senate Republicans Throw A Tantrum After Trump Conviction</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/31/senate-republicans-trump-conviction.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Eight Republican Senators, including J.D. Vance, Mike Lee, and Tommy Tuberville, vowed not to cooperate with Democrats on anything not related to national security or safety.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 21:51:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Illegal Aliens Call Lyft Ride After Getting Sick of Waiting for Border Patrol to Pick them Up</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/30/illegal-aliens-call-lyft-ride-after-getting-sick-of-waiting-for-border-patrol-to-pick-them-up/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>In yet another alarming display of the Biden administration’s failure to secure our southern border, Fox News’s Bill Melugin caught a group of Colombian illegal aliens using a ride-hailing app, To read the rest of the article click here The post Illegal Aliens Call Lyft Ride After Getting Sick of Waiting for Border Patrol to Pick them Up appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 18:58:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Is What Trump Really Looked Like At His Press Conference</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/31/this-is-what-trump-really-looked-like-at-his-press-conference.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Trump looked rough as a picture from Trump Tower captured what he really looked like during his post-conviction press conference.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 19:40:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Two Illegal Aliens Attempt to Breach U.S. Military Base, Dangerous Trend Continues Under Biden</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/29/two-illegal-aliens-attempt-to-breach-u-s-military-base-dangerous-trend-continues-under-biden/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Two Jordanian illegal aliens are in ICE custody awaiting deportation proceedings after attempting to breach the Marine Corps base in Quantico, Virginia, earlier this month. To read the rest of the article click here The post Two Illegal Aliens Attempt to Breach U.S. Military Base, Dangerous Trend Continues Under Biden appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 21:01:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Legal Expert Calls Out Trump’s Lies About His Failed Defense</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/31/legal-expert-calls-out-trumps-lies-about-his-failed-defense.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Katie Phang, host of MSNBC's The Katie Phang show, called Trump's excuses out, writing that he could have testified and that he and his team could have chosen to put on the elections expert, but chose not to.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 19:04:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Déjà Vu: Two Middle Eastern Illegal Aliens Attempt to Enter Secure Virginia Military Facility in a Box Truck</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/29/deja-vu-two-middle-eastern-illegal-aliens-attempt-to-enter-secure-virginia-military-facility-in-a-box-truck/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>On May 3, two Jordanian illegal aliens were apprehended as they attempted to enter the Marine Corps base in Quantico, Virginia, in a box truck. The two were posing as Amazon delivery drivers, although Amazon denies that they were employed by the company. To read the rest of the article click here The post Déjà Vu: Two Middle Eastern Illegal Aliens Attempt to Enter Secure Virginia Military Facility in a Box Truck appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 13:34:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CNN Highlights Trump’s Mental Decline While Dumping His Press Conference</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/31/cnn-dump-trump-press-conference.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>CNN anchors referred to Trump's press conference as rant without a teleprompter and referred to its "disjointed" presentation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 17:00:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tunisia Cracks Down on Africans Migrants: Outsourcing Border Security</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/28/tunisia-cracks-down-on-africans-migrants-outsourcing-border-security/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Tunisia is fighting a battle with illegal immigrants from other parts of Africa trying to use the country as a launch pad towards their ultimate destination, Europe. The North African country is close to the Italian coast and even closer to Italy’s smaller outlying islands. To read the rest of the article click here The post Tunisia Cracks Down on Africans Migrants: Outsourcing Border Security appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 20:02:35 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>