<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:16:41 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Biden Is Even Taking Steps To Make Americans Safer From Flooding</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/10/biden-is-even-taking-steps-to-make-americans-safer-from-flooding.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>The Biden administration is finalizing a new rule that will reduce the risk of flood impacts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 10:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Flashback: When Harry Reid was Right about Immigration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/02/flashback-when-harry-reid-was-right-about-immigration/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Just shy of 30 years ago, FAIR found what now seems to be an unlikely ally in The Los Angeles Times opinion page. On August 10, 1994, the late Sen. Harry Reid (D-Nevada) wrote a fantastic op-ed promoting his bill to slash legal immigration by two thirds, from approximately 1 million to 325,000. To read [...] The post Flashback: When Harry Reid was Right about Immigration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 19:33:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Forceful Biden Shows The World And NATO Allies He Can Handle The Job</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/09/biden-nato-ukraine.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>President Biden forcefully addressed NATO allies and gave a vigorous defense and pledge of support for Ukraine.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 23:43:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Massachusetts Governor Maura Healy’s Charade at the Southern Border</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/02/massachusetts-governor-maura-healys-charade-at-the-southern-border/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Things are pretty dire in the illegal alien sanctuary Bay State. As FAIR’s 2023 report showed, 393,000 illegal aliens and their U.S.-born children live in Massachusetts, costing taxpayers $2.9 billion annually for health care, education, criminal justice, and general welfare. To read the rest of the article click here The post Massachusetts Governor Maura Healy’s Charade at the Southern Border appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:51:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rep. Ted Lieu Points To The Epstein Files And Urges Trump To Drop Out</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/09/rep-ted-lieu-points-to-the-epstein-files-and-urges-trump-to-drop-out.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Rep. Ted Lieu (D-CA) told the media that Trump should drop out of the presidential race and referenced the disturbing revelations in the Epstein files.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 20:29:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayorkas Lies to the American People During Arizona Visit</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/01/mayorkas-lies-to-the-american-people-during-arizona-visit/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Recently impeached Department of Homeland Security Secretary Alejandro Mayorkas visited Tucson, Arizona, and attempted to sell President Biden’s recent executive action as having worked to reduce the number of illegal crossings at the southern border. To read the rest of the article click here The post Mayorkas Lies to the American People During Arizona Visit appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 19:31:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Justice Department Busts Russian Disinformation Operation Targeting US</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/09/doj-busts-russian-disinformation.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>The Justice Department announced that they have disrupted a Russian government run disinformation operation targeting the United States.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 19:59:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sanctuary Politicians Need to Stop Lying and Admit the Obvious</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/28/sanctuary-politicians-need-to-stop-lying-and-admit-the-obvious/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Sanctuary politicians are getting nervous, and understandably so. The public is outraged over the surge of high-profile crimes allegedly committed by illegal aliens including the recent murder of 12-year old Jocelyn Nungaray in Houston, the sexual assault of a 13-year-old girl in New York City, and the Maryland rape and murder of Rachel Morin, mother [...] The post Sanctuary Politicians Need to Stop Lying and Admit the Obvious appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 17:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Vows To “Attack, Attack, Attack” Trump</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/09/biden-vows-to-attack-attack-attack-trump.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>President Biden said that it is time to turn attention back to Trump and his agenda, and his plan is to "attack, attack, attack" the ex-president.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 19:18:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>White House Leaves Out Key Fact in Statements on Alleged Murders of Americans by Illegal Aliens</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/27/white-house-leaves-out-key-fact-in-statements-on-alleged-murders-of-americans-by-illegal-aliens/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Over the past two weeks, Americans have seen numerous stories about horrific crimes allegedly committed by illegal aliens. The White House commented on two cases but failed to mention a key fact. To read the rest of the article click here The post White House Leaves Out Key Fact in Statements on Alleged Murders of Americans by Illegal Aliens appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 15:22:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>