<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 14:47:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Jamie Raskin Shows Republicans What Real Respect For The Law Looks Like</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/11/jamie-raskin-shows-republicans-what-real-respect-for-the-law-looks-like.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Rep. Jamie Raskin (D-MD) pointed out that he hasn't heard a single Democrat attack the courts or cry fraud after the Hunter Biden verdict.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 19:02:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gun-Wielding Illegal Alien Allegedly Shoots Two NYPD Officers in Latest Migrant Crime Incident</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/05/gun-wielding-illegal-alien-allegedly-shoots-two-nypd-officers-in-latest-migrant-crime-incident/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>In the early hours of June 3, 2024, NYPD officers Christopher Abreu and Richard Yarusso were investigating a robbery when they encountered 19-year-old Bernardo Castro Mata, an illegal alien from Venezuela, driving a motorized scooter with no plates the wrong way down a street. To read the rest of the article click here The post Gun-Wielding Illegal Alien Allegedly Shoots Two NYPD Officers in Latest Migrant Crime Incident appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 18:21:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Puts America First In Touching Statement On Hunter Biden Conviction</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/11/biden-puts-america-first-in-touching-statement-on-hunter-biden-conviction.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>President Biden issued a touching statement about being a father and supporting his son after Hunter Biden's conviction.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 17:30:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Europe May Face a Second Middle Eastern Migrant Crisis</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/05/europe-may-face-a-second-middle-eastern-migrant-crisis/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Europe may once again be about to receive mass waves of migrants from the Middle East, invoking memories of the 2015-2016 period, when then-German Chancellor Angela Merkel invited Syrians (and others) to come to Europe without limitation. To read the rest of the article click here The post Europe May Face a Second Middle Eastern Migrant Crisis appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 18:11:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump’s Lawfare Claims Destroyed By Hunter Biden Gun Conviction</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/11/trumps-lawfare-claims-destroyed-by-hunter-biden-gun-conviction.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>A jury has found Hunter Biden guilty on all three federal felony gun charges, which undermines Trump's claims that Biden is behind prosecutions of the former president.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 16:49:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Baltimore Has an Obvious Problem. The Fix is Fairly Obvious Too.</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/05/baltimore-has-an-obvious-problem-the-fix-is-fairly-obvious-too/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>“Baltimore County releases illegal immigrants charged with crimes despite federal requests,” declared a recent headline on the local FOX 45 news site. To read the rest of the article click here The post Baltimore Has an Obvious Problem. The Fix is Fairly Obvious Too. appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 14:28:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jon Stewart Takes Down Corporate America’s Fake Morality</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/11/jon-stewart-takes-down-corporate-americas-fake-morality.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Jon Stewart celebrated Pride Month by exposing the fake morality of corporate America on The Daily Show.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 05:43:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fairfax County, Virginia: Public Schools, Limited English Proficiency, and the Opportunity Cost of Mass Migration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/03/fairfax-county-virginia-public-schools-limited-english-proficiency-and-the-opportunity-cost-of-mass-migration/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>In economics, opportunity cost is defined as “the potential benefits that a business, an investor, or an individual consumer misses out on when choosing one alternative over another.” A dollar spent on A cannot be simultaneously spent on B. To read the rest of the article click here The post Fairfax County, Virginia: Public Schools, Limited English Proficiency, and the Opportunity Cost of Mass Migration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 21:36:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stephen Colbert Explains To Trump Supporters That They’re In A Cult</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/11/stephen-colbert-explains-to-trump-supporters-that-theyre-in-a-cult.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Stephen Colbert used Trump's Las Vegas rally to explain to the ex-president's supporters that they are in a cult.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 05:17:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Massachusetts Response to its Migrant Crisis: Offer Even More Benefits</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/31/massachusetts-response-to-its-migrant-crisis-offer-even-more-benefits/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>If any state in America proves the axiom that “things in motion stay in motion” it’s Massachusetts. What else but perpetual motion physics can explain the logic behind the Bay State’s non-stop granting of benefits to illegal aliens? To read the rest of the article click here The post Massachusetts Response to its Migrant Crisis: Offer Even More Benefits appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 21:12:58 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>