<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:50:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Pecker Testifies that Donald Trump Had Knowledge of the Catch and Kill Contract with Karen McDougal</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/04/25/pecker-testifies-that-donald-trump-had-knowledge-of-the-catch-and-kill-contract-with-karen-mcdougal.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/2019-02-08T163118Z_1_LYNXNPEF1717H_RTROPTP_4_PEOPLE-BEZOS-e1713719404563.jpg</image_url><description>David Pecker testified that he believes Donald Trump also had knowledge of the catch and kill contract for the former Playboy model Karen McDougal.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:22:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Illegal Aliens Flown to Martha’s Vineyard Classified as Victims and Given Benefits</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/24/illegal-aliens-flown-to-marthas-vineyard-classified-as-victims-and-given-benefits/</link><description>Some of the illegal aliens that were flown from Florida to Martha’s Vineyard by Governor DeSantis in 2022 now have safe harbor from deportation and employment authorization documents allowing them to stay and work in the United States. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Illegal Aliens Flown to Martha’s Vineyard Classified as Victims and Given Benefits appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:53:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Supreme Court Immunity Hearing Has Been A Complete Disaster For Trump</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/04/25/supreme-court-immunity-hearing-has-been-a-complete-disaster-for-trump.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/2019-04-01T160956Z_3_LYNXNPEF3024K_RTROPTP_4_USA-COURT-EXECUTION-e1714056008730.jpg</image_url><description>Trump's lawyer made outlandish claims of broad and comprehensive presidential immunity that liberal and conservative justices seemed not to buy.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 15:42:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Clarity of Words is the Enemy of Mass Immigration Advocates</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/23/clarity-of-words-is-the-enemy-of-mass-immigration-advocates/</link><description>In his essay, “Politics and the English Language,” George Orwell observed that political language, by its very nature, is crafted to deceive and manipulate. He argued that politicians and propagandists deliberately twist language into falsehoods, so they become seemingly plausible statements hiding true agendas. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Clarity of Words is the Enemy of Mass Immigration Advocates appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 19:53:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>After Donald Trump Allegedly Violated Gag Order Four More Times Yet Another Contempt Order is Presented</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/04/25/after-donald-trump-allegedly-violated-gag-order-four-more-times-yet-another-contempt-order-is-presented.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/IMG_5188.jpg</image_url><description>After ex-president Donald Trump allegedly violated the court imposed gag order four times over the last three days, yet another order to show cause to hold him in contempt was presented on Thursday morning.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 15:16:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Italy and America: Shared Fight with Illegal Immigration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/23/italy-and-america-shared-fight-with-illegal-immigration/</link><description>Italy has struggled with mass migration, much of it composed of fraudulent “asylum seekers” from Africa. The key route of entry is from Africa by boat, with the island of Lampedusa close to the African mainland as the primary landing point. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Italy and America: Shared Fight with Illegal Immigration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 16:13:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden To Announce The Historic Creation Of 70,000 Good Paying Manufacturing Jobs</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/04/25/biden-to-announce-the-historic-creation-of-70000-good-paying-manufacturing-jobs.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/52833270905_0753b7fccc_b.jpg</image_url><description>President Biden will announce a historic cutting-edge chip manufacturing investment that will create 70,000 good-paying jobs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 10:00:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Migrants Refuse to Leave Soccer Field, Forcing High Schoolers to Cancel Game</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/23/migrants-refuse-to-leave-soccer-field-forcing-high-schoolers-to-cancel-game/</link><description>A disturbing scene unfolded at a public field in East Harlem, where a scheduled high school soccer game had to be canceled. About 30 migrants refused to leave the pitch, asserting their presence over the needs of high school soccer players. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Migrants Refuse to Leave Soccer Field, Forcing High Schoolers to Cancel Game appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 15:04:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RNC Election Integrity Counsel Indicted In Arizona Fake Elector Scheme</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/04/24/christina-bobb-indicted.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Bobb-Trump-Georgia.jpg</image_url><description>The RNC's Chief Election Integrity Counsel, Christina Bobb, has been indicted for her role in the Arizona fake elector scheme.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 02:39:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spain: Dangers of Mass Amnesty for Illegal Aliens</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/23/spain-dangers-of-mass-amnesty-for-illegal-aliens/</link><description>Going against historical examples of good judgment, Spain’s government has concluded that the solution to the problem of mass migration is simply to declare a mass amnesty for illegal immigrants. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Spain: Dangers of Mass Amnesty for Illegal Aliens appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 14:58:59 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>