<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 13:07:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>CNN’s Kasie Hunt Tosses A Trump Spokesperson Off Her Show For Smearing Debate Moderators</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/24/cnns-kasie-hunt-tosses-a-trump-spokesperson-off-her-show-for-smearing-debate-moderators.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>CNN's Kasie Hunt tried to get Trump campaign spokesperson Karoline Leavitt to stop attacking the debate moderators, but she wouldn't so Hunt cut off the interview and dumped her.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 16:49:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Isn’t the Solution to Police Staffing Shortages</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/19/this-isnt-the-solution-to-police-staffing-shortages/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Law enforcement agencies across the nation are suffering unprecedented staffing shortages so dire, that in some instances, entire departments have been forced to close. To read the rest of the article click here The post This Isn’t the Solution to Police Staffing Shortages appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 20:40:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elizabeth Warren Tells America Exactly What It Means If Trump Returns To The White House</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/23/elizabeth-warren-trump-white-house.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Sen. Elizabeth Warren (D-MA) made it clear what a Trump return to the White House would mean for women and families.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 21:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Administration Quietly Closes More than 350,000 Asylum Cases</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/19/biden-administration-quietly-closes-more-than-350000-asylum-cases/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Recent reports reveal that the Biden administration covertly closed over 350,000 asylum cases of illegal aliens since 2022, even as it attempts to convince the American public that it is cracking down on illegal immigration. To read the rest of the article click here The post Biden Administration Quietly Closes More than 350,000 Asylum Cases appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 19:12:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Campaign Brings The Pain To Convicted Felon Trump</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/23/biden-campaign-brings-the-pain-to-convicted-felon-trump.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Biden campaign co-chair Mitch Landrieu made it clear that the President will not be shying away from Trump's felony conviction at the debate.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 18:34:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Illegal Alien Arrested in Brutal Rape and Murder of Mom of Five</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/18/illegal-alien-arrested-in-brutal-rape-and-murder-of-mom-of-five/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>The Ma &amp; Pa Trail in Bel Air, Maryland, is 1,800 miles from the southern border. It’s where Rachel Morin, a mom of five, was raped and murdered while on a hike. To read the rest of the article click here The post Illegal Alien Arrested in Brutal Rape and Murder of Mom of Five appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 14:35:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sen. Chris Coons Turns The Tables On Fox News Over Law And Order</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/23/sen-chris-coons-turns-the-tables-on-fox-news-over-law-and-order.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Sen. Chris Coons (D-DE) was asked about Biden and law and order on Fox News Sunday, and he flipped the script on Trump and the GOP.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 17:40:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>European Election Results Show Tide Turning in Germany</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/18/european-election-results-show-tide-turning-in-germany/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>European Elections held across the continent in early June have shown some remarkable victories for parties advocating immigration control. With the possible exception of France, nowhere were the results more dramatic than in Germany. To read the rest of the article click here The post European Election Results Show Tide Turning in Germany appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 14:29:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump’s Former Drunk Doctor Rep. Ronny Jackson Wants Biden Drug Tested</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/23/ronny-jackson-biden-drug-test.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Rep. Ronny Jackson (R-TX) is demanding that President Biden be drug tested for performance enhancing drugs before and after the debate.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 16:58:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is That REALLY a Homeless Shelter for Needy Americans or…Illegal Alien Housing?</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/13/is-that-really-a-homeless-shelter-for-needy-americans-orillegal-alien-housing/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Promoting open border and amnesty policies is increasingly tricky business for the left. After all, illegal immigration is a major issue for most voters, a concern that’s apparently deepening as shown by a new CBS News poll revealing that 62 percent of Americans support, “in principle, a new government program to deport all undocumented immigrants [...] The post Is That REALLY a Homeless Shelter for Needy Americans or…Illegal Alien Housing? appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 14:49:48 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>