<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 01:04:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Colin Jost’s Message About His Grandfather, Biden, And Decency Will Define The Election</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/04/28/colin-jost-grandfather.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/jost-biden.jpg</image_url><description>Colin Jost delivered a powerful close at the White House Correspondents Dinner and his remarks about his grandfather, Biden, and decency may define the election.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 05:55:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>House Committee Aims to Stop Illegal Aliens from Slanting Congressional Apportionment</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/26/house-committee-aims-to-stop-illegal-aliens-from-slanting-congressional-apportionment/</link><description>The House Committee on Oversight and Accountability recently approved Congressmen Chuck Edwards’ (R-N.C.) and Warren Davidson’s (R-Ohio) H.R. 7109, the Equal Representation Act. To read the rest of the article click here
The post House Committee Aims to Stop Illegal Aliens from Slanting Congressional Apportionment appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 19:34:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Here Are Colin Jost’s Five Best Jokes At The White House Correspondents Dinner</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/04/27/here-are-colin-josts-five-best-jokes-at-the-white-house-correspondents-dinner.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/Colin-Jost-WHCD.jpg</image_url><description>Colin Jost brought the jokes, but he also closed with a touching and serious moment at the White House Correspondents Dinner.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 04:48:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Illegal Aliens Flown to Martha’s Vineyard Classified as Victims and Given Benefits</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/24/illegal-aliens-flown-to-marthas-vineyard-classified-as-victims-and-given-benefits/</link><description>Some of the illegal aliens that were flown from Florida to Martha’s Vineyard by Governor DeSantis in 2022 now have safe harbor from deportation and employment authorization documents allowing them to stay and work in the United States. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Illegal Aliens Flown to Martha’s Vineyard Classified as Victims and Given Benefits appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:53:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Won’t The Supreme Court Just Answer The Basic Question On Trump Immunity?</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/04/27/why-wont-the-supreme-court-just-answer-the-basic-question-on-trump-immunity.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/Screenshot-2024-04-27-at-12.48.50-PM.png</image_url><description>When it comes to the Supreme Court's questions regarding Donald J. Trump v. United States, they were supposed to answer the basic question of if Donald Trump had presidential immunity as he claims he does in the election interference trial in D.C.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 18:58:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Clarity of Words is the Enemy of Mass Immigration Advocates</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/23/clarity-of-words-is-the-enemy-of-mass-immigration-advocates/</link><description>In his essay, “Politics and the English Language,” George Orwell observed that political language, by its very nature, is crafted to deceive and manipulate. He argued that politicians and propagandists deliberately twist language into falsehoods, so they become seemingly plausible statements hiding true agendas. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Clarity of Words is the Enemy of Mass Immigration Advocates appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 19:53:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mar-a-Lago Storage Room Storing Highly Classified Docs Could be Opened with a Coat Hanger</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/04/27/mar-a-lago-storage-room-storing-highly-classified-docs-could-be-opened-with-a-coat-hanger.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-27-at-8.41.39-PM.jpg</image_url><description>Newly released exhibits reveal that the lock on the storage room in Mar-a-Lago where Trump kept highly classified documents was just a residential door lock that could be opened with a coat hanger.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 16:38:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Italy and America: Shared Fight with Illegal Immigration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/23/italy-and-america-shared-fight-with-illegal-immigration/</link><description>Italy has struggled with mass migration, much of it composed of fraudulent “asylum seekers” from Africa. The key route of entry is from Africa by boat, with the island of Lampedusa close to the African mainland as the primary landing point. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Italy and America: Shared Fight with Illegal Immigration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 16:13:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maine Vows To Counter If Trump Tries To Steal Nebraska Electoral College Vote</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/04/26/maine-vows-to-counter-if-trump-tries-to-steal-nebraska-electoral-college-vote.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/EC-map-2.jpg</image_url><description>The Maine House majority leader is vowing to counter any move by the Republican governor of Nebraska that would give Trump the state's lone split electoral college vote.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 00:05:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Migrants Refuse to Leave Soccer Field, Forcing High Schoolers to Cancel Game</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/23/migrants-refuse-to-leave-soccer-field-forcing-high-schoolers-to-cancel-game/</link><description>A disturbing scene unfolded at a public field in East Harlem, where a scheduled high school soccer game had to be canceled. About 30 migrants refused to leave the pitch, asserting their presence over the needs of high school soccer players. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Migrants Refuse to Leave Soccer Field, Forcing High Schoolers to Cancel Game appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 15:04:34 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>