<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 23:36:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>GOP In Disarray: Conservative Leaders Warn of Split in Trump Coalition Over Abortion</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/07/gop-in-disarray-conservative-leaders-warn-of-split-in-trump-coalition-over-abortion.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>While media hysterics hyping a few House Democrats' power grab try to divide the Left, conservative leaders are warning of a coming split in Donald Trump's coalition due to his stance on abortion.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 03:12:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Flashback: When Harry Reid was Right about Immigration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/02/flashback-when-harry-reid-was-right-about-immigration/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Just shy of 30 years ago, FAIR found what now seems to be an unlikely ally in The Los Angeles Times opinion page. On August 10, 1994, the late Sen. Harry Reid (D-Nevada) wrote a fantastic op-ed promoting his bill to slash legal immigration by two thirds, from approximately 1 million to 325,000. To read [...] The post Flashback: When Harry Reid was Right about Immigration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 19:33:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>4 More House Democrats Sabotage Themselves By Calling On Biden To Step Aside</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/07/4-more-house-democrats-sabotage-themselves-by-calling-on-biden-to-step-aside.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>The pathological mission of some House Democrats to cost their party a chance at the House majority accelerated as four more House Democrats said that Biden should step aside.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 22:31:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Massachusetts Governor Maura Healy’s Charade at the Southern Border</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/02/massachusetts-governor-maura-healys-charade-at-the-southern-border/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Things are pretty dire in the illegal alien sanctuary Bay State. As FAIR’s 2023 report showed, 393,000 illegal aliens and their U.S.-born children live in Massachusetts, costing taxpayers $2.9 billion annually for health care, education, criminal justice, and general welfare. To read the rest of the article click here The post Massachusetts Governor Maura Healy’s Charade at the Southern Border appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:51:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bernie Sanders Blasts The New York Times For Catering To Billionaires</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/07/bernie-sanders-blasts-the-new-york-times-for-catering-to-billionaires.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Sen. Bernie Sanders called out The New York Times for catering to the thoughts and feelings of billionaires while ignoring the American people.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 20:50:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayorkas Lies to the American People During Arizona Visit</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/01/mayorkas-lies-to-the-american-people-during-arizona-visit/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Recently impeached Department of Homeland Security Secretary Alejandro Mayorkas visited Tucson, Arizona, and attempted to sell President Biden’s recent executive action as having worked to reduce the number of illegal crossings at the southern border. To read the rest of the article click here The post Mayorkas Lies to the American People During Arizona Visit appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 19:31:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>J.D. Vance Breaks His Own Brain Trying To Claim Trump Is A Good Husband</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/07/j-d-vance-trump-mtp.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Sen. J.D. Vance's wants to be vice president so badly that he claimed Trump is a good husband, but even his brain wouldn't stand by that lie.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 18:08:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sanctuary Politicians Need to Stop Lying and Admit the Obvious</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/28/sanctuary-politicians-need-to-stop-lying-and-admit-the-obvious/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Sanctuary politicians are getting nervous, and understandably so. The public is outraged over the surge of high-profile crimes allegedly committed by illegal aliens including the recent murder of 12-year old Jocelyn Nungaray in Houston, the sexual assault of a 13-year-old girl in New York City, and the Maryland rape and murder of Rachel Morin, mother [...] The post Sanctuary Politicians Need to Stop Lying and Admit the Obvious appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 17:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kamala Harris Dropped An F-Bomb And Rallied Democrats Behind Biden</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/07/kamala-harris-f-bomb-biden.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Vice President Kamala Harris rallied Democratic governors around President Biden by reminding them that this election is about our "f-ing democracy."</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 16:31:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>White House Leaves Out Key Fact in Statements on Alleged Murders of Americans by Illegal Aliens</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/27/white-house-leaves-out-key-fact-in-statements-on-alleged-murders-of-americans-by-illegal-aliens/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Over the past two weeks, Americans have seen numerous stories about horrific crimes allegedly committed by illegal aliens. The White House commented on two cases but failed to mention a key fact. To read the rest of the article click here The post White House Leaves Out Key Fact in Statements on Alleged Murders of Americans by Illegal Aliens appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 15:22:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>