<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 06:35:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Biden Gets The Port Of Baltimore Fully Reopened Just 11 Weeks After Bridge Collapse</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/12/biden-port-of-baltimore-open.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>President Biden promised to put the full weight of the federal government behind getting the Port of Baltimore reopened after the Francis Scott Key Bridge collapsed, and just 11 weeks later, the port is fully reopened.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 10:00:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>House Committee Hears Testimony on Effects of the Border Crisis in North Dakota</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/11/house-committee-hears-testimony-on-effects-of-the-border-crisis-in-north-dakota/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>The House Judiciary Subcommittee on Immigration Integrity, Security, and Enforcement, recently held a field hearing to discuss the effects of the border crisis in North Dakota. To read the rest of the article click here The post House Committee Hears Testimony on Effects of the Border Crisis in North Dakota appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 19:51:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Convicted Felon Trump Admits That He Had An Illegal Gun</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/11/convicted-felon-trump-admits-that-he-had-an-illegal-gun.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Donald Trump admitted during an interview with a probation officer that he illegally had a gun in Florida in violation of federal and state laws.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 23:27:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gun-Wielding Illegal Alien Allegedly Shoots Two NYPD Officers in Latest Migrant Crime Incident</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/05/gun-wielding-illegal-alien-allegedly-shoots-two-nypd-officers-in-latest-migrant-crime-incident/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>In the early hours of June 3, 2024, NYPD officers Christopher Abreu and Richard Yarusso were investigating a robbery when they encountered 19-year-old Bernardo Castro Mata, an illegal alien from Venezuela, driving a motorized scooter with no plates the wrong way down a street. To read the rest of the article click here The post Gun-Wielding Illegal Alien Allegedly Shoots Two NYPD Officers in Latest Migrant Crime Incident appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 18:21:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Joe Biden And Kamala Harris Make Millions Of Lives Better With Changes To Medical Debt Rules</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/11/joe-biden-and-kamala-harris-make-millions-of-lives-better-with-sweeping-changes-to-medical-debt-rules.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Vice President Kamala Harris announced that medical debt will no longer be allowed to be counted against people's credit scores, as the Biden administration takes another step to improve lives.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 21:39:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Europe May Face a Second Middle Eastern Migrant Crisis</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/05/europe-may-face-a-second-middle-eastern-migrant-crisis/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Europe may once again be about to receive mass waves of migrants from the Middle East, invoking memories of the 2015-2016 period, when then-German Chancellor Angela Merkel invited Syrians (and others) to come to Europe without limitation. To read the rest of the article click here The post Europe May Face a Second Middle Eastern Migrant Crisis appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 18:11:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jamie Raskin Shows Republicans What Real Respect For The Law Looks Like</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/11/jamie-raskin-shows-republicans-what-real-respect-for-the-law-looks-like.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Rep. Jamie Raskin (D-MD) pointed out that he hasn't heard a single Democrat attack the courts or cry fraud after the Hunter Biden verdict.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 19:02:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Baltimore Has an Obvious Problem. The Fix is Fairly Obvious Too.</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/05/baltimore-has-an-obvious-problem-the-fix-is-fairly-obvious-too/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>“Baltimore County releases illegal immigrants charged with crimes despite federal requests,” declared a recent headline on the local FOX 45 news site. To read the rest of the article click here The post Baltimore Has an Obvious Problem. The Fix is Fairly Obvious Too. appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 14:28:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Puts America First In Touching Statement On Hunter Biden Conviction</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/11/biden-puts-america-first-in-touching-statement-on-hunter-biden-conviction.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>President Biden issued a touching statement about being a father and supporting his son after Hunter Biden's conviction.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 17:30:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fairfax County, Virginia: Public Schools, Limited English Proficiency, and the Opportunity Cost of Mass Migration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/03/fairfax-county-virginia-public-schools-limited-english-proficiency-and-the-opportunity-cost-of-mass-migration/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>In economics, opportunity cost is defined as “the potential benefits that a business, an investor, or an individual consumer misses out on when choosing one alternative over another.” A dollar spent on A cannot be simultaneously spent on B. To read the rest of the article click here The post Fairfax County, Virginia: Public Schools, Limited English Proficiency, and the Opportunity Cost of Mass Migration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 21:36:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>