<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 01:07:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Trump Runs Away From Reporters When Asked If He Will Testify</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/03/trump-runs-away-testify.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Trump-run-away-testify.jpg</image_url><description>Donald Trump's position on testifying shifted after the judge told him that he could testify at his criminal trial.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 21:30:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Illegal Aliens Issue List of Demands After Hundreds Take Over City Park and Refuse to Leave</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/03/illegal-aliens-issue-list-of-demands-after-hundreds-take-over-city-park-and-refuse-to-leave/</link><description>In a brazen display of entitlement, hundreds of illegal aliens from Africa and Venezuela swarmed and took over Powell Barnett Park in Seattle. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Illegal Aliens Issue List of Demands After Hundreds Take Over City Park and Refuse to Leave appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 20:23:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hope Hicks Confirms That Hush Money Payments Were About The Trump Campaign</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/03/hope-hicks-confirms-that-hush-money-payments-were-about-the-trump-campaign.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/2019-06-19T131227Z_1_LYNXNPEF5I1A2_RTROPTP_4_USA-TRUMP-HICKS-e1714765537228.jpg</image_url><description>During her testimony, Trump's defense appeared to take a hit when Hope Hicks testified that the Trump hush money payments were looked at through the prism of the campaign.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 20:53:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Japan is not Xenophobic, but Seems Poised to Repeat our Mistakes</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/03/japan-is-not-xenophobic-but-seems-poised-to-repeat-our-mistakes/</link><description>On Wednesday President Biden chastised America’s most important Pacific ally, Japan, as xenophobic. He smeared India with the same insult, conflating both democracies with China and Russia — suggesting tight borders as the primary driver of economic woes in all four. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Japan is not Xenophobic, but Seems Poised to Repeat our Mistakes appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 16:10:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Media’s Accountant Charged With Massive Fraud</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/03/trump-medias-accountant-charged-with-massive-fraud.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/trump-head-in-hands.jpg</image_url><description>The accounting firm that worked with Trump Media has been charged with massive fraud by the SEC.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 20:27:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ireland At the Breaking Point on Immigration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/01/ireland-at-the-breaking-point-on-immigration/</link><description>A weekend of forcefully suppressed protests against mass immigration in Ireland has underlined the growing disconnect between the government and the people. There has been understandable concern over Irish communities being forced to house and pay for migrant men without the locals being consulted. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Ireland At the Breaking Point on Immigration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 14:56:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Doesn’t Answer When Asked If Hope Hicks Betrayed Him</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/03/trump-doesnt-answer-when-asked-if-hope-hicks-betrayed-him.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/2019-06-04T164624Z_1_LYNXNPEF531IZ_RTROPTP_4_USA-TRUMP-e1714757848531.jpg</image_url><description>Hope Hicks is testifying at the hush money trial, and when Trump was asked if she betrayed him, he didn't answer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 18:39:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In Case You Missed This – Which is What the Open-Borders Network Hopes Happened</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/30/in-case-you-missed-this-which-is-what-the-open-borders-network-hopes-happened/</link><description>“As Maine Goes, So Goes the Nation” still lingers as a popular axiom except of course, it’s just no longer true. Politically, the state hasn’t been an accurate bellwether of elections for decades. Yet now, in the context of illegal immigration, Maine once again bears watching, despite its 2,400 miles distance from the southern border. [...]
The post In Case You Missed This – Which is What the Open-Borders Network Hopes Happened appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 18:08:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Judge Merchan Kills Trump’s Lie He Can’t Testify Due To Gag Order</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/03/judge-merchan-trump-testify.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/trump-remarks-after-jury-sworn-in.jpg</image_url><description>After Trump claimed outside of court yesterday that the gag order prohibited him from testifying Judge Merchan corrected Trump from the bench.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 14:59:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Enduring Relevance of National Sovereignty and Borders</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/30/the-enduring-relevance-of-national-sovereignty-and-borders/</link><description>“No border, no security.” That simple common-sense point was made by historian Marek Chodakiewicz as he opened up a conference on “U.S. Sovereignty: The Border Challenges” at the Institute of World Politics (IWP) in Washington, D.C., earlier this month. To read the rest of the article click here
The post The Enduring Relevance of National Sovereignty and Borders appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 14:59:27 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>