<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 06:50:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Sen. John Kennedy Tried To Attack Kamala Harris On Fox News And It Did Not Go Well</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/29/sen-john-kennedy-tried-to-attack-kamala-harris-on-fox-news-and-it-did-not-go-well.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Sen. John Kennedy (R-LA) called Vice President Kamala Harris a ding dong, but he looked like the ding dong as he imploded on the air.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 23:10:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Human Smuggler Who Facilitated Illegal Entry of Thousands of Aliens Indicted</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/29/human-smuggler-who-facilitated-illegal-entry-of-thousands-of-aliens-indicted/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>On July 18, reports surfaced that Abdul Karim Conteh, a national from Sierra Leone, had been indicted and sanctioned in the United States and arrested in Tijuana, Mexico. Conteh ran a smuggling organization that facilitated the transport of thousands of illegal aliens to the United States through Mexico, including many from terrorism hot spots. To [...] The post Human Smuggler Who Facilitated Illegal Entry of Thousands of Aliens Indicted appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 20:17:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mike Johnson Picks 1/6 Conspiracy Theorist For Trump Assassination Attempt Task Force</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/29/mike-johnson-picks-1-6-conspiracy-theorist-for-trump-assassination-attempt-task-force.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Speaker Mike Johnson has selected 1/6 conspiracy theorist and misinformer Rep. Clay Higgins (R-LA) to serve on the House Trump assassination attempt task force.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 20:31:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Did Biden Really Say Our Borders are More Secure than When He Took Office?</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/26/did-biden-really-say-our-borders-are-more-secure-than-when-he-took-office/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Every politician is prone to exaggerating their accomplishments in an attempt to define their legacy in the most positive possible terms. President Biden is certainly no exception. In his address to the nation on Wednesday evening, after he announced his decision to abandon his 2024 reelection bid, the president ticked off a long list of [...] The post Did Biden Really Say Our Borders are More Secure than When He Took Office? appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 21:24:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden-Harris Reform Plan Would Flip The Supreme Court</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/29/biden-harris-reform-plan-would-flip-the-supreme-court.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Under the Biden-Harris Supreme Court reform plan, Justices Thomas, Alito, and Roberts would all be retired as active Supreme Court justices.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 18:51:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maine Immigration Fanatics Focus on Efficiency and Cost to Increase Flows</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/26/maine-immigration-fanatics-focus-on-efficiency-and-cost-to-increase-flows/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Mass immigration advocates in Maine have a problem. They’ve overachieved their goals and now need to adjust their strategy to appease taxpayers alarmed over skyrocketing costs to house migrants. To read the rest of the article click here The post Maine Immigration Fanatics Focus on Efficiency and Cost to Increase Flows appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 17:31:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Announces Plan For Supreme Court Term Limits And No Immunity For Ex-Presidents</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/29/biden-announces-plan-for-supreme-court-term-limits-and-no-immunity-for-ex-presidents.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>President Biden will announce a bold plan for Supreme Court reform that includes term limits for Supreme Court justices and no immunity for crimes that an ex-president committed while in office.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 10:30:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Washington Turns a Blind Eye to Exploited Migrant Children, While their Tormentors Cash In</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/24/washington-turns-a-blind-eye-to-exploited-migrant-children-while-their-tormentors-cash-in/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>On July 17, the Biden-Harris administration’s Department of Justice filed a suit against its largest private housing provider for unaccompanied alien children (UAC) in the United States, alleging that the company, Southwest Key, subjected children to repeated and unwelcome sexual abuse, harassment, rape, solicitation of sex acts, and more. To read the rest of the [...] The post Washington Turns a Blind Eye to Exploited Migrant Children, While their Tormentors Cash In appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 21:03:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fox News Tried To Get JD Vance To Apologize To Childless Americans And It Was A Disaster</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/29/fox-news-tried-to-get-jd-vance-to-apologize-to-childless-americans-and-it-was-a-disaster.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Trey Gowdy tried to get JD Vance to apologize for his attack on childless Americans, but instead Trump's running mate claimed repeatedly to have been taken out of context.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 05:13:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kamala Harris Never Consulted with Border Patrol Chiefs Despite Record Illegal Immigration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/24/kamala-harris-never-consulted-with-border-patrol-chiefs-despite-record-illegal-immigration/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>In the early months of the Biden administration, Vice President Kamala Harris was tasked with addressing the border crisis by tackling its “root causes.” The results speak for themselves. To read the rest of the article click here The post Kamala Harris Never Consulted with Border Patrol Chiefs Despite Record Illegal Immigration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 17:56:23 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>