<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:39:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Marjorie Taylor Greene Is Embarrassing Herself On Motion To Vacate</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/07/marjorie-taylor-greene-is-embarrassing-herself-on-motion-to-vacate.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/Greene-Raskin.jpg</image_url><description>Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene (R-GA) keeps meeting with Speaker Johnson, threatening him, then embarrassingly giving him more time.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:34:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This North Carolina Sheriff Should Know Better</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/07/this-north-carolina-sheriff-should-know-better/</link><description>Generally speaking, police chiefs – particularly those in major urban areas – support illegal alien sanctuary policies that prohibit them from cooperating with federal immigration officials. They’re often pressured to do so by the politicians and special interests who appoint and influence them. To read the rest of the article click here
The post This North Carolina Sheriff Should Know Better appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:05:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump May Be Heading To Jail As He Attacks On Stormy Daniels During Court Break</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/07/trump-violate-gag-order-stormy-daniels.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/07/trump-hands-up-50x50.jpg</image_url><description>Trump appears to have violated the gag order by reposting an old attack on Stormy Daniels during the break in her testimony.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 19:12:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stats Show Fentanyl Replacing Heroin as Cartel Cash Cow</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/06/stats-show-fentanyl-replacing-heroin-as-cartel-cash-cow/</link><description>Fentanyl is rapidly replacing heroin as the drug cartels are using to make money. Statistics on drug seizures from U.S. Customs and Border Protection (CBP) show that there has been a clear shift in the cartels’ smuggling habits, and the data strongly indicate that the border chaos of recent years is facilitating this lethal trade. [...]
The post Stats Show Fentanyl Replacing Heroin as Cartel Cash Cow appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:33:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Marjorie Taylor Greene Demands That Mike Johnson Defund Jack Smith</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/07/marjorie-taylor-greene-defund-jack-smith.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Jack-Smith-1-6-indictment.jpg</image_url><description>Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene (R-GA) has listed her demands of Speaker Mike Johnson for her to drop her motion to vacate, which include defunding Jack Smith.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:33:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Illegal Aliens Issue List of Demands After Hundreds Take Over City Park and Refuse to Leave</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/03/illegal-aliens-issue-list-of-demands-after-hundreds-take-over-city-park-and-refuse-to-leave/</link><description>In a brazen display of entitlement, hundreds of illegal aliens from Africa and Venezuela swarmed and took over Powell Barnett Park in Seattle. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Illegal Aliens Issue List of Demands After Hundreds Take Over City Park and Refuse to Leave appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 20:23:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Told Stormy Daniels That She Reminded Him Of His Daughter Ivanka</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/07/trump-told-stormy-daniels-that-she-reminded-him-of-his-daughter-ivanka.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/10/Trump-Ivanka-Incest.jpg</image_url><description>Stormy Daniels said that Trump told her that she reminded him of his daughter Ivanka Trump.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:58:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Japan is not Xenophobic, but Seems Poised to Repeat our Mistakes</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/03/japan-is-not-xenophobic-but-seems-poised-to-repeat-our-mistakes/</link><description>On Wednesday President Biden chastised America’s most important Pacific ally, Japan, as xenophobic. He smeared India with the same insult, conflating both democracies with China and Russia — suggesting tight borders as the primary driver of economic woes in all four. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Japan is not Xenophobic, but Seems Poised to Repeat our Mistakes appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 16:10:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stormy Daniels Is Giving Details And Humiliating Trump In Court</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/07/stormy-daniels-is-giving-details-and-humiliating-trump-in-court.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/2018-08-28T195232Z_1_LYNXNPEE7R1HH_RTROPTP_4_USA-TRUMP-DANIELS-LAWSUIT-e1715098185283.jpg</image_url><description>Donald Trump claims that the affair with Stormy Daniels never happened, but Daniels is in court providing details.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:11:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ireland At the Breaking Point on Immigration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/01/ireland-at-the-breaking-point-on-immigration/</link><description>A weekend of forcefully suppressed protests against mass immigration in Ireland has underlined the growing disconnect between the government and the people. There has been understandable concern over Irish communities being forced to house and pay for migrant men without the locals being consulted. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Ireland At the Breaking Point on Immigration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 14:56:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>