<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 07:25:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Doctors, Nurses, And Healthcare Professionals Are Organizing For Joe Biden</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/13/doctors-nurses-and-healthcare-professionals-are-organizing-for-joe-biden.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>The Biden campaign announced the launch of Health Care Providers For Biden-Harris. The healthcare providers will organize other healthcare professionals to inform voters about the stakes in the 2024 election.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 12:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Illegal Alien Released Into U.S. Allegedly Pulls Girl Into Van and Sexually Assaults Her</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/10/illegal-alien-released-into-u-s-allegedly-pulls-girl-into-van-and-sexually-assaults-her/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>In another case of a horrifying and preventable crime, an illegal alien in Florida is accused of grabbing an 11-year-old girl, dragging her into a van and sexually assaulting her. To read the rest of the article click here The post Illegal Alien Released Into U.S. Allegedly Pulls Girl Into Van and Sexually Assaults Her appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 21:47:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden To Highlight His Historic Record With Infrastructure Week</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/13/biden-infrastructure-week.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>President Biden will hold a real infrastructure week to highlight the historic progress America has made on infrastructure during his administration.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 10:00:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Denmark Beat Mass Immigration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/10/how-denmark-beat-mass-immigration/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Open-borders apologists usually portray mass migration as an unstoppable force that national governments are powerless to stop. However, Denmark has shown that good policies can and do reduce mass immigration and protect a country’s economy. To read the rest of the article click here The post How Denmark Beat Mass Immigration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 15:15:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aerial Photo And Video Show The Real Size Of Trump New Jersey Rally Crowd</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/12/aerial-photo-and-video-show-the-real-size-of-trump-new-jersey-rally-crowd.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>An aerial photo shows the size of the beach space where Trump held his rally and the size of the crowd before the ex-president spoke, and it wasn't 80,000 people.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 22:10:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This North Carolina Sheriff Should Know Better</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/07/this-north-carolina-sheriff-should-know-better/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Generally speaking, police chiefs – particularly those in major urban areas – support illegal alien sanctuary policies that prohibit them from cooperating with federal immigration officials. They’re often pressured to do so by the politicians and special interests who appoint and influence them. To read the rest of the article click here The post This North Carolina Sheriff Should Know Better appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:05:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Marjorie Taylor Greene Said The Quiet Part Out Loud About Trump And House Republicans</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/12/marjorie-taylor-greene-said-the-quiet-part-out-loud-about-trump-and-house-republicans.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene (R-GA) admitted on Fox News that the real job of House Republicans is to defend Donald Trump.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 21:22:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stats Show Fentanyl Replacing Heroin as Cartel Cash Cow</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/06/stats-show-fentanyl-replacing-heroin-as-cartel-cash-cow/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Fentanyl is rapidly replacing heroin as the drug cartels are using to make money. Statistics on drug seizures from U.S. Customs and Border Protection (CBP) show that there has been a clear shift in the cartels’ smuggling habits, and the data strongly indicate that the border chaos of recent years is facilitating this lethal trade. [...] The post Stats Show Fentanyl Replacing Heroin as Cartel Cash Cow appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:33:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lindsey Graham Has A Total Screaming Meltdown On Meet The Press</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/12/lindsey-graham-has-a-total-screaming-meltdown-on-meet-the-press.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Sen. Lindsey Graham (R-SC) lost it and started yelling at Kristen Welker on Meet The Press when she pointed out that Biden is doing the same thing that Ronald Reagan did in limiting weapons transfers.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 19:07:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Illegal Aliens Issue List of Demands After Hundreds Take Over City Park and Refuse to Leave</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/03/illegal-aliens-issue-list-of-demands-after-hundreds-take-over-city-park-and-refuse-to-leave/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>In a brazen display of entitlement, hundreds of illegal aliens from Africa and Venezuela swarmed and took over Powell Barnett Park in Seattle. To read the rest of the article click here The post Illegal Aliens Issue List of Demands After Hundreds Take Over City Park and Refuse to Leave appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 20:23:29 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>