<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 00:43:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Post Claiming Juror Leaked Trump Deliberations Appears To Be A Hoax</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/07/post-claiming-juror-leaked-trump-deliberations-appears-to-be-a-hoax.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>On Friday, Judge Merchan sent a letter to all parties about a social media post claiming that a juror leaked a told a cousin Trump would be convicted. More evidence has surfaced that makes the post look like a hoax.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 23:42:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gun-Wielding Illegal Alien Allegedly Shoots Two NYPD Officers in Latest Migrant Crime Incident</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/05/gun-wielding-illegal-alien-allegedly-shoots-two-nypd-officers-in-latest-migrant-crime-incident/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>In the early hours of June 3, 2024, NYPD officers Christopher Abreu and Richard Yarusso were investigating a robbery when they encountered 19-year-old Bernardo Castro Mata, an illegal alien from Venezuela, driving a motorized scooter with no plates the wrong way down a street. To read the rest of the article click here The post Gun-Wielding Illegal Alien Allegedly Shoots Two NYPD Officers in Latest Migrant Crime Incident appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 18:21:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alvin Bragg Shoots Down Jim Jordan’s Demand For Testimony Next Week</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/07/alvin-bragg-shoots-down-jim-jordans-demand-for-testimony-next-week.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Manhattan DA Alvin Bragg told House Judiciary Chair Jim Jordan (R-OH) that he is willing to cooperate but only after Trump has been sentenced and the appeals process is underway.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 22:58:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Europe May Face a Second Middle Eastern Migrant Crisis</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/05/europe-may-face-a-second-middle-eastern-migrant-crisis/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Europe may once again be about to receive mass waves of migrants from the Middle East, invoking memories of the 2015-2016 period, when then-German Chancellor Angela Merkel invited Syrians (and others) to come to Europe without limitation. To read the rest of the article click here The post Europe May Face a Second Middle Eastern Migrant Crisis appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 18:11:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mike Johnson Faces Mega Flop As He Can’t Get Votes To Support Felon Trump</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/07/mike-johnson-faces-mega-flop-and-he-cant-get-votes-to-support-felon-trump.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Speaker Mike Johnson is under pressure to pass a bill that would support Trump and allow him to move stage charges to federal court, but Johnson can't get the votes to pass the bill.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 22:22:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Baltimore Has an Obvious Problem. The Fix is Fairly Obvious Too.</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/05/baltimore-has-an-obvious-problem-the-fix-is-fairly-obvious-too/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>“Baltimore County releases illegal immigrants charged with crimes despite federal requests,” declared a recent headline on the local FOX 45 news site. To read the rest of the article click here The post Baltimore Has an Obvious Problem. The Fix is Fairly Obvious Too. appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 14:28:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Uses Trump Own Attacks On Vets Against Him In Devastating New Video</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/07/biden-uses-trump-own-attacks-on-vets-against-him-in-devastating-new-video.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>While President Biden is overseas marking the 80th anniversary of D-Day, his presidential campaign is shredding Donald Trump.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 21:10:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fairfax County, Virginia: Public Schools, Limited English Proficiency, and the Opportunity Cost of Mass Migration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/03/fairfax-county-virginia-public-schools-limited-english-proficiency-and-the-opportunity-cost-of-mass-migration/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>In economics, opportunity cost is defined as “the potential benefits that a business, an investor, or an individual consumer misses out on when choosing one alternative over another.” A dollar spent on A cannot be simultaneously spent on B. To read the rest of the article click here The post Fairfax County, Virginia: Public Schools, Limited English Proficiency, and the Opportunity Cost of Mass Migration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 21:36:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Corrupt Conservative SCOTUS Starting To Crack As Clarence Thomas Admits He Should Have Disclosed Trips</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/07/corrupt-conservative-scotus-starting-to-crack-as-clarence-thomas-admit-he-should-have-disclosed-trips.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>For the first time ever, Justice Clarence Thomas has admitted that he should have disclosed two trips from conservative billionaire Harlan Crow.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 19:07:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Massachusetts Response to its Migrant Crisis: Offer Even More Benefits</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/31/massachusetts-response-to-its-migrant-crisis-offer-even-more-benefits/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>If any state in America proves the axiom that “things in motion stay in motion” it’s Massachusetts. What else but perpetual motion physics can explain the logic behind the Bay State’s non-stop granting of benefits to illegal aliens? To read the rest of the article click here The post Massachusetts Response to its Migrant Crisis: Offer Even More Benefits appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 21:12:58 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>