<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 06:56:41 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>New Videos: At NYC’s Roosevelt Hotel, the Migrant Crisis Continues to Rage</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/08/12/new-videos-at-nycs-roosevelt-hotel-the-migrant-crisis-continues-to-rage/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Last week, while in New York City, I decided to take a walk around 10:00 p.m. to see the Roosevelt Hotel, now known as the city’s official migrant welcome center. FAIR visited this same location last year, and you can read our detailed account from that visit here. To read the rest of the article [...] The post New Videos: At NYC’s Roosevelt Hotel, the Migrant Crisis Continues to Rage appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 20:21:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Everything was going Kamala Harris’ way. Then came the market sell-off.</title><link>https://www.politico.com/news/2024/08/06/market-sell-off-democrats-harris-00172740</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>"We cannot win if people think we’re headed into a recession," one Democratic National Committee member said.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lenovo Profit Grows Another Quarter, Helped by AI</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/lenovo-profit-grows-another-quarter-helped-by-ai-b0f7c384?mod=rss_Technology</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Lenovo’s profits rose for a second-straight quarter as the world’s largest PC maker emerges from a yearslong downturn in the industry and captures opportunities in artificial intelligence to drive growth.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 06:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Walz’s false claim that Vance never voted for any pro-worker bills</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/2024/08/15/walzs-false-claim-that-vance-never-voted-any-pro-worker-bills/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Walz relies on a dubious metric, which misses at least two pro-worker bills supported by Vance</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 11:00:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tren de Aragua Gang Given ‘Green Light’ to Open Fire on U.S. Law Enforcement Officers</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/08/09/tren-de-aragua-gang-given-green-light-to-open-fire-on-u-s-law-enforcement-officers/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>A new report reveals that more than 1,000 members of the violent Venezuelan Tren de Aragua gang have infiltrated the United States and have been given the “green light” to attack and open fire on law enforcement officers. To read the rest of the article click here The post Tren de Aragua Gang Given ‘Green Light’ to Open Fire on U.S. Law Enforcement Officers appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 15:40:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JD Vance at RNC: Trump is the working class' 'last, best hope'</title><link>https://www.politico.com/video/2024/07/18/j-d-vance-at-rnc-trump-is-the-working-class-last-best-hope-1369100</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description></description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 05:28:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eric Schmidt Walks Back Claim Google Is Behind on AI Because of Remote Work</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/google-eric-schmidt-ai-remote-work-stanford-f92f4ca5?mod=rss_Technology</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>The former CEO of Google had said the tech company decided that work-life balance is “more important than winning.”</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 02:47:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump, in North Carolina speech, signals openness to expanding tariff plans</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description></description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 01:09:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oklahoma Knows You Can’t Manage What You Don’t Measure</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/08/07/oklahoma-knows-you-cant-manage-what-you-dont-measure/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Oklahoma’s Superintendent of the State Department of Education is asking Oklahoma school districts to get a handle on the number of illegal aliens occupying classrooms statewide “to find accurate and effective counting of the cost and burden that illegal immigration has.” To read the rest of the article click here The post Oklahoma Knows You Can’t Manage What You Don’t Measure appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:04:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>US added 206,000 jobs in June in a sign of continued economic strength</title><link>https://www.politico.com/news/2024/07/05/us-added-206-000-jobs-in-june-in-a-sign-of-continued-economic-strength-00166606</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Though hiring remains strong, voters blame President Joe Biden for persistent high prices.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 14:02:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Foxconn Posts Higher Profit, Record Revenue on AI Server Demand</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/foxconns-second-quarter-profit-rose-on-record-revenue-7f70bd92?mod=rss_Technology</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>The world’s largest contract electronics maker reported higher quarterly net profit as its revenue rose to a record on robust demand for artificial-intelligence servers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 09:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump speaks on economy in battleground state of N.C.</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/elections/2024/08/14/2024-election-campaign-updates-harris-trump/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Get the latest news from the 2024 campaign trail in the contest between Vice President Kamala Harris and former president Donald Trump.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 01:09:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Massachusetts Migrant Housing Costs: Out of Orbit and Hard to Grasp</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/08/01/massachusetts-migrant-housing-costs-out-of-orbit-and-hard-to-grasp/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Beyond a certain threshold, numbers become abstract and lose their meaningful context. A quick view of the national debt clock which adds $100,000 of national debt every two-and-a-half seconds to America’s current obligations of $35 trillion is virtually impossible to comprehend. To read the rest of the article click here The post Massachusetts Migrant Housing Costs: Out of Orbit and Hard to Grasp appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 17:55:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dems to Biden: You must out-populist Trump at the debate</title><link>https://www.politico.com/news/2024/06/26/biden-debate-anti-corporate-billionaires-00165178</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>The president has a compelling antimonopoly record. But he doesn’t always lean into it. And voters don’t really know of it. The debate could change that.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:48:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Google's Gemini Live AI Sounds So Human, I Almost Forgot It Was a Bot</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/google-android-ai-rick-osterloh-apple-iphone-7c06b06e?mod=rss_Technology</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Google’s Android chief told our columnist the voice assistant was designed to impersonate humans, but he doesn’t want anyone getting romantic with it.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Robert F. Kennedy Jr. tried to meet with Kamala Harris to discuss Cabinet job</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description></description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 01:03:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>House Passes Resolution Condemning the Biden-Harris Administration’s Failure to Secure the Border</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/08/01/house-passes-resolution-condemning-the-biden-harris-administrations-failure-to-secure-the-border/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>On July 25, the House of Representatives passed H. Res. 1371, condemning President Biden and Vice President Kamala Harris’ failure to secure the border. The resolution passed the same week that President Biden announced he would not seek a second term. To read the rest of the article click here The post House Passes Resolution Condemning the Biden-Harris Administration’s Failure to Secure the Border appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 17:33:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Huawei Readies New Chip to Challenge Nvidia, Surmounting U.S. Sanctions</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/huawei-readies-new-chip-to-challenge-nvidia-surmounting-u-s-sanctions-e108187a?mod=rss_Technology</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>The Chinese tech company is looking for AI business with the Ascend series but still faces production problems.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:43:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump, in North Carolina speech, signals openness to expanding tariff plans</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/2024/08/14/trump-rally-speech-north-carolina-economy-jd-vance/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>The remarks suggested an escalation in proposals many experts already see as likely to cause a global trade war.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 00:42:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>