<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 07:31:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>RFK Jr. Is Quickly Becoming A Political WMD Wiping Out Trump</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/05/rfk-jr-is-quickly-becoming-a-political-wmd-wiping-out-trump.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/RFKJR-Trump.jpg</image_url><description>The latest ABC News poll showed that Trump's RFK Jr. problem is growing and getting worse by the day.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 21:56:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Illegal Aliens Issue List of Demands After Hundreds Take Over City Park and Refuse to Leave</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/03/illegal-aliens-issue-list-of-demands-after-hundreds-take-over-city-park-and-refuse-to-leave/</link><description>In a brazen display of entitlement, hundreds of illegal aliens from Africa and Venezuela swarmed and took over Powell Barnett Park in Seattle. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Illegal Aliens Issue List of Demands After Hundreds Take Over City Park and Refuse to Leave appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 20:23:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Face The Nation Took Kristi Noem To The Gravel Pit And Ended Her Career</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/05/face-the-nation-face-the-nation.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/noem-ftn.jpg</image_url><description>Face The Nation's Margret Brennan took apart Kristi Noem and ended any chance of her having a national political career.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 21:21:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Japan is not Xenophobic, but Seems Poised to Repeat our Mistakes</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/03/japan-is-not-xenophobic-but-seems-poised-to-repeat-our-mistakes/</link><description>On Wednesday President Biden chastised America’s most important Pacific ally, Japan, as xenophobic. He smeared India with the same insult, conflating both democracies with China and Russia — suggesting tight borders as the primary driver of economic woes in all four. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Japan is not Xenophobic, but Seems Poised to Repeat our Mistakes appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 16:10:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jamie Raskin Perfectly Explains Why Trump’s Criminal Trial Matters</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/05/jamie-raskin-trump-trial.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Raskin-Trump-hush-money-trial.jpg</image_url><description>Rep. Jamie Raskin (D-MD) explained that Trump's New York trial is part of his determination to predetermine elections.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 19:40:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ireland At the Breaking Point on Immigration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/01/ireland-at-the-breaking-point-on-immigration/</link><description>A weekend of forcefully suppressed protests against mass immigration in Ireland has underlined the growing disconnect between the government and the people. There has been understandable concern over Irish communities being forced to house and pay for migrant men without the locals being consulted. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Ireland At the Breaking Point on Immigration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 14:56:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tim Scott Humiliates Himself By Refusing To Accept 2024 Election Results</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/05/kristen-welker-tim-scott-2024.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Tim-Scott-meet-the-press.jpg</image_url><description>NBC's Kristen Welker asked Sen. Tim Scott (R-SC) if he would accept the 2024 election results. Scott refused to answer until he snapped at Welker.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 16:04:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In Case You Missed This – Which is What the Open-Borders Network Hopes Happened</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/30/in-case-you-missed-this-which-is-what-the-open-borders-network-hopes-happened/</link><description>“As Maine Goes, So Goes the Nation” still lingers as a popular axiom except of course, it’s just no longer true. Politically, the state hasn’t been an accurate bellwether of elections for decades. Yet now, in the context of illegal immigration, Maine once again bears watching, despite its 2,400 miles distance from the southern border. [...]
The post In Case You Missed This – Which is What the Open-Borders Network Hopes Happened appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 18:08:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Doug Burgum Crashes And Burns As He Tries To Defend Trump On CNN</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/05/doug-burgum-cnn.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Burgum-tapper.jpg</image_url><description>Trump VP hopeful Gov. Doug Burgum (R-ND) fell apart as he tried to push Trump's hush money trial talking points on CNN.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 14:48:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Enduring Relevance of National Sovereignty and Borders</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/30/the-enduring-relevance-of-national-sovereignty-and-borders/</link><description>“No border, no security.” That simple common-sense point was made by historian Marek Chodakiewicz as he opened up a conference on “U.S. Sovereignty: The Border Challenges” at the Institute of World Politics (IWP) in Washington, D.C., earlier this month. To read the rest of the article click here
The post The Enduring Relevance of National Sovereignty and Borders appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 14:59:27 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>