<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 07:15:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Kamala Harris Looks At The Camera And Humiliates Trump In Atlanta</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/30/kamala-harris-humiliates-trump.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>At one point, Vice President Harris looked directly in the camera, spoke to Donald Trump, and told him to come and say it to her face by showing up for the debate.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 01:00:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Human Smuggler Who Facilitated Illegal Entry of Thousands of Aliens Indicted</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/29/human-smuggler-who-facilitated-illegal-entry-of-thousands-of-aliens-indicted/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>On July 18, reports surfaced that Abdul Karim Conteh, a national from Sierra Leone, had been indicted and sanctioned in the United States and arrested in Tijuana, Mexico. Conteh ran a smuggling organization that facilitated the transport of thousands of illegal aliens to the United States through Mexico, including many from terrorism hot spots. To [...] The post Human Smuggler Who Facilitated Illegal Entry of Thousands of Aliens Indicted appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 20:17:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tens Of Thousands Show Up For Kamala Harris Rally In Georgia</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/30/tens-of-thousands-show-up-for-kamala-harris-rally-in-georgia.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>Donald Trump has a big problem as a crowd estimated to be at 10,000 or more has shown up in Atlanta for VP Kamala Harris's rally.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 23:57:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Did Biden Really Say Our Borders are More Secure than When He Took Office?</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/26/did-biden-really-say-our-borders-are-more-secure-than-when-he-took-office/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>Every politician is prone to exaggerating their accomplishments in an attempt to define their legacy in the most positive possible terms. President Biden is certainly no exception. In his address to the nation on Wednesday evening, after he announced his decision to abandon his 2024 reelection bid, the president ticked off a long list of [...] The post Did Biden Really Say Our Borders are More Secure than When He Took Office? appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 21:24:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kamala Harris Campaign Warns That Project 2025 Isn’t Going Anywhere</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/30/kamala-harris-campaign-warns-that-project-2025-isnt-going-anywhere.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>The Harris campaign is warning America that Trump's duck-and-dodge on Project 2025 doesn't change the fact that the agenda is the same.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 23:01:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maine Immigration Fanatics Focus on Efficiency and Cost to Increase Flows</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/26/maine-immigration-fanatics-focus-on-efficiency-and-cost-to-increase-flows/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>Mass immigration advocates in Maine have a problem. They’ve overachieved their goals and now need to adjust their strategy to appease taxpayers alarmed over skyrocketing costs to house migrants. To read the rest of the article click here The post Maine Immigration Fanatics Focus on Efficiency and Cost to Increase Flows appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 17:31:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kamala Harris Leads Trump By 4 Points In New Pennsylvania Poll</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/30/kamala-harris-leads-trump-by-4-points-in-ew-pennsylvania-poll.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>A new poll of Pennsylvania by Susquehanna Polling and Research has found that Vice President Kamala Harris now leads ex-president Donald Trump by four points in Pennsylvania.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 18:16:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Washington Turns a Blind Eye to Exploited Migrant Children, While their Tormentors Cash In</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/24/washington-turns-a-blind-eye-to-exploited-migrant-children-while-their-tormentors-cash-in/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>On July 17, the Biden-Harris administration’s Department of Justice filed a suit against its largest private housing provider for unaccompanied alien children (UAC) in the United States, alleging that the company, Southwest Key, subjected children to repeated and unwelcome sexual abuse, harassment, rape, solicitation of sex acts, and more. To read the rest of the [...] The post Washington Turns a Blind Eye to Exploited Migrant Children, While their Tormentors Cash In appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 21:03:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kamala Harris To Campaign In Battleground States With Her Running Mate Next Week</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/30/kamala-harris-to-campaign-in-battleground-states-with-her-running-mate-next-week.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>Vice President Kamala Harris will reportedly be campaigning in swing states next week with her chosen running mate.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 17:29:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kamala Harris Never Consulted with Border Patrol Chiefs Despite Record Illegal Immigration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/24/kamala-harris-never-consulted-with-border-patrol-chiefs-despite-record-illegal-immigration/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>In the early months of the Biden administration, Vice President Kamala Harris was tasked with addressing the border crisis by tackling its “root causes.” The results speak for themselves. To read the rest of the article click here The post Kamala Harris Never Consulted with Border Patrol Chiefs Despite Record Illegal Immigration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 17:56:23 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>