<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 07:27:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Biden Announces Plan For Supreme Court Term Limits And No Immunity For Ex-Presidents</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/29/biden-announces-plan-for-supreme-court-term-limits-and-no-immunity-for-ex-presidents.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>President Biden will announce a bold plan for Supreme Court reform that includes term limits for Supreme Court justices and no immunity for crimes that an ex-president committed while in office.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 10:30:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Did Biden Really Say Our Borders are More Secure than When He Took Office?</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/26/did-biden-really-say-our-borders-are-more-secure-than-when-he-took-office/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Every politician is prone to exaggerating their accomplishments in an attempt to define their legacy in the most positive possible terms. President Biden is certainly no exception. In his address to the nation on Wednesday evening, after he announced his decision to abandon his 2024 reelection bid, the president ticked off a long list of [...] The post Did Biden Really Say Our Borders are More Secure than When He Took Office? appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 21:24:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fox News Tried To Get JD Vance To Apologize To Childless Americans And It Was A Disaster</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/29/fox-news-tried-to-get-jd-vance-to-apologize-to-childless-americans-and-it-was-a-disaster.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Trey Gowdy tried to get JD Vance to apologize for his attack on childless Americans, but instead Trump's running mate claimed repeatedly to have been taken out of context.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 05:13:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maine Immigration Fanatics Focus on Efficiency and Cost to Increase Flows</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/26/maine-immigration-fanatics-focus-on-efficiency-and-cost-to-increase-flows/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Mass immigration advocates in Maine have a problem. They’ve overachieved their goals and now need to adjust their strategy to appease taxpayers alarmed over skyrocketing costs to house migrants. To read the rest of the article click here The post Maine Immigration Fanatics Focus on Efficiency and Cost to Increase Flows appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 17:31:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Michigan Voters Are Ditching Trump Since Kamala Harris Got In The Race</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/28/michigan-voters-harris.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Republicans and Independents in Michigan who were supporting or leaning toward Trump are now looking at Kamala Harris.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 04:05:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Washington Turns a Blind Eye to Exploited Migrant Children, While their Tormentors Cash In</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/24/washington-turns-a-blind-eye-to-exploited-migrant-children-while-their-tormentors-cash-in/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>On July 17, the Biden-Harris administration’s Department of Justice filed a suit against its largest private housing provider for unaccompanied alien children (UAC) in the United States, alleging that the company, Southwest Key, subjected children to repeated and unwelcome sexual abuse, harassment, rape, solicitation of sex acts, and more. To read the rest of the [...] The post Washington Turns a Blind Eye to Exploited Migrant Children, While their Tormentors Cash In appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 21:03:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Largest Crowd Ever Seen Shows Up For Kamala Harris Event In Georgia GOP Stronghold</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/28/georgia-large-crowd-kamala-harris.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>The largest crowd ever seen for a Democratic event showed up to support Kamala Harris in the GOP stronghold of Forsyth County, Georgia.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 22:23:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kamala Harris Never Consulted with Border Patrol Chiefs Despite Record Illegal Immigration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/24/kamala-harris-never-consulted-with-border-patrol-chiefs-despite-record-illegal-immigration/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>In the early months of the Biden administration, Vice President Kamala Harris was tasked with addressing the border crisis by tackling its “root causes.” The results speak for themselves. To read the rest of the article click here The post Kamala Harris Never Consulted with Border Patrol Chiefs Despite Record Illegal Immigration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 17:56:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kamala Harris Co-Chair Calls Trump Cray-Cray And Questions His Mental Acuity</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/28/kamala-harris-co-chair-calls-trump-cray-cray-and-questions-his-mental-acuity.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Harris campaign co-chair Mitch Landrieu called Trump cray-cray and said that the ex-president can barely say anything that makes sense anymore.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 21:43:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Biden’s Border Crisis is Destroying Heartland America: A Look at Springfield, Ohio</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/19/how-bidens-border-crisis-is-destroying-heartland-america-a-look-at-springfield-ohio/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>You’ve seen the videos of migrants blatantly violating our immigration laws by illegally crossing the southern border, and you are probably one of the many Americans rightfully horrified by the recent stories of illegal alien crime. To read the rest of the article click here The post How Biden’s Border Crisis is Destroying Heartland America: A Look at Springfield, Ohio appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 21:58:46 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>