<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 01:42:07 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Tren de Aragua Gang Given ‘Green Light’ to Open Fire on U.S. Law Enforcement Officers</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/08/09/tren-de-aragua-gang-given-green-light-to-open-fire-on-u-s-law-enforcement-officers/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>A new report reveals that more than 1,000 members of the violent Venezuelan Tren de Aragua gang have infiltrated the United States and have been given the “green light” to attack and open fire on law enforcement officers. To read the rest of the article click here The post Tren de Aragua Gang Given ‘Green Light’ to Open Fire on U.S. Law Enforcement Officers appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 15:40:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Everything was going Kamala Harris’ way. Then came the market sell-off.</title><link>https://www.politico.com/news/2024/08/06/market-sell-off-democrats-harris-00172740</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>"We cannot win if people think we’re headed into a recession," one Democratic National Committee member said.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Former YouTube CEO Susan Wojcicki Dies at Age 56</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/former-youtube-ceo-susan-wojcicki-dies-at-age-56-58d1911d?mod=rss_Technology</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>The Silicon Valley native joined Google as one of its earliest employees, was instrumental in its rise and stepped down last year after nearly a decade running its video platform.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 01:25:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Harris goes on offense over the border in attempt to undercut Trump</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/2024/08/10/harris-walz-border-immigration-trump/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Kamala Harris and her running mate, Minnesota Gov. Tim Walz, hosted another large rally Saturday in Las Vegas.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 03:35:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oklahoma Knows You Can’t Manage What You Don’t Measure</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/08/07/oklahoma-knows-you-cant-manage-what-you-dont-measure/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Oklahoma’s Superintendent of the State Department of Education is asking Oklahoma school districts to get a handle on the number of illegal aliens occupying classrooms statewide “to find accurate and effective counting of the cost and burden that illegal immigration has.” To read the rest of the article click here The post Oklahoma Knows You Can’t Manage What You Don’t Measure appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:04:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JD Vance at RNC: Trump is the working class' 'last, best hope'</title><link>https://www.politico.com/video/2024/07/18/j-d-vance-at-rnc-trump-is-the-working-class-last-best-hope-1369100</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description></description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 05:28:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Every Big Tech Company Has Failed to Dethrone Nvidia as King of AI</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/ai-nvidia-apple-amd-jensen-huang-software-bb581f5a?mod=rss_Technology</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Nvidia, like Apple, shows that if you want to become a giant, you’ve got to be as good at software as you are at hardware.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 02:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Harris, Walz continue swing-state tour</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/elections/2024/08/10/2024-election-campaign-updates-harris-trump/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Get the latest news from the 2024 campaign trail in the contest between Vice President Kamala Harris and former president Donald Trump.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 03:28:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Massachusetts Migrant Housing Costs: Out of Orbit and Hard to Grasp</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/08/01/massachusetts-migrant-housing-costs-out-of-orbit-and-hard-to-grasp/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Beyond a certain threshold, numbers become abstract and lose their meaningful context. A quick view of the national debt clock which adds $100,000 of national debt every two-and-a-half seconds to America’s current obligations of $35 trillion is virtually impossible to comprehend. To read the rest of the article click here The post Massachusetts Migrant Housing Costs: Out of Orbit and Hard to Grasp appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 17:55:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>US added 206,000 jobs in June in a sign of continued economic strength</title><link>https://www.politico.com/news/2024/07/05/us-added-206-000-jobs-in-june-in-a-sign-of-continued-economic-strength-00166606</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Though hiring remains strong, voters blame President Joe Biden for persistent high prices.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 14:02:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tech Bros Are Betting They Can Help Win a War With China</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/anduril-drones-palmer-luckey-china-ukraine-china-951494ec?mod=rss_Technology</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Billions of dollars of venture capital is flowing into defense-tech startups focused on futuristic, AI-enabled weapons. Palmer Luckey’s Anduril is their biggest bet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 02:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Harris, referencing her tenure as attorney general of California, stressed her record of “going after transnational...</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description></description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 03:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>House Passes Resolution Condemning the Biden-Harris Administration’s Failure to Secure the Border</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/08/01/house-passes-resolution-condemning-the-biden-harris-administrations-failure-to-secure-the-border/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>On July 25, the House of Representatives passed H. Res. 1371, condemning President Biden and Vice President Kamala Harris’ failure to secure the border. The resolution passed the same week that President Biden announced he would not seek a second term. To read the rest of the article click here The post House Passes Resolution Condemning the Biden-Harris Administration’s Failure to Secure the Border appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 17:33:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dems to Biden: You must out-populist Trump at the debate</title><link>https://www.politico.com/news/2024/06/26/biden-debate-anti-corporate-billionaires-00165178</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>The president has a compelling antimonopoly record. But he doesn’t always lean into it. And voters don’t really know of it. The debate could change that.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:48:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Screen Time You Shouldn't Feel Bad About</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-screen-time-you-shouldnt-feel-bad-about-72ec85f3?mod=rss_Technology</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Understanding what you actually do on your phone can help you make smarter adjustments.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 02:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Harris pledged to “raise the minimum wage and eliminate taxes on tips for service and hospitality...</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description></description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 02:58:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Disastrous Nexus of Biden-Harris Policies:  The Afghan Parole Program and Prohibition on Issuing Notices to Appear</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/31/a-disastrous-nexus-of-biden-harris-policies-the-afghan-parole-program-and-prohibition-on-issuing-notices-to-appear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>On this date three years ago – July 31, 2021 – the first group of Afghan nationals arrived in the United States after the President Biden’s disastrous withdrawal of U.S. troops from the country. To read the rest of the article click here The post A Disastrous Nexus of Biden-Harris Policies: The Afghan Parole Program and Prohibition on Issuing Notices to Appear appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 16:02:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chip Maker SMIC's Shares Jump on Earnings Beat, Strong Guidance</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/chip-maker-smics-shares-jump-on-earnings-beat-strong-guidance-8beccc30?mod=rss_Technology</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Shares in Semiconductor Manufacturing International Corp. rose sharply in Hong Kong on its better-than-expected quarterly results and rosy guidance, signaling a stronger recovery in demand.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 06:09:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vice President Kamala Harris will attend a fundraiser for the Harris Victory Fund in San Francisco...</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description></description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 02:24:24 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>