<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 01:49:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Trump Gets Booed And Bombs At The Libertarian Convention</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/25/trump-gets-booed-and-bombs-at-the-libertarian-convention.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Trump's speech at the Libertarian Convention featured him getting booed by the audience and was not the campaign platform he was hoping for.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 02:09:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Britain’s Migrant Boat Headache</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/23/britains-migrant-boat-headache/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Britain continues to see waves of boats landing on its coast carrying illegal immigrants. The sight of dinghies being towed to shore and migrant men disembarking has become a regular sight. To read the rest of the article click here The post Britain’s Migrant Boat Headache appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 18:14:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Makes Secret Service Confiscate Rubber Chickens At Libertarian Convention</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/25/trump-rubber-chickens.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Trump had the Secret Service confiscate rubber chickens that were handed out by the RFK Jr. campaign at the Libertarian Convention.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:44:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Your City Doesn’t Have a Migrant Crisis Yet? Just Ask Denver for its New How-To Guide.</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/23/your-city-doesnt-have-a-migrant-crisis-yet-just-ask-denver-for-its-new-how-to-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Denver city officials have just released a 22-page guide that comprehensively details how to house, feed, clothe, employ, and otherwise subsidize and reward illegal immigration. To read the rest of the article click here The post Your City Doesn’t Have a Migrant Crisis Yet? Just Ask Denver for its New How-To Guide. appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 18:06:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jack Smith Moves On Trump’s False FBI Assassination Plot Claims</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/25/jack-smith-moves-on-trumps-false-fbi-assassination-plot-claims.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Special Counsel Jack Smith is requesting that Trump be prohibited from making comments about law enforcement agents in the classified documents case.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 17:27:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dutch Migration Crisis and the New Government’s Proposed Solutions</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/22/dutch-migration-crisis-and-the-new-governments-proposed-solutions/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Like virtually every other Western nation, the Netherlands faces a mass migration crisis. As a result, last November saw Geert Wilders’ anti-mass-migration Party for Freedom (PVV) secure the most seats in the Dutch parliament. To read the rest of the article click here The post Dutch Migration Crisis and the New Government’s Proposed Solutions appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 19:52:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Could Get Hammered At Sentencing For Gag Order Violations</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/25/trump-could-get-hammered-at-sentencing-for-gag-order-violations.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Legal experts are suggesting that Trump could face a harsher sentence if he is convicted in Manhattan due to his dozens of gag order violations.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 16:08:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>House Committee Holds Arizona Field Hearing on Biden Border Crisis</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/22/house-committee-holds-arizona-field-hearing-on-biden-border-crisis/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>The House Judiciary Committee recently held a field hearing to examine the effects of the border crisis in Arizona. The hearing, titled “The Biden Border Crisis: Arizona Perspectives,” focused on testimony from law enforcement and Arizona residents. To read the rest of the article click here The post House Committee Holds Arizona Field Hearing on Biden Border Crisis appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 19:37:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hakeem Jeffries Tells The American People To Keep The Heat On Alito And Thomas</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/24/hakeem-jeffries-tells-the-american-people-to-keep-the-heat-on-alito-and-thomas.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>House Democratic Leader Hakeem Jeffries (D-NY) said it is up to the American people and their representatives in Congress to pressure Alito and Thomas to recuse.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 23:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Reason Magazine Misses the Mark on Immigration Crisis</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/22/reason-magazine-misses-the-mark-on-immigration-crisis/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Last week Fiona Harrigan of Reason Magazine published a piece titled, “The U.S. Should Welcome Chinese Migrants.” To read the rest of the article click here The post Reason Magazine Misses the Mark on Immigration Crisis appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 19:15:57 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>