<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 06:58:22 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Biden Expands Health Care Coverage to DACA Recipients</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/03/bidendaca-healthcare.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/2018-04-19T015429Z_2_LYNXMPEE3H1JV_RTROPTP_3_USA-IMMIGRATION-DACA.jpg</image_url><description>President Biden announced that he will be expanding Affordable Care Act coverage to DACA recipients.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 11:00:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ireland At the Breaking Point on Immigration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/01/ireland-at-the-breaking-point-on-immigration/</link><description>A weekend of forcefully suppressed protests against mass immigration in Ireland has underlined the growing disconnect between the government and the people. There has been understandable concern over Irish communities being forced to house and pay for migrant men without the locals being consulted. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Ireland At the Breaking Point on Immigration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 14:56:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden To Award The Medal Of Freedom To Nancy Pelosi And Jim Clyburn</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/03/biden-to-award-the-medal-of-freedom-to-nancy-pelosi-and-jim-clyburn.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/2021-06-30T194300Z_1694424150_MT1CVMD41549330_RTRMADP_3_COVER-IMAGES-200x200.jpg</image_url><description>President Biden will give the Medal of Freedom to 19 recipients including Reps. Nancy Pelosi and Jim Clyburn.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 10:00:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In Case You Missed This – Which is What the Open-Borders Network Hopes Happened</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/30/in-case-you-missed-this-which-is-what-the-open-borders-network-hopes-happened/</link><description>“As Maine Goes, So Goes the Nation” still lingers as a popular axiom except of course, it’s just no longer true. Politically, the state hasn’t been an accurate bellwether of elections for decades. Yet now, in the context of illegal immigration, Maine once again bears watching, despite its 2,400 miles distance from the southern border. [...]
The post In Case You Missed This – Which is What the Open-Borders Network Hopes Happened appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 18:08:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stephen Colbert Mocks Trump For Having 1 Fan Outside The Courthouse</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/03/stephen-colbert-mocks-trump-for-having-1-fan-outside-the-courthouse.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Colbert-Trump-supporter.jpg</image_url><description>Stephen Colbert pointed out that Trump's spirits had to be lifted because he had one supporter outside the courthouse.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 06:16:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Enduring Relevance of National Sovereignty and Borders</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/30/the-enduring-relevance-of-national-sovereignty-and-borders/</link><description>“No border, no security.” That simple common-sense point was made by historian Marek Chodakiewicz as he opened up a conference on “U.S. Sovereignty: The Border Challenges” at the Institute of World Politics (IWP) in Washington, D.C., earlier this month. To read the rest of the article click here
The post The Enduring Relevance of National Sovereignty and Borders appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 14:59:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Democrats Step In To Get Marjorie Taylor Greene Under Control</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/02/democrats-step-in-to-get-marjorie-taylor-greene-under-control.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Jeffries-Greene.jpg</image_url><description>House Democratic Leader Hakeem Jeffries made it clear that Democrats are stepping in to get Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene (R-GA) under control.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 23:09:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mexican Diplomat’s Dishonest Claims About Illegal Alien Law-Breaking Do Not Stand Up to Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/29/mexican-diplomats-dishonest-claims-about-illegal-alien-law-breaking-do-not-stand-up-to-scrutiny/</link><description>Mexican diplomats and politicians have a long history of lecturing Americans on illegal immigration, along with attempting to meddle in U.S. politics in ways that favor illegal aliens while undermining our border security and rule of law. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Mexican Diplomat’s Dishonest Claims About Illegal Alien Law-Breaking Do Not Stand Up to Scrutiny appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 19:04:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Poised For Huge Blunder As He Narrows VP Choices To 4 Anti-Abortion Men</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/02/trump-poised-for-huge-blunder-as-he-narrows-vp-choices-to-4-anti-abortion-men.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/2018-03-01T133023Z_1_LYNXNPEE2039I_RTROPTP_4_USA-GUNS-TRUMP-e1714672260508.jpg</image_url><description>Donald Trump seems to think that abortion won't hurt in the general election as his running mate finalists are Tim Scott, Marco Rubio, J.D. Vance, and Doug Burgum.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 18:57:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>House Committee Aims to Stop Illegal Aliens from Slanting Congressional Apportionment</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/26/house-committee-aims-to-stop-illegal-aliens-from-slanting-congressional-apportionment/</link><description>The House Committee on Oversight and Accountability recently approved Congressmen Chuck Edwards’ (R-N.C.) and Warren Davidson’s (R-Ohio) H.R. 7109, the Equal Representation Act. To read the rest of the article click here
The post House Committee Aims to Stop Illegal Aliens from Slanting Congressional Apportionment appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 19:34:54 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>