<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 06:47:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Trump Melts Down Over Not Being Able To Rig His Own Trial</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/29/trump-rig-trial.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Trump was bordering on incoherent as he angrily spoke outside of the courthouse after jury deliberations ended for the day.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 23:27:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Two Illegal Aliens Attempt to Breach U.S. Military Base, Dangerous Trend Continues Under Biden</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/29/two-illegal-aliens-attempt-to-breach-u-s-military-base-dangerous-trend-continues-under-biden/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Two Jordanian illegal aliens are in ICE custody awaiting deportation proceedings after attempting to breach the Marine Corps base in Quantico, Virginia, earlier this month. To read the rest of the article click here The post Two Illegal Aliens Attempt to Breach U.S. Military Base, Dangerous Trend Continues Under Biden appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 21:01:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>House Democrats Demand Answers From Chief Justice Roberts On Alito And SCOTUS Ethics Rules</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/29/house-democrats-demand-answers-from-chief-justice-roberts-on-alito-and-scotus-ethics-rules.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>House Democrats sent a letter to Chief Justice John Roberts demanding that he answer questions about whether the Supreme Court will enforce their ethics rules on Alito.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 22:15:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Déjà Vu: Two Middle Eastern Illegal Aliens Attempt to Enter Secure Virginia Military Facility in a Box Truck</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/29/deja-vu-two-middle-eastern-illegal-aliens-attempt-to-enter-secure-virginia-military-facility-in-a-box-truck/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>On May 3, two Jordanian illegal aliens were apprehended as they attempted to enter the Marine Corps base in Quantico, Virginia, in a box truck. The two were posing as Amazon delivery drivers, although Amazon denies that they were employed by the company. To read the rest of the article click here The post Déjà Vu: Two Middle Eastern Illegal Aliens Attempt to Enter Secure Virginia Military Facility in a Box Truck appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 13:34:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Justice Alito Refuses To Recuse Himself On 1/6 Cases</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/29/justice-alito-refuses-to-recuse-himself-on-1-6-cases.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Supreme Court Justice Samuel Alito has rejected a request from top Senate Democrats to recuse himself from upcoming cases related to the 1/6 attack.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 21:13:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tunisia Cracks Down on Africans Migrants: Outsourcing Border Security</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/28/tunisia-cracks-down-on-africans-migrants-outsourcing-border-security/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Tunisia is fighting a battle with illegal immigrants from other parts of Africa trying to use the country as a launch pad towards their ultimate destination, Europe. The North African country is close to the Italian coast and even closer to Italy’s smaller outlying islands. To read the rest of the article click here The post Tunisia Cracks Down on Africans Migrants: Outsourcing Border Security appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 20:02:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Conviction Could Wreck Trump With Senior Voters</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/29/a-conviction-could-wreck-trump-with-senior-voters.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>GOP strategist and CNN contributor Scott Jennings said that a conviction could harm Trump with senior citizen voters in the 2024 election.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 18:05:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Britain’s Migrant Boat Headache</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/23/britains-migrant-boat-headache/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Britain continues to see waves of boats landing on its coast carrying illegal immigrants. The sight of dinghies being towed to shore and migrant men disembarking has become a regular sight. To read the rest of the article click here The post Britain’s Migrant Boat Headache appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 18:14:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Sounds Like He Knows He’s Going To Be Convicted</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/29/trump-sounds-like-he-knows-hes-going-to-be-convicted.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Trump didn't sound confident as he left the courtroom, but instead seemed to already be trying to spin a guilty verdict.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 17:32:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Your City Doesn’t Have a Migrant Crisis Yet? Just Ask Denver for its New How-To Guide.</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/23/your-city-doesnt-have-a-migrant-crisis-yet-just-ask-denver-for-its-new-how-to-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Denver city officials have just released a 22-page guide that comprehensively details how to house, feed, clothe, employ, and otherwise subsidize and reward illegal immigration. To read the rest of the article click here The post Your City Doesn’t Have a Migrant Crisis Yet? Just Ask Denver for its New How-To Guide. appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 18:06:45 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>