<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 07:17:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Biden Announces Major New Action To Lower Housing Costs</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/16/biden-housing-action.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>The Biden administration has announced new actions that will lower housing costs and limit rent increases.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 10:00:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Warning for New Yorkers: Moped-Riding Illegal Aliens Allegedly Robbing Outdoor Diners</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/12/warning-for-new-yorkers-moped-riding-illegal-aliens-allegedly-robbing-outdoor-diners/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Imagine this: you’re enjoying a warm summer evening in New York City, dining al fresco, proudly wearing the luxury watch you worked so hard to buy. Suddenly, a pair of armed, moped-riding bandits appear, robbing you of your prized possession. And it turns out these suspected criminals are reportedly newly-arrived illegal aliens. To read the [...] The post Warning for New Yorkers: Moped-Riding Illegal Aliens Allegedly Robbing Outdoor Diners appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 19:43:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Republicans Show The World That They Are To Blame For Political Violence</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/15/republicans-fight-convention.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Just in case anyone had any doubt where the violent rhetoric and impulses were coming from in American politics, Republicans chanted fight as Trump entered their convention.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 04:06:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Illegal Aliens Aren’t the Only Ones Migrating. Americans are Too</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/10/illegal-aliens-arent-the-only-ones-migrating-americans-are-too/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>IRS data shows that American taxpayers are leaving sanctuary states for states that actually enforce the law. The negative impact of misguided sanctuary policies goes well beyond simply releasing dangerous criminals back onto the streets, it also impacts state economies and tax bases. To read the rest of the article click here The post Illegal Aliens Aren’t the Only Ones Migrating. Americans are Too appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:02:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Calls Out Pro-Trump Media Bias In Lester Holt Interview</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/15/biden-lester-holt.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>During his interview with NBC's Lester Holt, President Biden called out the media for not fact checking Trump's lies or being concerned about Trump's age.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 03:02:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Massachusetts Governor Maura Healey’s Charade at the Southern Border</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/02/massachusetts-governor-maura-healeys-charade-at-the-southern-border/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Things are pretty dire in the illegal alien sanctuary Bay State. As FAIR’s 2023 report showed, 393,000 illegal aliens and their U.S.-born children live in Massachusetts, costing taxpayers $2.9 billion annually for health care, education, criminal justice, and general welfare. To read the rest of the article click here The post Massachusetts Governor Maura Healey’s Charade at the Southern Border appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:51:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Campaign Immediately Hammers J.D. Vance</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/15/biden-campaign-wastes-no-time-hammering-j-d-vance.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>In a call with reporters, the Biden campaign quickly hammered J.D. Vance for his support of Project 2025 and his willingness to be Trump's criminal lapdog.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 22:37:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayorkas Lies to the American People During Arizona Visit</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/01/mayorkas-lies-to-the-american-people-during-arizona-visit/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Recently impeached Department of Homeland Security Secretary Alejandro Mayorkas visited Tucson, Arizona, and attempted to sell President Biden’s recent executive action as having worked to reduce the number of illegal crossings at the southern border. To read the rest of the article click here The post Mayorkas Lies to the American People During Arizona Visit appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 19:31:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Thinks Fake Hillbilly J.D. Vance Will Help Him In Michigan, Pennsylvania, And Wisconsin</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/15/trump-jd-vance-swing-states.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>In his statement officially announcing Sen. J.D. Vance as his running mate Trump expressed a borderline delusional belief that Vance will help him in critical swing states Michigan, Pennsylvania, and Wisconsin.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 20:39:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sanctuary Politicians Need to Stop Lying and Admit the Obvious</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/28/sanctuary-politicians-need-to-stop-lying-and-admit-the-obvious/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Sanctuary politicians are getting nervous, and understandably so. The public is outraged over the surge of high-profile crimes allegedly committed by illegal aliens including the recent murder of 12-year old Jocelyn Nungaray in Houston, the sexual assault of a 13-year-old girl in New York City, and the Maryland rape and murder of Rachel Morin, mother [...] The post Sanctuary Politicians Need to Stop Lying and Admit the Obvious appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 17:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>