<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 12:44:30 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Stephen Colbert Says He Needs Trump To Be In Jail</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/01/stephen-colbert-says-he-needs-trump-to-be-in-jail.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Colbert-Trump-jail.jpg</image_url><description>On The Late Show, Stephen Colbert responded to the judge's threat to lock the ex-president up by saying that he needs Trump in jail.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 06:00:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ireland At the Breaking Point on Immigration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/01/ireland-at-the-breaking-point-on-immigration/</link><description>A weekend of forcefully suppressed protests against mass immigration in Ireland has underlined the growing disconnect between the government and the people. There has been understandable concern over Irish communities being forced to house and pay for migrant men without the locals being consulted. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Ireland At the Breaking Point on Immigration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 14:56:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Even Trump’s Own Lawyer Seems To Think He’s Going To Get Convicted</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/04/30/trumps-lawyer-convicted-fox-news.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/Habba-Trump-convicted.jpg</image_url><description>Alina Habba went on Fox News and acknowledged that a "blue jury" may ultimately convict Trump.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 22:28:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In Case You Missed This – Which is What the Open-Borders Network Hopes Happened</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/30/in-case-you-missed-this-which-is-what-the-open-borders-network-hopes-happened/</link><description>“As Maine Goes, So Goes the Nation” still lingers as a popular axiom except of course, it’s just no longer true. Politically, the state hasn’t been an accurate bellwether of elections for decades. Yet now, in the context of illegal immigration, Maine once again bears watching, despite its 2,400 miles distance from the southern border. [...]
The post In Case You Missed This – Which is What the Open-Borders Network Hopes Happened appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 18:08:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>“Trump Is F-ed:” A Day Full Of Damaging Evidence At Hush Money Trial</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/04/30/trump-is-f-ed-a-day-full-of-damaging-evidence-at-hush-money-trial.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/Trump-hush-money-trial-3-1.jpg</image_url><description>Witnesses have offered testimony that Trump was trying to hide damaging information from voters and committed crimes to cover up his scheme.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 21:44:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Enduring Relevance of National Sovereignty and Borders</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/30/the-enduring-relevance-of-national-sovereignty-and-borders/</link><description>“No border, no security.” That simple common-sense point was made by historian Marek Chodakiewicz as he opened up a conference on “U.S. Sovereignty: The Border Challenges” at the Institute of World Politics (IWP) in Washington, D.C., earlier this month. To read the rest of the article click here
The post The Enduring Relevance of National Sovereignty and Borders appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 14:59:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Removes Truth Social Posts After Being Threatened With Jail</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/04/30/trump-removes-truth-social-posts.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/07/trump-hands-up-50x50.jpg</image_url><description>After being threatened with potential jail time, Donald Trump removed posts from Truth Social that violated the judge's gag order.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 20:22:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mexican Diplomat’s Dishonest Claims About Illegal Alien Law-Breaking Do Not Stand Up to Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/29/mexican-diplomats-dishonest-claims-about-illegal-alien-law-breaking-do-not-stand-up-to-scrutiny/</link><description>Mexican diplomats and politicians have a long history of lecturing Americans on illegal immigration, along with attempting to meddle in U.S. politics in ways that favor illegal aliens while undermining our border security and rule of law. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Mexican Diplomat’s Dishonest Claims About Illegal Alien Law-Breaking Do Not Stand Up to Scrutiny appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 19:04:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Marjorie Taylor Greene Called On To Resign After Democrats Humiliate Her</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/04/30/house-democrats-marjorie-taylor-greene.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/MTG-Hunter-Biden-Newsmax.jpg</image_url><description>Marjorie Taylor Greene was called on to resign from Congress after Democrats took away her power and humiliated her on her plot to oust Mike Johnson.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 19:19:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>House Committee Aims to Stop Illegal Aliens from Slanting Congressional Apportionment</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/26/house-committee-aims-to-stop-illegal-aliens-from-slanting-congressional-apportionment/</link><description>The House Committee on Oversight and Accountability recently approved Congressmen Chuck Edwards’ (R-N.C.) and Warren Davidson’s (R-Ohio) H.R. 7109, the Equal Representation Act. To read the rest of the article click here
The post House Committee Aims to Stop Illegal Aliens from Slanting Congressional Apportionment appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 19:34:54 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>