<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 07:48:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Rachel Maddow Blasts Republicans For Showing Up At Trump’s Trial To Attack Judicial System</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/17/rachel-maddow-gop-trump-trial.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Rachel Maddow blasted Republicans for showing up at Trump's trial and attempting to damage or destroy the judicial system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 05:40:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In Spite of Border Crisis Calls for Amnesty Continue</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/16/in-spite-of-border-crisis-calls-for-amnesty-continue/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>The border crisis and mass illegal migration have exceeded all historical records. In Fiscal Year 2023, over 3.2 million illegal aliens were encountered nationwide, and we are on track to exceed even that unprecedented annual figure this fiscal year. To read the rest of the article click here The post In Spite of Border Crisis Calls for Amnesty Continue appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 19:23:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Michael Cohen Names Katy Tur As One Of His Close Journalists For Trump</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/16/michael-cohen-katy-tur.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Michael Cohen outed MSNBC's Katy Tur as one of the journalists with whom he had a close relationship and fed Trump stories.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:04:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Border County Sees 5,000 Percent Increase in Prosecutions During Biden’s Border Crisis</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/16/border-county-sees-5000-percent-increase-in-prosecutions-during-bidens-border-crisis/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>In Kinney County, Texas, a stark example of the direct consequences of open-borders policies under the Biden administration is unfolding. To read the rest of the article click here The post Border County Sees 5,000 Percent Increase in Prosecutions During Biden’s Border Crisis appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 17:41:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Corporate Media Ignores The Stock Market Hitting Historic 40,000 Under Biden</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/16/corporate-media-ignores-the-stock-market-hitting-historic-40000-under-biden.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>For the first time in history, the Dow Jones Industrial Average hit 40,000. It happened under Joe Biden, and some of the biggest corporate media outlets are ignoring it.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 19:53:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This May Be the Most Far-Flung Argument Yet to Reward Illegal Aliens</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/15/this-may-be-the-most-far-flung-argument-yet-to-reward-illegal-aliens/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Illegal aliens can’t legally drive in Missouri. Legislation passed in 2009 specifies that applicants for driver’s licenses must be U.S. citizens, or have proof of lawful presence in the United States. Admirably, Missouri is holding fast against trends to the contrary. To read the rest of the article click here The post This May Be the Most Far-Flung Argument Yet to Reward Illegal Aliens appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 14:15:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump’s Lawyer Spins Out Of Control And Can’t Break Cohen’s Jury Connection</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/16/trumps-lawyer-cohen.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Trump's lawyer Todd Blanche is reportedly going on off on long speeches to please his client, while Michael Cohen and the jury stay connected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 18:13:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>UK Study Shows Mass Immigration Will NOT Help the Economy</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/14/uk-study-shows-mass-immigration-will-not-help-the-economy/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Supporters of open borders often claim there will be major economic gains from relaxed border and immigration policies. To read the rest of the article click here The post UK Study Shows Mass Immigration Will NOT Help the Economy appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:30:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Appears To Be Using Lauren Boebert To Violate Gag Order</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/16/trump-lauren-boebert-court.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Rep. Lauren Boebert showed up in court with Trump, and she is posting on line what appears to be instructions on violating the gag order.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 15:50:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Do We Want? Everything! Migrants Send List of Demands to Denver City Officials</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/14/what-do-we-want-everything-migrants-send-list-of-demands-to-denver-city-officials/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>As the surge of illegal immigration began to unfold at the start of the Biden administration, the city of Denver, Colorado – or at least the politicians who run the city and state – decided that what most Americans see as a crisis would be a great opportunity for them to virtue signal. To read [...] The post What Do We Want? Everything! Migrants Send List of Demands to Denver City Officials appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 15:26:54 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>