<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 02:11:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Clueless Congressional Republicans Want Trump To Pick Nikki Haley For VP</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/26/clueless-congressional-republicans-want-trump-to-pick-nikki-haley-for-vp.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Some Republicans in Congress are clamoring for Trump to pick Nikki Haley, Tim Scott, or Marco Rubio for his VP running mate.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 19:39:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Britain’s Migrant Boat Headache</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/23/britains-migrant-boat-headache/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Britain continues to see waves of boats landing on its coast carrying illegal immigrants. The sight of dinghies being towed to shore and migrant men disembarking has become a regular sight. To read the rest of the article click here The post Britain’s Migrant Boat Headache appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 18:14:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pete Buttigieg Devastates Trump On EVs</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/26/pete-buttigieg-devastates-trump-on-evs.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Sec. of Transportation Pete Buttigieg devastated Trump for putting America last on EVs.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 17:52:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Your City Doesn’t Have a Migrant Crisis Yet? Just Ask Denver for its New How-To Guide.</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/23/your-city-doesnt-have-a-migrant-crisis-yet-just-ask-denver-for-its-new-how-to-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Denver city officials have just released a 22-page guide that comprehensively details how to house, feed, clothe, employ, and otherwise subsidize and reward illegal immigration. To read the rest of the article click here The post Your City Doesn’t Have a Migrant Crisis Yet? Just Ask Denver for its New How-To Guide. appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 18:06:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump’s Lawyer Is Already Trying To Blame MSNBC And CNN For His Conviction</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/26/alina-habba-trump-msnbc.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Trump lawyer Alina Habba went on Fox News and claimed that the jury may convict Trump because they watched MSNBC and CNN over Memorial Day.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 17:07:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dutch Migration Crisis and the New Government’s Proposed Solutions</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/22/dutch-migration-crisis-and-the-new-governments-proposed-solutions/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Like virtually every other Western nation, the Netherlands faces a mass migration crisis. As a result, last November saw Geert Wilders’ anti-mass-migration Party for Freedom (PVV) secure the most seats in the Dutch parliament. To read the rest of the article click here The post Dutch Migration Crisis and the New Government’s Proposed Solutions appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 19:52:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tim Scott Gives A Delusional Answer To Libertarians Booing Trump</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/26/tim-scott-gives-a-delusional-answer-to-libertarians-booing-trump.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Sen. Tim Scott (R-SC) said that Donald Trump's popularity is growing when asked about the Libertarian convention booing the ex-president.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 16:16:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>House Committee Holds Arizona Field Hearing on Biden Border Crisis</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/22/house-committee-holds-arizona-field-hearing-on-biden-border-crisis/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>The House Judiciary Committee recently held a field hearing to examine the effects of the border crisis in Arizona. The hearing, titled “The Biden Border Crisis: Arizona Perspectives,” focused on testimony from law enforcement and Arizona residents. To read the rest of the article click here The post House Committee Holds Arizona Field Hearing on Biden Border Crisis appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 19:37:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Gets Booed And Bombs At The Libertarian Convention</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/25/trump-gets-booed-and-bombs-at-the-libertarian-convention.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Trump's speech at the Libertarian Convention featured him getting booed by the audience and was not the campaign platform he was hoping for.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 02:09:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Reason Magazine Misses the Mark on Immigration Crisis</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/22/reason-magazine-misses-the-mark-on-immigration-crisis/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Last week Fiona Harrigan of Reason Magazine published a piece titled, “The U.S. Should Welcome Chinese Migrants.” To read the rest of the article click here The post Reason Magazine Misses the Mark on Immigration Crisis appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 19:15:57 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>