<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:41:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>If Trump Gets Convicted, Michael Cohen Will End Being A Big Reason Why</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/14/michael-cohen-testimony-ends.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Michael Cohen has drawn praise so far for being a calm, credible, and poised witness, but the powerful way that he closed his testimony did major damage to Trump.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 18:42:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>UK Study Shows Mass Immigration Will NOT Help the Economy</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/14/uk-study-shows-mass-immigration-will-not-help-the-economy/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Supporters of open borders often claim there will be major economic gains from relaxed border and immigration policies. To read the rest of the article click here The post UK Study Shows Mass Immigration Will NOT Help the Economy appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:30:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Reuters: More Than 150 Physical Threats Against Judges in Trump Cases Since March</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/14/reuters-more-than-150-physical-threats-against-judges-in-trump-cases-since-march.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Since March, there have been more than 150 physical threats against judges in Trump cases, according to a Reuters special report filed Tuesday.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:48:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Do We Want? Everything! Migrants Send List of Demands to Denver City Officials</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/14/what-do-we-want-everything-migrants-send-list-of-demands-to-denver-city-officials/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>As the surge of illegal immigration began to unfold at the start of the Biden administration, the city of Denver, Colorado – or at least the politicians who run the city and state – decided that what most Americans see as a crisis would be a great opportunity for them to virtue signal. To read [...] The post What Do We Want? Everything! Migrants Send List of Demands to Denver City Officials appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 15:26:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maggie Haberman Just Got Outed As A Trump Puppet At Trial</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/14/maggie-haberman-trump-trial.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Texts introduced as evidence at Trump's criminal trial show Maggie Haberman acting as Trump's stenographer and media puppet.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:25:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DHS Awards Millions to NGOs Facilitating Illegal Immigration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/14/dhs-awards-millions-to-ngos-facilitating-illegal-immigration/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Last month, the Department of Homeland Security (DHS) awarded another $300 million to nongovernmental organizations (NGOs) and state and local governments supporting illegal immigration through the Shelter and Services Program (SSP). To read the rest of the article click here The post DHS Awards Millions to NGOs Facilitating Illegal Immigration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 15:09:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Speaker Johnson and Other Republicans to Gather at Trump’s Criminal Trial</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/14/speaker-johnson-and-other-republicans-to-gather-at-trumps-criminal-trial.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Apparently there is nothing serious compelling Speaker Johnson to show up for his actual job, so instead he will give ex-president Donald Trump the fawning cheer section he requires in court on Tuesday.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:12:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Illegal Alien Released Into U.S. Allegedly Pulls Girl Into Van and Sexually Assaults Her</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/10/illegal-alien-released-into-u-s-allegedly-pulls-girl-into-van-and-sexually-assaults-her/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>In another case of a horrifying and preventable crime, an illegal alien in Florida is accused of grabbing an 11-year-old girl, dragging her into a van and sexually assaulting her. To read the rest of the article click here The post Illegal Alien Released Into U.S. Allegedly Pulls Girl Into Van and Sexually Assaults Her appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 21:47:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Takes Action To Protect American Workers And Businesses From China</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/14/biden-takes-action-to-protect-american-workers-and-businesses-from-china.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>President Biden is taking action to protect American jobs from Chinese cheating in markets like steel and semiconductors.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 10:01:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Denmark Beat Mass Immigration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/10/how-denmark-beat-mass-immigration/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Open-borders apologists usually portray mass migration as an unstoppable force that national governments are powerless to stop. However, Denmark has shown that good policies can and do reduce mass immigration and protect a country’s economy. To read the rest of the article click here The post How Denmark Beat Mass Immigration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 15:15:30 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>