<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 07:34:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Justice Alito Also Flew An Insurrection Flag At His Beach House Last Summer</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/22/justice-alito-also-flew-an-insurrectionist-flag-at-his-beach-house-last-summer.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Supreme Court Justice Samuel Alito had his excuse for flying a flag supporting the insurrection shattered when it was reported that a different flag supporting Trump's insurrection flew at his beach house last summer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:07:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dutch Migration Crisis and the New Government’s Proposed Solutions</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/22/dutch-migration-crisis-and-the-new-governments-proposed-solutions/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Like virtually every other Western nation, the Netherlands faces a mass migration crisis. As a result, last November saw Geert Wilders’ anti-mass-migration Party for Freedom (PVV) secure the most seats in the Dutch parliament. To read the rest of the article click here The post Dutch Migration Crisis and the New Government’s Proposed Solutions appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 19:52:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RNC’s Election Integrity Lawyer Arraigned For Election Crimes</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/22/rncs-election-integrity-lawyer-arraigned-for-election-crimes.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Christina Bobb, the RNC's election integrity lawyer, was arraigned on criminal charges related to the fake elector scheme in Arizona.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 19:54:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>House Committee Holds Arizona Field Hearing on Biden Border Crisis</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/22/house-committee-holds-arizona-field-hearing-on-biden-border-crisis/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>The House Judiciary Committee recently held a field hearing to examine the effects of the border crisis in Arizona. The hearing, titled “The Biden Border Crisis: Arizona Perspectives,” focused on testimony from law enforcement and Arizona residents. To read the rest of the article click here The post House Committee Holds Arizona Field Hearing on Biden Border Crisis appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 19:37:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fani Willis Cites Appearance On Rachel Maddow In Primary Victory Speech</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/21/fani-willis-cites-appearance-on-rachel-maddow-in-primary-victory-speech.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Fulton County DA Fani Willis was interviewed by Rachel Maddow the night before the Democratic primary and she cited her appearance on the show in her victory speech.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 02:15:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Reason Magazine Misses the Mark on Immigration Crisis</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/22/reason-magazine-misses-the-mark-on-immigration-crisis/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Last week Fiona Harrigan of Reason Magazine published a piece titled, “The U.S. Should Welcome Chinese Migrants.” To read the rest of the article click here The post Reason Magazine Misses the Mark on Immigration Crisis appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 19:15:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Is Losing It As He Claims Fascists Are Prosecuting Him</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/21/trump-is-losing-it-as-he-claims-fascists-are-prosecuting-him.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Trump came up with the conspiracy theory that it is fascists who are controlling the Oval Office who are behind his prosecution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 23:32:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Murderer from Colombia Released Into U.S. by ICE After Crossing Border Illegally</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/22/murderer-from-colombia-released-into-u-s-by-ice-after-crossing-border-illegally/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>The recent arrest of Efrain Vidales Vargas, a convicted murderer from Colombia, is another example of the perilous consequences of the Biden administration’s failure to secure our borders. To read the rest of the article click here The post Murderer from Colombia Released Into U.S. by ICE After Crossing Border Illegally appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 19:06:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Legal Expert Says Robert Costello’s Cross Was A Kill Shot To Trump</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/21/legal-expert-says-robert-costellos-cross-was-a-kill-shot-to-trump.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Andrew Weissmann said on MSNBC that Robert Costello delivered a kill shot, but it was to Trump, not the prosecution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 21:58:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New York Mayor Adam’s Botched Understanding of Merit-Based Immigration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/21/new-york-mayor-adams-botched-understanding-of-merit-based-immigration/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Evidently impressed by the physical stamina of those who make it across the Rio Grande River, New York Mayor Eric Adams offered a novel idea for how to deal with his city’s migrant crisis. To read the rest of the article click here The post New York Mayor Adam’s Botched Understanding of Merit-Based Immigration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 17:55:29 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>