<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 12:08:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Gossiping Reporters Have Openly Loathed Biden for Years, Former Speechwriter Says</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/03/gossiping-reporters-have-openly-loathed-biden-for-years-former-speechwriter-says.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>"These reporters are cherry-picking shreds of gossip at best… and making shit up at worst. Some have openly loathed Biden for years, &amp; are salivating at the chance to torch his team," former speechwriter to President Joe Biden Dan Cluchey wrote.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 16:48:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Flashback: When Harry Reid was Right about Immigration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/02/flashback-when-harry-reid-was-right-about-immigration/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Just shy of 30 years ago, FAIR found what now seems to be an unlikely ally in The Los Angeles Times opinion page. On August 10, 1994, the late Sen. Harry Reid (D-Nevada) wrote a fantastic op-ed promoting his bill to slash legal immigration by two thirds, from approximately 1 million to 325,000. To read [...] The post Flashback: When Harry Reid was Right about Immigration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 19:33:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NYT: Biden Is Seriously Considering Dropping Out</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/03/biden-is-seriously-considering-dropping-out.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>President Biden is reportedly considering dropping out of the presidential race as he realizes he has until the end of the week to turn his campaign around.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 16:14:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Massachusetts Governor Maura Healy’s Charade at the Southern Border</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/02/massachusetts-governor-maura-healys-charade-at-the-southern-border/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Things are pretty dire in the illegal alien sanctuary Bay State. As FAIR’s 2023 report showed, 393,000 illegal aliens and their U.S.-born children live in Massachusetts, costing taxpayers $2.9 billion annually for health care, education, criminal justice, and general welfare. To read the rest of the article click here The post Massachusetts Governor Maura Healy’s Charade at the Southern Border appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:51:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GOP Speaker Mike Johnson Says We Don’t Know How Long Our Freedom Is Going to Last</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/03/gop-speaker-mike-johnson-says-we-dont-know-how-long-our-freedom-is-going-to-last.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Speaker Mike Johnson (R-LA) reminded voters ahead of the nation’s 248 years old “Independence” birthday that we don’t know how long our experiment in self-governance is going to last. This week, the greatest country in the history of the world turns 248 years old. We have to remember that this is an experiment in self-governance,...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 15:53:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayorkas Lies to the American People During Arizona Visit</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/01/mayorkas-lies-to-the-american-people-during-arizona-visit/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Recently impeached Department of Homeland Security Secretary Alejandro Mayorkas visited Tucson, Arizona, and attempted to sell President Biden’s recent executive action as having worked to reduce the number of illegal crossings at the southern border. To read the rest of the article click here The post Mayorkas Lies to the American People During Arizona Visit appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 19:31:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Thug Trump Goes After Stormy Daniels’ 13-Year-Old Child</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/03/daniels-maddow.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>In yet another story of Donald Trump harassing witnesses, Stormy Daniels told MSNBC's Rachel Maddow that Donald Trump is trying to get her 13-year-old daughter's address.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 15:06:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sanctuary Politicians Need to Stop Lying and Admit the Obvious</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/28/sanctuary-politicians-need-to-stop-lying-and-admit-the-obvious/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Sanctuary politicians are getting nervous, and understandably so. The public is outraged over the surge of high-profile crimes allegedly committed by illegal aliens including the recent murder of 12-year old Jocelyn Nungaray in Houston, the sexual assault of a 13-year-old girl in New York City, and the Maryland rape and murder of Rachel Morin, mother [...] The post Sanctuary Politicians Need to Stop Lying and Admit the Obvious appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 17:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Finally, The New York Times Mentions That Trump Is Mentally Declining</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/02/finally-the-new-york-times-mentions-that-trump-is-mentally-declining.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Buried in a story about Biden contained one paragraph that noted Trump's mental decline and lack of transparency on his medical records.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 22:59:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>White House Leaves Out Key Fact in Statements on Alleged Murders of Americans by Illegal Aliens</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/27/white-house-leaves-out-key-fact-in-statements-on-alleged-murders-of-americans-by-illegal-aliens/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Over the past two weeks, Americans have seen numerous stories about horrific crimes allegedly committed by illegal aliens. The White House commented on two cases but failed to mention a key fact. To read the rest of the article click here The post White House Leaves Out Key Fact in Statements on Alleged Murders of Americans by Illegal Aliens appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 15:22:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>