<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 06:56:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Trump Forced To Stay In Milwaukee After Trashing GOP Convention Host City</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/18/trump-forced-to-stay-in-milwaukee-after-trashing-gop-convention-host-city.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Donald Trump was going to stay in Chicago during the Republican convention, but now he will stay in Milwaukee after reporters started asking questions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 00:00:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Illegal Alien Arrested in Brutal Rape and Murder of Mom of Five</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/18/illegal-alien-arrested-in-brutal-rape-and-murder-of-mom-of-five/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>The Ma &amp; Pa Trail in Bel Air, Maryland, is 1,800 miles from the southern border. It’s where Rachel Morin, a mom of five, was raped and murdered while on a hike. To read the rest of the article click here The post Illegal Alien Arrested in Brutal Rape and Murder of Mom of Five appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 14:35:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Tries To Steal Credit For Biden’s Economy At Wisconsin Rally Fiasco</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/18/trump-tries-to-steal-credit-for-bidens-economy-at-wisconsin-rally-fiasco.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Trump claimed that he gave Biden the current economy, which is a total lie, in a series of many at the ex-president's Wisconsin rally.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 22:34:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>European Election Results Show Tide Turning in Germany</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/18/european-election-results-show-tide-turning-in-germany/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>European Elections held across the continent in early June have shown some remarkable victories for parties advocating immigration control. With the possible exception of France, nowhere were the results more dramatic than in Germany. To read the rest of the article click here The post European Election Results Show Tide Turning in Germany appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 14:29:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Speaker Accidentally Slams Trump At His Own Rally For Being Old</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/18/speaker-accidentally-slams-trump-at-his-own-rally-for-being-old.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Rep. Bryan Steil (R-WI) tried to slam Biden, but accidentally took a shot at Trump while speaking at the ex-president's rally in Wisconsin.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 20:34:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is That REALLY a Homeless Shelter for Needy Americans or…Illegal Alien Housing?</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/13/is-that-really-a-homeless-shelter-for-needy-americans-orillegal-alien-housing/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Promoting open border and amnesty policies is increasingly tricky business for the left. After all, illegal immigration is a major issue for most voters, a concern that’s apparently deepening as shown by a new CBS News poll revealing that 62 percent of Americans support, “in principle, a new government program to deport all undocumented immigrants [...] The post Is That REALLY a Homeless Shelter for Needy Americans or…Illegal Alien Housing? appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 14:49:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump’s Truth Media Stock Is Plunging And Down More Than 50%</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/18/trumps-truth-media-stock-down-50.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Trump's Truth Media stock is now down more than 50% and still sliding since he was convicted of 34 felonies.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 19:38:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Crisis on NATO’s Eastern Border Shows How Anti-Western Regimes Weaponize Illegal Mass Migration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/12/crisis-on-natos-eastern-border-shows-how-anti-western-regimes-weaponize-illegal-mass-migration/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>A Polish soldier is dead, after being stabbed by an illegal migrant making an attempted incursion from the territory of neighboring Belarus. This incident represents a dangerous escalation of a “hybrid war” that has been ongoing on the eastern flank of NATO since 2021. To read the rest of the article click here The post Crisis on NATO’s Eastern Border Shows How Anti-Western Regimes Weaponize Illegal Mass Migration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 19:56:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Remains Gagged As Appeal Of Order Crashes And Burns</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/18/trump-remains-gagged-as-appeal-of-order-crashes-and-burns.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>New York's highest court rejected Donald Trump's appeal to have his gag order lifted before he is sentenced for 34 felony convictions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 18:52:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eight Illegal Aliens with Ties to ISIS Arrested Inside the U.S</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/12/eight-illegal-aliens-with-ties-to-isis-arrested-inside-the-u-s/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>In the latest alarming national security incident, eight suspected terrorists with ties to ISIS were arrested on immigration violations in a joint U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE) in conjunction with the FBI Joint Terrorism Task Force. To read the rest of the article click here The post Eight Illegal Aliens with Ties to ISIS Arrested Inside the U.S appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 18:36:43 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>