<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 06:50:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Trump Has A Breakdown Over Biden Leading Fox News Poll</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/20/trump-has-a-breakdown-over-biden-leading-fox-news-poll.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Donald Trump is watching his false narrative that he is leading all of the polls crumble, and the ex-president can't handle it.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 23:48:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Isn’t the Solution to Police Staffing Shortages</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/19/this-isnt-the-solution-to-police-staffing-shortages/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Law enforcement agencies across the nation are suffering unprecedented staffing shortages so dire, that in some instances, entire departments have been forced to close. To read the rest of the article click here The post This Isn’t the Solution to Police Staffing Shortages appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 20:40:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aileen Cannon’s Colleagues Tried To Get Her To Step Aside From Trump Classified Docs Case</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/20/aileen-cannons-colleagues-tried-to-get-her-to-step-aside-from-trump-classified-docs-case.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Two of Judge Aileen Cannon's colleagues urged her to step aside and not take the Trump classified documents case, but she refused.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 22:55:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Administration Quietly Closes More than 350,000 Asylum Cases</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/19/biden-administration-quietly-closes-more-than-350000-asylum-cases/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Recent reports reveal that the Biden administration covertly closed over 350,000 asylum cases of illegal aliens since 2022, even as it attempts to convince the American public that it is cracking down on illegal immigration. To read the rest of the article click here The post Biden Administration Quietly Closes More than 350,000 Asylum Cases appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 19:12:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Even Fox News Says Biden Is The Frontrunner After 11 Point Swing With Independent Voters</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/20/even-fox-news-says-biden-is-the-frontrunner-after-11-point-swing-with-independent-voters.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>A new Fox News poll caused Trump's favorite network to label President Biden as the frontrunner in the 2024 election.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 19:23:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Illegal Alien Arrested in Brutal Rape and Murder of Mom of Five</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/18/illegal-alien-arrested-in-brutal-rape-and-murder-of-mom-of-five/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>The Ma &amp; Pa Trail in Bel Air, Maryland, is 1,800 miles from the southern border. It’s where Rachel Morin, a mom of five, was raped and murdered while on a hike. To read the rest of the article click here The post Illegal Alien Arrested in Brutal Rape and Murder of Mom of Five appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 14:35:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Democrats Hold Republicans’ Feet to the Fire Ahead of 2-Year Anniversary of Overturn of Roe</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/20/democrats-hold-republicans-feet-to-the-fire-ahead-of-2-year-anniversary-of-overturn-of-roe.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Democrats are on the freedom warpath. Democrats say abortion is defining the races for the White House, Senate and House and they have every intention of holding Republicans accountable for their MAGA extremism.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 18:20:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>European Election Results Show Tide Turning in Germany</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/18/european-election-results-show-tide-turning-in-germany/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>European Elections held across the continent in early June have shown some remarkable victories for parties advocating immigration control. With the possible exception of France, nowhere were the results more dramatic than in Germany. To read the rest of the article click here The post European Election Results Show Tide Turning in Germany appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 14:29:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jimmy Kimmel Says Trump’s Dementia And Lying Might Be Teaming Up</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/20/jimmy-kimmel-says-trumps-dementia-and-lying-might-be-teaming-up.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Late night host Jimmy Kimmel played allegations of Trump's cognitive decline and came to the conclusion that Trump's dementia and lying might be teaming up.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 12:00:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is That REALLY a Homeless Shelter for Needy Americans or…Illegal Alien Housing?</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/13/is-that-really-a-homeless-shelter-for-needy-americans-orillegal-alien-housing/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Promoting open border and amnesty policies is increasingly tricky business for the left. After all, illegal immigration is a major issue for most voters, a concern that’s apparently deepening as shown by a new CBS News poll revealing that 62 percent of Americans support, “in principle, a new government program to deport all undocumented immigrants [...] The post Is That REALLY a Homeless Shelter for Needy Americans or…Illegal Alien Housing? appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 14:49:48 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>