<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 07:25:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Joe Biden Is Leading The Biggest US Small Business Boom In 25 Years</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/12/biden-small-business-boom.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>The Small Business Administration (SBA) announced that 18.1 million new business applications have been filed since Biden took office, the biggest boom in 25 years.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 23:47:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Crisis on NATO’s Eastern Border Shows How Anti-Western Regimes Weaponize Illegal Mass Migration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/12/crisis-on-natos-eastern-border-shows-how-anti-western-regimes-weaponize-illegal-mass-migration/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>A Polish soldier is dead, after being stabbed by an illegal migrant making an attempted incursion from the territory of neighboring Belarus. This incident represents a dangerous escalation of a “hybrid war” that has been ongoing on the eastern flank of NATO since 2021. To read the rest of the article click here The post Crisis on NATO’s Eastern Border Shows How Anti-Western Regimes Weaponize Illegal Mass Migration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 19:56:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eric Swalwell Goes Off On House Republicans For Dodging 1/6 Subpoenas</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/12/eric-swalwell-goes-off-on-house-republicans-for-dodging-1-6-subpoenas.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>During the floor debate on holding Attorney General Merrick Garland in contempt of Congress, Rep. Eric Swalwell called out House Republicans for not honoring 1/6 Committee subpoenas.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 21:26:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eight Illegal Aliens with Ties to ISIS Arrested Inside the U.S</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/12/eight-illegal-aliens-with-ties-to-isis-arrested-inside-the-u-s/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>In the latest alarming national security incident, eight suspected terrorists with ties to ISIS were arrested on immigration violations in a joint U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE) in conjunction with the FBI Joint Terrorism Task Force. To read the rest of the article click here The post Eight Illegal Aliens with Ties to ISIS Arrested Inside the U.S appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 18:36:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump’s New Jersey Golf Clubs May Lose Their Liquor Licenses After Felony Conviction</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/12/trump-liquor-license.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>The New Jersey AG is investigating whether Trump is still eligible to have liquor licenses at any of his three golf clubs in the state after his felony conviction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 17:46:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>House Committee Hears Testimony on Effects of the Border Crisis in North Dakota</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/11/house-committee-hears-testimony-on-effects-of-the-border-crisis-in-north-dakota/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>The House Judiciary Subcommittee on Immigration Integrity, Security, and Enforcement, recently held a field hearing to discuss the effects of the border crisis in North Dakota. To read the rest of the article click here The post House Committee Hears Testimony on Effects of the Border Crisis in North Dakota appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 19:51:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Gets The Port Of Baltimore Fully Reopened Just 11 Weeks After Bridge Collapse</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/12/biden-port-of-baltimore-open.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>President Biden promised to put the full weight of the federal government behind getting the Port of Baltimore reopened after the Francis Scott Key Bridge collapsed, and just 11 weeks later, the port is fully reopened.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 10:00:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gun-Wielding Illegal Alien Allegedly Shoots Two NYPD Officers in Latest Migrant Crime Incident</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/05/gun-wielding-illegal-alien-allegedly-shoots-two-nypd-officers-in-latest-migrant-crime-incident/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>In the early hours of June 3, 2024, NYPD officers Christopher Abreu and Richard Yarusso were investigating a robbery when they encountered 19-year-old Bernardo Castro Mata, an illegal alien from Venezuela, driving a motorized scooter with no plates the wrong way down a street. To read the rest of the article click here The post Gun-Wielding Illegal Alien Allegedly Shoots Two NYPD Officers in Latest Migrant Crime Incident appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 18:21:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Convicted Felon Trump Admits That He Had An Illegal Gun</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/11/convicted-felon-trump-admits-that-he-had-an-illegal-gun.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Donald Trump admitted during an interview with a probation officer that he illegally had a gun in Florida in violation of federal and state laws.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 23:27:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Europe May Face a Second Middle Eastern Migrant Crisis</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/05/europe-may-face-a-second-middle-eastern-migrant-crisis/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Europe may once again be about to receive mass waves of migrants from the Middle East, invoking memories of the 2015-2016 period, when then-German Chancellor Angela Merkel invited Syrians (and others) to come to Europe without limitation. To read the rest of the article click here The post Europe May Face a Second Middle Eastern Migrant Crisis appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 18:11:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>