<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 06:59:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Jon Stewart, “Trump Is The Real Cancel Culture.”</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/21/jon-stewart-trump-cancel-culture.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Jon Stewart called out the right's fake cancel culture and pointed out that the one real source of cancel culture is Donald Trump.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 05:22:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In Spite of Border Crisis Calls for Amnesty Continue</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/16/in-spite-of-border-crisis-calls-for-amnesty-continue/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>The border crisis and mass illegal migration have exceeded all historical records. In Fiscal Year 2023, over 3.2 million illegal aliens were encountered nationwide, and we are on track to exceed even that unprecedented annual figure this fiscal year. To read the rest of the article click here The post In Spite of Border Crisis Calls for Amnesty Continue appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 19:23:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden To Use Massive Fundraising Haul To Hammer Trump In Swing States</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/20/biden-to-use-massive-fundraising-haul-to-hammer-trump-in-swing-states.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>The Biden campaign announced that they raised another $51 million last month to their historic war chest to $192 million as they make a sizable investment in swing states.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 01:48:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Border County Sees 5,000 Percent Increase in Prosecutions During Biden’s Border Crisis</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/16/border-county-sees-5000-percent-increase-in-prosecutions-during-bidens-border-crisis/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>In Kinney County, Texas, a stark example of the direct consequences of open-borders policies under the Biden administration is unfolding. To read the rest of the article click here The post Border County Sees 5,000 Percent Increase in Prosecutions During Biden’s Border Crisis appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 17:41:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Demands Case Be Dismissed As He Whines About Being Cold</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/20/trump-demands-case-be-dismissed-as-he-whines-about-being-cold.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Donald Trump must think that being the GOP nominee makes him immune from prosecution, as he demanded that Judge Merchan drop the criminal case.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 23:16:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This May Be the Most Far-Flung Argument Yet to Reward Illegal Aliens</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/15/this-may-be-the-most-far-flung-argument-yet-to-reward-illegal-aliens/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Illegal aliens can’t legally drive in Missouri. Legislation passed in 2009 specifies that applicants for driver’s licenses must be U.S. citizens, or have proof of lawful presence in the United States. Admirably, Missouri is holding fast against trends to the contrary. To read the rest of the article click here The post This May Be the Most Far-Flung Argument Yet to Reward Illegal Aliens appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 14:15:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump’s Defense Case Implodes As Witness Robert Costello Gets Reprimanded By Judge</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/20/trumps-defense-case-implodes-as-witness-robert-costello-gets-reprimanded-by-judge.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Trump's defense witness Robert Costello was turning red in the face and muttering his breath over sustained objections, so the judge cleared the courtroom and reprimanded Costello.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 21:35:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>UK Study Shows Mass Immigration Will NOT Help the Economy</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/14/uk-study-shows-mass-immigration-will-not-help-the-economy/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Supporters of open borders often claim there will be major economic gains from relaxed border and immigration policies. To read the rest of the article click here The post UK Study Shows Mass Immigration Will NOT Help the Economy appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:30:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Appears To Be Spending Most Of His Day In Court Asleep</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/20/trump-appears-to-be-spending-most-of-his-day-in-court-asleep.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Donald Trump can't seem to stay awake during his trial, and multiple reporters have noted that Trump is asleep or has his eyes closed for long periods of time.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 18:45:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Do We Want? Everything! Migrants Send List of Demands to Denver City Officials</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/14/what-do-we-want-everything-migrants-send-list-of-demands-to-denver-city-officials/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>As the surge of illegal immigration began to unfold at the start of the Biden administration, the city of Denver, Colorado – or at least the politicians who run the city and state – decided that what most Americans see as a crisis would be a great opportunity for them to virtue signal. To read [...] The post What Do We Want? Everything! Migrants Send List of Demands to Denver City Officials appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 15:26:54 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>