<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 07:00:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>New Videos: At NYC’s Roosevelt Hotel, the Migrant Crisis Continues to Rage</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/08/12/new-videos-at-nycs-roosevelt-hotel-the-migrant-crisis-continues-to-rage/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Last week, while in New York City, I decided to take a walk around 10:00 p.m. to see the Roosevelt Hotel, now known as the city’s official migrant welcome center. FAIR visited this same location last year, and you can read our detailed account from that visit here. To read the rest of the article [...] The post New Videos: At NYC’s Roosevelt Hotel, the Migrant Crisis Continues to Rage appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 20:21:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Everything was going Kamala Harris’ way. Then came the market sell-off.</title><link>https://www.politico.com/news/2024/08/06/market-sell-off-democrats-harris-00172740</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>"We cannot win if people think we’re headed into a recession," one Democratic National Committee member said.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Foxconn Posts Higher Profit, Record Revenue on AI Server Demand</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/foxconns-second-quarter-profit-rose-on-record-revenue-7f70bd92?mod=rss_Technology</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>The world’s largest contract electronics maker reported higher quarterly net profit as its revenue rose to a record on robust demand for artificial-intelligence servers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 09:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Democrats invite public to off-site ‘DemPalooza’ convention events in Chicago</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/2024/08/14/public-dempalooza-dnc-convention-chicago/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>The public events at the McCormick Place convention center will be separate from the nightly televised events for party delegates</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 10:00:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tren de Aragua Gang Given ‘Green Light’ to Open Fire on U.S. Law Enforcement Officers</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/08/09/tren-de-aragua-gang-given-green-light-to-open-fire-on-u-s-law-enforcement-officers/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>A new report reveals that more than 1,000 members of the violent Venezuelan Tren de Aragua gang have infiltrated the United States and have been given the “green light” to attack and open fire on law enforcement officers. To read the rest of the article click here The post Tren de Aragua Gang Given ‘Green Light’ to Open Fire on U.S. Law Enforcement Officers appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 15:40:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JD Vance at RNC: Trump is the working class' 'last, best hope'</title><link>https://www.politico.com/video/2024/07/18/j-d-vance-at-rnc-trump-is-the-working-class-last-best-hope-1369100</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description></description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 05:28:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Google's Gemini Live AI Sounds So Human, I Almost Forgot It Was a Bot</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/google-android-ai-rick-osterloh-apple-iphone-7c06b06e?mod=rss_Technology</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Google’s Android chief told our columnist the voice assistant was designed to impersonate humans, but he doesn’t want anyone getting romantic with it.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Trump keeps talking about fictional serial killer Hannibal Lecter</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/2024/08/14/why-trump-keeps-talking-about-fictional-serial-killer-hannibal-lecter/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Trump is the “crypt keeper for the 1980′s,” a Trump biographer said. Trump has mentioned Lecter while making baseless claims about immigrants.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 10:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oklahoma Knows You Can’t Manage What You Don’t Measure</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/08/07/oklahoma-knows-you-cant-manage-what-you-dont-measure/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Oklahoma’s Superintendent of the State Department of Education is asking Oklahoma school districts to get a handle on the number of illegal aliens occupying classrooms statewide “to find accurate and effective counting of the cost and burden that illegal immigration has.” To read the rest of the article click here The post Oklahoma Knows You Can’t Manage What You Don’t Measure appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:04:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>US added 206,000 jobs in June in a sign of continued economic strength</title><link>https://www.politico.com/news/2024/07/05/us-added-206-000-jobs-in-june-in-a-sign-of-continued-economic-strength-00166606</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Though hiring remains strong, voters blame President Joe Biden for persistent high prices.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 14:02:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Huawei Readies New Chip to Challenge Nvidia, Surmounting U.S. Sanctions</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/huawei-readies-new-chip-to-challenge-nvidia-surmounting-u-s-sanctions-e108187a?mod=rss_Technology</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>The Chinese tech company is looking for AI business with the Ascend series but still faces production problems.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:43:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump vs. Harris magnifies America’s generational and cultural divides</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/elections/2024/08/14/trump-harris-voters-generation-culture-election-2024/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>The candidates, their movements and their rallies embody two very different identities, setting up a stark contrast for voters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Massachusetts Migrant Housing Costs: Out of Orbit and Hard to Grasp</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/08/01/massachusetts-migrant-housing-costs-out-of-orbit-and-hard-to-grasp/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Beyond a certain threshold, numbers become abstract and lose their meaningful context. A quick view of the national debt clock which adds $100,000 of national debt every two-and-a-half seconds to America’s current obligations of $35 trillion is virtually impossible to comprehend. To read the rest of the article click here The post Massachusetts Migrant Housing Costs: Out of Orbit and Hard to Grasp appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 17:55:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dems to Biden: You must out-populist Trump at the debate</title><link>https://www.politico.com/news/2024/06/26/biden-debate-anti-corporate-billionaires-00165178</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>The president has a compelling antimonopoly record. But he doesn’t always lean into it. And voters don’t really know of it. The debate could change that.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 23:48:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Australian Billionaire on a Crusade to Force Facebook to Police AI Scams</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-billionaire-suing-facebook-to-remove-his-face-from-ai-scams-50aa222e?mod=rss_Technology</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>A mining executive’s lawsuit is one of the first to threaten tech immunity protections, alleging that Facebook’s AI-powered ad systems amplify scams.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Congress didn’t recognize a race riot. Biden will make the site a monument.</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/nation/2024/08/14/1908-springfield-race-riot-monument/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>The president will designate the Springfield Race Riot National Monument on Friday, the White House confirmed to The Post.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>House Passes Resolution Condemning the Biden-Harris Administration’s Failure to Secure the Border</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/08/01/house-passes-resolution-condemning-the-biden-harris-administrations-failure-to-secure-the-border/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>On July 25, the House of Representatives passed H. Res. 1371, condemning President Biden and Vice President Kamala Harris’ failure to secure the border. The resolution passed the same week that President Biden announced he would not seek a second term. To read the rest of the article click here The post House Passes Resolution Condemning the Biden-Harris Administration’s Failure to Secure the Border appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 17:33:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Novel Ideas to Cool Data Centers: Liquid in Pipes or a Dunking Bath</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/novel-ideas-to-cool-data-centers-liquid-in-pipes-or-a-dunking-bath-cdb7a393?mod=rss_Technology</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Nvidia is trying a novel method of keeping its cutting-edge servers cool and limiting the use of power-hungry air conditioning.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ilhan Omar defeats challenger in Minnesota House primary</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/2024/08/13/ilhan-omar-don-samuels-minnesota-primary/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>The American Israel Public Affairs Committee has declined to seriously target Rep. Ilhan Omar after helping unseat Democratic Reps. Cori Bush and Jamaal Bowman.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 03:45:48 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>