<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 15:18:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Trump Doesn’t Answer When Asked If Hope Hicks Betrayed Him</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/03/trump-doesnt-answer-when-asked-if-hope-hicks-betrayed-him.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/2019-06-04T164624Z_1_LYNXNPEF531IZ_RTROPTP_4_USA-TRUMP-e1714757848531.jpg</image_url><description>Hope Hicks is testifying at the hush money trial, and when Trump was asked if she betrayed him, he didn't answer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 18:39:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Japan is not Xenophobic, but Seems Poised to Repeat our Mistakes</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/03/japan-is-not-xenophobic-but-seems-poised-to-repeat-our-mistakes/</link><description>On Wednesday President Biden chastised America’s most important Pacific ally, Japan, as xenophobic. He smeared India with the same insult, conflating both democracies with China and Russia — suggesting tight borders as the primary driver of economic woes in all four. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Japan is not Xenophobic, but Seems Poised to Repeat our Mistakes appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 16:10:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Judge Merchan Kills Trump’s Lie He Can’t Testify Due To Gag Order</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/03/judge-merchan-trump-testify.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/trump-remarks-after-jury-sworn-in.jpg</image_url><description>After Trump claimed outside of court yesterday that the gag order prohibited him from testifying Judge Merchan corrected Trump from the bench.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 14:59:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ireland At the Breaking Point on Immigration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/01/ireland-at-the-breaking-point-on-immigration/</link><description>A weekend of forcefully suppressed protests against mass immigration in Ireland has underlined the growing disconnect between the government and the people. There has been understandable concern over Irish communities being forced to house and pay for migrant men without the locals being consulted. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Ireland At the Breaking Point on Immigration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 14:56:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump’s Truth Social Fraud Revealed As Numbers Show Site Has Almost No Users</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/03/trump-truth-social-no-users.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/Trump-wsj.jpg</image_url><description>Donald Trump's Truth Social media site has just 113,000 users and has seen a drop of 4% over the past month, and 19% this year.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 14:36:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In Case You Missed This – Which is What the Open-Borders Network Hopes Happened</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/30/in-case-you-missed-this-which-is-what-the-open-borders-network-hopes-happened/</link><description>“As Maine Goes, So Goes the Nation” still lingers as a popular axiom except of course, it’s just no longer true. Politically, the state hasn’t been an accurate bellwether of elections for decades. Yet now, in the context of illegal immigration, Maine once again bears watching, despite its 2,400 miles distance from the southern border. [...]
The post In Case You Missed This – Which is What the Open-Borders Network Hopes Happened appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 18:08:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Expands Health Care Coverage to DACA Recipients</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/03/bidendaca-healthcare.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/2018-04-19T015429Z_2_LYNXMPEE3H1JV_RTROPTP_3_USA-IMMIGRATION-DACA.jpg</image_url><description>President Biden announced that he will be expanding Affordable Care Act coverage to DACA recipients.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 11:00:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Enduring Relevance of National Sovereignty and Borders</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/30/the-enduring-relevance-of-national-sovereignty-and-borders/</link><description>“No border, no security.” That simple common-sense point was made by historian Marek Chodakiewicz as he opened up a conference on “U.S. Sovereignty: The Border Challenges” at the Institute of World Politics (IWP) in Washington, D.C., earlier this month. To read the rest of the article click here
The post The Enduring Relevance of National Sovereignty and Borders appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 14:59:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden To Award The Medal Of Freedom To Nancy Pelosi And Jim Clyburn</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/03/biden-to-award-the-medal-of-freedom-to-nancy-pelosi-and-jim-clyburn.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/2021-06-30T194300Z_1694424150_MT1CVMD41549330_RTRMADP_3_COVER-IMAGES-200x200.jpg</image_url><description>President Biden will give the Medal of Freedom to 19 recipients including Reps. Nancy Pelosi and Jim Clyburn.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 10:00:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mexican Diplomat’s Dishonest Claims About Illegal Alien Law-Breaking Do Not Stand Up to Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/29/mexican-diplomats-dishonest-claims-about-illegal-alien-law-breaking-do-not-stand-up-to-scrutiny/</link><description>Mexican diplomats and politicians have a long history of lecturing Americans on illegal immigration, along with attempting to meddle in U.S. politics in ways that favor illegal aliens while undermining our border security and rule of law. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Mexican Diplomat’s Dishonest Claims About Illegal Alien Law-Breaking Do Not Stand Up to Scrutiny appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 19:04:52 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>