<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 13:15:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Kristi Noem’s VP Chances Are As Dead As The Dog She Murdered</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/02/kristi-noems-vp-chances-are-as-dead-as-the-dog-she-murdered.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/trumpnoem-e1714656047230.jpg</image_url><description>According to Trump aides, Kristi Noem's chances of being his running mate are dead, because she has disqualified herself.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 14:27:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ireland At the Breaking Point on Immigration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/01/ireland-at-the-breaking-point-on-immigration/</link><description>A weekend of forcefully suppressed protests against mass immigration in Ireland has underlined the growing disconnect between the government and the people. There has been understandable concern over Irish communities being forced to house and pay for migrant men without the locals being consulted. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Ireland At the Breaking Point on Immigration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 14:56:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Takes Unprecedented Action To Remove Lead Pipes And Provide Clean Drinking Water To American Families</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/02/biden-lead-pipes.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Biden-white-house.jpg</image_url><description>President Biden is living up to his moral responsibility as president while delivering environmental justice for millions of Americans.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 10:00:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In Case You Missed This – Which is What the Open-Borders Network Hopes Happened</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/30/in-case-you-missed-this-which-is-what-the-open-borders-network-hopes-happened/</link><description>“As Maine Goes, So Goes the Nation” still lingers as a popular axiom except of course, it’s just no longer true. Politically, the state hasn’t been an accurate bellwether of elections for decades. Yet now, in the context of illegal immigration, Maine once again bears watching, despite its 2,400 miles distance from the southern border. [...]
The post In Case You Missed This – Which is What the Open-Borders Network Hopes Happened appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 18:08:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Melts Down In Michigan And Starts Yelling Profanities</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/01/trump-melts-down-in-michigan-and-starts-yelling-profanities.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Trump-Michigan.jpg</image_url><description>Donald Trump could not hold it together to do two campaign events in a day, as he melted down in Michigan.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 23:43:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Enduring Relevance of National Sovereignty and Borders</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/30/the-enduring-relevance-of-national-sovereignty-and-borders/</link><description>“No border, no security.” That simple common-sense point was made by historian Marek Chodakiewicz as he opened up a conference on “U.S. Sovereignty: The Border Challenges” at the Institute of World Politics (IWP) in Washington, D.C., earlier this month. To read the rest of the article click here
The post The Enduring Relevance of National Sovereignty and Borders appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 14:59:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lauren Boebert Tries And Fails To Rip Down Palestinian Flag At Campus Protest</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/01/lauren-boebert-palestinian-flag.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Boebert-flag-fail.jpg</image_url><description>Rep. Lauren Boebert (R-CO) showed up at a George Washington University campus protest and tried to rip down a Palestinian flag, but her political grandstanding failed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 23:02:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mexican Diplomat’s Dishonest Claims About Illegal Alien Law-Breaking Do Not Stand Up to Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/29/mexican-diplomats-dishonest-claims-about-illegal-alien-law-breaking-do-not-stand-up-to-scrutiny/</link><description>Mexican diplomats and politicians have a long history of lecturing Americans on illegal immigration, along with attempting to meddle in U.S. politics in ways that favor illegal aliens while undermining our border security and rule of law. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Mexican Diplomat’s Dishonest Claims About Illegal Alien Law-Breaking Do Not Stand Up to Scrutiny appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 19:04:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Embarrasses Himself Trying To Campaign In Wisconsin</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/01/trump-embarrasses-himself-trying-to-campaign-in-wisconsin.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Trump-Wisconsin.jpg</image_url><description>Donald Trump tried to campaign in Wisconsin on his day off from court, and the Manhattan defendant embarrassed himself.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 21:13:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>House Committee Aims to Stop Illegal Aliens from Slanting Congressional Apportionment</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/26/house-committee-aims-to-stop-illegal-aliens-from-slanting-congressional-apportionment/</link><description>The House Committee on Oversight and Accountability recently approved Congressmen Chuck Edwards’ (R-N.C.) and Warren Davidson’s (R-Ohio) H.R. 7109, the Equal Representation Act. To read the rest of the article click here
The post House Committee Aims to Stop Illegal Aliens from Slanting Congressional Apportionment appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 19:34:54 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>