<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 06:40:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Trump Prepares To Debate Biden By Trying To End Bill Maher’s Career</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/22/trump-bill-maher.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Instead of preparing for the presidential debate, Trump is spending his time attacking Bill Maher and telling conservative media to ignore the comedian.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 16:43:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Isn’t the Solution to Police Staffing Shortages</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/19/this-isnt-the-solution-to-police-staffing-shortages/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Law enforcement agencies across the nation are suffering unprecedented staffing shortages so dire, that in some instances, entire departments have been forced to close. To read the rest of the article click here The post This Isn’t the Solution to Police Staffing Shortages appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 20:40:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump To Waste His Time Campaigning In Virginia</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/21/trump-to-waste-his-time-campaigning-in-virginia.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Former President Donald Trump plans to return to Virginia for a campaign event on June 28, the day after the first presidential debate, CBS News has learned.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 23:18:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Administration Quietly Closes More than 350,000 Asylum Cases</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/19/biden-administration-quietly-closes-more-than-350000-asylum-cases/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Recent reports reveal that the Biden administration covertly closed over 350,000 asylum cases of illegal aliens since 2022, even as it attempts to convince the American public that it is cracking down on illegal immigration. To read the rest of the article click here The post Biden Administration Quietly Closes More than 350,000 Asylum Cases appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 19:12:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Says No Domestic Abusers Should Get Guns While Trump Goes Silent</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/21/biden-no-domestic-abusers-guns.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>President Joe Biden put out a clear and strong statement agreement that domestic abusers shouldn't get guns, while convicted felon Trump has said nothing.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 21:39:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Illegal Alien Arrested in Brutal Rape and Murder of Mom of Five</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/18/illegal-alien-arrested-in-brutal-rape-and-murder-of-mom-of-five/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>The Ma &amp; Pa Trail in Bel Air, Maryland, is 1,800 miles from the southern border. It’s where Rachel Morin, a mom of five, was raped and murdered while on a hike. To read the rest of the article click here The post Illegal Alien Arrested in Brutal Rape and Murder of Mom of Five appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 14:35:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kamala Harris Blasts Weak Trump For Bowing Down To The Gun Lobby</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/21/kamala-harris-blasts-weak-trump-for-bowing-down-to-the-gun-lobby.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Vice President Kamala Harris reacted to the Supreme Court ruling that domestic abusers can be banned from owning guns by hammering Donald Trump.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 19:02:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>European Election Results Show Tide Turning in Germany</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/18/european-election-results-show-tide-turning-in-germany/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>European Elections held across the continent in early June have shown some remarkable victories for parties advocating immigration control. With the possible exception of France, nowhere were the results more dramatic than in Germany. To read the rest of the article click here The post European Election Results Show Tide Turning in Germany appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 14:29:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Manhattan Prosecutors Says Trump’s Attacks Have Inspired Bomb Threats</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/21/manhattan-prosecutors-says-trumps-attacks-have-inspired-bomb-threats.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Manhattan prosecutors have asked Judge Merchan to keep Trump's gag order in place due to his history of threatening and inflammatory statements that have led to threats against others.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 18:36:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is That REALLY a Homeless Shelter for Needy Americans or…Illegal Alien Housing?</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/13/is-that-really-a-homeless-shelter-for-needy-americans-orillegal-alien-housing/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Promoting open border and amnesty policies is increasingly tricky business for the left. After all, illegal immigration is a major issue for most voters, a concern that’s apparently deepening as shown by a new CBS News poll revealing that 62 percent of Americans support, “in principle, a new government program to deport all undocumented immigrants [...] The post Is That REALLY a Homeless Shelter for Needy Americans or…Illegal Alien Housing? appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 14:49:48 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>