<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 06:47:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Joe Biden Cements His Legacy Of Greatness In Oval Office Address</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/24/joe-biden-cements-his-legacy-of-greatness-in-oval-office-address.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>President Biden delivered an Oval Office address that emphasized putting the country ahead of himself and cemented his legacy of presidential greatness.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 01:44:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Washington Turns a Blind Eye to Exploited Migrant Children, While their Tormentors Cash In</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/24/washington-turns-a-blind-eye-to-exploited-migrant-children-while-their-tormentors-cash-in/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>On July 17, the Biden-Harris administration’s Department of Justice filed a suit against its largest private housing provider for unaccompanied alien children (UAC) in the United States, alleging that the company, Southwest Key, subjected children to repeated and unwelcome sexual abuse, harassment, rape, solicitation of sex acts, and more. To read the rest of the [...] The post Washington Turns a Blind Eye to Exploited Migrant Children, While their Tormentors Cash In appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 21:03:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Tried To Attack Kamala Harris In North Carolina And It Was Pathetic</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/24/trump-north-carolina-2024.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Trump tried to attack Kamala Harris at his rally in North Carolina, but his efforts were old, pathetic, and tired.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 23:59:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kamala Harris Never Consulted with Border Patrol Chiefs Despite Record Illegal Immigration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/24/kamala-harris-never-consulted-with-border-patrol-chiefs-despite-record-illegal-immigration/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>In the early months of the Biden administration, Vice President Kamala Harris was tasked with addressing the border crisis by tackling its “root causes.” The results speak for themselves. To read the rest of the article click here The post Kamala Harris Never Consulted with Border Patrol Chiefs Despite Record Illegal Immigration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 17:56:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>March For Our Lives Makes First Ever Presidential Endorsement For Kamala Harris</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/24/march-for-our-lives-makes-first-ever-presidential-endorsement-for-kamala-harris.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>The influential young people gun reform organization March For Our Lives has made its first-ever presidential endorsement for Vice President Kamala Harris.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 22:35:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Biden’s Border Crisis is Destroying Heartland America: A Look at Springfield, Ohio</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/19/how-bidens-border-crisis-is-destroying-heartland-america-a-look-at-springfield-ohio/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>You’ve seen the videos of migrants blatantly violating our immigration laws by illegally crossing the southern border, and you are probably one of the many Americans rightfully horrified by the recent stories of illegal alien crime. To read the rest of the article click here The post How Biden’s Border Crisis is Destroying Heartland America: A Look at Springfield, Ohio appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 21:58:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Congressman Calls On Netanyahu To Resign After Speech To Congress</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/24/congressman-calls-on-netanyahu-to-resign-after-lie-filled-speech-to-congress.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Rep. Jimmy Gomez (D-CA) called on Israeli Prime Minister Netanyahu to resign after his speech to Congress, which left many cold.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 21:43:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maryland Governor Wes Moore Says No to Statewide Immigration Policy</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/19/maryland-governor-wes-moore-says-no-to-statewide-immigration-policy/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>In a recent interview, Governor Wes Moore claimed that Maryland cannot establish a policy that dictates how the state interacts with U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE) because “it’s a federal agency.” To read the rest of the article click here The post Maryland Governor Wes Moore Says No to Statewide Immigration Policy appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 16:29:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Democrats Mass Boycott Netanyahu Speech To Congress</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/24/democrats-mass-boycott-netanyahu-speech-to-congress.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>At least 80 House Democrats, including former Speaker Pelosi and several Senate Democrats, will be boycotting Netanyahu's speech to Congress.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 17:36:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DHS Extends Temporary Protected Status to Haitians, Encouraging More Illegal Immigration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/17/dhs-extends-temporary-protected-status-to-haitians-encouraging-more-illegal-immigration/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Extending and re-designating TPS to Haitian nationals, at a time of unprecedented illegal immigration to the United States, is yet another example of how the Biden administration’s open-border agenda prioritizes illegal aliens over American citizens. To read the rest of the article click here The post DHS Extends Temporary Protected Status to Haitians, Encouraging More Illegal Immigration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 21:34:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>