<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 06:58:01 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Trump Blows A Gasket As He Realizes He’s Probably Going To Get Convicted</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/09/trump-blows-a-gasket-as-he-realizes-hes-probably-going-to-get-convicted.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Trump-judge-corrupt.jpg</image_url><description>Trump blew a gasket and went on a rage-fueled tirade about the judge outside the courthouse after his mistrial motion was rejected.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 23:01:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This North Carolina Sheriff Should Know Better</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/07/this-north-carolina-sheriff-should-know-better/</link><description>Generally speaking, police chiefs – particularly those in major urban areas – support illegal alien sanctuary policies that prohibit them from cooperating with federal immigration officials. They’re often pressured to do so by the politicians and special interests who appoint and influence them. To read the rest of the article click here
The post This North Carolina Sheriff Should Know Better appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:05:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Judge Denies Trump Mistrial Over Stormy Spanking</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/09/judge-denies-trump-mistrial-over-stormy-spanking.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/Trump-worn-out-at-trial.jpg</image_url><description>Judge Juan Merchan denied Trump's motion for a mistrial over Stormy Daniels telling the jury about how she spanked him with a magazine.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 22:06:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stats Show Fentanyl Replacing Heroin as Cartel Cash Cow</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/06/stats-show-fentanyl-replacing-heroin-as-cartel-cash-cow/</link><description>Fentanyl is rapidly replacing heroin as the drug cartels are using to make money. Statistics on drug seizures from U.S. Customs and Border Protection (CBP) show that there has been a clear shift in the cartels’ smuggling habits, and the data strongly indicate that the border chaos of recent years is facilitating this lethal trade. [...]
The post Stats Show Fentanyl Replacing Heroin as Cartel Cash Cow appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:33:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Loses As Judge Will Not Exempt Stormy Daniels From Gag Order</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/09/trump-loses-as-judge-will-not-exempt-stormy-daniels-from-gag-order.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/2018-10-08T194308Z_1_LYNXNPEE97197_RTROPTP_4_USA-TRUMP-DANIELS-LAWSUIT-e1712341853947.jpg</image_url><description>Trump, through his legal team, requested that Judge Merchan exempt Stormy Daniels from the gag order so that he could attack her. The judge denied the request.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:34:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Illegal Aliens Issue List of Demands After Hundreds Take Over City Park and Refuse to Leave</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/03/illegal-aliens-issue-list-of-demands-after-hundreds-take-over-city-park-and-refuse-to-leave/</link><description>In a brazen display of entitlement, hundreds of illegal aliens from Africa and Venezuela swarmed and took over Powell Barnett Park in Seattle. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Illegal Aliens Issue List of Demands After Hundreds Take Over City Park and Refuse to Leave appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 20:23:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Blasts Trump For Selling Out Working Families To Big Oil</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/09/biden-blasts-trump-for-selling-out-working-families-to-big-oil.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Biden-new-mexico-e1715277089556.jpg</image_url><description>The Biden campaign hammered Trump for promising Big Oil that he would roll back job-creating green energy programs if they donated a billion dollars to his campaign.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 18:54:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Japan is not Xenophobic, but Seems Poised to Repeat our Mistakes</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/03/japan-is-not-xenophobic-but-seems-poised-to-repeat-our-mistakes/</link><description>On Wednesday President Biden chastised America’s most important Pacific ally, Japan, as xenophobic. He smeared India with the same insult, conflating both democracies with China and Russia — suggesting tight borders as the primary driver of economic woes in all four. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Japan is not Xenophobic, but Seems Poised to Repeat our Mistakes appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 16:10:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Trump Cross Examination Of Stormy Daniels Destroys His Own Defense</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/09/the-trump-cross-examination-of-stormy-daniels-destroys-his-own-defense.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/Trump-hush-money-trial-3.jpg</image_url><description>Trump claims that he never had sex with Stormy Daniels, but his own lawyer asked Daniels if the sex was consensual.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 17:18:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ireland At the Breaking Point on Immigration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/01/ireland-at-the-breaking-point-on-immigration/</link><description>A weekend of forcefully suppressed protests against mass immigration in Ireland has underlined the growing disconnect between the government and the people. There has been understandable concern over Irish communities being forced to house and pay for migrant men without the locals being consulted. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Ireland At the Breaking Point on Immigration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 14:56:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>