<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 06:53:44 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Supreme Court Rejects Effort To Block Trump’s Felony Sentencing</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/08/05/supreme-court-rejects-effort-to-block-trumps-felony-sentencing.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>The Supreme Court rejected an effort by the state of Missouri to block Trump's felony sentencing and lift his gag order.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 20:30:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Massachusetts Migrant Housing Costs: Out of Orbit and Hard to Grasp</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/08/01/massachusetts-migrant-housing-costs-out-of-orbit-and-hard-to-grasp/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>Beyond a certain threshold, numbers become abstract and lose their meaningful context. A quick view of the national debt clock which adds $100,000 of national debt every two-and-a-half seconds to America’s current obligations of $35 trillion is virtually impossible to comprehend. To read the rest of the article click here The post Massachusetts Migrant Housing Costs: Out of Orbit and Hard to Grasp appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 17:55:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Implodes And Keeps Attacking Black Journalist</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/08/05/trump-implodes-and-keeps-attacking-black-journalist.html</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f1fa-1f1f8.png</image_url><description>While doing an interview with a right-wing streamer, Donald Trump again attacked ABC's Rachel Scott and cost himself support from black voters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 19:29:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>House Passes Resolution Condemning the Biden-Harris Administration’s Failure to Secure the Border</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/08/01/house-passes-resolution-condemning-the-biden-harris-administrations-failure-to-secure-the-border/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>On July 25, the House of Representatives passed H. Res. 1371, condemning President Biden and Vice President Kamala Harris’ failure to secure the border. The resolution passed the same week that President Biden announced he would not seek a second term. To read the rest of the article click here The post House Passes Resolution Condemning the Biden-Harris Administration’s Failure to Secure the Border appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 17:33:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Arizona Republicans Endorse Kamala Harris</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/08/05/arizona-republicans-endorse-kamala-harris.html</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f5f3.png</image_url><description>A group of current and former Republican elected officials in Arizona have endorsed Kamala Harris and are forming an advisory committee to help her win the state. Harris Arizona communications director Delaney Corcoran posted, “HAPPENING NOW: Arizona Republicans endorse Vice President Harris and slam Trump for his attacks on democracy. GOP leaders will form a...</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 17:38:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Disastrous Nexus of Biden-Harris Policies:  The Afghan Parole Program and Prohibition on Issuing Notices to Appear</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/31/a-disastrous-nexus-of-biden-harris-policies-the-afghan-parole-program-and-prohibition-on-issuing-notices-to-appear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>On this date three years ago – July 31, 2021 – the first group of Afghan nationals arrived in the United States after the President Biden’s disastrous withdrawal of U.S. troops from the country. To read the rest of the article click here The post A Disastrous Nexus of Biden-Harris Policies: The Afghan Parole Program and Prohibition on Issuing Notices to Appear appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 16:02:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Crumbling Trump Falsely Blames Kamala Harris For The Stock Market</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/08/05/trump-harris-stock-market.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>Trump falsely blamed Kamala Harris for the stock market correction that was expected, and he is trying to call it a new Great Depression.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 16:32:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Human Smuggler Who Facilitated Illegal Entry of Thousands of Aliens Indicted</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/29/human-smuggler-who-facilitated-illegal-entry-of-thousands-of-aliens-indicted/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>On July 18, reports surfaced that Abdul Karim Conteh, a national from Sierra Leone, had been indicted and sanctioned in the United States and arrested in Tijuana, Mexico. Conteh ran a smuggling organization that facilitated the transport of thousands of illegal aliens to the United States through Mexico, including many from terrorism hot spots. To [...] The post Human Smuggler Who Facilitated Illegal Entry of Thousands of Aliens Indicted appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 20:17:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Support Is Cracking As Kamala Harris Puts The Sun Belt In Play</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/08/05/trump-support-is-cracking-as-kamala-harris-puts-the-sun-belt-in-play.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Kamala Harris has now put the states of North Carolina, Georgia, and Arizona back into play as potential Democratic wins in November. Axios reported: Georgia, Arizona and North Carolina — which had looked to be trending toward former President Trump — are suddenly crackling battlegrounds online, on the airwaves and on the ground. Pennsylvania is...</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 14:46:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Did Biden Really Say Our Borders are More Secure than When He Took Office?</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/26/did-biden-really-say-our-borders-are-more-secure-than-when-he-took-office/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Every politician is prone to exaggerating their accomplishments in an attempt to define their legacy in the most positive possible terms. President Biden is certainly no exception. In his address to the nation on Wednesday evening, after he announced his decision to abandon his 2024 reelection bid, the president ticked off a long list of [...] The post Did Biden Really Say Our Borders are More Secure than When He Took Office? appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 21:24:59 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>