<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 06:58:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Biden To Meet With Brown v. Board of Education Participants And Families</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/16/biden-to-meet-with-brown-v-board-of-education-participants-and-families.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>President Biden will meet with participants and family members of the historic Brown v. Board of Education ruling on Thursday.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 10:00:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This May Be the Most Far-Flung Argument Yet to Reward Illegal Aliens</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/15/this-may-be-the-most-far-flung-argument-yet-to-reward-illegal-aliens/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Illegal aliens can’t legally drive in Missouri. Legislation passed in 2009 specifies that applicants for driver’s licenses must be U.S. citizens, or have proof of lawful presence in the United States. Admirably, Missouri is holding fast against trends to the contrary. To read the rest of the article click here The post This May Be the Most Far-Flung Argument Yet to Reward Illegal Aliens appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 14:15:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jake Tapper And Dana Bash To Moderate Biden/Trump Debate</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/15/jake-tapper-and-dana-bash-to-moderate-biden-trump-debate.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>CNN's Jake Tapper and Dana Bash will moderate the first 2024 Biden/Trump debate in June.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 22:28:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>UK Study Shows Mass Immigration Will NOT Help the Economy</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/14/uk-study-shows-mass-immigration-will-not-help-the-economy/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Supporters of open borders often claim there will be major economic gains from relaxed border and immigration policies. To read the rest of the article click here The post UK Study Shows Mass Immigration Will NOT Help the Economy appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:30:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Seems Excited That Kristi Noem Murdered Her Puppy</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/15/trump-seems-excited-that-kristi-noem-murdered-her-puppy.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Trump didn't condemn Kristi Noem for murdering her dog, but instead hyped her up and said he wanted to know more.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 21:42:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Do We Want? Everything! Migrants Send List of Demands to Denver City Officials</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/14/what-do-we-want-everything-migrants-send-list-of-demands-to-denver-city-officials/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>As the surge of illegal immigration began to unfold at the start of the Biden administration, the city of Denver, Colorado – or at least the politicians who run the city and state – decided that what most Americans see as a crisis would be a great opportunity for them to virtue signal. To read [...] The post What Do We Want? Everything! Migrants Send List of Demands to Denver City Officials appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 15:26:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Walked Into A Biden Debate Trap</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/15/trump-walked-into-a-total-biden-debate-trap.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Trump and his advisers are reportedly irked that President Biden has jumped in and taken the debate narrative away from them.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 20:48:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DHS Awards Millions to NGOs Facilitating Illegal Immigration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/14/dhs-awards-millions-to-ngos-facilitating-illegal-immigration/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Last month, the Department of Homeland Security (DHS) awarded another $300 million to nongovernmental organizations (NGOs) and state and local governments supporting illegal immigration through the Shelter and Services Program (SSP). To read the rest of the article click here The post DHS Awards Millions to NGOs Facilitating Illegal Immigration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 15:09:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Tries To Con Biden Into Debating Him On Fox News</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/15/trump-fox-news-debate-biden.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Trump announced that he had accepted an invitation to debate President Biden on Fox News in October. It is highly doubtful that Biden will accept.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 20:14:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Illegal Alien Released Into U.S. Allegedly Pulls Girl Into Van and Sexually Assaults Her</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/10/illegal-alien-released-into-u-s-allegedly-pulls-girl-into-van-and-sexually-assaults-her/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>In another case of a horrifying and preventable crime, an illegal alien in Florida is accused of grabbing an 11-year-old girl, dragging her into a van and sexually assaulting her. To read the rest of the article click here The post Illegal Alien Released Into U.S. Allegedly Pulls Girl Into Van and Sexually Assaults Her appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 21:47:34 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>