<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 16:15:32 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Weak And Declining Trump Holds Less Than 5 Minute Fake Press Conference With 0 Questions</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/13/trump-senate-gop-press-conference.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>A sign of Trump's ongoing decline was that he held an event billed as a press conference with Republican Senators that lasted for less than five minutes, during which he took zero questions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 19:42:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is That REALLY a Homeless Shelter for Needy Americans or…Illegal Alien Housing?</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/13/is-that-really-a-homeless-shelter-for-needy-americans-orillegal-alien-housing/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Promoting open border and amnesty policies is increasingly tricky business for the left. After all, illegal immigration is a major issue for most voters, a concern that’s apparently deepening as shown by a new CBS News poll revealing that 62 percent of Americans support, “in principle, a new government program to deport all undocumented immigrants [...] The post Is That REALLY a Homeless Shelter for Needy Americans or…Illegal Alien Housing? appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 14:49:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Former 1/6 Committee Chair Tells Trump To Go Home And Wait For His Sentencing</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/13/former-1-6-committee-chair-tells-trump-to-go-home-and-wait-for-his-sentencing.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Former 1/6 Committee Chair Rep. Bennie Thompson (D-MS) told Trump to go back to Mar-a-Lago and wait for his felony sentencing.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 18:57:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Crisis on NATO’s Eastern Border Shows How Anti-Western Regimes Weaponize Illegal Mass Migration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/12/crisis-on-natos-eastern-border-shows-how-anti-western-regimes-weaponize-illegal-mass-migration/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>A Polish soldier is dead, after being stabbed by an illegal migrant making an attempted incursion from the territory of neighboring Belarus. This incident represents a dangerous escalation of a “hybrid war” that has been ongoing on the eastern flank of NATO since 2021. To read the rest of the article click here The post Crisis on NATO’s Eastern Border Shows How Anti-Western Regimes Weaponize Illegal Mass Migration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 19:56:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Releases New Devastating Swing State Ad Against Insurrectionist In Chief Trump</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/13/biden-releases-new-devastating-swing-state-ad-against-insurrectionist-in-chief-trump.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>The Biden campaign responded to Trump returning to the Capitol by reminding voters in swing states of his support for the 1/6 insurrectionists.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 17:59:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eight Illegal Aliens with Ties to ISIS Arrested Inside the U.S</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/12/eight-illegal-aliens-with-ties-to-isis-arrested-inside-the-u-s/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>In the latest alarming national security incident, eight suspected terrorists with ties to ISIS were arrested on immigration violations in a joint U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE) in conjunction with the FBI Joint Terrorism Task Force. To read the rest of the article click here The post Eight Illegal Aliens with Ties to ISIS Arrested Inside the U.S appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 18:36:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rep. Jasmine Crockett Blasts Republicans For Welcoming Trump Back To The Capitol He Attacked</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/13/rep-jasmine-crockett-blasts-republicans-for-welcoming-trump-back-to-the-capitol-he-attacked.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Rep. Jasmine Crockett (D-TX) called out Republicans in Congress for inviting Trump back to the place that he tried to attack on 1/6.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 17:08:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>House Committee Hears Testimony on Effects of the Border Crisis in North Dakota</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/11/house-committee-hears-testimony-on-effects-of-the-border-crisis-in-north-dakota/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>The House Judiciary Subcommittee on Immigration Integrity, Security, and Enforcement, recently held a field hearing to discuss the effects of the border crisis in North Dakota. To read the rest of the article click here The post House Committee Hears Testimony on Effects of the Border Crisis in North Dakota appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 19:51:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Joe Biden Is Leading The Biggest US Small Business Boom In 25 Years</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/12/biden-small-business-boom.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>The Small Business Administration (SBA) announced that 18.1 million new business applications have been filed since Biden took office, the biggest boom in 25 years.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 23:47:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gun-Wielding Illegal Alien Allegedly Shoots Two NYPD Officers in Latest Migrant Crime Incident</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/05/gun-wielding-illegal-alien-allegedly-shoots-two-nypd-officers-in-latest-migrant-crime-incident/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>In the early hours of June 3, 2024, NYPD officers Christopher Abreu and Richard Yarusso were investigating a robbery when they encountered 19-year-old Bernardo Castro Mata, an illegal alien from Venezuela, driving a motorized scooter with no plates the wrong way down a street. To read the rest of the article click here The post Gun-Wielding Illegal Alien Allegedly Shoots Two NYPD Officers in Latest Migrant Crime Incident appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 18:21:58 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>