<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 03:52:07 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Steve Bannon Reports To Prison Monday After SCOTUS Rejection</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/28/steve-bannon-reports-to-prison-monday-after-scotus-rejection.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Steve Bannon will report to prison on Monday after the Supreme Court declined to hear his appeal.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 20:58:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sanctuary Politicians Need to Stop Lying and Admit the Obvious</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/28/sanctuary-politicians-need-to-stop-lying-and-admit-the-obvious/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Sanctuary politicians are getting nervous, and understandably so. The public is outraged over the surge of high-profile crimes allegedly committed by illegal aliens including the recent murder of 12-year old Jocelyn Nungaray in Houston, the sexual assault of a 13-year-old girl in New York City, and the Maryland rape and murder of Rachel Morin, mother [...] The post Sanctuary Politicians Need to Stop Lying and Admit the Obvious appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 17:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>About Last Night…</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/28/about-last-night-bebate.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Like many incumbents before him, Biden had a bad debate. But a bad debate does not a bad president make.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 19:40:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>White House Leaves Out Key Fact in Statements on Alleged Murders of Americans by Illegal Aliens</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/27/white-house-leaves-out-key-fact-in-statements-on-alleged-murders-of-americans-by-illegal-aliens/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Over the past two weeks, Americans have seen numerous stories about horrific crimes allegedly committed by illegal aliens. The White House commented on two cases but failed to mention a key fact. To read the rest of the article click here The post White House Leaves Out Key Fact in Statements on Alleged Murders of Americans by Illegal Aliens appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 15:22:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>An On Fire Joe Biden Directly Address His Debate Performance</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/28/joe-bifden-debate-performance-nc.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>President Joe Biden looked and sounded completely different as he honestly spoke about his debate performance during a rally in North Carolina.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 19:04:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Drive Down the Cost of Medical Care for Illegals? Just Ask</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/27/how-to-drive-down-the-cost-of-medical-care-for-illegals-just-ask/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>The ballooning costs of medical care for illegal aliens is a huge burden on states and cities across the U.S. FAIR’s 2023 cost study found that at least $21 billion in taxpayer funds are spent by states and local governments on healthcare for illegal aliens every year, and that number is only increasing as the [...] The post How to Drive Down the Cost of Medical Care for Illegals? Just Ask appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 15:13:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Crowd Chants Lock Him Up As Biden Calls Trump A One Man Crime Wave</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/28/biden-trump-crime-wave.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>A fired up and totally different President Joe Biden told supporters in North Carolina that Trump is a one man crime wave as the crowd chanted lock him up.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 18:43:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Great Paradox: How Unchecked Mass Migration Hurts Migrants</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/25/the-great-paradox-how-unchecked-mass-migration-hurts-migrants/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Pro-mass-migration voices depict mass migration as an unqualified good for everyone involved, minimizing or refusing to even acknowledge negative side effects or costs. To read the rest of the article click here The post The Great Paradox: How Unchecked Mass Migration Hurts Migrants appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 20:19:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rep. Jim Clyburn Tells Nervous Democrats To “Chill Out”</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/28/rep-jim-clyburn-tells-nervous-democrats-to-chill-out.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Rep. Jim Clyburn (D-SC) had a message for Democrats who are nervous about Biden's debate performance. He advised Democrats to chill out.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 18:11:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Senators Move to Overturn Biden Rule, Prevent Further Exploitation of Unaccompanied Children</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/25/senators-move-to-overturn-biden-rule-prevent-further-exploitation-of-unaccompanied-children-3/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Earlier this month, Senator Chuck Grassley (R-Iowa) introduced S.J. Res. 94, a Congressional Review Act (CRA) resolution to overturn the Biden administration’s Unaccompanied Children Program Foundational Rule. To read the rest of the article click here The post Senators Move to Overturn Biden Rule, Prevent Further Exploitation of Unaccompanied Children appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 17:27:09 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>