<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 07:24:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Stephen Colbert Perfectly Takes Down Trump’s Republican Convention Enterance</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/17/stephen-colbert-trump-convention.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Stephen Colbert described Trump's entrance during the second night of the GOP convention as being like Rocky Balboa if Rocky fought for Russia.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 05:59:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Voting Integrity Matters at the Federal AND Local Levels</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/16/voting-integrity-matters-at-the-federal-and-local-levels/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>University of Virginia political analyst Larry Sabato once said with intended obviousness, “every election is determined by the people who show up.” Yet now, in an era with endlessly increasing illegal immigration that risks undermining the electorate, the statement is woefully insufficient. What matters most to the integrity of America’s representative democracy is to ensure [...] The post Voting Integrity Matters at the Federal AND Local Levels appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 15:03:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden To Support Term Limits For Supreme Court Justices</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/16/biden-to-support-term-limits-for-supreme-court-justices.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>President Joe Biden is set to call for major changes to the Supreme Court, including ethics reform and term limits for Justices.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 23:08:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Warning for New Yorkers: Moped-Riding Illegal Aliens Allegedly Robbing Outdoor Diners</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/12/warning-for-new-yorkers-moped-riding-illegal-aliens-allegedly-robbing-outdoor-diners/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Imagine this: you’re enjoying a warm summer evening in New York City, dining al fresco, proudly wearing the luxury watch you worked so hard to buy. Suddenly, a pair of armed, moped-riding bandits appear, robbing you of your prized possession. And it turns out these suspected criminals are reportedly newly-arrived illegal aliens. To read the [...] The post Warning for New Yorkers: Moped-Riding Illegal Aliens Allegedly Robbing Outdoor Diners appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 19:43:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Leaked Phone Calls Shows Trump Colluding With RFK Jr.</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/16/leaked-phone-calls-shows-trump-colluding-with-rfk-jr.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>In a leaked call, Trump can be heard trying to woo RFK Jr. with promises of all the big things that they can do together in the 2024 campaign.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 22:22:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Illegal Aliens Aren’t the Only Ones Migrating. Americans are Too</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/10/illegal-aliens-arent-the-only-ones-migrating-americans-are-too/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>IRS data shows that American taxpayers are leaving sanctuary states for states that actually enforce the law. The negative impact of misguided sanctuary policies goes well beyond simply releasing dangerous criminals back onto the streets, it also impacts state economies and tax bases. To read the rest of the article click here The post Illegal Aliens Aren’t the Only Ones Migrating. Americans are Too appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:02:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When You See J.D. Vance Think Marjorie Taylor Greene</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/16/jd-vance-marjorie-taylor-greene.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>When you think of JD Vance, see MTG. It's what she wants. Independent voters will no doubt be persuaded, but perhaps not in the direction the Republican thinks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:53:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Massachusetts Governor Maura Healey’s Charade at the Southern Border</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/02/massachusetts-governor-maura-healeys-charade-at-the-southern-border/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Things are pretty dire in the illegal alien sanctuary Bay State. As FAIR’s 2023 report showed, 393,000 illegal aliens and their U.S.-born children live in Massachusetts, costing taxpayers $2.9 billion annually for health care, education, criminal justice, and general welfare. To read the rest of the article click here The post Massachusetts Governor Maura Healey’s Charade at the Southern Border appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:51:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Joe Scarborough Says NBC Gave Him No Good Answer For Why He Was Pulled Off The Air</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/16/joe-scarborough-nbc-trump-rally-shooting.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Joe Scarborough addressed his network's baffling decision to pull the Morning Joe show on Monday, saying that they were told that the network would be running breaking news all morning but that didn't happen.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 16:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayorkas Lies to the American People During Arizona Visit</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/01/mayorkas-lies-to-the-american-people-during-arizona-visit/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Recently impeached Department of Homeland Security Secretary Alejandro Mayorkas visited Tucson, Arizona, and attempted to sell President Biden’s recent executive action as having worked to reduce the number of illegal crossings at the southern border. To read the rest of the article click here The post Mayorkas Lies to the American People During Arizona Visit appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 19:31:50 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>