<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 06:54:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Trump’s Audience Fell Asleep On Him During His Acceptance Speech</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/19/trumps-audience-fell-asleep-on-him-during-his-acceptance-speech.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Donald Trump rambled and babbled for more than 90 minutes, and even his most adoring fans at the Republican convention got so bored that they fell asleep.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 05:51:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DHS Extends Temporary Protected Status to Haitians, Encouraging More Illegal Immigration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/17/dhs-extends-temporary-protected-status-to-haitians-encouraging-more-illegal-immigration/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Extending and re-designating TPS to Haitian nationals, at a time of unprecedented illegal immigration to the United States, is yet another example of how the Biden administration’s open-border agenda prioritizes illegal aliens over American citizens. To read the rest of the article click here The post DHS Extends Temporary Protected Status to Haitians, Encouraging More Illegal Immigration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 21:34:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Shows He’s Still Unfit For Office With Disastrous Acceptance Speech</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/19/trump-acceptance-speech-2024.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Donald Trump showed that nothing has changed as he used the person who died at his rally as a prop in set piece, rambled and brought his old grievances during his nomination acceptance speech.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 05:16:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Voting Integrity Matters at the Federal AND Local Levels</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/16/voting-integrity-matters-at-the-federal-and-local-levels/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>University of Virginia political analyst Larry Sabato once said with intended obviousness, “every election is determined by the people who show up.” Yet now, in an era with endlessly increasing illegal immigration that risks undermining the electorate, the statement is woefully insufficient. What matters most to the integrity of America’s representative democracy is to ensure [...] The post Voting Integrity Matters at the Federal AND Local Levels appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 15:03:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>America Ignores J.D. Vance In Convention Speech Flop</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/18/america-ignores-j-d-vance-in-convention-speech-flop.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>J.D. Vance's vice presidential nominee acceptance speech drew 5 million fewer viewers than Mike Pence's speech in 2016.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 22:55:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Warning for New Yorkers: Moped-Riding Illegal Aliens Allegedly Robbing Outdoor Diners</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/12/warning-for-new-yorkers-moped-riding-illegal-aliens-allegedly-robbing-outdoor-diners/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Imagine this: you’re enjoying a warm summer evening in New York City, dining al fresco, proudly wearing the luxury watch you worked so hard to buy. Suddenly, a pair of armed, moped-riding bandits appear, robbing you of your prized possession. And it turns out these suspected criminals are reportedly newly-arrived illegal aliens. To read the [...] The post Warning for New Yorkers: Moped-Riding Illegal Aliens Allegedly Robbing Outdoor Diners appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 19:43:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aileen Cannon Backfires As Hunter Biden Moves To Have Conviction Dismissed</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/18/aileen-cannon-backfires-as-hunter-biden-moves-to-have-conviction-dismissed.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Hunter Biden's lawyers are using Aileen Cannon's order dismissing the Trump classified documents case to request the dismissal of his own special counsel conviction.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 21:49:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Illegal Aliens Aren’t the Only Ones Migrating. Americans are Too</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/10/illegal-aliens-arent-the-only-ones-migrating-americans-are-too/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>IRS data shows that American taxpayers are leaving sanctuary states for states that actually enforce the law. The negative impact of misguided sanctuary policies goes well beyond simply releasing dangerous criminals back onto the streets, it also impacts state economies and tax bases. To read the rest of the article click here The post Illegal Aliens Aren’t the Only Ones Migrating. Americans are Too appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:02:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Has Provided More Medical Updates About His COVID Than Trump Has About Assassination Attempt</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/18/biden-has-provided-more-medical-updates-about-his-covid-than-trump-has-about-assassination-attempt.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>President Biden released a letter from his doctor about his COVID treatment, which is one more official document than Donald Trump has released about the assassination attempt.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 20:12:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Massachusetts Governor Maura Healey’s Charade at the Southern Border</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/02/massachusetts-governor-maura-healeys-charade-at-the-southern-border/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Things are pretty dire in the illegal alien sanctuary Bay State. As FAIR’s 2023 report showed, 393,000 illegal aliens and their U.S.-born children live in Massachusetts, costing taxpayers $2.9 billion annually for health care, education, criminal justice, and general welfare. To read the rest of the article click here The post Massachusetts Governor Maura Healey’s Charade at the Southern Border appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:51:45 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>