<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:39:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Sean Hannity Couldn’t Save Trump For Disastrous Crash And Burn</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/06/sean-hannity-couldnt-save-trump-for-disastrous-crash-and-burn.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Sean Hannity tried to get Trump to say that he didn't want to use the presidency for revenge, but Trump refused to do it.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 05:14:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gun-Wielding Illegal Alien Allegedly Shoots Two NYPD Officers in Latest Migrant Crime Incident</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/05/gun-wielding-illegal-alien-allegedly-shoots-two-nypd-officers-in-latest-migrant-crime-incident/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>In the early hours of June 3, 2024, NYPD officers Christopher Abreu and Richard Yarusso were investigating a robbery when they encountered 19-year-old Bernardo Castro Mata, an illegal alien from Venezuela, driving a motorized scooter with no plates the wrong way down a street. To read the rest of the article click here The post Gun-Wielding Illegal Alien Allegedly Shoots Two NYPD Officers in Latest Migrant Crime Incident appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 18:21:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Could Be Charged With Gun Crimes After Felony Conviction</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/05/trump-could-be-charged-with-gun-law-crimes-after-felony-conviction.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Trump is expected to have his gun license revoked and could be violating gun laws by being a convicted felon who still has a gun in Florida.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 23:03:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Europe May Face a Second Middle Eastern Migrant Crisis</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/05/europe-may-face-a-second-middle-eastern-migrant-crisis/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Europe may once again be about to receive mass waves of migrants from the Middle East, invoking memories of the 2015-2016 period, when then-German Chancellor Angela Merkel invited Syrians (and others) to come to Europe without limitation. To read the rest of the article click here The post Europe May Face a Second Middle Eastern Migrant Crisis appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 18:11:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Georgia Appeals Court Delays Trump RICO Trial</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/05/georgia-appeals-court-delays-trump-rico-trial.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>A Georgia appeals court has delayed Trump's RICO trial until they hear the appeal of the decision not to disqualify DA Fani Willis.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 22:34:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Baltimore Has an Obvious Problem. The Fix is Fairly Obvious Too.</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/05/baltimore-has-an-obvious-problem-the-fix-is-fairly-obvious-too/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>“Baltimore County releases illegal immigrants charged with crimes despite federal requests,” declared a recent headline on the local FOX 45 news site. To read the rest of the article click here The post Baltimore Has an Obvious Problem. The Fix is Fairly Obvious Too. appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 14:28:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hakeem Jeffries Goes Off After Byron Donalds Suggests Black People Were Better Off During Jim Crow</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/05/hakeem-jeffries-goes-off-after-byron-donalds-suggests-black-people-were-better-off-during-jim-crow.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>House Democratic Leader Hakeem Jeffries (D-NY) called Rep. Byron Donalds's comments ignorant after he suggested black people were better off during Jim Crow.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 21:59:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fairfax County, Virginia: Public Schools, Limited English Proficiency, and the Opportunity Cost of Mass Migration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/03/fairfax-county-virginia-public-schools-limited-english-proficiency-and-the-opportunity-cost-of-mass-migration/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>In economics, opportunity cost is defined as “the potential benefits that a business, an investor, or an individual consumer misses out on when choosing one alternative over another.” A dollar spent on A cannot be simultaneously spent on B. To read the rest of the article click here The post Fairfax County, Virginia: Public Schools, Limited English Proficiency, and the Opportunity Cost of Mass Migration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 21:36:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>James Comer And Jim Jordan Humiliate Themselves With Criminal Referral Of Hunter And James Biden To DOJ</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/05/james-comer-jim-jordan-biden-criminal-referral.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Reps. James Comer and Jim Jordan embarrassingly have made criminal referrals of Hunter and James Biden to the DOJ for false testimony.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 20:06:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Massachusetts Response to its Migrant Crisis: Offer Even More Benefits</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/31/massachusetts-response-to-its-migrant-crisis-offer-even-more-benefits/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>If any state in America proves the axiom that “things in motion stay in motion” it’s Massachusetts. What else but perpetual motion physics can explain the logic behind the Bay State’s non-stop granting of benefits to illegal aliens? To read the rest of the article click here The post Massachusetts Response to its Migrant Crisis: Offer Even More Benefits appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 21:12:58 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>