<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 06:39:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>J.D. Vance Hits A New Low By Blaming Biden For Trump Shooting</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/13/j-d-vance-hits-a-new-low-by-blaming-biden-for-trump-shooting.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Sen. J.D. Vance's statement on the Trump rally shooting was a new low, even by the already low standards that he has established for himself.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 02:24:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Warning for New Yorkers: Moped-Riding Illegal Aliens Allegedly Robbing Outdoor Diners</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/12/warning-for-new-yorkers-moped-riding-illegal-aliens-allegedly-robbing-outdoor-diners/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Imagine this: you’re enjoying a warm summer evening in New York City, dining al fresco, proudly wearing the luxury watch you worked so hard to buy. Suddenly, a pair of armed, moped-riding bandits appear, robbing you of your prized possession. And it turns out these suspected criminals are reportedly newly-arrived illegal aliens. To read the [...] The post Warning for New Yorkers: Moped-Riding Illegal Aliens Allegedly Robbing Outdoor Diners appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 19:43:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Tries To Unify The Nation After Trump Rally Shooting As Republicans Lose Their Minds</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/13/biden-tries-to-unify-the-nation-after-trump-rally-shooting-as-republicans-lose-their-minds.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>President Biden addressed the nation after the shooting at Donald Trump's Pennsylvania rally and denounced political violence while calling for national unity.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 02:01:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Illegal Aliens Aren’t the Only Ones Migrating. Americans are Too</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/10/illegal-aliens-arent-the-only-ones-migrating-americans-are-too/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>IRS data shows that American taxpayers are leaving sanctuary states for states that actually enforce the law. The negative impact of misguided sanctuary policies goes well beyond simply releasing dangerous criminals back onto the streets, it also impacts state economies and tax bases. To read the rest of the article click here The post Illegal Aliens Aren’t the Only Ones Migrating. Americans are Too appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:02:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>House Republican Demands That Biden Be Criminally Charged For Attempted Trump Assassination</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/13/house-republican-demands-that-biden-be-criminally-charged-for-attempted-trump-assassination.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Rep. Mike Collins (R-GA) claimed that Biden ordered Trump assassinated, and demanded that the Butler County, PA DA criminally charge Joe Biden for trying to assassinate Trump.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 00:35:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Massachusetts Governor Maura Healey’s Charade at the Southern Border</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/02/massachusetts-governor-maura-healeys-charade-at-the-southern-border/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Things are pretty dire in the illegal alien sanctuary Bay State. As FAIR’s 2023 report showed, 393,000 illegal aliens and their U.S.-born children live in Massachusetts, costing taxpayers $2.9 billion annually for health care, education, criminal justice, and general welfare. To read the rest of the article click here The post Massachusetts Governor Maura Healey’s Charade at the Southern Border appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:51:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Secret Service Investigating Potential Shots Fired At Trump</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/13/secret-service-investigating-potential-shots-fired-at-trump.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>The Secret Service has announced that they are investigating an incident at Trump's rally in Butler, PA.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 00:11:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayorkas Lies to the American People During Arizona Visit</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/01/mayorkas-lies-to-the-american-people-during-arizona-visit/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Recently impeached Department of Homeland Security Secretary Alejandro Mayorkas visited Tucson, Arizona, and attempted to sell President Biden’s recent executive action as having worked to reduce the number of illegal crossings at the southern border. To read the rest of the article click here The post Mayorkas Lies to the American People During Arizona Visit appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 19:31:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Rushed Off Stage After Shots Fired At Him During Pennsylvania Rally</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/13/trump-rushed-off-stage-after-shots-fired-at-him-during-pennsylvania-rally.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Donald Trump was speaking at a campaign rally in Butler, PA when shots rang out and Trump was rushed off the stage by Secret Service.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 23:40:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sanctuary Politicians Need to Stop Lying and Admit the Obvious</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/28/sanctuary-politicians-need-to-stop-lying-and-admit-the-obvious/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Sanctuary politicians are getting nervous, and understandably so. The public is outraged over the surge of high-profile crimes allegedly committed by illegal aliens including the recent murder of 12-year old Jocelyn Nungaray in Houston, the sexual assault of a 13-year-old girl in New York City, and the Maryland rape and murder of Rachel Morin, mother [...] The post Sanctuary Politicians Need to Stop Lying and Admit the Obvious appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 17:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>