<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 06:52:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Democrats Abandon Effort To Remove Joe Biden As Nominee</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/14/democrats-abandon-effort-to-remove-joe-biden-as-nomnee.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>It is being reported that those Democrats who were trying to force President Biden to step aside and leave the presidential race are giving up their effort.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 20:27:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Warning for New Yorkers: Moped-Riding Illegal Aliens Allegedly Robbing Outdoor Diners</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/12/warning-for-new-yorkers-moped-riding-illegal-aliens-allegedly-robbing-outdoor-diners/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Imagine this: you’re enjoying a warm summer evening in New York City, dining al fresco, proudly wearing the luxury watch you worked so hard to buy. Suddenly, a pair of armed, moped-riding bandits appear, robbing you of your prized possession. And it turns out these suspected criminals are reportedly newly-arrived illegal aliens. To read the [...] The post Warning for New Yorkers: Moped-Riding Illegal Aliens Allegedly Robbing Outdoor Diners appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 19:43:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Debunks MAGA Claim That Trump Was Denied Extra Security</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/14/biden-debunks-maga-claim-that-trump-was-denied-extra-security.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>President Biden told the nation that he has always personally authorized that Trump, as a former president and the Republican nominee, has the highest level of security.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 19:56:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Illegal Aliens Aren’t the Only Ones Migrating. Americans are Too</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/10/illegal-aliens-arent-the-only-ones-migrating-americans-are-too/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>IRS data shows that American taxpayers are leaving sanctuary states for states that actually enforce the law. The negative impact of misguided sanctuary policies goes well beyond simply releasing dangerous criminals back onto the streets, it also impacts state economies and tax bases. To read the rest of the article click here The post Illegal Aliens Aren’t the Only Ones Migrating. Americans are Too appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:02:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Obama Birther Melania Trump Now Wants National Unity</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/14/obama-birther-melania-trump-now-wants-national-unity.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>In a statement, Melania Trump called for the nation to unify, even though she along with her husband have spent years dividing the country.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 18:42:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Massachusetts Governor Maura Healey’s Charade at the Southern Border</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/02/massachusetts-governor-maura-healeys-charade-at-the-southern-border/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Things are pretty dire in the illegal alien sanctuary Bay State. As FAIR’s 2023 report showed, 393,000 illegal aliens and their U.S.-born children live in Massachusetts, costing taxpayers $2.9 billion annually for health care, education, criminal justice, and general welfare. To read the rest of the article click here The post Massachusetts Governor Maura Healey’s Charade at the Southern Border appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:51:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Secret Service Debunks MAGA Lie That Biden Denied Trump Extra Security</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/14/secret-service-debunks-maga-lie-that-biden-denied-trump-extra-security.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>The Secret Service pushed back on a MAGA assertion that President Biden denied a request for extra security to be provided to Trump.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 17:24:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayorkas Lies to the American People During Arizona Visit</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/01/mayorkas-lies-to-the-american-people-during-arizona-visit/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Recently impeached Department of Homeland Security Secretary Alejandro Mayorkas visited Tucson, Arizona, and attempted to sell President Biden’s recent executive action as having worked to reduce the number of illegal crossings at the southern border. To read the rest of the article click here The post Mayorkas Lies to the American People During Arizona Visit appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 19:31:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>That Time J.D. Vance Called Trump ‘America’s Hitler’</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/14/that-time-j-d-vance-called-trump-americas-hitler.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>In 2016, J.D. Vance's college roommate says he called Donald Trump "America's Hitler." In 2024, J.D. Vance blamed President Biden's "rhetoric" for the shooting carried out by someone who appears to have been a registered Republican.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 16:44:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sanctuary Politicians Need to Stop Lying and Admit the Obvious</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/28/sanctuary-politicians-need-to-stop-lying-and-admit-the-obvious/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Sanctuary politicians are getting nervous, and understandably so. The public is outraged over the surge of high-profile crimes allegedly committed by illegal aliens including the recent murder of 12-year old Jocelyn Nungaray in Houston, the sexual assault of a 13-year-old girl in New York City, and the Maryland rape and murder of Rachel Morin, mother [...] The post Sanctuary Politicians Need to Stop Lying and Admit the Obvious appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 17:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>