<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 16:32:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Hunter Biden Gives Fox News A Big New Problem</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/04/29/hunter-biden-fox-news.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/Hunter-Biden-Fox-News.jpg</image_url><description>Hunter Biden's legal team is vowing to hold Fox News accountable for attacking Hunter Biden with lies for financial gain.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 21:16:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mexican Diplomat’s Dishonest Claims About Illegal Alien Law-Breaking Do Not Stand Up to Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/29/mexican-diplomats-dishonest-claims-about-illegal-alien-law-breaking-do-not-stand-up-to-scrutiny/</link><description>Mexican diplomats and politicians have a long history of lecturing Americans on illegal immigration, along with attempting to meddle in U.S. politics in ways that favor illegal aliens while undermining our border security and rule of law. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Mexican Diplomat’s Dishonest Claims About Illegal Alien Law-Breaking Do Not Stand Up to Scrutiny appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 19:04:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Kicks Kari Lake Out Of Mar-a-Lago And Worries She’s Been Taping Him</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/04/29/trump-kicks-kari-lake-out-of-mar-a-lago-and-worries-shes-been-taping-him.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Kari-Lake-Trump-Giant.jpg</image_url><description>Trump gave Kari Lake the boot from Mar-a-Lago and expressed surprise that Lake taped conversations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 20:42:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>House Committee Aims to Stop Illegal Aliens from Slanting Congressional Apportionment</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/26/house-committee-aims-to-stop-illegal-aliens-from-slanting-congressional-apportionment/</link><description>The House Committee on Oversight and Accountability recently approved Congressmen Chuck Edwards’ (R-N.C.) and Warren Davidson’s (R-Ohio) H.R. 7109, the Equal Representation Act. To read the rest of the article click here
The post House Committee Aims to Stop Illegal Aliens from Slanting Congressional Apportionment appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 19:34:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Bitter New York Times Is Now Complaining About Colin Jost</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/04/29/new-york-times-colin-jost.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/2018-06-28T203701Z_1_LYNXMPEE5R2D8_RTROPTP_3_MARYLAND-SHOOTING.jpg</image_url><description>The New York Times is upset and complaining because Colin Jost made a joke about them needing Wordle to survive financially.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 18:35:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Illegal Aliens Flown to Martha’s Vineyard Classified as Victims and Given Benefits</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/24/illegal-aliens-flown-to-marthas-vineyard-classified-as-victims-and-given-benefits/</link><description>Some of the illegal aliens that were flown from Florida to Martha’s Vineyard by Governor DeSantis in 2022 now have safe harbor from deportation and employment authorization documents allowing them to stay and work in the United States. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Illegal Aliens Flown to Martha’s Vineyard Classified as Victims and Given Benefits appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:53:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hunter Biden Threatens Fox News With Defamation Lawsuit</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/04/29/hunter-biden-threatens-fox-news-with-defamation-lawsuit.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Hunter-Biden-oversight-committee.jpg</image_url><description>Lawyers for Hunter Biden have threatened to sue Fox News for defamation if they don't correct their bogus bribery allegation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 17:54:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Clarity of Words is the Enemy of Mass Immigration Advocates</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/23/clarity-of-words-is-the-enemy-of-mass-immigration-advocates/</link><description>In his essay, “Politics and the English Language,” George Orwell observed that political language, by its very nature, is crafted to deceive and manipulate. He argued that politicians and propagandists deliberately twist language into falsehoods, so they become seemingly plausible statements hiding true agendas. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Clarity of Words is the Enemy of Mass Immigration Advocates appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 19:53:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Is Freaking Out As His RFK Jr. Problem Worsens</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/04/28/trump-rfk-jr-freakout.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/RFK-Jr-Trump.jpg</image_url><description>As a new poll shows RFK Jr. hurting Trump in critical swing states, the ex-president is lashing out that the third party monster he created.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 17:41:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Italy and America: Shared Fight with Illegal Immigration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/23/italy-and-america-shared-fight-with-illegal-immigration/</link><description>Italy has struggled with mass migration, much of it composed of fraudulent “asylum seekers” from Africa. The key route of entry is from Africa by boat, with the island of Lampedusa close to the African mainland as the primary landing point. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Italy and America: Shared Fight with Illegal Immigration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 16:13:17 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>