<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 06:51:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Fox News Poll Has Terrible News For Trump In Pennsylvania</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/26/fox-news-pennsylvania-poll.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>If Trump thought Biden stepping aside would help him in Pennsylvania, he was wrong as Kamala Harris has tied the ex-president in the Keystone State and Gov. Josh Shapiro is wildly popular.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 23:45:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Did Biden Really Say Our Borders are More Secure than When He Took Office?</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/26/did-biden-really-say-our-borders-are-more-secure-than-when-he-took-office/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Every politician is prone to exaggerating their accomplishments in an attempt to define their legacy in the most positive possible terms. President Biden is certainly no exception. In his address to the nation on Wednesday evening, after he announced his decision to abandon his 2024 reelection bid, the president ticked off a long list of [...] The post Did Biden Really Say Our Borders are More Secure than When He Took Office? appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 21:24:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Even Rupert Murdoch’s Wall Street Journal Finds Kamala Harris Has Wiped Out Trump’s Lead</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/26/even-rupert-murdochs-wall-street-journal-finds-kamala-harris-has-wiped-out-trumps-lead.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Even the conservative Rupert Murdoch-owned Wall Street Journal released a poll showing that Donald Trump's lead is gone.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 23:15:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maine Immigration Fanatics Focus on Efficiency and Cost to Increase Flows</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/26/maine-immigration-fanatics-focus-on-efficiency-and-cost-to-increase-flows/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Mass immigration advocates in Maine have a problem. They’ve overachieved their goals and now need to adjust their strategy to appease taxpayers alarmed over skyrocketing costs to house migrants. To read the rest of the article click here The post Maine Immigration Fanatics Focus on Efficiency and Cost to Increase Flows appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 17:31:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Harris Campaign Says Trump Is Hiding At Mar-a-Lago And Refusing To Debate</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/26/harris-campaign-says-trump-is-hiding-at-mar-a-lago-and-refusing-to-debate.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>The Harris campaign responded to Trump trying to back out of debating the presumptive Democratic nominee by saying that the ex-president is hiding at Mar-a-Lago.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 20:27:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Washington Turns a Blind Eye to Exploited Migrant Children, While their Tormentors Cash In</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/24/washington-turns-a-blind-eye-to-exploited-migrant-children-while-their-tormentors-cash-in/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>On July 17, the Biden-Harris administration’s Department of Justice filed a suit against its largest private housing provider for unaccompanied alien children (UAC) in the United States, alleging that the company, Southwest Key, subjected children to repeated and unwelcome sexual abuse, harassment, rape, solicitation of sex acts, and more. To read the rest of the [...] The post Washington Turns a Blind Eye to Exploited Migrant Children, While their Tormentors Cash In appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 21:03:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Holds A Fake Cabinet Meeting With Netanyahu At Mar-a-Lago</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/26/trump-holds-a-fake-cabinet-meeting-with-netanyahu-at-mar-a-lago.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>In a truly weird scene, Trump tried to stage a cabinet meeting in a dark room in Mar-a-Lago with Netanyahu.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 18:55:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kamala Harris Never Consulted with Border Patrol Chiefs Despite Record Illegal Immigration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/24/kamala-harris-never-consulted-with-border-patrol-chiefs-despite-record-illegal-immigration/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>In the early months of the Biden administration, Vice President Kamala Harris was tasked with addressing the border crisis by tackling its “root causes.” The results speak for themselves. To read the rest of the article click here The post Kamala Harris Never Consulted with Border Patrol Chiefs Despite Record Illegal Immigration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 17:56:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Release New Ronny Jackson Letter Adding To Speculation Ex-President Wasn’t Shot</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/26/trump-release-new-ronny-jackson-letter-adding-to-speculation-ex-president-wasnt-shot.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Rep. Ronny Jackson (R-TX) wrote another letter for Trump claiming that the ex-president was shot and attacking the FBI Director, stating that the cause of Trump's ear wound is unknown at this time.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 17:58:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Biden’s Border Crisis is Destroying Heartland America: A Look at Springfield, Ohio</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/19/how-bidens-border-crisis-is-destroying-heartland-america-a-look-at-springfield-ohio/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>You’ve seen the videos of migrants blatantly violating our immigration laws by illegally crossing the southern border, and you are probably one of the many Americans rightfully horrified by the recent stories of illegal alien crime. To read the rest of the article click here The post How Biden’s Border Crisis is Destroying Heartland America: A Look at Springfield, Ohio appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 21:58:46 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>