<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 15:43:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Biden Makes His Move To Expose Debate Coward Trump</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/04/26/biden-makes-his-move-to-expose-debate-coward-trump.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/2021-03-16T000000Z_776881412_RC2ICM9SNQFE_RTRMADP_3_USA-ELECTION-CYBER-200x200.jpg</image_url><description>President Biden put the pressure on Trump, as he told Howard Stern that he is willing to debate the ex-president.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 20:07:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>House Committee Aims to Stop Illegal Aliens from Slanting Congressional Apportionment</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/26/house-committee-aims-to-stop-illegal-aliens-from-slanting-congressional-apportionment/</link><description>The House Committee on Oversight and Accountability recently approved Congressmen Chuck Edwards’ (R-N.C.) and Warren Davidson’s (R-Ohio) H.R. 7109, the Equal Representation Act. To read the rest of the article click here
The post House Committee Aims to Stop Illegal Aliens from Slanting Congressional Apportionment appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 19:34:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Gives Howard Stern An Interview Instead Of The New York Times</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/04/26/biden-gives-howard-stern-an-interview-instead-of-the-new-york-times.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/Biden-stern.jpg</image_url><description>President Biden has responded to The New York Times complaining about not getting an interview with him by giving Howard Stern an exclusive interview.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 16:02:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Illegal Aliens Flown to Martha’s Vineyard Classified as Victims and Given Benefits</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/24/illegal-aliens-flown-to-marthas-vineyard-classified-as-victims-and-given-benefits/</link><description>Some of the illegal aliens that were flown from Florida to Martha’s Vineyard by Governor DeSantis in 2022 now have safe harbor from deportation and employment authorization documents allowing them to stay and work in the United States. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Illegal Aliens Flown to Martha’s Vineyard Classified as Victims and Given Benefits appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:53:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Is Sound Asleep As His Lawyer Cross Examines David Pecker</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/04/26/trump-is-sound-asleep-as-his-lawyer-cross-examines-david-pecker.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/Trump-hush-money-trial-3.jpg</image_url><description>Low energy Trump has returned to court as he is taking a deep sleep nap as his lawyer cross examines David Pecker.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 15:39:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Clarity of Words is the Enemy of Mass Immigration Advocates</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/23/clarity-of-words-is-the-enemy-of-mass-immigration-advocates/</link><description>In his essay, “Politics and the English Language,” George Orwell observed that political language, by its very nature, is crafted to deceive and manipulate. He argued that politicians and propagandists deliberately twist language into falsehoods, so they become seemingly plausible statements hiding true agendas. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Clarity of Words is the Enemy of Mass Immigration Advocates appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 19:53:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>David Pecker Has Trump So Rattled That He Just Melted Down Outside Court</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/04/25/david-pecker-has-trump-so-rattled-that-he-just-melted-down-outside-the-courthouse.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/Trump-Pecker-testimony.jpg</image_url><description>Trump made a massive mistake as he tried to change the subject from David Pecker's testimony by calling the racist attack in Charlottesville nothing.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 22:05:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Italy and America: Shared Fight with Illegal Immigration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/23/italy-and-america-shared-fight-with-illegal-immigration/</link><description>Italy has struggled with mass migration, much of it composed of fraudulent “asylum seekers” from Africa. The key route of entry is from Africa by boat, with the island of Lampedusa close to the African mainland as the primary landing point. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Italy and America: Shared Fight with Illegal Immigration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 16:13:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Judge Crushes Trump’s Bid For New E. Jean Carroll Trial</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/04/25/judge-crushes-trumps-bid-for-new-e-jean-carroll-trial.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/e-jean-carroll-lawsuit.jpg</image_url><description>Trump's effort to get a new trial in the E. Jean Carroll case wasn't just rejected by Judge Kaplan. It was crushed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 21:09:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Migrants Refuse to Leave Soccer Field, Forcing High Schoolers to Cancel Game</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/23/migrants-refuse-to-leave-soccer-field-forcing-high-schoolers-to-cancel-game/</link><description>A disturbing scene unfolded at a public field in East Harlem, where a scheduled high school soccer game had to be canceled. About 30 migrants refused to leave the pitch, asserting their presence over the needs of high school soccer players. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Migrants Refuse to Leave Soccer Field, Forcing High Schoolers to Cancel Game appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 15:04:34 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>