<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 01:05:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Trump’s Own Supporters Walked Out On Him In Georgia</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/08/04/trumps-own-supporters-walked-out-on-him-in-georgia.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>Trump spoke for so long at his Georgia rally that sizable chunks of his supporters got up and left while he was still talking.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 23:41:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Massachusetts Migrant Housing Costs: Out of Orbit and Hard to Grasp</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/08/01/massachusetts-migrant-housing-costs-out-of-orbit-and-hard-to-grasp/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>Beyond a certain threshold, numbers become abstract and lose their meaningful context. A quick view of the national debt clock which adds $100,000 of national debt every two-and-a-half seconds to America’s current obligations of $35 trillion is virtually impossible to comprehend. To read the rest of the article click here The post Massachusetts Migrant Housing Costs: Out of Orbit and Hard to Grasp appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 17:55:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Melts Down As Kamala Harris Support Swells</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/08/04/trump-harris-support-swells.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>The Trump campaign reacted to new polling showing that support for Vice President Kamala Harris swelling to new highs by attacking the poll.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 22:20:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>House Passes Resolution Condemning the Biden-Harris Administration’s Failure to Secure the Border</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/08/01/house-passes-resolution-condemning-the-biden-harris-administrations-failure-to-secure-the-border/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>On July 25, the House of Representatives passed H. Res. 1371, condemning President Biden and Vice President Kamala Harris’ failure to secure the border. The resolution passed the same week that President Biden announced he would not seek a second term. To read the rest of the article click here The post House Passes Resolution Condemning the Biden-Harris Administration’s Failure to Secure the Border appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 17:33:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elon Musk Trump PAC Is Under Investigation For Potential Election Law Violations</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/08/04/elon-musk-trump-pac-investigation.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>Elon Musk's pro-Trump PAC is under investigation in Michigan for potentially illegally collecting voter data.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 21:45:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Disastrous Nexus of Biden-Harris Policies:  The Afghan Parole Program and Prohibition on Issuing Notices to Appear</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/31/a-disastrous-nexus-of-biden-harris-policies-the-afghan-parole-program-and-prohibition-on-issuing-notices-to-appear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>On this date three years ago – July 31, 2021 – the first group of Afghan nationals arrived in the United States after the President Biden’s disastrous withdrawal of U.S. troops from the country. To read the rest of the article click here The post A Disastrous Nexus of Biden-Harris Policies: The Afghan Parole Program and Prohibition on Issuing Notices to Appear appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 16:02:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sen. Chris Murphy Shakes Up Fox With The Truth On Kamala Harris And The Border</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/08/04/chris-murphy-fox-news-sunday.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>Sen. Chris Murphy (D-CT) went on Fox News Sunday and delivered the facts about Vice President Kamala Harris and the border.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 21:21:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Human Smuggler Who Facilitated Illegal Entry of Thousands of Aliens Indicted</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/29/human-smuggler-who-facilitated-illegal-entry-of-thousands-of-aliens-indicted/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>On July 18, reports surfaced that Abdul Karim Conteh, a national from Sierra Leone, had been indicted and sanctioned in the United States and arrested in Tijuana, Mexico. Conteh ran a smuggling organization that facilitated the transport of thousands of illegal aliens to the United States through Mexico, including many from terrorism hot spots. To [...] The post Human Smuggler Who Facilitated Illegal Entry of Thousands of Aliens Indicted appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 20:17:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Republican Ex-Government Officials Endorse Kamala Harris</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/08/04/republican-ex-government-officials-endorse-kamala-harris.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>Republicans, including former Trump administration officials, government secretaries, and governors, are endorsing Vice President Kamala Harris.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 20:38:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Did Biden Really Say Our Borders are More Secure than When He Took Office?</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/26/did-biden-really-say-our-borders-are-more-secure-than-when-he-took-office/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>Every politician is prone to exaggerating their accomplishments in an attempt to define their legacy in the most positive possible terms. President Biden is certainly no exception. In his address to the nation on Wednesday evening, after he announced his decision to abandon his 2024 reelection bid, the president ticked off a long list of [...] The post Did Biden Really Say Our Borders are More Secure than When He Took Office? appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 21:24:59 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>