<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 06:48:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Trump Appears To Fall Asleep Multiple Times During Night 3 Of Republican Convention</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/18/trump-appears-to-fall-asleep-multiple-times-during-night-3-of-republican-convention.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Trump appeared to fall asleep both during his son Donald Trump Jr.'s speech and during his running mate J.D. Vance's speech.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 05:17:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DHS Extends Temporary Protected Status to Haitians, Encouraging More Illegal Immigration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/17/dhs-extends-temporary-protected-status-to-haitians-encouraging-more-illegal-immigration/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Extending and re-designating TPS to Haitian nationals, at a time of unprecedented illegal immigration to the United States, is yet another example of how the Biden administration’s open-border agenda prioritizes illegal aliens over American citizens. To read the rest of the article click here The post DHS Extends Temporary Protected Status to Haitians, Encouraging More Illegal Immigration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 21:34:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Has COVID And Will Be Self-Isolating</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/17/biden-has-covid-and-will-be-self-isolating.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>The White House announced that President Biden has tested positive for COVID and will be returning to Delaware to self-isolate.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 00:19:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Voting Integrity Matters at the Federal AND Local Levels</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/16/voting-integrity-matters-at-the-federal-and-local-levels/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>University of Virginia political analyst Larry Sabato once said with intended obviousness, “every election is determined by the people who show up.” Yet now, in an era with endlessly increasing illegal immigration that risks undermining the electorate, the statement is woefully insufficient. What matters most to the integrity of America’s representative democracy is to ensure [...] The post Voting Integrity Matters at the Federal AND Local Levels appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 15:03:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dripping With Insincerity J.D. Vance Flops In First Running Mate Appearance</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/17/dripping-with-insincerity-j-d-vance-flops-in-first-running-mate-appearance.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Sen. J.D. Vance (R-OH) tried to make it sound like he was really concerned for Trump's safety, but he came off as completely insincere.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 20:55:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Warning for New Yorkers: Moped-Riding Illegal Aliens Allegedly Robbing Outdoor Diners</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/12/warning-for-new-yorkers-moped-riding-illegal-aliens-allegedly-robbing-outdoor-diners/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Imagine this: you’re enjoying a warm summer evening in New York City, dining al fresco, proudly wearing the luxury watch you worked so hard to buy. Suddenly, a pair of armed, moped-riding bandits appear, robbing you of your prized possession. And it turns out these suspected criminals are reportedly newly-arrived illegal aliens. To read the [...] The post Warning for New Yorkers: Moped-Riding Illegal Aliens Allegedly Robbing Outdoor Diners appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 19:43:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>57% Of Americans Want Trump To Drop Out Of The Race</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/17/57-of-americans-want-trump-to-drop-out-of-the-race.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>The latest AP poll is focused on Democrats wanting President Biden to drop out of the race, but buried in the poll is the finding that a majority of Americans want Trump to drop out.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 18:39:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Illegal Aliens Aren’t the Only Ones Migrating. Americans are Too</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/10/illegal-aliens-arent-the-only-ones-migrating-americans-are-too/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>IRS data shows that American taxpayers are leaving sanctuary states for states that actually enforce the law. The negative impact of misguided sanctuary policies goes well beyond simply releasing dangerous criminals back onto the streets, it also impacts state economies and tax bases. To read the rest of the article click here The post Illegal Aliens Aren’t the Only Ones Migrating. Americans are Too appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:02:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Press Conference Draws Millions More Viewers Than Republican Convention</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/17/biden-press-conference-draws-millions-more-viewers-than-republican-convention.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>The Republican convention has been a ratings loser as millions more people tuned in to President Biden's press conference than are watching the convention.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 14:20:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Massachusetts Governor Maura Healey’s Charade at the Southern Border</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/02/massachusetts-governor-maura-healeys-charade-at-the-southern-border/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Things are pretty dire in the illegal alien sanctuary Bay State. As FAIR’s 2023 report showed, 393,000 illegal aliens and their U.S.-born children live in Massachusetts, costing taxpayers $2.9 billion annually for health care, education, criminal justice, and general welfare. To read the rest of the article click here The post Massachusetts Governor Maura Healey’s Charade at the Southern Border appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:51:45 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>