<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 15:28:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Trump Aide And Lawyers Criminally Charged In Wisconsin Fake Elector Scheme</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/04/trump-aide-and-lawyers-criminally-charged-in-wisconsin-fake-elector-scheme.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>A Trump aide and two of his lawyers have been criminally charged for their roles in the 2020 fake elector scheme in Wisconsin.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 17:38:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fairfax County, Virginia: Public Schools, Limited English Proficiency, and the Opportunity Cost of Mass Migration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/03/fairfax-county-virginia-public-schools-limited-english-proficiency-and-the-opportunity-cost-of-mass-migration/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>In economics, opportunity cost is defined as “the potential benefits that a business, an investor, or an individual consumer misses out on when choosing one alternative over another.” A dollar spent on A cannot be simultaneously spent on B. To read the rest of the article click here The post Fairfax County, Virginia: Public Schools, Limited English Proficiency, and the Opportunity Cost of Mass Migration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 21:36:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stephen Colbert Audience Chants Lock Him Up In Response To Trump Conviction</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/04/stephen-colbert-audience-chants-lock-him-up-in-response-to-trump-conviction.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Stephen Colbert asked his audience for their thoughts on Trump going to jail, and the crowd chanted lock him up.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 06:55:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Massachusetts Response to its Migrant Crisis: Offer Even More Benefits</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/31/massachusetts-response-to-its-migrant-crisis-offer-even-more-benefits/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>If any state in America proves the axiom that “things in motion stay in motion” it’s Massachusetts. What else but perpetual motion physics can explain the logic behind the Bay State’s non-stop granting of benefits to illegal aliens? To read the rest of the article click here The post Massachusetts Response to its Migrant Crisis: Offer Even More Benefits appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 21:12:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jon Stewart Goes Off On The Media With A Classic Rant</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/03/jon-stewart-goes-off-on-the-media-with-a-classic-rant.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Jon Stewart showed how the corporate media has dropped the ball by pretending like reality doesn’t exist to coddle Republicans. Stewart played several clips of people in the media claiming that there are two realities in the country, and then he responded, “No! You are thinking of the multi-verse. We are all living in one...</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 04:46:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Illegal Aliens Call Lyft Ride After Getting Sick of Waiting for Border Patrol to Pick them Up</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/30/illegal-aliens-call-lyft-ride-after-getting-sick-of-waiting-for-border-patrol-to-pick-them-up/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>In yet another alarming display of the Biden administration’s failure to secure our southern border, Fox News’s Bill Melugin caught a group of Colombian illegal aliens using a ride-hailing app, To read the rest of the article click here The post Illegal Aliens Call Lyft Ride After Getting Sick of Waiting for Border Patrol to Pick them Up appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 18:58:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Convicted Felon Trump Still Isn’t Campaigning</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/03/convicted-felon-trump-still-isnt-campaigning.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Trump complained that his criminal trial was keeping him off of the campaign trail, but the trial has been over for days, and Donald Trump has held zero campaign events.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 20:55:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Two Illegal Aliens Attempt to Breach U.S. Military Base, Dangerous Trend Continues Under Biden</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/29/two-illegal-aliens-attempt-to-breach-u-s-military-base-dangerous-trend-continues-under-biden/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Two Jordanian illegal aliens are in ICE custody awaiting deportation proceedings after attempting to breach the Marine Corps base in Quantico, Virginia, earlier this month. To read the rest of the article click here The post Two Illegal Aliens Attempt to Breach U.S. Military Base, Dangerous Trend Continues Under Biden appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 21:01:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Busts House Republicans For Violating Agreement By Trying To Defund The Police</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/03/biden-busts-house-republicans-for-violating-agreement-by-trying-to-defund-the-police.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>In a Statement of Administration Policy, the Biden administration called out House Republicans for violating their spending agreement and trying to cut funding for law enforcement.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 18:24:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Déjà Vu: Two Middle Eastern Illegal Aliens Attempt to Enter Secure Virginia Military Facility in a Box Truck</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/29/deja-vu-two-middle-eastern-illegal-aliens-attempt-to-enter-secure-virginia-military-facility-in-a-box-truck/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>On May 3, two Jordanian illegal aliens were apprehended as they attempted to enter the Marine Corps base in Quantico, Virginia, in a box truck. The two were posing as Amazon delivery drivers, although Amazon denies that they were employed by the company. To read the rest of the article click here The post Déjà Vu: Two Middle Eastern Illegal Aliens Attempt to Enter Secure Virginia Military Facility in a Box Truck appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 13:34:34 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>