<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 07:52:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Rachel Maddow: Republicans Have Already Wounded Democracy</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/06/rachel-maddow-republicans-democracy.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Rachel-Maddow-democracy-GOP.jpg</image_url><description>Rachel Maddow showed that by refusing to accept election results Republicans have already harmed democracy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 03:14:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stats Show Fentanyl Replacing Heroin as Cartel Cash Cow</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/06/stats-show-fentanyl-replacing-heroin-as-cartel-cash-cow/</link><description>Fentanyl is rapidly replacing heroin as the drug cartels are using to make money. Statistics on drug seizures from U.S. Customs and Border Protection (CBP) show that there has been a clear shift in the cartels’ smuggling habits, and the data strongly indicate that the border chaos of recent years is facilitating this lethal trade. [...]
The post Stats Show Fentanyl Replacing Heroin as Cartel Cash Cow appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:33:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Former Georgia GOP Lt. Governor Explains Why He’s Voting For Biden</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/06/former-georgia-gop-lt-governor-explains-why-hes-voting-for-biden.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Geoff-Duncan-after-testifying.jpg</image_url><description>Former Georgia Lt. Gov. Geoff Duncan said that he disagrees with Biden on policy, but he is voting for the president because he is decent.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 22:48:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Illegal Aliens Issue List of Demands After Hundreds Take Over City Park and Refuse to Leave</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/03/illegal-aliens-issue-list-of-demands-after-hundreds-take-over-city-park-and-refuse-to-leave/</link><description>In a brazen display of entitlement, hundreds of illegal aliens from Africa and Venezuela swarmed and took over Powell Barnett Park in Seattle. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Illegal Aliens Issue List of Demands After Hundreds Take Over City Park and Refuse to Leave appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 20:23:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Melts Down Over Being Threatened With Jail</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/06/trump-melts-down-over-being-threatened-with-jail.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Trump-Jail-gag-order-2.jpg</image_url><description>Trump melted down outside the courtroom over being threatened with jail if he violated the gag order again.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 21:59:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Japan is not Xenophobic, but Seems Poised to Repeat our Mistakes</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/03/japan-is-not-xenophobic-but-seems-poised-to-repeat-our-mistakes/</link><description>On Wednesday President Biden chastised America’s most important Pacific ally, Japan, as xenophobic. He smeared India with the same insult, conflating both democracies with China and Russia — suggesting tight borders as the primary driver of economic woes in all four. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Japan is not Xenophobic, but Seems Poised to Repeat our Mistakes appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 16:10:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>One Screw Up From His Lawyer May Have Blown Up Trump’s Defense</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/06/trump-lawyer-screw-up-defense.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Trump-bond-press-conference.jpg</image_url><description>Trump's lawyer accidentally got an admission from a witness that he knew that the payments to Michael Cohen were a hush money reimbursement.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 21:06:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ireland At the Breaking Point on Immigration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/01/ireland-at-the-breaking-point-on-immigration/</link><description>A weekend of forcefully suppressed protests against mass immigration in Ireland has underlined the growing disconnect between the government and the people. There has been understandable concern over Irish communities being forced to house and pay for migrant men without the locals being consulted. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Ireland At the Breaking Point on Immigration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 14:56:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oh Crap Moment For Trump As Prosecutors Introduce Docs Showing He Cooked The Books</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/06/oh-crap-moment-for-trump-as-prosecutors-introduce-docs-showing-he-cooked-the-books.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Trump-fraud-trial-defense-table.jpg</image_url><description>Trump Organization exec Jeffrey McConney is testifying as prosecutors have introduced evidence that Donald Trump cooked the books to hide reimbursing hush money to Michael Cohen.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:27:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In Case You Missed This – Which is What the Open-Borders Network Hopes Happened</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/04/30/in-case-you-missed-this-which-is-what-the-open-borders-network-hopes-happened/</link><description>“As Maine Goes, So Goes the Nation” still lingers as a popular axiom except of course, it’s just no longer true. Politically, the state hasn’t been an accurate bellwether of elections for decades. Yet now, in the context of illegal immigration, Maine once again bears watching, despite its 2,400 miles distance from the southern border. [...]
The post In Case You Missed This – Which is What the Open-Borders Network Hopes Happened appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 18:08:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>