<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 23:16:07 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Biden’s D-Day Trip Triggers A Trump Las Vegas Meltdown</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/09/bidens-d-day-trip-triggers-a-trump-las-vegas-meltdown.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Donald Trump fell apart in Las Vegas as he tried to lie his way out of confirmed reports that he called the troops suckers and losers.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 22:15:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gun-Wielding Illegal Alien Allegedly Shoots Two NYPD Officers in Latest Migrant Crime Incident</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/05/gun-wielding-illegal-alien-allegedly-shoots-two-nypd-officers-in-latest-migrant-crime-incident/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>In the early hours of June 3, 2024, NYPD officers Christopher Abreu and Richard Yarusso were investigating a robbery when they encountered 19-year-old Bernardo Castro Mata, an illegal alien from Venezuela, driving a motorized scooter with no plates the wrong way down a street. To read the rest of the article click here The post Gun-Wielding Illegal Alien Allegedly Shoots Two NYPD Officers in Latest Migrant Crime Incident appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 18:21:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>People Are Being Paid To Attend Trump’s Las Vegas Rally</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/09/people-are-being-paid-to-attend-trumps-las-vegas-rally.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>A Craigslist ad is recruiting people to attend Trump's Las Vegas rally for branding and marketing purposes.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 18:15:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Europe May Face a Second Middle Eastern Migrant Crisis</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/05/europe-may-face-a-second-middle-eastern-migrant-crisis/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>Europe may once again be about to receive mass waves of migrants from the Middle East, invoking memories of the 2015-2016 period, when then-German Chancellor Angela Merkel invited Syrians (and others) to come to Europe without limitation. To read the rest of the article click here The post Europe May Face a Second Middle Eastern Migrant Crisis appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 18:11:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Campaign Isn’t Letting Voters Forget That Trump Is A Convicted Felon Rapist</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/09/biden-campaign-trump-felon.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>The Biden campaign is reminding voters at every opportunity that Trump is a convicted felon and a rapist.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 17:47:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Baltimore Has an Obvious Problem. The Fix is Fairly Obvious Too.</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/05/baltimore-has-an-obvious-problem-the-fix-is-fairly-obvious-too/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>“Baltimore County releases illegal immigrants charged with crimes despite federal requests,” declared a recent headline on the local FOX 45 news site. To read the rest of the article click here The post Baltimore Has an Obvious Problem. The Fix is Fairly Obvious Too. appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 14:28:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump’s Polling Lead Vanishes As Democrats Activate</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/09/trumps-polling-lead-vanishes-as-democrats-activate.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>Trump's conviction seemed to activate more Democratic voters against him, as the ex-president's polling lead has vanished in the latest CBS News Poll.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 17:02:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fairfax County, Virginia: Public Schools, Limited English Proficiency, and the Opportunity Cost of Mass Migration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/06/03/fairfax-county-virginia-public-schools-limited-english-proficiency-and-the-opportunity-cost-of-mass-migration/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>In economics, opportunity cost is defined as “the potential benefits that a business, an investor, or an individual consumer misses out on when choosing one alternative over another.” A dollar spent on A cannot be simultaneously spent on B. To read the rest of the article click here The post Fairfax County, Virginia: Public Schools, Limited English Proficiency, and the Opportunity Cost of Mass Migration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 21:36:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>James Comer Admits He Setting Up Trump To Prosecute Biden</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/06/09/james-comer-admits-he-setting-up-trump-to-prosecute-biden.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-PU_Favicon-e1620048539241-60x60.jpg</image_url><description>James Comer talks about issuing criminal referrals for the Bidens with Maria Bartiromo on Fox News.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 16:28:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Massachusetts Response to its Migrant Crisis: Offer Even More Benefits</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/31/massachusetts-response-to-its-migrant-crisis-offer-even-more-benefits/</link><image_url>https://www.immigrationreform.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-IR-Favicon-100x100.png</image_url><description>If any state in America proves the axiom that “things in motion stay in motion” it’s Massachusetts. What else but perpetual motion physics can explain the logic behind the Bay State’s non-stop granting of benefits to illegal aliens? To read the rest of the article click here The post Massachusetts Response to its Migrant Crisis: Offer Even More Benefits appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 21:12:58 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>