<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 07:44:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Democrats Respond To Trump’s Racist Attack On Harris By Raising $23 Million</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/08/01/democrats-respond-to-trumps-racist-attack-on-harris-by-raising-23-million.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>Not only did Donald Trump implode while speaking to black journalists, but his racist attack on VP Harris caused Democrats to raise $23 million.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 05:08:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Disastrous Nexus of Biden-Harris Policies:  The Afghan Parole Program and Prohibition on Issuing Notices to Appear</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/31/a-disastrous-nexus-of-biden-harris-policies-the-afghan-parole-program-and-prohibition-on-issuing-notices-to-appear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>On this date three years ago – July 31, 2021 – the first group of Afghan nationals arrived in the United States after the President Biden’s disastrous withdrawal of U.S. troops from the country. To read the rest of the article click here The post A Disastrous Nexus of Biden-Harris Policies: The Afghan Parole Program and Prohibition on Issuing Notices to Appear appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 16:02:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Knows He’s Losing So He Goes Full Racist At Pennsylvania Rally</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/31/trump-knows-hes-losing-so-he-goes-full-racist-at-pennsylvania-rally.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>Donald Trump's campaign knows that they are losing more ground each day to Kamala Harris which is why their Harrisburg, PA rally has gone full racist.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 23:51:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Human Smuggler Who Facilitated Illegal Entry of Thousands of Aliens Indicted</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/29/human-smuggler-who-facilitated-illegal-entry-of-thousands-of-aliens-indicted/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>On July 18, reports surfaced that Abdul Karim Conteh, a national from Sierra Leone, had been indicted and sanctioned in the United States and arrested in Tijuana, Mexico. Conteh ran a smuggling organization that facilitated the transport of thousands of illegal aliens to the United States through Mexico, including many from terrorism hot spots. To [...] The post Human Smuggler Who Facilitated Illegal Entry of Thousands of Aliens Indicted appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 20:17:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Melts Down Over Kamala Harris’s Big Georgia Rally</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/31/trump-harris-georgia.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Trump went on a bitter rant about Kamala Harris's Georgia rally as he seemed both jealous and worried.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 18:34:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Did Biden Really Say Our Borders are More Secure than When He Took Office?</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/26/did-biden-really-say-our-borders-are-more-secure-than-when-he-took-office/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>Every politician is prone to exaggerating their accomplishments in an attempt to define their legacy in the most positive possible terms. President Biden is certainly no exception. In his address to the nation on Wednesday evening, after he announced his decision to abandon his 2024 reelection bid, the president ticked off a long list of [...] The post Did Biden Really Say Our Borders are More Secure than When He Took Office? appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 21:24:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kamala Harris To Hold Her First Rally With Her Running Mate On Tuesday In PA</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/31/kamala-harris-running-mate-rally.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Kamala Harris will be holding her first rally with her new running mate in Philadelphia on Tuesday in the home state of Gov. Josh Shapiro.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 17:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maine Immigration Fanatics Focus on Efficiency and Cost to Increase Flows</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/26/maine-immigration-fanatics-focus-on-efficiency-and-cost-to-increase-flows/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>Mass immigration advocates in Maine have a problem. They’ve overachieved their goals and now need to adjust their strategy to appease taxpayers alarmed over skyrocketing costs to house migrants. To read the rest of the article click here The post Maine Immigration Fanatics Focus on Efficiency and Cost to Increase Flows appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 17:31:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kamala Harris Excites Democrats In Wisconsin’s Fastest Growing County</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/07/31/kamala-harris-excites-democrats-in-wisconsins-fastest-growing-county.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>Democrats in Dane County, Wisconsin, are reporting a massive uptick in enthusiasm for Kamala Harris in the state's fastest-growing county.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 13:37:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Washington Turns a Blind Eye to Exploited Migrant Children, While their Tormentors Cash In</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/07/24/washington-turns-a-blind-eye-to-exploited-migrant-children-while-their-tormentors-cash-in/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>On July 17, the Biden-Harris administration’s Department of Justice filed a suit against its largest private housing provider for unaccompanied alien children (UAC) in the United States, alleging that the company, Southwest Key, subjected children to repeated and unwelcome sexual abuse, harassment, rape, solicitation of sex acts, and more. To read the rest of the [...] The post Washington Turns a Blind Eye to Exploited Migrant Children, While their Tormentors Cash In appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 21:03:24 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>