<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 17:28:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Trump Is Scared That He Will Be Put In Prison For “A Long Period Of Time”</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/08/trump-is-scared-that-he-will-be-put-in-prison-for-a-long-period-of-time.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/Trump-Newsmax.jpg</image_url><description>Trump posted on his social media platform complaining that his free speech rights have been taken away and that he could be put in prison for a long period of time.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 19:12:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This North Carolina Sheriff Should Know Better</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/07/this-north-carolina-sheriff-should-know-better/</link><description>Generally speaking, police chiefs – particularly those in major urban areas – support illegal alien sanctuary policies that prohibit them from cooperating with federal immigration officials. They’re often pressured to do so by the politicians and special interests who appoint and influence them. To read the rest of the article click here
The post This North Carolina Sheriff Should Know Better appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:05:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kristi Noem’s Career Death Spiral Worsens As She Bails On CNN</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/08/kristi-noem-cnn.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/noem-ftn.jpg</image_url><description>CNN announced that Gov. Kristi Noem (R-SC) abruptly bailed on an interview with the network that was scheduled weeks in advance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 18:47:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stats Show Fentanyl Replacing Heroin as Cartel Cash Cow</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/06/stats-show-fentanyl-replacing-heroin-as-cartel-cash-cow/</link><description>Fentanyl is rapidly replacing heroin as the drug cartels are using to make money. Statistics on drug seizures from U.S. Customs and Border Protection (CBP) show that there has been a clear shift in the cartels’ smuggling habits, and the data strongly indicate that the border chaos of recent years is facilitating this lethal trade. [...]
The post Stats Show Fentanyl Replacing Heroin as Cartel Cash Cow appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:33:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bernie Sanders Praises Biden’s Bomb Halt To Israel As A Good First Step</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/08/bernie-sanders-biden-bomb-halt.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/2020-03-20T164340Z_521695054_MT1USATODAY14197974_RTRMADP_3_BERNIE-SANDERS-AND-JOE-BIDEN-SHAKE-HANDS-BERNBIDEN-e1715187607673.jpg</image_url><description>Sen. Bernie Sanders (I-VT) praised President Biden's decision to halt offensive weapons transfers to Israel and urged the US to exert maximum pressure for a ceasefire.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 18:15:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Illegal Aliens Issue List of Demands After Hundreds Take Over City Park and Refuse to Leave</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/03/illegal-aliens-issue-list-of-demands-after-hundreds-take-over-city-park-and-refuse-to-leave/</link><description>In a brazen display of entitlement, hundreds of illegal aliens from Africa and Venezuela swarmed and took over Powell Barnett Park in Seattle. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Illegal Aliens Issue List of Demands After Hundreds Take Over City Park and Refuse to Leave appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 20:23:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Disaster For Trump As Nikki Haley Gets Over 20% Of The GOP Primary Vote In Indiana</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/07/disaster-for-trump-as-nikki-haley-gets-over-20-of-the-gop-primary-vote-in-indiana.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/trump-hands-head.jpg</image_url><description>Trump had another massive underperformance to a candidate who dropped out months ago. This time Nikki Haley got over 20% of the vote in deep red Indiana.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 04:16:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Japan is not Xenophobic, but Seems Poised to Repeat our Mistakes</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/03/japan-is-not-xenophobic-but-seems-poised-to-repeat-our-mistakes/</link><description>On Wednesday President Biden chastised America’s most important Pacific ally, Japan, as xenophobic. He smeared India with the same insult, conflating both democracies with China and Russia — suggesting tight borders as the primary driver of economic woes in all four. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Japan is not Xenophobic, but Seems Poised to Repeat our Mistakes appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 16:10:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>After Disastrous Day In Court, Trump Demands Campus Protesters Be Arrested</title><link>https://www.politicususa.com/2024/05/07/after-disastrous-day-in-court-trump-demands-campus-protesters-be-arrested.html</link><image_url>https://www.politicususa.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Trump-biden-plants.jpg</image_url><description>Donald Trump had a very bad day in court on Tuesday, so after his trial ended for the day, he claimed that campus protesters are Biden plants and called for their arrest.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:04:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ireland At the Breaking Point on Immigration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/05/01/ireland-at-the-breaking-point-on-immigration/</link><description>A weekend of forcefully suppressed protests against mass immigration in Ireland has underlined the growing disconnect between the government and the people. There has been understandable concern over Irish communities being forced to house and pay for migrant men without the locals being consulted. To read the rest of the article click here
The post Ireland At the Breaking Point on Immigration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 14:56:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>