<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 12:08:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Flashback: When Harry Reid was Right about Immigration</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/08/15/flashback-when-harry-reid-was-right-about-immigration/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Thirty years ago, FAIR found what would now be an unlikely ally in The Los Angeles Times opinion page. On August 10, 1994, the late Sen. Harry Reid (D-Nevada) wrote a fantastic op-ed promoting his bill, the Immigration Stabilization Act (S. 1351), to slash legal immigration by two thirds, from approximately 1 million to 325,000 [...] The post Flashback: When Harry Reid was Right about Immigration appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:37:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Harris' economic plan supercharges Biden proposals to fight inflation</title><link>https://www.politico.com/news/2024/08/16/harris-economic-policy-plan-00174336</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>The vice president's plan aims to make housing more affordable, ease health care costs and crack down on corporations for rising grocery prices.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple's Hold on the App Store Is Loosening, at Least in Europe</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/epic-games-apple-app-store-europe-44ceda50?mod=rss_Technology</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Epic Games and Spotify are among the developers taking advantage of European rule changes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 16:48:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Analysis: The effects of a graying America seep into the 2024 campaign</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 17:00:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Videos: At NYC’s Roosevelt Hotel, the Migrant Crisis Continues to Rage</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/08/12/new-videos-at-nycs-roosevelt-hotel-the-migrant-crisis-continues-to-rage/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Last week, while in New York City, I decided to take a walk around 10:00 p.m. to see the Roosevelt Hotel, now known as the city’s official migrant welcome center. FAIR visited this same location last year, and you can read our detailed account from that visit here. To read the rest of the article [...] The post New Videos: At NYC’s Roosevelt Hotel, the Migrant Crisis Continues to Rage appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 20:21:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump hits Harris on the economy: 'She destroys everything she touches'</title><link>https://www.politico.com/video/2024/08/15/trump-hits-harris-on-the-economy-she-destroys-everything-she-touches-1404599</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description></description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 22:20:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lawmakers Seek Answers From Meta About Ads for Illicit Drugs</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/lawmakers-seek-answers-from-meta-about-ads-for-illicit-drugs-d24cf420?mod=rss_Technology</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>A bipartisan group of 19 legislators sent a letter to Meta Platforms asking why such ads on Instagram and other apps have continued to proliferate.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 00:32:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Election 2024 live updates: Harris to deliver economic speech in battleground state of N.C.</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/elections/2024/08/16/2024-election-campaign-updates-harris-trump/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Get the latest news from the 2024 campaign trail in the contest between Vice President Kamala Harris and former president Donald Trump.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 17:00:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tren de Aragua Gang Given ‘Green Light’ to Open Fire on U.S. Law Enforcement Officers</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/08/09/tren-de-aragua-gang-given-green-light-to-open-fire-on-u-s-law-enforcement-officers/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>A new report reveals that more than 1,000 members of the violent Venezuelan Tren de Aragua gang have infiltrated the United States and have been given the “green light” to attack and open fire on law enforcement officers. To read the rest of the article click here The post Tren de Aragua Gang Given ‘Green Light’ to Open Fire on U.S. Law Enforcement Officers appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 15:40:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Everything was going Kamala Harris’ way. Then came the market sell-off.</title><link>https://www.politico.com/news/2024/08/06/market-sell-off-democrats-harris-00172740</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>"We cannot win if people think we’re headed into a recession," one Democratic National Committee member said.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lenovo Profit Grows Another Quarter, Helped by AI</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/lenovo-profit-grows-another-quarter-helped-by-ai-b0f7c384?mod=rss_Technology</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Lenovo’s profits rose for a second-straight quarter as the world’s largest PC maker emerges from a yearslong downturn in the industry and captures opportunities in artificial intelligence to drive growth.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 06:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>N.J. Gov. Murphy appoints former chief of staff to Menendez’s Senate seat</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 16:34:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oklahoma Knows You Can’t Manage What You Don’t Measure</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/08/07/oklahoma-knows-you-cant-manage-what-you-dont-measure/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Oklahoma’s Superintendent of the State Department of Education is asking Oklahoma school districts to get a handle on the number of illegal aliens occupying classrooms statewide “to find accurate and effective counting of the cost and burden that illegal immigration has.” To read the rest of the article click here The post Oklahoma Knows You Can’t Manage What You Don’t Measure appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:04:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JD Vance at RNC: Trump is the working class' 'last, best hope'</title><link>https://www.politico.com/video/2024/07/18/j-d-vance-at-rnc-trump-is-the-working-class-last-best-hope-1369100</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description></description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 05:28:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eric Schmidt Walks Back Claim Google Is Behind on AI Because of Remote Work</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/google-eric-schmidt-ai-remote-work-stanford-f92f4ca5?mod=rss_Technology</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>The former CEO of Google had said the tech company decided that work-life balance is “more important than winning.”</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 02:47:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ian Sams will leave White House and join Harris campaign</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/2024/08/16/ian-sams-leaving-white-house-expected-join-harris-campaign/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Sams was a vocal defender of Harris, regularly appearing on television during her presidential campaign.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 16:32:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Massachusetts Migrant Housing Costs: Out of Orbit and Hard to Grasp</title><link>https://www.immigrationreform.com/2024/08/01/massachusetts-migrant-housing-costs-out-of-orbit-and-hard-to-grasp/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Beyond a certain threshold, numbers become abstract and lose their meaningful context. A quick view of the national debt clock which adds $100,000 of national debt every two-and-a-half seconds to America’s current obligations of $35 trillion is virtually impossible to comprehend. To read the rest of the article click here The post Massachusetts Migrant Housing Costs: Out of Orbit and Hard to Grasp appeared first on ImmigrationReform.com .</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 17:55:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>US added 206,000 jobs in June in a sign of continued economic strength</title><link>https://www.politico.com/news/2024/07/05/us-added-206-000-jobs-in-june-in-a-sign-of-continued-economic-strength-00166606</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Though hiring remains strong, voters blame President Joe Biden for persistent high prices.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 14:02:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Foxconn Posts Higher Profit, Record Revenue on AI Server Demand</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/foxconns-second-quarter-profit-rose-on-record-revenue-7f70bd92?mod=rss_Technology</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>The world’s largest contract electronics maker reported higher quarterly net profit as its revenue rose to a record on robust demand for artificial-intelligence servers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 09:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Within their parties, both JD Vance and Tim Walz are well-liked. Vance’s net favorability among Republicans...</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 16:20:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>