<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 02:38:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Historic records provide new insight</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/historic-records-provide-new-insight</link><description>U.S. National Science Foundation-funded researchers recently released a new study in Ecology and Evolution o utlining their in-depth analysis of historic baleen plates, the comb structures that are used by some species of whales to filter food, from…</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 21:27:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New snake discovery rewrites history, points to North America's role in snake evolution</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240719180253.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>A new species of fossil snake unearthed in Wyoming is rewriting our understanding of snake evolution. The discovery, based on four remarkably well-preserved specimens found curled together in a burrow, reveals a new species named Hibernophis breithaupti. This snake lived in North America 34 million years ago and sheds light on the origin and diversification of boas and pythons.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 23:02:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists discover which parts of the Amazon rainforest are most vulnerable to drought</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/scientists-discover-which-parts-amazon-rainforest</link><description>Regions of the Amazon rainforest respond to drought according to differences in local forest environments and in the properties of trees, Scott Saleska of the University of Arizona and colleagues have discovered. In the southern Amazon rainforest…</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 15:15:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Good timing: Study unravels how our brains track time</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240718205236.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Ever hear the old adage that time flies when you're having fun? A new study suggests that there's a lot of truth to the trope.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 01:52:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF–DOE Rubin Observatory will detect thousands of elusive brown dwarfs, unlocking Milky Way mysteries</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/rubin-observatory-will-detect-thousands-dwarfs</link><description>Too big to be planets but too small to be stars, distant brown dwarfs are a key ingredient for understanding the history of the Milky Way. These elusive objects have existed since the early universe and have remained relatively unchanged. Anticipated…</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 19:05:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Another intermediate-mass black hole discovered at the center of our galaxy</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240718124854.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>So far, only about ten intermediate-mass black holes have been discovered in the entire universe. The newly identified black hole causes surrounding stars in a cluster to move in an unexpectedly orderly way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 17:48:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-58</link><description>NSF has been bustling with activity in recent weeks, achieving many significant milestones. NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan welcomed Phoenix, Arizona Mayor Kate Gallego to NSF headquarters. Their discussions centered around collaboration…</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Microbes found to destroy certain 'forever chemicals'</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240717162500.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>An environmental engineering team has discovered that specific bacterial species can cleave the strong fluorine-to-carbon bond certain kinds of 'forever chemical' water pollutants, offering promise for low-cost treatments of contaminated drinking water.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 21:25:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wildfire smoke is reaching almost all lakes in North America</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/wildfire-smoke-reaching-almost-all-lakes-north</link><description>Wildfire smoke, sometimes drifting across hundreds of miles, reached almost every lake in North America at least one day each year from 2019 to 2021, according to U.S. National Science Foundation- supported findings published in the journal Global…</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 17:28:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Evidence for butchery of giant armadillo-like mammals in Argentina 21,000 years ago</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240717162440.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Cut marks on fossils could be evidence of humans exploiting large mammals in Argentina more than 20,000 years ago, according to a new study.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 21:24:40 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>