<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 11:09:22 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Healthy eating in midlife linked to overall healthy aging</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/03/250324141952.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Maintaining a healthy diet rich in plant-based foods, with low to moderate intake of healthy animal-based foods and lower intake of ultra-processed fo...</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 19:19:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chimpanzees act as 'engineers', choosing materials to make tools based on structural and mechanical properties</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/03/250324142002.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Researchers have discovered that chimpanzees living in Gombe Stream National Park in Tanzania employ a degree of engineering when making their tools, ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 19:20:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>3D nanotech blankets offer new path to clean drinking water</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/03/250324141946.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Researchers have developed a new material that, by harnessing the power of sunlight, can clear water of dangerous pollutants.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 19:19:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mathematicians uncover the logic behind how people walk in crowds</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/03/250324152433.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Mathematicians studied the flow of human crowds and developed a way to predict when pedestrian paths will transition from orderly to entangled. Their ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 20:24:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New non-surgical contraceptive implant is delivered through tiny needles</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/03/250324141949.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Investigators have developed a long-acting contraceptive implant that can be delivered through tiny needles to minimize patient discomfort and increas...</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 19:19:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chainmail-like polymer could be the future of body armor</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/chainmail-polymer-could-be-future-body-armor</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Researchers supported by grants and instrumentation provided by the U.S. National Science Foundation have created the first 2D polymer material that m...</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 19:34:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cutting-edge air quality monitoring strengthens public health nationwide</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/cutting-edge-air-quality-monitoring-strengthens-public</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>The fires that devastated many in Los Angeles in January 2025 not only scarred the landscape but also changed the air. A day after the Eaton fire burn...</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 15:20:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Unique skeletal tissue may enable new regenerative medical treatments</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/unique-skeletal-tissue-may-enable-new-regenerative-medical</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Supported by multiple grants from the U.S. National Science Foundation, researchers have comprehensively characterized the properties of a unique type...</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 16:25:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New method to keep protein-based drugs stable without refrigeration</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/new-method-keep-protein-based-drugs-stable-without</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>A team of researchers led by the recipient of a U.S. National Science Foundation Faculty Early Career Development grant has developed a new storage me...</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 16:28:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF-DOE Vera C. Rubin Observatory installs LSST Camera on telescope</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-doe-vera-c-rubin-observatory-installs-lsst-camera</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>NSF-DOE Vera C. Rubin Observatory, funded by the U.S. National Science Foundation and the U.S. Department of Energy’s Office of Science, has achieved ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 15:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>