<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 23:18:08 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-54</link><description>NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan traveled to Interlaken, Switzerland, to join international partners for the Global Research Council's (GRC) annual meeting. GRC aims to promote long-term multilateral research and collaboration across continents…</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 20:32:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A new study reveals that marine cyanobacteria communicate</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240606152330.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>A breakthrough study changes the way we understand cyanobacteria, which are essential for the sustenance of life. The study shows that these organisms do not operate in isolation, but rather physically interact through membrane-nanotubes, which function as exchange bridges between cells.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 20:23:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF enhances research security with new TRUST proposal assessment process</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-enhances-research-security-new-trust-proposal</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has announced a new risk mitigation process, the Trusted Research Using Safeguards and Transparency (TRUST) framework, which will guide the agency in assessing grant proposals for potential national security risks…</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 15:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>People feel more connected to 'tweezer-like' bionic tools that don't resemble human hands</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240606152145.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Some say the next step in human evolution will be the integration of technology with flesh. Now, researchers have used virtual reality to test whether humans can feel embodiment -- the sense that something is part of one's body -- toward prosthetic 'hands' that resemble a pair of tweezers. They report that participants felt an equal degree of embodiment for the tweezer-hands and were also faster and more accurate in completing motor tasks in virtual reality than when they were equipped with a virtual human hand.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 20:21:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Widely used climate theory doesn't 'ring' true, according to new tree data</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/widely-used-climate-theory-doesnt-ring-true</link><description>New data on over 1,500 trees across nearly 1,000 sites shows that an existing theory of how individuals within a species will respond to a changing climate might not be true. The data, in the form of tree rings from an aridland pine, contradicts the…</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 21:00:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Planet-forming disks around very low-mass stars are different</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240606152101.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Using the James Webb Space Telescope, a team of astronomers studied the properties of a planet-forming disk around a young and very low-mass star. The results reveal the richest hydrocarbon composition seen to date in a protoplanetary disk, including the first extrasolar detection of ethane and a relatively low abundance of oxygen-bearing species. By including previous similar detections, this finding confirms a trend of disks around very low-mass stars to be chemically distinct from those around more massive stars like the Sun, influencing the atmospheres of planets forming there.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 20:21:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF, NEH and partner funding agencies from seven countries announce the winners of the Canada-led 2023 International Joint Initiative for Research on Climate Change Adaptation and Mitigation competition</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-neh-partner-funding-agencies-seven-countries</link><description>Today, the U.S. National Science Foundation and the National Endowment of the Humanities (NEH) joined partner funding agencies from Brazil, Canada, Germany, Norway, South Africa, Switzerland and the United Kingdom in announcing the awardees for the…</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 16:15:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oral insulin drops offer relief for diabetes patients</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240605162742.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Diabetes rates continue to rise. Scientists have now created a pain-free drug delivery method to help people with diabetes manage the disease and maintain their health more easily. Researchers have developed oral insulin drops that when placed under the tongue are quickly and efficiently absorbed by the body, potentially replacing the need for insulin injections.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 21:27:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mountain building linked to major extinction event half a billion years ago</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/mountain-building-linked-major-extinction-event</link><description>As life on Earth rapidly expanded a little over 500 million years ago during the "Cambrian explosion," Earth had tectonic plates slowly crashing into each other, building mountains and starting a series of unfortunate events that led to a mass…</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 22:57:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists identify 'missing piece' required for blood stem cell self-renewal</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240605162720.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Blood stem cells -- key to transplants that are used as life-saving treatments for blood cancers and blood and immune disorders -- have the capacity to self-renew, but quickly lose their ability to do so in a lab dish. Scientists have identified a protein that not only enables blood stem cells to self-renew in a lab dish, but also allows these expanded cells to function effectively after being transplanted into mouse models. The findings could help make blood stem cell transplants available to more people and improve the accessibility and safety of gene therapies that use these cells.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 21:27:20 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>