<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 15:32:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>A new film on baffling Baffin Bay</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/new-film-baffling-baffin-bay</link><description>A new NSF-supported documentary follows the Baffin Bay Deglacial Experiment team on its journey to investigate what happened to the Greenland Ice Sheet over 15,000 years ago Although scientists know that the Earth has seen major climate changes from…</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 22:24:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This desert moss has the potential to grow on Mars</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240630153052.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>The desert moss Syntrichia caninervis is a promising candidate for Mars colonization thanks to its extreme ability to tolerate harsh conditions lethal to most life forms. The moss is well known for its ability to tolerate drought conditions, but researchers now report that it can also survive freezing temperatures as low as 196 C, high levels of gamma radiation, and simulated Martian conditions involving these three stressors combined. In all cases, prior dehydration seemed to help the plants cope.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 20:30:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deep-sea discovery opens up ocean of potential</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/deep-sea-discovery-opens-ocean-potential</link><description>New research by U.S. National Science Foundation-funded scientists making use of NSF facilities has provided insight into how related ocean creatures have adapted to live in vastly different environments. The study may also provide new knowledge…</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 20:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Investigating newly discovered hydrothermal vents at depths of 3,000 meters off Svalbard</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240628125250.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Hydrothermal vents can be found around the world at the junctions of drifting tectonic plates. But there are many hydrothermal fields still to be discovered. During a 2022 expedition of the MARIA S. MERIAN, the first field of hydrothermal vents on the 500-kilometer-long Knipovich Ridge off the coast of Svalbard was discovered.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 17:52:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF awards $35M for networks to transform research capacity and competitiveness</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-awards-35m-networks-transform-research</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has awarded $35 million through the Established Program to Stimulate Competitive Research (EPSCoR) Research Incubators for STEM Excellence Research Infrastructure Improvement (E-RISE RII) to boost research…</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tiny bright objects discovered at dawn of universe baffle scientists</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240628125241.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>A recent discovery by NASA's James Webb Space Telescope (JWST) confirmed that luminous, very red objects previously detected in the early universe upend conventional thinking about the origins and evolution of galaxies and their supermassive black holes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 17:52:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF launches new investment to accelerate the transition of privacy-enhancing technologies to practice</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-launches-new-investment-accelerate-transition</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation yesterday published a new investment to advance privacy-enhancing technologies (PETs) and promote their use to solve real-world problems. The Privacy-Preserving Data Sharing in Practice (PDaSP) program, which…</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 15:20:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Soft, stretchy electrode simulates touch sensations using electrical signals</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240628125235.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>A team of researchers has developed a soft, stretchy electronic device capable of simulating the feeling of pressure or vibration when worn on the skin. This device represents a step towards creating haptic technologies that can reproduce a more varied and realistic range of touch sensations for applications such as virtual reality, medical prosthetics and wearable technology.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 17:52:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Physicists create first-ever Bose-Einstein condensate made of molecules</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/physicists-create-first-ever-bose-einstein</link><description>A team of physicists has successfully created a unique quantum state of matter called a Bose-Einstein condensate (BEC) out of molecules. The team is led by Sebastian Will at Columbia University, who received a U.S. National Science Foundation Faculty…</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 20:53:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wireless receiver blocks interference for better mobile device performance</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240628125227.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Researchers developed a new wireless receiver that can block strong interference signals at the earliest opportunity, which could improve the performance of a mobile device.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 17:52:27 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>