<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:52:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Studying the journey, not the destination, provides new insight into songbird migrations</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/studying-journey-into-songbird-migrations</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>New research supported by the U.S. National Science Foundation using two decades worth of data could change how scientists think about bird migrations and the interdependencies and relationships they involve. Driving any long distance usually…</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 20:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Engineers bring efficient optical neural networks into focus</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240812123155.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Researchers have published a programmable framework that overcomes a key computational bottleneck of optics-based artificial intelligence systems. In a series of image classification experiments, they used scattered light from a low-power laser to perform accurate, scalable computations using a fraction of the energy of electronics.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 17:31:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>This week, NSF marked the second anniversary of the "CHIPS and Science Act of 2022," signed into law on August 9, 2022. This landmark legislation has empowered NSF to accelerate innovation and build a resilient, inclusive, and productive American…</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:27:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Long-distance relationship revealed in the seemingly random behavior of bowhead whales</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240811233247.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Applying chaos theory to the movement of iconic arctic whales uncovered a 24-hour diving cycle and a long-range (~100 km) synchronization.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 04:32:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Radio astronomers and satellite internet provider develop new sky-sharing system</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/radio-astronomers-satellite-internet-provider</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>New techniques developed by the U.S. National Science Foundation National Radio Astronomy Observatory (NSF NRAO) and SpaceX enable radio astronomy telescopes to operate without interference from satellite transmissions. The techniques allow…</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 22:20:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Millions of years for plants to recover from global warming</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240809135943.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Catastrophic volcanic eruptions that warmed the planet millions of years ago shed new light on how plants evolve and regulate climate. Researchers reveal the long-term effects of disturbed natural ecosystems on climate in geological history and its implications for today.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 18:59:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF National Quantum Virtual Laboratory advances with first five pilot projects</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-national-quantum-virtual-laboratory-advances</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Realizing practical advantages and societal benefits from quantum-scale phenomena has been a long-sought milestone in quantum information science. The U.S. National Science Foundation today announced the initial $5 million investment across five…</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 14:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Potential new approach to enhancing stem-cell transplants</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240809135941.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>A discovery may boost the effectiveness of stem-cell transplants, commonly used for patients with cancer, blood disorders, or autoimmune diseases caused by defective stem cells, which produce all the body's different blood cells.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 18:59:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Massive genes allow golden algae to synthesize its toxin</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/massive-genes-allow-golden-algae-synthesize-its</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>The toxic golden alga, Prymnesium parvum, can cause mass mortality events involving fish, including the environmental disaster that impacted the Oder River in Europe in 2022, killing half the river's fish population. Now, NSF-supported researchers…</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 19:27:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Largest protein yet discovered builds algal toxins</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240809135939.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>While seeking to unravel how marine algae create their chemically complex toxins, scientists have discovered the largest protein yet identified in biology. Uncovering the biological machinery the algae evolved to make its intricate toxin also revealed previously unknown strategies for assembling chemicals, which could unlock the development of new medicines and materials.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 18:59:39 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>