<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 11:04:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Farming without famine: Ancient Andean innovation rewrites agricultural origins</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/06/250625232202.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Farming didn t emerge in the Andes due to crisis or scarcity it was a savvy and resilient evolution. Ancient diets remained stable for millennia, blen...</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 11:55:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists reveal your morning coffee flips an ancient longevity switch</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/06/250625075024.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Caffeine appears to do more than perk you up—it activates AMPK, a key cellular fuel sensor that helps cells cope with stress and energy shortages. Thi...</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 03:29:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This team tried to cross 140 miles of treacherous ocean like stone-age humans—and it worked</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/06/250625232204.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Experiments and simulations show Paleolithic paddlers could outwit the powerful Kuroshio Current by launching dugout canoes from northern Taiwan and s...</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 08:07:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chemical process more efficiently converts carbon dioxide to methanol, a chemical used in manufacturing and a potential fuel</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/chemical-process-more-efficiently-converts-carbon-dioxide</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>A new chemical process funded by the U.S. National Science Foundation has produced methanol — a type of alcohol essential for manufacturing many commo...</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 14:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mammals didn't walk upright until late—here's what fossils reveal</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/06/250625075018.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>The shift from lizard-like sprawl to upright walking in mammals wasn’t a smooth climb up the evolutionary ladder. Instead, it was a messy saga full of...</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 15:14:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The brain’s sweet spot: How criticality could unlock learning, memory—and prevent Alzheimer’s</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/06/250625075016.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Our brains may work best when teetering on the edge of chaos. A new theory suggests that criticality a sweet spot between order and randomness is the ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 14:41:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Superconducting material stabilized at everyday pressure, another step toward real-world applications</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/superconducting-material-stabilized-everyday-pressure</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>U.S. National Science Foundation-funded researchers have stabilized a composite material in a superconducting state at ambient or normal, everyday pre...</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 15:19:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF invests $25.5M in research to drive new U.S. manufacturing technologies and talent pipelines</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-invests-255m-research-drive-new-us-manufacturing</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has announced a $25.5 million investment to support fundamental research and workforce development aimed at enabl...</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 15:07:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF Graduate Research Fellow's work on light contributes to nanodot breakthrough</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-graduate-research-fellows-work-light-contributes-nanodot</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Americans spend a lot of time on their screens. The images on those screens are made of pixels — tiny dots that represent a single point of color. Sci...</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 13:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ever-changing universe revealed in first imagery from NSF-DOE Vera C. Rubin Observatory</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/first-imagery-nsf-doe-vera-c-rubin-observatory</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>The NSF-DOE Vera C. Rubin Observatory, a major new scientific facility jointly funded by the U.S. National Science Foundation and the U.S. Department ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 16:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>