<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 06:00:44 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NSF congratulates laureates of the 2024 Nobel Prize in physics</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-congratulates-laureates-2024-nobel-prize-physics</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation congratulates John J. Hopfield and Geoffrey E. Hinton for their Nobel Prize in physics. Their research and innova...</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 20:04:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Loss of lake ice has wide-ranging environmental and societal consequences</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/10/241010142529.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>The world's freshwater lakes are freezing over for shorter periods of time due to climate change. This shift has major implications for human safety, ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 19:25:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A look into 'mirror molecules' may lead to new medicines</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/10/241010205852.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Chemists have developed a new chemical reaction that will allow researchers to synthesize selectively the left-handed or right-handed versions of 'mir...</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 01:58:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>U.S. releases National Spectrum Research and Development Plan to guide spectrum innovation</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/us-releases-national-spectrum-research-development-plan</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>The U.S. government has released the National Spectrum Research and Development Plan, a crucial step forward in maintaining America's global leadershi...</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 17:41:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Folding the future: The rise of origami-inspired robots</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/folding-future-rise-origami-inspired-robots</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Origami, the ancient art of paper folding, is taking a futuristic turn with the work of Cynthia Sung at the University of Pennsylvania. Supported by t...</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 21:12:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A stiff material that stops vibrations and noise</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/10/241010124905.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Materials researchers have created a new composite material that combines two incompatible properties: stiff yet with a high damping capacity.</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 17:49:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF Growing Convergence Research awards advance innovation across disciplines</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-growing-convergence-research-awards-advance-innovation</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation Growing Convergence Research (NSF GCR) awards are fostering deep integration across disciplines and pushing the b...</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 20:15:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF congratulates laureates of the 2024 Nobel Prize in chemistry</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-congratulates-laureates-2024-nobel-prize-chemistry</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation congratulates David Baker, Demis Hassabis and John Jumper on being awarded the 2024 Nobel Prize in chemistry. Bak...</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 20:57:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fossils and fires: Insights into early modern human activity in the jungles of Southeast Asia</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/10/241010002142.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Studying microscopic layers of dirt dug from the Tam Pa Ling cave site in northeastern Laos has provided a team of archaeologists further insights int...</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 05:21:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How a bunch of seemingly disorganized cells go on to form a robust embryo</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/10/241010142527.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Embryo development starts when a single egg cell is fertilized and starts dividing continuously. Initially a chaotic cluster, it gradually evolves int...</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 19:25:27 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>