<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 06:59:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Statement by Director Sethuraman Panchanathan on NSF ranking in Best Places to Work in the Federal Government</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/statement-director-panchanathan-nsf-ranking-best-places-work</link><description>I am pleased to announce that the U.S. National Science Foundation has again been recognized among the 2023 Best Places to Work in the Federal Government®. NSF ranked No. 8 among mid-sized agencies as featured in a special edition released today by …</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 15:10:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Vigorous melting' at Antarctica's Thwaites 'Doomsday' Glacier</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240520155541.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Glaciologists show evidence of warm ocean water intruding kilometers beneath grounded ice at Thwaites Glacier in West Antarctica. The findings suggest that existing climate models are underestimating the impact of ocean and ice interactions in future sea level rise projections.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 20:55:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF planning major infrastructure overhaul to support future research in South Pole</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-planning-major-infrastructure-overhaul-support</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation released the draft of its South Pole Station Master Plan (SPSMP), which will inform investments planned under the NSF Antarctic Infrastructure Recapitalization program and ensure that the mission and priorities of…</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 14:39:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Webb Telescope offers first glimpse of an exoplanet's interior</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240520122840.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>A surprisingly low amount of methane and a super-sized core hide within the cotton candy -- like planet WASP-107 b.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 17:28:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF announces pilot phase and anticipated opening date of Arecibo C3 at the site of the NSF Arecibo Observatory Historic District in Puerto Rico</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-pilot-phase-anticipated-opening-date-of-arecibo</link><description>| En Español | As excitement builds for the grand opening of the new U.S. National Science Foundation Arecibo Center for Culturally Relevant and Inclusive Science Education, Computational Skills, and Community Engagement (NSF Arecibo C3), anticipated…</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 16:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blueprints of self-assembly</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240520122835.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Scientists have taken a step closer to replicating nature's processes of self-assembly. The study describes the synthetic construction of a tiny, self-assembled crystal known as a 'pyrochlore,' which bears unique optical properties. The advance provides a steppingstone to the eventual construction of sophisticated, self-assembling devices at the nanoscale -- roughly the size of a single virus.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 17:28:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-51</link><description>This week was full of celebrations and milestones — including recognizing NSF staff and public servants for their hard work to better the nation; celebrating teachers for their dedication to educating the next generation of scientists, engineers and…</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 22:11:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meerkat chit-chat</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240520122825.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Researchers unravel the vocal interactions of meerkat groups and show they use two different types of interactions to stay in touch.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 17:28:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF announces $24M investment across three EPSCoR jurisdictions</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-24m-investment-across-three-epscor</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has awarded teams from South Dakota, New Hampshire and Maine roughly $8 million each through the Established Program to Stimulate Competitive Research (EPSCoR) Collaborations for Optimizing Research Ecosystems…</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 18:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Record low Antarctic sea ice 'extremely unlikely' without climate change</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240520122718.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Scientists have found that the record-low levels of sea ice around Antarctica in 2023 were extremely unlikely to happen without the influence of climate change. This low was a one-in-a-2000-year event without climate change and four times more likely under its effects.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 17:27:18 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>