<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 22:36:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Mountain building linked to major extinction event half a billion years ago</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/mountain-building-linked-major-extinction-event</link><description>As life on Earth rapidly expanded a little over 500 million years ago during the "Cambrian explosion," Earth had tectonic plates slowly crashing into each other, building mountains and starting a series of unfortunate events that led to a mass…</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 22:57:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A greener, more effective way to kill termites</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240531182855.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Scientists have discovered a highly effective, nontoxic, and less expensive way to lure hungry termites to their doom.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 23:28:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF and DOE partner on new internship opportunity in clean hydrogen energy</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-doe-partner-new-internship-opportunity-clean</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation and the Department of Energy, through its Office of Energy Efficiency and Renewable Energy (EERE), have initiated a joint training and professional development opportunity for NSF-supported graduate students in…</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 18:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Martian meteorites deliver a trove of information on Red Planet's structure</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240531182852.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Mars has a distinct structure in its mantle and crust with discernible reservoirs, and this is known thanks to meteorites that scientists have analyzed. These results are important for understanding not only how Mars formed and evolved, but also for providing precise data that can inform recent NASA missions like Insight and Perseverance and the Mars Sample Return.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 23:28:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Climate change will make it harder to see the forest for the trees</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/climate-change-will-make-it-harder-see-forest</link><description>Individual trees can't move to escape climate change, and new U.S. National Science Foundation-supported research shows that species will be limited in their ability to migrate via seed dispersal and other methods because of a lack of symbiotic fungi…</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 14:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Glimpses of a volcanic world: New telescope images of Jupiter's moon Io rival those from spacecraft</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240530182217.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Combining a new imaging instrument with the powerful adaptive optics capabilities of the Large Binocular Telescope, astronomers have captured a volcanic event on Jupiter's moon Io at a resolution never before achieved with Earth-based observations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 23:22:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-53</link><description>From testifying in front of the Senate Committee on Commerce, Science, and Transportation hearing to celebrating new graduates entering the STEM enterprise, this week NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan reinforced the significance of the agency's…</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 22:30:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Ugly' fossil places extinct saber-toothed cat on Texas coast</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240530182207.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>This fossil looks like a lumpy, rounded rock with a couple of exposed teeth that are a little worse for wear, having been submerged and tumbled along the floor of the Gulf of Mexico for thousands of years before washing up on a beach. But when it was X-rayed a doctoral student saw there was more to the fossil that met the eye: a hidden canine tooth that had not yet erupted from the jaw bone. It was just what researchers needed to identify the fossil as belonging to a Homotherium, a genus of large cat that roamed much of the Earth for millions of years.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 23:22:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Navajo Technical University partners with NSF center, creating new opportunities in materials research and education</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/navajo-technical-university-partners-nsf-center</link><description>A partnership that began in 2017 between Navajo Technical University (NTU) and the U.S. National Science Foundation Materials Research Science and Engineering Center at Harvard University is providing Navajo students with new opportunities to pursue…</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 17:30:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In the brain at rest, neurons rehearse future experience</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240530182203.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>New research sheds light on how individual neurons in the hippocampus of rats stabilize and tune spatial representations during periods of rest following the animals' first time running a maze, offering first proof of neuroplasticity during sleep.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 23:22:03 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>