<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 08:01:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NSF invests $7.6M in educational projects to build a skilled semiconductor manufacturing workforce in partnership with Intel Corporation</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-invests-76m-educational-projects-build-skilled</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent.png</image_url><description>Today, the U.S. National Science Foundation and Intel Corporation announced a $7.6 million investment in six projects to advance equitable STEM education and training opportunities that strengthen the nation's semiconductor workforce. This investment…</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>3D-printed blood vessels bring artificial organs closer to reality</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240807225648.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent3.png</image_url><description>Lab-grown organs are a long-time 'holy grail' of organ engineering that has yet to be achieved, but new research has brought that goal a big step closer to reality using a new 3D-printing method called co-SWIFT. co-SWIFT prints branching networks of double-layered vessels that are infused with smooth muscle cells and endothelial cells into living human cardiac tissue, and can even replicate patient-specific vascular structures,indicating that it could one day be used for personalized medicine.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 03:56:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF promotes the transition to a circular economy in advanced materials</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-promotes-transition-circular-economy-advanced</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent3.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation, in partnership with Australia's national science agency, Commonwealth Scientific and Industrial Research Organisation (CSIRO), are investing in solutions that will accelerate the transition of materials…</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists lay out revolutionary method to warm Mars</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240807225455.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent2.png</image_url><description>Ever since we learned that the surface of planet Mars is cold and dead, people have wondered if there is a way to make it friendlier to life. The newly proposed method is over 5,000 times more efficient than previous schemes to globally warm Mars, representing a significant leap forward in our ability to modify the Martian environment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 03:54:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Celebrating two years of “Chips and Science”</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/celebrating-two-years-chips-science</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent.png</image_url><description>NSF unleashed critical investments to support use-inspired research and innovation in key technology areas and to support solutions to pressing national, societal and geostrategic challenges, as articulated in the “CHIPS and Science Act of 2022.” The…</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Giant prehistoric flying reptile took off using similar method to bats, study finds</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240807122807.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent2.png</image_url><description>The pterosaur likely used all four limbs to propel itself in the air, as seen in bats today, researchers have found.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 17:28:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-61</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent.png</image_url><description>This week, NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan participated in key international and strategic dialogues, demonstrating NSF's leadership in fostering global partnerships and advancing cutting-edge research. At the second "U.S.-Singapore Critical and…</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 16:32:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Social rank may determine if animals live fast, die young</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240807122737.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent2.png</image_url><description>Social rank may determine whether animals prioritize immediate fitness over long-term health, according to a study. Researchers studied macaques on a Thai island and found that the animals' unusual habit of washing their food is in fact based on social rank. Dominant monkeys quickly brush their food on their fur before eating it, along with mouthfuls of tooth-degrading sand, while lower-ranked monkeys obsessively wash their food in the surf. Citing the disposable soma hypothesis, the researchers suggest that high-ranking macaques are looking to quickly consume energy to mate and fend off challengers. But food-washing monkeys may be preserving their long-term health to produce more offspring over time. The findings could shed light on how the wear observed in the fossilized teeth of early humans relates to social structure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 17:27:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF invests $2.8M to strengthen technical AI education at two-year institutions</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-invests-28m-strengthen-technical-ai-education</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent2.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has announced a grant of $2.8 million to establish a National Applied Artificial Intelligence Consortium (NAAIC) at Miami Dade College. Funded through the NSF Advanced Technological Education program, this…</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 16:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Processing traumatic memories during sleep leads to changes in the brain associated with improvement in PTSD symptoms</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240807122724.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent3.png</image_url><description>Currently, the first-choice treatment for PTSD is exposure-based psychotherapy, where therapists help rewire the emotions associated with the traumatic memory in the patient's brain, shifting from fear and arousal to a more neutral response. However, up to 50% of patients fail to respond well to this treatment. In a new study scientists showed for the first time that reactivating therapeutically-altered memories during sleep leads to more brain activity related to memory processing, which is associated with a reduction in PTSD symptoms.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 17:27:24 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>