<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 06:51:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>A window into the body: groundbreaking technique makes skin transparent</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/window-into-body-invisible-skin</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Researchers have developed a new way to see organs within a body by rendering overlying tissues transparent to visible light. The counterintuitive pro...</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 19:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists make tissue of living animals see-through</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240905143615.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>In a pioneering new study, researchers made the skin on the skulls and abdomens of live mice transparent by applying to the areas a mixture of water a...</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 19:36:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weather anomaly experienced in the McMurdo Dry Valleys</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/weather-anomaly-experienced-mcmurdo-dry-valleys</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>The McMurdo Dry Valleys are a unique region of Antarctica, nearly devoid of snow and ice. An atmospheric river event in March 2022 led to record warm ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 15:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gravitational waves unveil previously unseen properties of neutron stars</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240905131242.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>A better understanding of the inner workings of neutron stars will lead to a greater knowledge of the dynamics that underpin the workings of the unive...</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 18:12:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nothing to 'shrub' about: How plant coverage is affecting the Arctic carbon cycle</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nothing-shrub-about-how-plant-coverage-affecting-arctic</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Researchers at Columbia University's Department of Earth and Environment Science have discovered new implications for the Arctic carbon cycle in the f...</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 19:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Travel could be the best defense against aging</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240905121025.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Forget about retinol night creams, researchers believe travel could be the best way to defy premature aging. An interdisciplinary study has applied th...</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 17:10:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF investing nearly $8M in EducateAI awards to develop next generation of well-trained AI workforce</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-investing-nearly-8m-educateai-awards-develop-next</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Artificial Intelligence is transforming research, education, manufacturing and everyday life. To prepare the next generation of talent for a diverse, ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 16:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Researchers discover a space oddity -- an exoplanet moving in mysterious ways</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240905120944.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>A research team has discovered a small planet that displays peculiar orbital motion. The shimmying planet, located 455 light-years from Earth, shows t...</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 17:09:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Antarctic Dragonfish Species Discovered</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/new-antarctic-dragonfish-species-discovered</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>A research team at the Virginia Institute of Marine Science at William &amp; Mary has uncovered a new species of Antarctic fish, which could reshape how s...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 19:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fungus-controlled robots tap into the unique power of nature</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240904192325.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>In creating a pair of new robots, researchers cultivated an unlikely component, one found on the forest floor: fungal mycelia. By harnessing mycelia's...</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 00:23:25 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>