<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 06:58:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NSF and industry partners announce sustainable polymer research funding opportunity</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-industry-partners-announce-sustainable-polymer</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has launched a $9.5 million research funding opportunity in partnership with BASF, Dow, IBM, PepsiCo Inc. and Procter &amp; Gamble Co. Sustainable Polymers Enabled by Emerging Data Analytics (SPEED) is part of NSF's…</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 18:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists track 'doubling' in origin of cancer cells</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240502141250.htm</link><description>Working with human breast and lung cells, scientists say they have charted a molecular pathway that can lure cells down a hazardous path of duplicating their genome too many times, a hallmark of cancer cells.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 19:12:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New NSF grant targets large language models and generative AI, exploring how they work and implications for societal impacts</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/new-nsf-grant-targets-large-language-models</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has announced a grant of $9 million to Northeastern University for research to investigate how large language models (LLMs) and generative AI operate, focusing on the computing process called deep inference and AI…</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sugar-based catalyst upcycles carbon dioxide</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240502141205.htm</link><description>New catalyst is made from an inexpensive, abundant metal and table sugar. Catalyst converts carbon dioxide (CO2) into carbon monoxide, a building block for producing a variety of useful chemicals including syngas. With recent advances in carbon capture technologies, post-combustion carbon capture is becoming a plausible option to help tackle the global climate change crisis. But how to handle the captured carbon remains an open-ended question. The new catalyst potentially could provide one solution for disposing the potent greenhouse gas by converting it into a more valuable product.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 19:12:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prolific potholes in the prairie star in award-winning short film</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/prolific-potholes-prairie-star-award-winning-short</link><description>Most of us think potholes are something to avoid. However, some potholes are worth protecting. The U.S. National Science Foundation is funding researchers to study prairie pothole wetlands, which are ecologically and economically important, but under…</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 14:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Random robots are more reliable</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240502113808.htm</link><description>New algorithm encourages robots to move more randomly to collect more diverse data for learning. In tests, robots started with no knowledge and then learned and correctly performed tasks within a single attempt. New model could improve safety and practicality of self-driving cars, delivery drones and more.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:38:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF and NIH partner on internship opportunity in biomedical engineering</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-nih-partner-internship-opportunity-biomedical</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation and the National Institutes of Health's National Institute of Biomedical Imaging and Bioengineering (NIBIB) have initiated a joint research training opportunity through the NSF Non-Academic Research Internships…</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 17:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Significant new discovery in teleportation research -- Noise can improve the quality of quantum teleportation</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240502113805.htm</link><description>Researchers succeeded in conducting an almost perfect quantum teleportation despite the presence of noise that usually disrupts the transfer of quantum state.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:38:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF and USDA join forces to boost innovation in agricultural robotics</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-usda-join-forces-boost-innovation-agricultural</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation and the U.S. Department of Agriculture's National Institute of Food and Agriculture (USDA NIFA) are teaming up to advance foundational research in agricultural robotics. The agencies are issuing a new Dear…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wild orangutan treats wound with pain-relieving plant</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240502113715.htm</link><description>A wild orangutan was observed applying a plant with known medicinal properties to a wound, a first for a wild animal.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:37:15 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>