<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 07:08:12 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Illuminating the twist: Light-driven inversion of supramolecular chirality</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/04/250411105900.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>In a striking demonstration of molecular control, a team of scientists has harnessed light to reverse the twist in self-assembling molecules. The stud...</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 15:59:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From boring to bursting: Giant black hole awakens</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/04/250411105903.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Astronomers are investigating the longest and most energetic bursts of X-rays seen from a newly awakened black hole. Watching this strange behavior un...</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 15:59:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Genes in bacterial genomes are arranged in a meaningful order</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/04/250410160707.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Bioinformaticians have established that the genes in bacterial genomes are arranged in a meaningful order. They describe that the genes are arranged b...</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 21:07:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Drug pollution alters salmon migration</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/04/250410160719.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Study reveals commonly detected environmental levels of clobazam -- a medication often prescribed for sleep disorders -- increased the river-to-sea mi...</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 21:07:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ancient tools from a South African cave reveal connections between prehistoric people</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/04/250409212539.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In a cave overlooking the ocean on the southern coast of South Africa, archaeologists discovered thousands of stone tools, created by ancient humans r...</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 02:25:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF expands access to advanced cloud computing for scientific research</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-expands-access-advanced-cloud-computing-scientific</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation (NSF) has awarded a $20 million grant to expand the NSF CloudBank, an initiative designed to accelerate science a...</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 14:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Solid or liquid? Scientists accurately predict complex tissue changes in fruit fly embryos</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/solid-or-liquid-scientists-accurately-predict-complex-tissue</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Funded by the U.S. National Science Foundation, scientists have accurately modeled particular cellular changes in Drosophila melanogaster, or the frui...</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 13:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quantum quasiparticle could make future quantum computers more reliable</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/quantum-quasiparticle-could-make-future-quantum-computers</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Supported by the U.S. National Science Foundation, physicists have revealed the presence of a previously unobserved type of subatomic phenomenon calle...</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tiny lenses grown from bacteria and enzymes may help doctors see inside cells</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/tiny-lenses-grown-bacteria-enzymes-may-help-doctors-see</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>A team of researchers supported by the U.S. National Science Foundation has successfully made self-growing microlenses using bacteria and enzymes foun...</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 21:44:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Conserving the White Oak Tree: Critical for timber and distilling industries</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/conserving-white-oak-tree-critical-timber-distilling</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>A group of researchers from the University of Kentucky, The University of Tennessee and Indiana University, including those supported by the U.S. Nati...</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>