<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 10:39:44 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>New study informs fire prevention strategies to save lives and property</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/new-study-informs-fire-prevention-strategies-save-lives</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>U.S. National Science Foundation-supported research shows that fires in populated areas are three times more likely to lead to premature deaths than w...</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 13:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From electronic bugs to real ones, methods for listening provide insights into communication and hearing</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/electronic-bugs-real-ones-methods-listening-provide-insights</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>A new study by U.S. National Science Foundation-funded researchers on how members of the animal world sense and react to sounds provides insight into ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 14:33:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The secret to happiness lies within you, or society -- or both</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/05/250502102702.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>What is the secret to happiness? Does happiness come from within, or is it shaped by external influences such as our jobs, health, relationships and m...</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 15:27:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists discover key to taming unrest at Italy's Campi Flegrei</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/05/250502182509.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>New research shows that elevation changes and earthquakes in Italy's Campi Flegrei volcanic area are caused by rising pressure in a geothermal reservo...</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 23:25:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The future of brain activity monitoring may look like a strand of hair</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/05/250502133950.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Researchers have created a hairlike device for long-term, non-invasive monitoring of the brain's electrical activity. The lightweight and flexible ele...</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 18:39:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Antivenom neutralizes the neurotoxins of 19 of the world's deadliest snakes</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/05/250502133806.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>By using antibodies from a human donor with a self-induced hyper-immunity to snake venom, scientists have developed the most broadly effective antiven...</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 18:38:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The all-female Korean Haenyeo divers show genetic adaptions to cold water diving</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/05/250502133925.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>The Haenyeo, a group of all-female divers from the Korean island of Jeju, are renowned for their ability to dive in frigid waters without the aid of b...</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 18:39:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In extreme conditions, heat does not flow between materials. It bounces off.</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/extreme-conditions-heat-does-not-flow-between-materials-it</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>A new study supported by the U.S. National Science Foundation shows, for the first time, how heat moves — or rather, doesn't — between materials in a ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 18:51:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Statement by Director Sethuraman Panchanathan on his departure</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/statement-director-sethuraman-panchanathan-his-departure</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>"Today, I am announcing my decision to step down as Director of the U.S. National Science Foundation (NSF), effective today. It has been an honor and ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 19:40:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Atmospheric winds have surprising impact on ocean weather</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/atmospheric-winds-have-surprising-impact-ocean-weather</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>U.S. National Science Foundation-supported researchers published a new paper that explains how atmospheric wind affects eddies, an ocean weather pheno...</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>