<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 00:43:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Woolly mammoth chromosomes reconstructed using fossilized sample</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/woolly-mammoth-chromosomes-reconstructed</link><description>An international team of scientists assembled the woolly mammoth's genetic code using fossilized chromosomes from a 52,000-year-old carcass discovered in Siberian permafrost. The mammoth became freeze-dried on death, preserving the 3D structure of…</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 21:16:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Insight into one of life's earliest ancestors revealed in new study</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240712124116.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Researchers have shed light on Earth's earliest ecosystem, showing that within a few hundred million years of planetary formation, life on Earth was already flourishing.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 17:41:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF announces groundbreaking Leadership-Class Computing Facility project</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-groundbreaking-computing-facility</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has begun construction on the Leadership-Class Computing Facility (LCCF), a cutting-edge facility led by the Texas Advanced Computing Center (TACC) at The University of Texas at Austin (UT Austin) that will…</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How the 'heart and lungs' of a galaxy extend its life</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240712124039.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Galaxies avoid an early death because they have a 'heart and lungs' which effectively regulate their 'breathing' and prevent them growing out of control, a new study suggests. If they didn't, the universe would have aged much faster than it has and all we would see today is huge 'zombie' galaxies teeming with dead and dying stars. That's according to a new study that investigates one of the great mysteries of the Universe -- why galaxies are not as large as astronomers would expect.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 17:40:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF appoints Micah Cheatham as chief management officer</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-appoints-micah-cheatham-chief-management</link><description>Today, the U.S. National Science Foundation is pleased to announce the appointment of Micah Cheatham as chief management officer (CMO). In this role, Cheatham will serve as principal advisor to the NSF director and deputy director on agency…</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Muscle machine: How water controls the speed of muscle contraction</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240711215518.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>The flow of water within a muscle fiber may dictate how quickly muscle can contract, according to a new study.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 02:55:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Transformers: Cooler side of the grid</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/transformers-cooler-side-grid</link><description>In a significant step towards resilient, sustainable energy, researchers at The University of Texas at Austin (UT Austin) are undertaking a groundbreaking initiative to enhance the performance and longevity of grid transformers, a critical component…</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:19:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hydrogen flight looks ready for take-off with new advances</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240711111519.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>The possibility of hydrogen-powered flight means greater opportunities for fossil-free travel, and the technological advances to make this happen are moving fast. New studies show that almost all air travel within a 750-mile radius (1200 km) could be made with hydrogen-powered aircraft by 2045, and with a novel heat exchanger currently in development, this range could be even further.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:15:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Statement from NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan on the U.S. Economic Development Administration's Regional Technology and Innovation Hub awardees</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/statement-on-economic-development-admin-regional-tech-innovation</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation congratulates the U.S. Economic Development Administration (EDA) on its announcement today of its Regional Technology and Innovation Hubs (Tech Hubs). In alignment with the 'CHIPS and Science Act of 2022,' NSF and…</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dark matter in dwarf galaxy tracked using stellar motions</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240711111354.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>The qualities and behavior of dark matter, the invisible 'glue' of the universe, continue to be shrouded in mystery. Though galaxies are mostly made of dark matter, understanding how it is distributed within a galaxy offers clues to what this substance is, and how it's relevant to a galaxy's evolution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:13:54 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>