<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 11:06:10 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Quantum dice: Scientists harness true randomness from entangled photons</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/06/250622225927.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Scientists at NIST and the University of Colorado Boulder have created CURBy, a cutting-edge quantum randomness beacon that draws on the intrinsic unp...</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 03:59:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Affordances in the brain: The human superpower AI hasn’t mastered</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/06/250622225921.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Scientists at the University of Amsterdam discovered that our brains automatically understand how we can move through different environments—whether i...</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 03:59:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This triple-layer sunlight catalyst supercharges green hydrogen by 800%</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/06/250623072757.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Researchers in Sweden have developed a powerful new material that dramatically boosts the ability to create hydrogen fuel from water using sunlight, m...</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 12:27:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From cursed tomb fungus to cancer cure: Aspergillus flavus yields potent new drug</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/06/250623072748.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>In a remarkable twist of science, researchers have transformed a fungus long associated with death into a potential weapon against cancer. Found in to...</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 12:27:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rice University breakthrough keeps CO₂ electrolyzers running 50x longer</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/06/250622030532.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>A Rice University team discovered that bubbling CO₂ through a mild acid dramatically improves the lifespan and efficiency of electrochemical devices t...</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 08:05:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Microbes from Brooklyn could help mitigate industrial contamination</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/microbes-brooklyn-could-help-mitigate-industrial</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Microorganisms with extreme abilities have laid the groundwork for decades of biotechnologies from the PCR technique that enables amplification of DNA...</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 16:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF ZEUS becomes the most powerful laser in the U.S.</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-zeus-becomes-most-powerful-laser-us</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation Zettawatt-Equivalent Ultrashort pulse laser System (NSF ZEUS) laser facility at the University of Michigan now ha...</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 14:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Training AI to see more like humans</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/training-ai-see-more-humans</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>At Brown University, an innovative new project is revealing that teaching artificial intelligence to perceive things more like people may begin with s...</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 14:00:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sparking curiosity in the future semiconductor workforce</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/sparking-curiosity-future-semiconductor-workforce</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>The United States semiconductor industry is projected to have between 60,000 and 100,000 unfilled jobs by 2030. As the need for semiconductor technici...</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 14:00:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Researchers discover microplastics at all ocean depths</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/researchers-discover-microplastics-all-ocean-depths</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Researchers with support from the U.S. National Science Foundation published a global benchmark of microplastic distribution in the ocean, revealing t...</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 14:00:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>