<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 07:25:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-62</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Last week, the U.S. National Science Foundation made major strides in research, innovation and conservation, marked by key announcements and engagemen...</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 22:12:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>First low frequency search for alien technology in distant galaxies</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240826131354.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Researchers have announced a groundbreaking study using the Murchison Widefield Array (MWA) in Western Australia. The research is the first to search ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 18:13:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Resilitix supports Beryl emergency response efforts with NSF-supported digital twin technology</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/resilitix-supports-beryl-emergency-response-efforts-nsf</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Hurricane Beryl hit Houston, Texas, on Sunday, July 7, causing death and injury and leaving more than two million people suffering power outages and s...</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 20:56:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Matching dinosaur footprints found on opposite sides of the Atlantic Ocean</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240826131303.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>An international team of paleontologists has found matching sets of Early Cretaceous dinosaur footprints on what are now two different continents.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 18:13:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Quantum coherence' survives in ultracold molecules</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/quantum-coherence-survives-ultracold-molecules</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Scientists are hot on the trail of a process called quantum coherence, the ability of particles to maintain phase relationships and exist in multiple ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 19:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Early galaxies were not too big for their britches after all</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240826131300.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>According to a new study, some of the earliest galaxies observed with the James Webb Space Telescope are in fact much less massive than they first app...</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 18:13:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF selects David B. Berkowitz as new assistant director for the Mathematics and Physical Sciences Directorate</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-selects-david-b-berkowitz-new-assistant-director</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has selected David B. Berkowitz as assistant director for Mathematical and Physical Sciences (MPS), starting Sept...</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 16:29:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why children can't pay attention to the task at hand</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240826131209.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Scientists have learned that children find it hard to focus on a task, and often take in information that won't help them complete their assignment. B...</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 18:12:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New NSF centers will take a multidisciplinary approach to pandemic prediction and prevention</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/new-nsf-centers-will-take-multidisciplinary</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Early detection and prevention of potential pandemics — whether they affect humans, animals or plants — are vital to the health, economy and security ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 16:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Looking for clues about your biological age? Your grandparents' education may offer some insight.</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240826131203.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Eating well, exercising and attending regular doctor appointments can support a long healthy life, but a new study identified one possible factor beyo...</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 18:12:03 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>