<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 06:52:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-56</link><description>This week, NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan highlighted NSF’s commitment to innovation and STEM advancements through several key events. The Director joined Senator Shaheen in a conversation on Capitol Hill with New Hampshire business leaders to…</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 19:53:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bedtime battles: 1 in 4 parents say their child can't go to sleep because they're worried or anxious</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240617173714.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>One in four parents describe getting their young child to bed as difficult -- and these parents are less likely to have a bedtime routine, more likely to leave on a video or TV show, and more likely to stay with their child until they're asleep.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 22:37:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A deeper look into where the really big one could occur</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/deeper-look-where-really-big-one-could-occur</link><description>For the first time, NSF-funded researchers revealed a detailed look at the potential for a major earthquake off the coasts of southern British Columbia, Washington, Oregon and northern California. The new study characterizes the Cascadia Subduction…</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 17:28:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Direct evidence found for dairy consumption in the Pyrenees in the earliest stages of the Neolithic</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240617173552.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>A study on the remains of the Chaves and Puyascada caves, both located in the province of Huesca, Spain, yields the first direct proof of the consumption and processing of dairy products in the Pyrenees already at the start of the Neolithic period, approximately 7,500 years ago, as well as the consumption of pig. The results lead to doubts about the belief that these products were first used much later in the Pyrenean mountain range.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 22:35:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trouble dead ahead: Acidifying oceans harm tropical corals</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/trouble-dead-ahead-acidifying-oceans-harm-tropical</link><description>The French Polynesian island Moorea is the most beautiful isle in the world, some say. Its lagoons are surrounded by reefs dominated by Porites corals. These corals and other calcifying marine species are the world's primary reef-builders. Therein…</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 16:35:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A high-fat diet may fuel anxiety</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240617173547.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>New research shows when animals are fed a diet high in saturated fat for nine weeks, their gut bacteria change in ways that influence brain chemicals and fuel anxiety.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 22:35:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF and AACC announce 2024 Community College Innovation Challenge winners</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-aacc-2024-community-college-winners</link><description>Today, the U.S. National Science Foundation, in partnership with the American Association of Community Colleges (AACC), announced the three winning teams of the 2024 Community College Innovation Challenge (CCIC). The annual competition seeks to…</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:49:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wear it, then recycle: Designers make dissolvable textiles from gelatin</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240617173521.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Researchers hope their DIY machine will help designers around the world experiment with making their own, sustainable fashion and other textiles from a range of natural ingredients -- maybe even the chitin in crab shells or agar-agar from algae.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 22:35:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cloudy with a chance of climate predictions</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/cloudy-chance-climate-predictions</link><description>Whether they're fluffy, bright or ominous, clouds are key to regulating Earth's energy and water cycles. Two sets of U.S. National Science Foundation-supported researchers recently published findings to help scientists better understand what's…</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 21:15:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ancient polar sea reptile fossil is oldest ever found in Southern Hemisphere</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240617173438.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>An international team of scientists has identified the oldest fossil of a sea-going reptile from the Southern Hemisphere -- a nothosaur vertebra found on New Zealand's South Island. 246 million years ago, at the beginning of the Age of Dinosaurs, New Zealand was located on the southern polar coast of a vast super-ocean called Panthalassa. 'The nothosaur found in New Zealand is over 40 million years older than the previously oldest known sauropterygian fossils from the Southern Hemisphere.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 22:34:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>