<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 07:26:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NSF and NIH partner on internship opportunity in biomedical engineering</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-nih-partner-internship-opportunity-biomedical</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation and the National Institutes of Health's National Institute of Biomedical Imaging and Bioengineering (NIBIB) have initiated a joint research training opportunity through the NSF Non-Academic Research Internships…</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 17:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Methane emissions from landfill could be turned into sustainable jet fuel in plasma chemistry leap</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/04/240430131902.htm</link><description>Researchers have developed a chemical process using plasma that could create sustainable jet fuel from methane gas emitted from landfills, potentially creating a low-carbon aviation industry.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 18:19:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF and USDA join forces to boost innovation in agricultural robotics</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-usda-join-forces-boost-innovation-agricultural</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation and the U.S. Department of Agriculture's National Institute of Food and Agriculture (USDA NIFA) are teaming up to advance foundational research in agricultural robotics. The agencies are issuing a new Dear…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biodegradable 'living plastic' houses bacterial spores that help it break down</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/04/240430131849.htm</link><description>A new type of bioplastic could help reduce the plastic industry's environmental footprint. Researchers have developed a biodegradable form of thermoplastic polyurethane (TPU) filled with bacterial spores that, when exposed to nutrients present in compost, germinate and break down the material at the end of its life cycle.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 18:18:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New center supported by NSF will catalyze data-driven insights in molecular and cellular biosciences</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/new-center-supported-nsf-will-catalyze-data-driven</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has made a $20 million award to support the creation of the National Synthesis Center for Emergence in the Molecular and Cellular Sciences (NCEMS). The center will combine vast amounts of available data on…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 14:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NASA's Webb maps weather on planet 280 light-years away</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/04/240430131829.htm</link><description>Researchers have successfully used NASA's James Webb Space Telescope to map the weather on the hot gas-giant exoplanet WASP-43 b.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 18:18:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF honors 3 outstanding early-career researchers with the Alan T. Waterman Award</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-honors-3-outstanding-early-career-researchers</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation honored three researchers with the Alan T. Waterman Award, the nation's highest honor for early-career scientists and engineers. The 2024 recipients: Muyinatu A. Lediju Bell, a biomedical engineer at Johns Hopkins…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Researchers identify over 2,000 genetic signals linked to blood pressure in study of over one million people</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/04/240430105545.htm</link><description>Researchers have discovered over a hundred new regions of the human genome, also known as genomic loci, that appear to influence a person's blood pressure. In total, over 2,000 independent genetic signals for blood pressure are now reported, demonstrating that blood pressure is a highly complex trait influenced by thousands of different genetic variants.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 15:55:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF invests $90M in innovative national scientific cyberinfrastructure for transforming STEM education</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-invests-90m-innovative-national-scientific</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation announced today a strategic investment of $90 million over five years in SafeInsights, a unique national scientific cyberinfrastructure aimed at transforming learning research and STEM education. Funded through…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:30:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A virus could help save billions of gallons of wastewater produced by fracking</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/04/240430105540.htm</link><description>An estimated 168 billion gallons of wastewater -- or produced water -- is generated annually by the Permian Basin fracking industry, according to a 2022 report. The major waste stream has proved both difficult and costly to treat because of the chemical complexity of the water.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 15:55:40 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>