<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:24:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>A deeper look into where the really big one could occur</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/deeper-look-where-really-big-one-could-occur</link><description>For the first time, NSF-funded researchers revealed a detailed look at the potential for a major earthquake off the coasts of southern British Columbia, Washington, Oregon and northern California. The new study characterizes the Cascadia Subduction…</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 17:28:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pair plasmas found in deep space can now be generated in the lab</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240613161155.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Researchers have experimentally generated high-density relativistic electron-positron pair-plasma beams by producing two to three orders of magnitude more pairs than previously reported.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:11:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trouble dead ahead: Acidifying oceans harm tropical corals</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/trouble-dead-ahead-acidifying-oceans-harm-tropical</link><description>The French Polynesian island Moorea is the most beautiful isle in the world, some say. Its lagoons are surrounded by reefs dominated by Porites corals. These corals and other calcifying marine species are the world's primary reef-builders. Therein…</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 16:35:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists preserve DNA in an amber-like polymer</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240613161153.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>With their 'T-REX' method, researchers developed a glassy, amber-like polymer that can be used for long-term storage of DNA, such as entire human genomes or digital files such as photos.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:11:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF and AACC announce 2024 Community College Innovation Challenge winners</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-aacc-2024-community-college-winners</link><description>Today, the U.S. National Science Foundation, in partnership with the American Association of Community Colleges (AACC), announced the three winning teams of the 2024 Community College Innovation Challenge (CCIC). The annual competition seeks to…</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:49:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are mixed emotions real? New research says yes</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240613161150.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Neuroscientists found that brains display distinct neural activity when experiencing emotions such as bitter-sweetness. The advance could help solve a longstanding scientific debate: whether 'mixed emotions' arise from unique activity in the brain, or if we're just flip-flopping back and forth between positive and negative feelings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:11:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-55</link><description>US National Science Foundation Director Sethuraman Panchanathan had a dynamic week, engaging with various organizations and audiences. On June 5, he participated in The Science Coalition /Association of American Universities (AAU)/Association of…</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The rotation of Earth's inner core has slowed, new study confirms</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240613161147.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>The new study provides unambiguous evidence that the inner core began to decrease its speed around 2010, moving slower than the Earth's surface.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:11:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cloudy with a chance of climate predictions</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/cloudy-chance-climate-predictions</link><description>Whether they're fluffy, bright or ominous, clouds are key to regulating Earth's energy and water cycles. Two sets of U.S. National Science Foundation-supported researchers recently published findings to help scientists better understand what's…</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 21:15:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paleontology: New fossil fish genus discovered</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240613140915.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Paleontologists have identified a new genus of fossil goby, revealing evolutionary secrets of a lineage that stretches back millions of years.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 19:09:15 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>