<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:05:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NSF and AACC announce 2024 Community College Innovation Challenge winners</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-aacc-2024-community-college-winners</link><description>Today, the U.S. National Science Foundation, in partnership with the American Association of Community Colleges (AACC), announced the three winning teams of the 2024 Community College Innovation Challenge (CCIC). The annual competition seeks to…</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:49:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pair plasmas found in deep space can now be generated in the lab</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240613161155.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Researchers have experimentally generated high-density relativistic electron-positron pair-plasma beams by producing two to three orders of magnitude more pairs than previously reported.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:11:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cloudy with a chance of climate predictions</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/cloudy-chance-climate-predictions</link><description>Whether they're fluffy, bright or ominous, clouds are key to regulating Earth's energy and water cycles. Two sets of U.S. National Science Foundation-supported researchers recently published findings to help scientists better understand what's…</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 21:15:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists preserve DNA in an amber-like polymer</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240613161153.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>With their 'T-REX' method, researchers developed a glassy, amber-like polymer that can be used for long-term storage of DNA, such as entire human genomes or digital files such as photos.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:11:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Cells to Galaxies' unites astronomers, medical imaging experts to advance both fields</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/cells-galaxies-unites-astronomers</link><description>In May 2024, experts from the U.S. National Science Foundation National Radio Astronomy Observatory (NSF NRAO) and the medical imaging field presented at the International Society for Magnetic Resonance in Medicine conference on the surprising…</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 15:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are mixed emotions real? New research says yes</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240613161150.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Neuroscientists found that brains display distinct neural activity when experiencing emotions such as bitter-sweetness. The advance could help solve a longstanding scientific debate: whether 'mixed emotions' arise from unique activity in the brain, or if we're just flip-flopping back and forth between positive and negative feelings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:11:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Synthetic platelets stanch bleeding, promote healing using advanced materials</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/synthetic-platelets-stanch-bleeding-promote-healing</link><description>A research team has developed synthetic platelets that can stop bleeding and enhance healing at the site of an injury. They demonstrated that the synthetic platelets work well in some animals but have not yet begun clinical trials in humans. The…</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 15:03:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The rotation of Earth's inner core has slowed, new study confirms</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240613161147.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>The new study provides unambiguous evidence that the inner core began to decrease its speed around 2010, moving slower than the Earth's surface.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:11:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-54</link><description>NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan traveled to Interlaken, Switzerland, to join international partners for the Global Research Council's (GRC) annual meeting. GRC aims to promote long-term multilateral research and collaboration across continents…</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 20:32:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paleontology: New fossil fish genus discovered</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240613140915.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Paleontologists have identified a new genus of fossil goby, revealing evolutionary secrets of a lineage that stretches back millions of years.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 19:09:15 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>