<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 07:44:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Garden to table: Turning a backyard plant into a mainstream crop</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/garden-table-turning-backyard-plant-mainstream</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>It looks like a cherry tomato wrapped in a paper lantern, but in fact it's called a groundcherry. Little-known beyond gardeners and farmers, the groundcherry has quietly produced fruit across North America for centuries. Now it's emerging from…</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 17:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists devise method to secure Earth's biodiversity on the moon</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240731141234.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>New research led proposes a plan to safeguard Earth's imperiled biodiversity by cryogenically preserving biological material on the moon. The moon's permanently shadowed craters are cold enough for cryogenic preservation without the need for electricity or liquid nitrogen.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 19:12:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why does the United States have the most tornadoes in the world?  Scientists find new answers.</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/why-does-united-states-have-most-tornadoes-world</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>The central and eastern regions of the United States are the hotspots for Earth's most damaging and frequent tornadoes, scientists have found. In fact, the U.S. has the most tornadoes of any country in the world, but why? In a study published in…</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 17:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cannabinoid CBG reduces anxiety and stress in first human clinical trial</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240731141232.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>A lesser-known cannabinoid that is gaining in popularity Cannabigerol (CBG) effectively reduced anxiety in a clinical trial without the intoxication typically associated with whole plant cannabis. It may even have some memory enhancing effects, according to a new study. For the study, researchers conducted the first human clinical trial investigating the acute effects of CBG on anxiety, stress and mood. The research revealed that 20 mg of hemp-derived CBG significantly reduced feelings of anxiety at 20, 45 and 60 minutes after ingestion compared to a placebo.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 19:12:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-60</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>This week, NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan participated in a series of pivotal discussions and events, underscoring U.S. National Science Foundation’s role at the forefront of scientific innovation and workforce development in the United States…</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 18:12:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Barriers designed to prevent saltwater intrusion may worsen inland flooding</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240731141130.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Building protection barriers without accounting for potential inland flooding risks from groundwater can eventually worsen the very issues they aim to solve.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 19:11:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF funds over $50M in new partnerships to broaden participation in materials science</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-funds-over-50m-new-partnerships-broaden</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation is announcing $50 million in Partnerships for Research and Education in Materials (PREM) awards to 15 collaborative research projects nationwide to expand participation and access to materials science-focused…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 14:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The rotation of a nearby star stuns astronomers</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240731141033.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>Astronomers have found that the rotational profile of a nearby star, V889 Herculis, differs considerably from that of the Sun. The observation provides insights into the fundamental stellar astrophysics and helps us understand the activity of the Sun, its spot structures and eruptions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 19:10:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jumping on the jumping gene bandwagon to speed up plant breeding</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/jumping-jumping-gene-bandwagon-speed-plant</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>Getting a new variety of corn, tomato, soybean or other crop to market can be a long and costly effort, with breeders working to ensure the eventual product has the right mix of genetics that will let it withstand change, produce large amounts of…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 18:48:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Recent volcanic 'fires' in Iceland triggered by storage and melting in crust</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240731140924.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>Scientists have detected geochemical signatures of magma pooling and melting beneath the subsurface during the 'Fagradalsfjall Fires', that began on Iceland's Reykjanes peninsula in 2021. Samples show that the start of the eruption began with massive pooling of magma, contrasting initial hypothesis for magma ascent straight from the mantle.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 19:09:24 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>