<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 16:16:33 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Physicists create first-ever Bose-Einstein condensate made of molecules</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/physicists-create-first-ever-bose-einstein</link><description>A team of physicists has successfully created a unique quantum state of matter called a Bose-Einstein condensate (BEC) out of molecules. The team is led by Sebastian Will at Columbia University, who received a U.S. National Science Foundation Faculty…</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 20:53:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Iceland's volcano eruptions may last decades</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240626152033.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Scientists predict from geochemical data that Iceland is entering a new volcanic era that will last for decades, possibly centuries. Under an hour's drive from the country's capital city, the ongoing eruptions pose considerable risks for economic disruption, and they leave evacuated communities uncertain of a possible return.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 20:20:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI-powered underwater robots revolutionize marine conservation, NSF-funded researchers lead the charge</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/ai-powered-underwater-robots-revolutionize-marine</link><description>The underwater environment, covering nearly 80% of the planet, is critical in maintaining ecological balance and supporting human well-being. Effective conservation relies on thoroughly understanding underwater species distribution and ecosystem…</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 16:33:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Surprising phosphate finding in NASA's OSIRIS-REx asteroid sample</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240626151925.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Early analysis of the asteroid Bennu sample returned by NASA's OSIRIS-REx mission has revealed dust rich in carbon, nitrogen, and organic compounds, all of which are essential components for life as we know it. Dominated by clay minerals, particularly serpentine, the sample mirrors the type of rock found at mid-ocean ridges on Earth. The magnesium-sodium phosphate found in the sample hints that the asteroid could have splintered off from an ancient, small, primitive ocean world.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 20:19:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Creating a diverse and inclusive AI research community is the goal of new NSF awards</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/creating-diverse-inclusive-ai-research-community</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation is excited to announce a new round of ExpandAI awards dedicated to fostering diversity and inclusion within the artificial intelligence research community. In collaboration with the departments of Homeland…</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 16:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Non-stop flight: 4,200 km transatlantic flight of the Painted Lady butterfly mapped</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240625221740.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>In October 2013 a researcher made a surprising discovery of Painted Lady Butterflies on the Atlantic beaches of French Guiana -- a species not typically found in South America. This unusual sighting prompted an international study to investigate the origin of these butterflies.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 03:17:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-57</link><description>Last week, US National Science Foundation Director Sethuraman Panchanathan accompanied National Security Advisor Jake Sullivan, Deputy Secretary of State Kurt Campbell, and other senior U.S. government officials to participate in the second annual U…</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 18:34:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Your future medications could be personalized for you on a 3D printer</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240625205649.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Scientists are helping to develop standards and safety protocols that would allow pharmacies to print drugs onsite at a dosage best for you.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 01:56:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF announces $20 million investment in quantum nanofabrication infrastructure</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-20-million-investment-quantum</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation (NSF) announced a nearly $20 million award that will support the construction of a nanoscale fabrication facility at the University of Colorado Boulder to accelerate the co-design and development of atomic…</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 19:36:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wildfires increasingly threaten oil and gas drill sites, compounding potential health risks</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240625205644.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>More than 100,000 oil and gas wells across the western U.S. are in areas burned by wildfires in recent decades, a new study has found, and some 3 million people live next to wells that in the future could be in the path of fires worsened by climate change.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 01:56:44 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>