<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 11:54:24 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>DNA evidence rewrites story of people buried in Pompeii eruption</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/11/241107160923.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Researchers have used ancient DNA to challenge long-held interpretations of the people of Pompeii. Contrary to physical appearances, the DNA evidence ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 21:09:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Memories are not only in the brain, new research finds</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/11/241107193111.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>It's common knowledge that our brains -- and, specifically, our brain cells -- store memories. But a team of scientists has discovered that cells from...</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 00:31:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF names three new I-Corps Hubs expanding the National Innovation Network across the U.S.</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-names-three-new-i-corps-hubs-expanding-national</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation today announced the addition of three new NSF Innovation Corps (NSF I-Corps™) Hubs that will scale the NSF-led Na...</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 17:35:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Astrophysicists use echoes of light to illuminate black holes</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/11/241107160747.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Researchers have developed an innovative technique to search for black hole light echoes. Their novel method, which will make it easier for the mass a...</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 21:07:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New study maps dramatic 100-million-year explosion in color signals used by animals</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/11/241107193216.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>A recent study finds that color vision evolved in animals more than 100 million years before the emergence of colorful fruits and flowers. And there h...</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 00:32:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF Arecibo C3 opening moved to 2025, aligning with NSF's 75th anniversary commemorations</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-arecibo-c3-opening-moved-2025-aligning-nsfs-75th</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has announced that the official opening of the NSF Arecibo Center for Culturally Relevant and Inclusive Science E...</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 18:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-71</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Last week, Director Sethuraman Panchanathan engaged in meetings that deepened U.S. National Science Foundation's relationships with current internatio...</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 20:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Creating a buzz about bee nest symmetry</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/creating-buzz-about-bee-nest-symmetry</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Mirroring the mechanisms that make human faces and bodies — and those of many multicellular organisms — symmetrical, bee colonies build symmetrical ne...</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 16:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A remarkable fossil assemblage gets a new interpretation</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/remarkable-fossil-assemblage-gets-new-interpretation</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>A team of paleontologists recently discovered that an ancient seascape known for its diverse assemblage of exceptionally preserved fossils represents ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 18:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Off-the-shelf thermoelectric generators can upgrade CO2 into chemicals: The combination could help us colonize Mars</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/11/241107115225.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Readily available thermoelectric generators operating under modest temperature differences can power CO2 conversion, according to a proof-of-concept s...</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 16:52:25 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>