<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 01:39:07 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Scientists identify mutation that could facilitate H5N1 'bird flu' virus infection and potential transmission in humans</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/12/241205142418.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Avian influenza viruses typically require several mutations to adapt and spread among humans, but what happens when just one change can increase the r...</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 19:24:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A novel method to shed light on heat waves</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/novel-method-shed-light-heat-waves</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>A U.S. National Science Foundation-supported researcher developed a machine learning model that uses data stored in paleoclimate archives, such as tre...</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 19:58:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The National Secure Data Service Demonstration Project builds steam in year 2</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/national-secure-data-service-demonstration-project-builds</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>In response to the "CHIPS and Science Act of 2022," the U.S. National Science Foundation National Center for Science and Engineering Statistics (NCSES...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 14:53:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Iberian Neolithic societies had a deep knowledge of archery techniques and materials</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/12/241205142749.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>A research team has made exceptional discoveries on prehistoric archery from the early Neolithic period, 7,000 years ago. The well organic preservatio...</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 19:27:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>3 areas where NSF is supporting STEM research and education in tribal nations</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/3-areas-where-nsf-supporting-stem-research-education-tribal</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Across America, Indigenous communities are working to advance programs that honor their people's cultural, societal and economic values. One of the wa...</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 14:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF announces funding opportunity to train and expand the U.S. workforce across a range of key technologies</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-funding-opportunity-train-expand-us-workforce</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>The NSF ExLENT program offers all Americans opportunities to gain the skills needed to succeed in key technologies and prepare them to enter the workf...</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 18:40:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Manta rays inspire fast swimming soft robot yet</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/12/241204145135.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>A team of researchers has beaten its own record for the fastest swimming soft robot, drawing inspiration from manta rays to improve their ability to c...</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 19:51:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tyrannosaur teeth discovered in Bexhill-on-Sea, England</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/12/241205142905.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Research has revealed that several groups of meat-eating dinosaur stalked the Bexhill-on-Sea region of coastal East Sussex 135 million years ago.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 19:29:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Researchers call for sustainable governance as groundwater resources become scarce</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/researchers-call-sustainable-governance-groundwater</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>In recent decades, the Western United States has faced a mounting environmental crisis: the depletion of groundwater resources. This pressing issue, d...</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 18:05:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mothers massively change their intestines during pregnancy and nursing</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/12/241205142959.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>When women are pregnant and nurse their babies, their bodies change and various organs, such as the breasts or the immune system, are adapted to ensur...</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 19:29:59 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>