<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 14:06:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Scientists discover which parts of the Amazon rainforest are most vulnerable to drought</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/scientists-discover-which-parts-amazon-rainforest</link><description>Regions of the Amazon rainforest respond to drought according to differences in local forest environments and in the properties of trees, Scott Saleska of the University of Arizona and colleagues have discovered. In the southern Amazon rainforest…</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 15:15:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New research demonstrates potential for increasing effectiveness of popular diabetes, weight-loss drugs</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240715170850.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>A network of proteins found in the central nervous system could be harnessed to increase the effectiveness and reduce the side effects of popular diabetes and weight-loss drugs, according to new research.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 22:08:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF–DOE Rubin Observatory will detect thousands of elusive brown dwarfs, unlocking Milky Way mysteries</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/rubin-observatory-will-detect-thousands-dwarfs</link><description>Too big to be planets but too small to be stars, distant brown dwarfs are a key ingredient for understanding the history of the Milky Way. These elusive objects have existed since the early universe and have remained relatively unchanged. Anticipated…</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 19:05:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NASA's Webb investigates eternal sunrises, sunsets on distant world</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240715135814.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Researchers using NASA's James Webb Space Telescope have finally confirmed what models have previously predicted: An exoplanet has differences between its eternal morning and eternal evening atmosphere. WASP-39 b, a giant planet with a diameter 1.3 times greater than Jupiter, but similar mass to Saturn that orbits a star about 700 light-years away from Earth, is tidally locked to its parent star. This means it has a constant dayside and a constant nightside -- one side of the planet is always exposed to its star, while the other is always shrouded in darkness.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 18:58:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wildfire smoke is reaching almost all lakes in North America</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/wildfire-smoke-reaching-almost-all-lakes-north</link><description>Wildfire smoke, sometimes drifting across hundreds of miles, reached almost every lake in North America at least one day each year from 2019 to 2021, according to U.S. National Science Foundation- supported findings published in the journal Global…</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 17:28:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scorching storms on distant worlds revealed</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240715135802.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>An international study reveals the extreme atmospheric conditions on the celestial objects, which are swathed in swirling clouds of hot sand amid temperatures of 950C. Using NASA's powerful James Webb Space Telescope (JWST), researchers set out to capture the weather on a pair of brown dwarfs -- cosmic bodies that are bigger than planets but smaller than stars.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 18:58:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seasonal shifts: Phenology events at the bottom of the world</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/seasonal-shifts-phenology-events-bottom-world</link><description>Climate change has affected more than the planet's temperature. As climate change has become more influential, seasonal event timing has fluctuated. Flower blooms are harder to predict, and animal migration schedules have shifted. These events, known…</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 16:41:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JWST unveils stunning ejecta and CO structures in Cassiopeia A's young supernova</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240715135800.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Researchers announced the latest findings from the James Webb Space Telescope (JWST) of the supernova remnant, Cassiopeia A (Cas A). These observations of the youngest known core collapse supernova in the Milky Way provide insights into the conditions that lead to the formation and destruction of molecules and dust within supernova ejecta. The study's findings change our understanding of dust formation in the early universe in the galaxies detected by JWST 300 million years after the Big Bang.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 18:58:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Woolly mammoth chromosomes reconstructed using fossilized sample</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/woolly-mammoth-chromosomes-reconstructed</link><description>An international team of scientists assembled the woolly mammoth's genetic code using fossilized chromosomes from a 52,000-year-old carcass discovered in Siberian permafrost. The mammoth became freeze-dried on death, preserving the 3D structure of…</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 21:16:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New geological datings place the first European hominids in the south of the Iberian Peninsula 1.3 million years ago</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240715135719.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>One of the most important controversies about human evolution and expansion is when and by what route the first hominids arrived in Europe from the African continent. Now, geological dating techniques at the Orce sites (Baza basin, Granada, Spain) place the human remains found in this area as the oldest in Europe, at approximately 1.3 million years old. These results reinforce the hypothesis that humans arrived in Europe through the south of the Iberian Peninsula, through the Strait of Gibraltar, instead of returning to the Mediterranean via the Asian route.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 18:57:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>