<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 06:59:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>'Far out' blazar discovery suggests early universe had more supermassive black holes than previously thought</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/far-out-blazar-discovery-suggests-early-universe-had-more</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Scientists have discovered the most distant and therefore oldest blazar ever seen. Labeled J0410–0139, the blazar is at the center of a galaxy 12.9 bi...</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 20:29:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When the only thing you can eat can kill you, having more gene copies can help</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/when-only-thing-you-can-eat-can-kill-you-having-more-gene</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>According to research supported by the U.S. National Science Foundation, gene duplications being selected over evolutionary time — not the specializat...</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 17:47:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI vs. supercomputers: New AI-based method solves complex equations faster and uses less computing power</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/ai-vs-supercomputers-new-ai-based-method-solves-complex</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>A new artificial intelligence-based method quickly solves complex math equations used broadly across many industries — and it's faster running on a pe...</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 19:37:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This quasar may have helped turn the lights on for the universe</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/01/250115164904.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Astronomers have detected an intensely brightening and dimming quasar that may help explain how some objects in the early universe grew at a highly ac...</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 21:49:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Not all Hot Jupiters orbit solo</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/01/250115125432.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Hot Jupiters are giant planets initially known to orbit alone close to their star. During their migration towards their star, these planets were thoug...</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 17:54:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is eating more red meat bad for your brain?</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/01/250115164828.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>People who eat more red meat, especially processed red meat like bacon, sausage and bologna, are more likely to have a higher risk of cognitive declin...</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 21:48:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Octopus arms have segmented nervous systems to power extraordinary movements</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/01/250115125422.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>New research has revealed that the nervous system circuitry that controls arm movement in octopuses is segmented, giving these extraordinary creatures...</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 17:54:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Migration memory: How caribou adapt to changing winter conditions</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/migration-memory-how-caribou-adapt-changing-winter</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>U.S. National Science Foundation-supported research shows that caribou will optimize their migration path based on their collective memories. Caribou ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 17:39:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-77</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>This week, NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan began the new year by strengthening strategic global partnerships and commemorating the groundbreaking...</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 19:30:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Super-Earth vs. Sub-Neptune? The winner is Super-Venus!</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/01/250115125704.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>New observational data and simulation models have confirmed a new type of planet unlike anything found in the Solar System. This provides another piec...</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 17:57:04 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>