<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 12:24:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Creating a diverse and inclusive AI research community is the goal of new NSF awards</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/creating-diverse-inclusive-ai-research-community</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation is excited to announce a new round of ExpandAI awards dedicated to fostering diversity and inclusion within the artificial intelligence research community. In collaboration with the departments of Homeland…</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 16:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Facial recognition linked to close social bonds, not social butterflies</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240624125612.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Do you have trouble recognizing faces, or do you never forget a face? The better you are at facial recognition, the more supportive relationships you are likely to have, regardless of your personality type.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 17:56:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-57</link><description>Last week, US National Science Foundation Director Sethuraman Panchanathan accompanied National Security Advisor Jake Sullivan, Deputy Secretary of State Kurt Campbell, and other senior U.S. government officials to participate in the second annual U…</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 18:34:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New study confirms forever chemicals are absorbed through human skin</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240624125549.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>A study of 17 commonly used synthetic 'forever chemicals' has shown that these toxic substances can readily be absorbed through human skin.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 17:55:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF announces $20 million investment in quantum nanofabrication infrastructure</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-20-million-investment-quantum</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation (NSF) announced a nearly $20 million award that will support the construction of a nanoscale fabrication facility at the University of Colorado Boulder to accelerate the co-design and development of atomic…</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 19:36:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A hidden treasure in the Milky Way -- Astronomers uncover ultrabright x-ray source</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240624125515.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Astronomers uncovered that a well-known X-ray binary, whose exact nature has been a mystery to scientists until now, is actually a hidden ultraluminous X-ray source.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 17:55:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Democratizing data: Discovering data use and value for research and policy</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/democratizing-data-discovering-data-use-value</link><description>Data access and discovery continue to be topics of great interest across the federal data ecosystem. The National Center for Science and Engineering Statistics (NCSES) within the U.S. National Science Foundation supported a pilot study seeking to…</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 16:09:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Carbon dioxide's heavy stamp on temperature: Doubling CO2 may mean 7 to 14 degree increase</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240624125500.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>A doubling of the amount of CO2 in the atmosphere could cause an increase in the average temperature on earth from 7 to even a maximum of 14 degrees. That is shown in the analysis of sediments from the Pacific Ocean off the coast of California.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 17:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Collaborative approaches improve materials informatics workforce training</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/collaborative-approaches-improve-materials</link><description>A wide range of innovative products, from biomedical implants to aerospace composites, come from research in materials informatics (MI) — the combination of machine learning, artificial intelligence and computational methodologies with materials…</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 17:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Star clusters observed within a galaxy in the early Universe</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240624125435.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>The history of how stars and galaxies came to be and evolved into the present day remains among the most challenging astrophysical questions to solve yet, but new research brings us closer to understanding it. New insights about young galaxies during the Epoch of Reionization have been revealed. Observations with the James Webb Space Telescope (JWST) of the galaxy Cosmic Gems arc (SPT0615-JD) have confirmed that the light of the galaxy was emitted 460 million years after the big bang. What makes this galaxy unique is that it is magnified through an effect called gravitational lensing, which has not been observed in other galaxies formed during that age.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 17:54:35 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>