<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:45:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NSF invites K-12 students to design their own video games and compete for Game Maker Awards</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-invites-k-12-students-design-their-own-video</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation announces the NSF Game Maker Awards "Life in 2100" competition for K-12 students. To commemorate the agency’s milestone 75th anniversary, this competition invites students to create video games that imagine life…</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 15:10:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SwRI-led team finds evidence of hydration on Asteroid Psyche</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240813152147.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Using data from NASA's James Webb Space Telescope, astronomers have confirmed hydroxyl molecules on the surface of the metallic asteroid Psyche. The presence of hydrated minerals suggests a complex history for Psyche, important context for the NASA spacecraft en route to this interesting asteroid orbiting the Sun between Mars and Jupiter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 20:21:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Studying the journey, not the destination, provides new insight into songbird migrations</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/studying-journey-into-songbird-migrations</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>New research supported by the U.S. National Science Foundation using two decades worth of data could change how scientists think about bird migrations and the interdependencies and relationships they involve. Driving any long distance usually…</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 20:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists achieve more than 98% efficiency removing nanoplastics from water</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240813152142.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Linked to cardiovascular and respiratory diseases in people, nanoplastics continue to build up, largely unnoticed, in the world's bodies of water. The challenge remains to develop a cost-effective solution to get rid of nanoplastics while leaving clean water behind. That's where Mizzou comes in. Recently, researchers created a new liquid-based solution that eliminates more than 98% of these microscopic plastic particles from water.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 20:21:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>This week, NSF marked the second anniversary of the "CHIPS and Science Act of 2022," signed into law on August 9, 2022. This landmark legislation has empowered NSF to accelerate innovation and build a resilient, inclusive, and productive American…</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:27:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Measuring Martian winds with sound</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240813132036.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Martian landers have been able capture measurements of wind speeds -- some gauging the cooling rate of heated materials when winds blow over them, others using cameras to image 'tell-tales' that blow in the wind -- but there's still room for improvement. Researchers now demonstrate a novel sonic anemometric system featuring a pair of narrow-band piezoelectric transducers to measure the travel time of sound pulses through Martian air. The study accounted for variables including transducer diffraction effects and wind direction.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 18:20:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Radio astronomers and satellite internet provider develop new sky-sharing system</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/radio-astronomers-satellite-internet-provider</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>New techniques developed by the U.S. National Science Foundation National Radio Astronomy Observatory (NSF NRAO) and SpaceX enable radio astronomy telescopes to operate without interference from satellite transmissions. The techniques allow…</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 22:20:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Say 'aah' and get a diagnosis on the spot: is this the future of health?</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240813132031.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>A computer algorithm has achieved a 98% accuracy in predicting different diseases by analyzing the color of the human tongue. The proposed imaging system can diagnose diabetes, stroke, anemia, asthma, liver and gallbladder conditions, COVID-19, and a range of vascular and gastrointestinal issues, according to new research.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 18:20:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF National Quantum Virtual Laboratory advances with first five pilot projects</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-national-quantum-virtual-laboratory-advances</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Realizing practical advantages and societal benefits from quantum-scale phenomena has been a long-sought milestone in quantum information science. The U.S. National Science Foundation today announced the initial $5 million investment across five…</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 14:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Significant link found between heme iron, found in red meat and other animal products, and type 2 diabetes risk</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240813132019.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Higher intake of heme iron, the type found in red meat and other animal products -- as opposed to non-heme iron, found mostly in plant-based foods -- was associated with a higher risk of developing type 2 diabetes (T2D) in a new study. While the link between heme iron and T2D has been reported previously, the study's findings more clearly establish and explain the link.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 18:20:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>