<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2024 06:00:44 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Pterosaurs needed feet on the ground to become giants</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/10/241004121701.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>A study determines when and how pterosaurs went from tiny tree-climbers to towering terrestrial titans Flying reptiles first came down from the trees ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 17:17:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists discover new way of predicting where and when rivers suddenly change course and flood</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/scientists-discover-new-way-predicting-where-when-rivers</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>An avulsion is a river term referring to the rapid abandonment of a channel and the formation of a new one, often resulting in devastating flooding. N...</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 19:40:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists uncover auditory 'sixth sense' in geckos</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/10/241004121658.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Researchers discover that geckos use a mechanism usually associated with balance to sense vibrations, leading to new insights about how animals hear a...</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 17:16:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Impact of NSF commitment to basic research reflected in 2024 Golden Goose winners</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/impact-nsf-research-reflected-2024-golden-goose-winners</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>All three research projects that received the 2024 Golden Goose Award celebrating the wide-ranging impact of federally funded research that has led to...</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 18:44:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF, NIH and FDA support research in digital twin technology for biomedical applications</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-nih-fda-support-research-digital-twin-technology</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation, in collaboration with the National Institutes of Health (NIH) and the Food and Drug Administration (FDA), has aw...</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 21:08:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Green subsidies may have hidden costs, experts warn</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/10/241003145456.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Government subsidies for business practices and processes should be approached with caution, even when they seem to be environmentally friendly, write...</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 19:54:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In odd galaxy, NASA's Webb finds potential missing link to first stars</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/10/241003152018.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Looking deep into the early universe with NASA's James Webb Space Telescope, astronomers have found something unprecedented: a galaxy with an odd ligh...</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 20:20:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Toddlers get nearly half their calories from ultra-processed foods</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/10/241003221629.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Toddlers in the UK obtain nearly half (47%) of their calories from ultra-processed foods (UPFs), and this rises to 59% by the age of seven, according ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 03:16:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Creating the largest, most comprehensive picture of neural connections to date</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/creating-largest-most-comprehensive-picture-neural</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Flip a switch on the wall, and it turns on a light across the room through a simple circuit. Now add 140,000 other switches and try and figure out whi...</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 15:31:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spanish cave's submerged land bridge reveals that humans colonized the western Mediterranean earlier than thought</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/spanish-caves-submerged-land-bridge-reveals-humans-colonized</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>When did humans colonize the western Mediterranean? New U.S. National Science Foundation -supported research shows that it may be much earlier than ar...</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 18:44:12 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>