<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 01:50:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Sounding the alarm: Fire's speed is more threatening than its size</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/sounding-alarm-fires-speed-more-threatening-its-size</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Most news reports about wildfires include the number of acres a given fire has burned, but according to a new study by U.S. National Science Foundatio...</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 19:30:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Restricting sugar consumption in utero and in early childhood significantly reduces risk of midlife chronic disease</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/10/241031185320.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Children who experienced sugar restrictions during their first 1,000 days after conception had up to 35% lower risk of developing type 2 diabetes and ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 23:53:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NASA's Hubble, Webb probe surprisingly smooth disk around Vega</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/11/241101123528.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Teams of astronomers used the combined power of NASA's Hubble and James Webb space telescopes to revisit the legendary Vega disk.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 17:35:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-71</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Last week, Director Sethuraman Panchanathan engaged in meetings that deepened U.S. National Science Foundation's relationships with current internatio...</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 20:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Echolocating bats use an acoustic cognitive map for navigation</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/10/241031151724.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Echolocating bats have been found to possess an acoustic cognitive map of their home range, enabling them to navigate over kilometer-scale distances u...</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 20:17:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A remarkable fossil assemblage gets a new interpretation</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/remarkable-fossil-assemblage-gets-new-interpretation</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>A team of paleontologists recently discovered that an ancient seascape known for its diverse assemblage of exceptionally preserved fossils represents ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 18:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Violating Bredt's rule: Chemists just broke a 100-year-old rule and say it's time to rewrite the textbooks</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/10/241031151834.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>According to Bredt's rule, double bonds cannot exist at certain positions on organic molecules if the molecule's geometry deviates too far from what w...</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 20:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF names three new I-Corps Hubs expanding the National Innovation Network across the U.S.</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-names-three-new-i-corps-hubs-expanding-national</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation today announced the addition of three new NSF Innovation Corps (NSF I-Corps™) Hubs that will scale the NSF-led Na...</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 17:35:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF Arecibo C3 opening moved to 2025, aligning with NSF's 75th anniversary commemorations</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-arecibo-c3-opening-moved-2025-aligning-nsfs-75th</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has announced that the official opening of the NSF Arecibo Center for Culturally Relevant and Inclusive Science E...</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 18:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>First blueprint of the human spliceosome revealed</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/10/241031151843.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Researchers have created the first blueprint of the human spliceosome, the most complex and intricate molecular machine in human biology. The vast maj...</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 20:18:43 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>