<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 07:48:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Statement by Director Sethuraman Panchanathan on NSF ranking in Best Places to Work in the Federal Government</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/statement-director-panchanathan-nsf-ranking-best-places-work</link><description>I am pleased to announce that the U.S. National Science Foundation has again been recognized among the 2023 Best Places to Work in the Federal Government®. NSF ranked No. 8 among mid-sized agencies as featured in a special edition released today by …</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 15:10:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Otters, especially females, use tools to survive a changing world</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240516160511.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Sea otters are one of the few animals that use tools to access their food, and a new study has found that individual sea otters that use tools -- most of whom are female -- are able to eat larger prey and reduce tooth damage when their preferred prey becomes depleted.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 21:05:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF planning major infrastructure overhaul to support future research in South Pole</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-planning-major-infrastructure-overhaul-support</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation released the draft of its South Pole Station Master Plan (SPSMP), which will inform investments planned under the NSF Antarctic Infrastructure Recapitalization program and ensure that the mission and priorities of…</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 14:39:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How did sabre-toothed tigers acquire their long upper canine teeth?</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240516122644.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>In a groundbreaking study an international team of scientists has investigated the evolutionary patterns behind the development of sabre teeth, with some unexpected results along the way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 17:26:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF announces pilot phase and anticipated opening date of Arecibo C3 at the site of the NSF Arecibo Observatory Historic District in Puerto Rico</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-pilot-phase-anticipated-opening-date-of-arecibo</link><description>| En Español | As excitement builds for the grand opening of the new U.S. National Science Foundation Arecibo Center for Culturally Relevant and Inclusive Science Education, Computational Skills, and Community Engagement (NSF Arecibo C3), anticipated…</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 16:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why do we overindulge?</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240516122539.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>If you tend to do other things or get distracted while eating dinner, you may be running the risk of over-consuming everyday pleasures later, possibly because the distraction caused you to enjoy yourself less, according to new research.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 17:25:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-51</link><description>This week was full of celebrations and milestones — including recognizing NSF staff and public servants for their hard work to better the nation; celebrating teachers for their dedication to educating the next generation of scientists, engineers and…</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 22:11:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When saying 'please' is more strategic than magic</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240515225104.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>By kindergarten age, most children have been taught that 'please' is a magic word. 'Please' is an expression of politeness that shows courtesy and respect, turning a potential demand into a request that will -- poof! -- magically be granted. But a new study on the ways people make requests of one another suggests that 'please' might not be an all-purpose marker of politeness, but rather a more focused, strategic tool to manage frictions or obstacles among family members, friends and even coworkers. The study shows that people say 'please' much less often than expected, and mostly when they expect a 'no' response is forthcoming.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 03:51:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF announces $24M investment across three EPSCoR jurisdictions</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-24m-investment-across-three-epscor</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has awarded teams from South Dakota, New Hampshire and Maine roughly $8 million each through the Established Program to Stimulate Competitive Research (EPSCoR) Collaborations for Optimizing Research Ecosystems…</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 18:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jet-propelled sea creatures could improve ocean robotics</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240515225101.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Scientists have discovered that colonies of gelatinous sea animals swim through the ocean in giant corkscrew shapes using coordinated jet propulsion, an unusual kind of locomotion that could inspire new designs for efficient underwater vehicles.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 03:51:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>