<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:59:36 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Particle research gets closer to answering why we're here</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/12/241205184326.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Physicists have outlined the next 10 years of global research into the behavior of neutrinos, particles so tiny that they pass through virtually every...</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 23:43:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mothers massively change their intestines during pregnancy and nursing</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/12/241205142959.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>When women are pregnant and nurse their babies, their bodies change and various organs, such as the breasts or the immune system, are adapted to ensur...</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 19:29:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF announces funding opportunity to train and expand the U.S. workforce across a range of key technologies</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-funding-opportunity-train-expand-us-workforce</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>The NSF ExLENT program offers all Americans opportunities to gain the skills needed to succeed in key technologies and prepare them to enter the workf...</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 18:40:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Researchers call for sustainable governance as groundwater resources become scarce</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/researchers-call-sustainable-governance-groundwater</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>In recent decades, the Western United States has faced a mounting environmental crisis: the depletion of groundwater resources. This pressing issue, d...</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 18:05:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>That's no straw: Hummingbirds evolved surprisingly flexible bills to help them drink nectar</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/12/241205184323.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Hummingbird bills -- their long, thin beaks -- look a little like drinking straws. But new research shows just how little water, or nectar, that compa...</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 23:43:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Molecular zip code draws killer T cells straight to brain tumors</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/12/241205184621.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Scientists have developed a 'molecular GPS' to guide immune cells into the brain and kill tumors without harming healthy tissue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 23:46:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>3 areas where NSF is supporting STEM research and education in tribal nations</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/3-areas-where-nsf-supporting-stem-research-education-tribal</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Across America, Indigenous communities are working to advance programs that honor their people's cultural, societal and economic values. One of the wa...</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 14:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The National Secure Data Service Demonstration Project builds steam in year 2</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/national-secure-data-service-demonstration-project-builds</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>In response to the "CHIPS and Science Act of 2022," the U.S. National Science Foundation National Center for Science and Engineering Statistics (NCSES...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 14:53:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A novel method to shed light on heat waves</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/novel-method-shed-light-heat-waves</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>A U.S. National Science Foundation-supported researcher developed a machine learning model that uses data stored in paleoclimate archives, such as tre...</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 19:58:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rapid surge in global warming mainly due to reduced planetary albedo</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/12/241205184615.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Rising sea levels, melting glaciers, heatwaves at sea -- 2023 set a number of alarming new records. The global mean temperature also rose to nearly 1....</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 23:46:15 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>