<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 13:15:36 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NSF and industry partners announce sustainable polymer research funding opportunity</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-industry-partners-announce-sustainable-polymer</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has launched a $9.5 million research funding opportunity in partnership with BASF, Dow, IBM, PepsiCo Inc. and Procter &amp; Gamble Co. Sustainable Polymers Enabled by Emerging Data Analytics (SPEED) is part of NSF's…</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 18:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>75,000-year-old female Neanderthal from cave where species buried their dead</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240501193650.htm</link><description>A new documentary has recreated the face of a 75,000-year-old female Neanderthal whose flattened skull was discovered and rebuilt from hundreds of bone fragments by a team of archaeologists and conservators.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 00:36:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New NSF grant targets large language models and generative AI, exploring how they work and implications for societal impacts</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/new-nsf-grant-targets-large-language-models</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has announced a grant of $9 million to Northeastern University for research to investigate how large language models (LLMs) and generative AI operate, focusing on the computing process called deep inference and AI…</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sleep resets brain connections -- but only for first few hours</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240501125828.htm</link><description>During sleep, the brain weakens the new connections between neurons that had been forged while awake -- but only during the first half of a night's sleep, according to a new study.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 17:58:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prolific potholes in the prairie star in award-winning short film</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/prolific-potholes-prairie-star-award-winning-short</link><description>Most of us think potholes are something to avoid. However, some potholes are worth protecting. The U.S. National Science Foundation is funding researchers to study prairie pothole wetlands, which are ecologically and economically important, but under…</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 14:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists identify new brain circuit in mice that controls body's inflammatory reactions</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240501125818.htm</link><description>The brain can direct the immune system to an unexpected degree, capable of detecting, ramping up and tamping down inflammation, shows a new study in mice.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 17:58:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF and NIH partner on internship opportunity in biomedical engineering</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-nih-partner-internship-opportunity-biomedical</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation and the National Institutes of Health's National Institute of Biomedical Imaging and Bioengineering (NIBIB) have initiated a joint research training opportunity through the NSF Non-Academic Research Internships…</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 17:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A 'cosmic glitch' in gravity</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240501125809.htm</link><description>Researchers have discovered a potential 'cosmic glitch' in the universe's gravity, explaining its strange behavior on a cosmic scale.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 17:58:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF and USDA join forces to boost innovation in agricultural robotics</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-usda-join-forces-boost-innovation-agricultural</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation and the U.S. Department of Agriculture's National Institute of Food and Agriculture (USDA NIFA) are teaming up to advance foundational research in agricultural robotics. The agencies are issuing a new Dear…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists work out the effects of exercise at the cellular level</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240501125227.htm</link><description>The health benefits of exercise are well known but new research shows that the body's response to exercise is more complex and far-reaching than previously thought. In a study on rats, a team of scientists has found that physical activity causes many cellular and molecular changes in all 19 of the organs they studied in the animals.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 17:52:27 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>