<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 12:44:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Prolific potholes in the prairie star in award-winning short film</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/prolific-potholes-prairie-star-award-winning-short</link><description>Most of us think potholes are something to avoid. However, some potholes are worth protecting. The U.S. National Science Foundation is funding researchers to study prairie pothole wetlands, which are ecologically and economically important, but under…</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 14:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Time zones and tiredness strongly influence NBA results, study of 25,000 matches shows</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240501091642.htm</link><description>The body clock has a significant impact on the performance of NBA players. Data shows vastly better win ratio for home teams from the Western Time Zone Area (PDT) when playing an EDT team, compared to vice versa.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 14:16:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF and NIH partner on internship opportunity in biomedical engineering</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-nih-partner-internship-opportunity-biomedical</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation and the National Institutes of Health's National Institute of Biomedical Imaging and Bioengineering (NIBIB) have initiated a joint research training opportunity through the NSF Non-Academic Research Internships…</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 17:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Climate change and mercury pollution stressed plants for millions of years</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/04/240430145626.htm</link><description>The link between massive flood basalt volcanism and the end-Triassic (201 million years ago) mass-extinction is commonly accepted. However, exactly how volcanism led to the collapse of ecosystems and the extinction of entire families of organisms is difficult to establish. Extreme climate change from the release of carbon dioxide, degradation of the ozone layer due to the injection of damaging chemicals, and the emissions of toxic pollutants, are all seen as contributing factors. One toxic element stands out: mercury.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 19:56:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF and USDA join forces to boost innovation in agricultural robotics</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-usda-join-forces-boost-innovation-agricultural</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation and the U.S. Department of Agriculture's National Institute of Food and Agriculture (USDA NIFA) are teaming up to advance foundational research in agricultural robotics. The agencies are issuing a new Dear…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Webb captures top of iconic horsehead nebula in unprecedented detail</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/04/240430145620.htm</link><description>NASA's James Webb Space Telescope has captured the sharpest infrared images to date of a zoomed-in portion of one of the most distinctive objects in our skies, the Horsehead Nebula. These observations show the top of the 'horse's mane' or edge of this iconic nebula in a whole new light, capturing the region's complexity with unprecedented spatial resolution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 19:56:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New center supported by NSF will catalyze data-driven insights in molecular and cellular biosciences</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/new-center-supported-nsf-will-catalyze-data-driven</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has made a $20 million award to support the creation of the National Synthesis Center for Emergence in the Molecular and Cellular Sciences (NCEMS). The center will combine vast amounts of available data on…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 14:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Methane emissions from landfill could be turned into sustainable jet fuel in plasma chemistry leap</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/04/240430131902.htm</link><description>Researchers have developed a chemical process using plasma that could create sustainable jet fuel from methane gas emitted from landfills, potentially creating a low-carbon aviation industry.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 18:19:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF honors 3 outstanding early-career researchers with the Alan T. Waterman Award</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-honors-3-outstanding-early-career-researchers</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation honored three researchers with the Alan T. Waterman Award, the nation's highest honor for early-career scientists and engineers. The 2024 recipients: Muyinatu A. Lediju Bell, a biomedical engineer at Johns Hopkins…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biodegradable 'living plastic' houses bacterial spores that help it break down</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/04/240430131849.htm</link><description>A new type of bioplastic could help reduce the plastic industry's environmental footprint. Researchers have developed a biodegradable form of thermoplastic polyurethane (TPU) filled with bacterial spores that, when exposed to nutrients present in compost, germinate and break down the material at the end of its life cycle.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 18:18:49 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>