<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 13:07:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NSF announces $20 million investment in quantum nanofabrication infrastructure</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-20-million-investment-quantum</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation (NSF) announced a nearly $20 million award that will support the construction of a nanoscale fabrication facility at the University of Colorado Boulder to accelerate the co-design and development of atomic…</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 19:36:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Simple test for flu could improve diagnosis and surveillance</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240621172402.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Fewer than one percent of people who get the flu every year get tested, in part because most tests require trained personnel and expensive equipment. Now researchers have developed a low-cost paper strip test that could allow more patients to find out which type of flu they have and get the right treatment. The test uses CRISPR to distinguish between the two main types of seasonal flu, influenza A and B, as well as seasonal flu subtypes H1N1 and H3N2. It can also identify strains that resist antiviral treatment, and with further work, could potentially detect swine and avian flu strains, including H5N1, which is currently infecting cattle.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 22:24:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Democratizing data: Discovering data use and value for research and policy</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/democratizing-data-discovering-data-use-value</link><description>Data access and discovery continue to be topics of great interest across the federal data ecosystem. The National Center for Science and Engineering Statistics (NCSES) within the U.S. National Science Foundation supported a pilot study seeking to…</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 16:09:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Study challenges popular idea that Easter islanders committed 'ecocide'</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240621172346.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Some 1,000 years ago, a small band of Polynesians sailed thousands of miles across the Pacific to settle one of the world's most isolated places -- a small, previously uninhabited island they named Rapa Nui. Eventually, their numbers ballooned to unsustainable levels, they wrecked the environment, and their civilization collapsed. At least that is the longtime story, told in academic studies and popular books. A new study challenges this narrative of 'ecocide' saying that Rapa Nui's population never spiraled to unsustainable levels.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 22:23:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Collaborative approaches improve materials informatics workforce training</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/collaborative-approaches-improve-materials</link><description>A wide range of innovative products, from biomedical implants to aerospace composites, come from research in materials informatics (MI) — the combination of machine learning, artificial intelligence and computational methodologies with materials…</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 17:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chilling discovery: Study reveals evolution of human cold and menthol sensing protein, offering hope for future non-addictive pain therapies</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240621172345.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Menthol sensing appeared long before cold sensing, suggesting distinct activation modes that can be disentangled, paving the way for new pain therapies without adverse thermal side effects.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 22:23:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shipworms still hold some sea-crets</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/shipworms-still-hold-some-sea-crets</link><description>Although they have been known to mariners for centuries — having aided in shipwrecking Columbus and sinking parts of the Spanish Armada — scientists have not been able to determine how shipworms digest wood, until now. Sometimes known as "termites of…</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 14:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prying open the AI black box</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240621122906.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Meet SQUID, a new computational tool. Compared with other genomic AI models, SQUID is more consistent, reduces background noise, and can yield better predictions regarding critical mutations. The new system aims to bring scientists closer to their findings' true medical implications.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 17:29:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-56</link><description>This week, NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan highlighted NSF’s commitment to innovation and STEM advancements through several key events. The Director joined Senator Shaheen in a conversation on Capitol Hill with New Hampshire business leaders to…</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 19:53:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Iron meteorites hint that our infant solar system was more doughnut than dartboard</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240620194009.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Iron meteorites are remnants of the metallic cores of the earliest asteroids in our solar system. Iron meteorites contain refractory metals, such as iridium and platinum, that formed near the sun but were transported to the outer solar system. New research shows that for this to have happened, the protoplanetary disk of our solar system had to have been doughnut-shaped because the refractory metals could not have crossed the large gaps in a target-shaped disk of concentric rings. The paper suggests that the refractory metals moved outward as the protoplanetary disk rapidly expanded, and were trapped in the outer solar system by Jupiter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 00:40:09 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>