<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 06:38:12 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Astronomers create first detailed map of sun's coronal magnetic fields</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/astronomers-create-first-detailed-map-suns-coronal-magnetic</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Researchers at the U.S. National Science Foundation National Solar Observatory have successfully mapped the magnetic fields of the sun's atmospheric c...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 15:08:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Discovery could lead to longer-lasting EV batteries, hasten energy transition</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240912142413.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Researchers have discovered why lithium-ion batteries, which power most electronic devices, lose capacity overtime. The findings could enable the deve...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 19:24:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ideas Labs to advance research capacity at the nation's historically Black colleges and universities</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/ideas-labs-advance-research-capacity-nations-historically</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has awarded $10.5 million for Ideas Lab projects to assess and address research capacity needs, increase access t...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 15:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How El Nino and mega ocean warming caused the greatest-ever mass extinction</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240912142358.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Mega ocean warming El Nino events were key in driving the largest extinction of life on planet Earth some 252 million years ago, according to new rese...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 19:23:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New study reveals evidence of ice-free times at the center of the Greenland Ice Sheet</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/new-study-reveals-evidence-ice-free-times-center-greenland</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>A new paper published in the Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences shows direct evidence of Greenland being ice-free within the last 1.1 mil...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 13:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Climate-change-triggered 2023 mega-landslide caused Earth to vibrate for nine days</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240912142355.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>A landslide in a remote part of Greenland caused a 200 meter (650 foot) mega-tsunami that sloshed back and forth across a fjord for nine days, generat...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 19:23:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF and Micron invest in STEM teacher training to support future microelectronics workforce</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-micron-invest-stem-teacher-training-support-future</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Today, the U.S. National Science Foundation and the Micron Foundation announced an investment in four projects to advance STEM education training to f...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 18:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trilobite fossils from upstate New York reveal 'extra' set of legs</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240912135844.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>A new study finds that a trilobite species with exceptionally well-preserved fossils from upstate New York has an additional set of legs underneath it...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 18:58:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lakes in marginalized communities sampled less, study finds</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/lakes-marginalized-communities-sampled-less-study-finds</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Water is essential for all forms of life — humans included — and understanding the quality of available water is critical to knowing where to drink, s...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 20:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hair-thin wire to help simulate cosmic conditions</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240912135814.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Extreme conditions prevail inside stars and planets. The pressure reaches millions of bars, and it can be several million degrees hot. Sophisticated m...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 18:58:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>