<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 02:04:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NSF invests $2.8M to strengthen technical AI education at two-year institutions</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-invests-28m-strengthen-technical-ai-education</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has announced a grant of $2.8 million to establish a National Applied Artificial Intelligence Consortium (NAAIC) at Miami Dade College. Funded through the NSF Advanced Technological Education program, this…</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 16:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How the rising earth in Antarctica will impact future sea level rise</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240802170947.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>The rising earth beneath the Antarctic Ice Sheet will likely become a major factor in future sea level rise, a new study suggests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 22:09:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>An Iceland volcano modifies its magma</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/iceland-volcano-modifies-its-magma</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>A team of NSF-funded researchers has discovered that an Iceland volcano changed how it formed magma as it continued to erupt from 2021 to 2022. The researchers published their findings in the journal Nature. The ongoing Fagradalsfjall eruptions near…</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 14:26:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Link between global warming and rising sea levels</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240802144615.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>A new study suggests that Earth's natural forces could substantially reduce Antarctica's impact on rising sea levels, but only if carbon emissions are swiftly reduced in the coming decades. By the same token, if emissions continue on the current trajectory, Antarctic ice loss could lead to more future sea level rise than previously thought.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 19:46:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A thorny problem, a genetic answer</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/thorny-problem-genetic-answer</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Every rose has its thorn. Or rather, every rose has its prickle, a sharp projection of the plant's skin that can serve as a deterrent to herbivores but also makes cultivating roses and other plants more difficult. New research supported by the U.S…</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 19:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists pin down the origins of the moon's tenuous atmosphere</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240802144558.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>Scientists say they have identified the main process that formed the moon's atmosphere and continues to sustain it today. The team reports that the lunar atmosphere is primarily a product of 'impact vaporization.'</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 19:45:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Astronomers uncover new phenomenon in growth dynamics of supermassive black hole</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/astronomers-uncover-new-phenomenon-growth-dynamics</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Scientists at the U.S. National Science Foundation National Radio Astronomy Observatory (NSF NRAO), along with an international team of astronomers, have uncovered a new cosmic mechanism in the complex dynamics of supermassive black holes — one that…</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 13:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fossil shows how penguins' wings evolved</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240802132919.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>A tiny fossil penguin plays a huge role in the evolutionary history of the bird, an international study shows.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 18:29:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Garden to table: Turning a backyard plant into a mainstream crop</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/garden-table-turning-backyard-plant-mainstream</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>It looks like a cherry tomato wrapped in a paper lantern, but in fact it's called a groundcherry. Little-known beyond gardeners and farmers, the groundcherry has quietly produced fruit across North America for centuries. Now it's emerging from…</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 17:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sea level changes shaped early life on Earth, fossil study reveals</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240802132909.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Shifts in the Earth's continental plates that drove long-term changes in sea level set the stage for the evolution of the earliest animals on Earth, a study suggests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 18:29:09 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>