<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 16:16:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Synthetic platelets stanch bleeding, promote healing using advanced materials</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/synthetic-platelets-stanch-bleeding-promote-healing</link><description>A research team has developed synthetic platelets that can stop bleeding and enhance healing at the site of an injury. They demonstrated that the synthetic platelets work well in some animals but have not yet begun clinical trials in humans. The…</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 15:03:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Webb telescope reveals asteroid collision in neighboring star system</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240610140338.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Astronomers have captured what appears to be a snapshot of a massive collision of giant asteroids in Beta Pictoris, a neighboring star system known for its early age and tumultuous planet-forming activity.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 19:03:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-54</link><description>NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan traveled to Interlaken, Switzerland, to join international partners for the Global Research Council's (GRC) annual meeting. GRC aims to promote long-term multilateral research and collaboration across continents…</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 20:32:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Optimism wards off procrastination</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240610140256.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>People with an optimistic outlook on the future are less likely to be severe procrastinators, according to new research. While procrastinators often admonish themselves for their 'bad habit,' it turns out that their worries for the future are more to blame. Through a survey of nearly 300 young people, researchers found that those who had a positive view about their stress levels decreasing in the future, compared to the past or present, were less likely to experience severe procrastination. Views on personal well-being didn't appear to have an effect. Improving people's outlook and readiness for the future could help them overcome procrastination and achieve a less stressful lifestyle.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 19:02:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF enhances research security with new TRUST proposal assessment process</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-enhances-research-security-new-trust-proposal</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has announced a new risk mitigation process, the Trusted Research Using Safeguards and Transparency (TRUST) framework, which will guide the agency in assessing grant proposals for potential national security risks…</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 15:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The solar system may have passed through dense interstellar clouds 2 million years ago, altering Earth's climate</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240610140249.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Astrophysicists calculate the likelihood that Earth was exposed to cold, harsh interstellar clouds, a phenomenon not previously considered in geologic climate models.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 19:02:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Widely used climate theory doesn't 'ring' true, according to new tree data</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/widely-used-climate-theory-doesnt-ring-true</link><description>New data on over 1,500 trees across nearly 1,000 sites shows that an existing theory of how individuals within a species will respond to a changing climate might not be true. The data, in the form of tree rings from an aridland pine, contradicts the…</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 21:00:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Planetary Health Diet associated with lower risk of premature death, lower environmental impact</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240610140239.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>People who eat a healthy, sustainable diet may substantially lower their risk of premature death in addition to their environmental impact, according to a new study. This large study directly evaluates the impacts of adherence to recommendations in the landmark 2019 EAT-Lancet report. The researchers have named the dietary pattern outlined in the report -- which emphasizes a variety of minimally processed plant foods but allows for modest consumption of meat and dairy foods -- the Planetary Health Diet (PHD).</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 19:02:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF, NEH and partner funding agencies from seven countries announce the winners of the Canada-led 2023 International Joint Initiative for Research on Climate Change Adaptation and Mitigation competition</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-neh-partner-funding-agencies-seven-countries</link><description>Today, the U.S. National Science Foundation and the National Endowment of the Humanities (NEH) joined partner funding agencies from Brazil, Canada, Germany, Norway, South Africa, Switzerland and the United Kingdom in announcing the awardees for the…</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 16:15:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Benefits of failure are overrated</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240610140218.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>The platitude that failure leads to success may be both inaccurate and damaging to society, according to new research.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 19:02:18 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>