<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 11:58:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Statement from NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan on the release of the U.S. Extremely Large Telescope External Evaluation Panel Report</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/statement-nsf-director-sethuraman-panchanathan-release-us</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation is grateful to the panel of independent experts commissioned to evaluate the readiness of the Giant Magellan Tele...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 16:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Earliest deep-cave ritual compound in Southwest Asia discovered</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/12/241209162441.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>A cave in Galilee, Israel, has yielded evidence for ritualistic gathering 35,000 years ago, the earliest on the Asian continent.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 21:24:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>3 areas where NSF is supporting STEM research and education in tribal nations</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/3-areas-where-nsf-supporting-stem-research-education-tribal</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Across America, Indigenous communities are working to advance programs that honor their people's cultural, societal and economic values. One of the wa...</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 14:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The National Secure Data Service Demonstration Project builds steam in year 2</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/national-secure-data-service-demonstration-project-builds</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>In response to the "CHIPS and Science Act of 2022," the U.S. National Science Foundation National Center for Science and Engineering Statistics (NCSES...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 14:53:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>At what age do children begin identifying with STEM? The answer is younger than we thought</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/what-age-do-children-begin-identifying-stem-answer-younger</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Much of early childhood development is well-documented and understood. For example, most parents know that children have favorite foods, colors and to...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 15:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-75</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan spent the last two weeks reinforcing NSF's strategic partnerships to ensure the United States remains at the vang...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 15:32:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Not so simple machines: Cracking the code for materials that can learn</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/12/241209122941.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Physicists have devised an algorithm that provides a mathematical framework for how learning works in lattices called mechanical neural networks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 17:29:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mars' infamous dust storms can engulf the entire planet: A new study examines how</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/12/241209123224.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Dust storms on Mars could one day pose dangers to human astronauts, damaging equipment and burying solar panels. New research gets closer to predictin...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 17:32:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pups of powerful meerkat matriarchs pay a price for their mom's status</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/12/241209162517.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>In meerkat society a dominant female is in charge, growling, biting, pushing and shoving to keep others in line. The matriarch's bullying behavior is ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 21:25:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dogs use two-word button combos to communicate</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/12/241209162449.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>A new study shows that dogs trained to use soundboards to 'talk' are capable of making two-word button combinations that go beyond random behavior or ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 21:24:49 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>