<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 06:53:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Scientists extend El Niño forecasts to 18 months in advance</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/scientists-extend-el-nino-forecasts-18-months</link><description>From 2023 to 2024, the world experienced a major El Niño event, affecting everything from global weather and climate to ecosystems and economies. Now, with U.S. National Science Foundation support from three grants and a new modeling approach…</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 17:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Converting captured carbon to fuel: Study assesses what's practical and what's not</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240722155154.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>A new analysis sheds light on major shortfalls of a recently proposed approach to capture CO2 from air and directly convert it to fuel using electricity. The authors also provide a new, more sustainable, alternative.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 20:51:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-59</link><description>This week, NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan visited Seoul, South Korea, to celebrate U.S.-South Korea partnerships in semiconductor and bioeconomy research and explore new collaboration opportunities. During his trip, Panchanathan met with…</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Breakthrough in skeletal muscle regeneration</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240722155152.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>In a finding that opens the door to the development of targeted therapies for various muscle disorders, newly published research identifies key mechanisms of skeletal muscle regeneration and growth of muscles following resistance exercise.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 20:51:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Historic records provide new insight</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/historic-records-provide-new-insight</link><description>U.S. National Science Foundation-funded researchers recently released a new study in Ecology and Evolution o utlining their in-depth analysis of historic baleen plates, the comb structures that are used by some species of whales to filter food, from…</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 21:27:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Boosting fruit intake during midlife can ward off late-life blues</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240722155127.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>In a large Singapore cohort study involving over 13,000 participants spanning close to 20 years, higher consumption of fruits during midlife was found to be associated with lower odds of depressive symptoms at late-life.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 20:51:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists discover which parts of the Amazon rainforest are most vulnerable to drought</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/scientists-discover-which-parts-amazon-rainforest</link><description>Regions of the Amazon rainforest respond to drought according to differences in local forest environments and in the properties of trees, Scott Saleska of the University of Arizona and colleagues have discovered. In the southern Amazon rainforest…</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 15:15:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>An over- or under-synchronized brain may predict psychosis</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240722155117.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Is it possible to assess an individual's risk of psychosis? Identifying predictive markers is a key challenge in psychiatry. A team now shows that overly strong or weak interconnections between certain brain areas could be a predictive marker of the disease.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 20:51:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF–DOE Rubin Observatory will detect thousands of elusive brown dwarfs, unlocking Milky Way mysteries</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/rubin-observatory-will-detect-thousands-dwarfs</link><description>Too big to be planets but too small to be stars, distant brown dwarfs are a key ingredient for understanding the history of the Milky Way. These elusive objects have existed since the early universe and have remained relatively unchanged. Anticipated…</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 19:05:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Smell of human stress affects dogs' emotions leading them to make more pessimistic choices</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240722155111.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Dogs experience emotional contagion from the smell of human stress, leading them to make more 'pessimistic' choices, new research finds. Researchers tested how human stress odors affect dogs' learning and emotional state.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 20:51:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>