<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 06:00:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Study probes how eating less can extend lifespan</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/10/241009121347.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Researchers tracked the health of nearly one thousand mice on a variety of diets to see if these diets would extend the mice's lifespan. The study was...</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 17:13:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF congratulates laureates of the 2024 Nobel Prize in physiology or medicine</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-congratulates-laureates-2024-nobel-prize-physiology-medicine</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation congratulates Victor Ambros and Gary Ruvkun for their Nobel Prize in physiology or medicine. Their breakthrough d...</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 22:39:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Genetic analysis of 25,000 Chinese mothers and infants reveals unique genes associated with disease risk</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/10/241009121544.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Genome-wide association studies have great potential for advancing our understanding of the genetic background of diseases, but so far, few associatio...</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 17:15:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nature and plastics inspire breakthrough in soft sustainable materials</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/10/241009121344.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Using peptides and a snippet of the large molecules in plastics, materials scientists have developed materials made of tiny, flexible nano-sized ribbo...</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 17:13:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Viruses are teeming on your toothbrush, showerhead</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/10/241009122630.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Microbiologists found that showerheads and toothbrushes are teeming with an extremely diverse collection of viruses -- most of which have never been s...</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 17:26:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF congratulates laureates of the 2024 Nobel Prize in physics</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-congratulates-laureates-2024-nobel-prize-physics</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation congratulates John J. Hopfield and Geoffrey E. Hinton for their Nobel Prize in physics. Their research and innova...</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 20:04:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF congratulates laureates of the 2024 Nobel Prize in chemistry</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-congratulates-laureates-2024-nobel-prize-chemistry</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation congratulates David Baker, Demis Hassabis and John Jumper on being awarded the 2024 Nobel Prize in chemistry. Bak...</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 20:57:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-68</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation Director Sethuraman Panchanathan had a dynamic week as he met with domestic and international partners to emphasi...</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 19:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF Growing Convergence Research awards advance innovation across disciplines</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-growing-convergence-research-awards-advance-innovation</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation Growing Convergence Research (NSF GCR) awards are fostering deep integration across disciplines and pushing the b...</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 20:15:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NASA's Hubble watches Jupiter's Great Red Spot behave like a stress ball</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/10/241009183537.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Astronomers have observed Jupiter's legendary Great Red Spot (GRS), an anticyclone large enough to swallow Earth, for at least 150 years. But there ar...</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 23:35:37 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>