<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 07:54:39 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-51</link><description>This week was full of celebrations and milestones — including recognizing NSF staff and public servants for their hard work to better the nation; celebrating teachers for their dedication to educating the next generation of scientists, engineers and…</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 22:11:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Virtual reality becomes more engaging when designers use cinematic tools</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240514141501.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Cinematography techniques can significantly increase user engagement with virtual environments and, in particular, the aesthetic appeal of what users see in virtual reality.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:15:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF announces $24M investment across three EPSCoR jurisdictions</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-24m-investment-across-three-epscor</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has awarded teams from South Dakota, New Hampshire and Maine roughly $8 million each through the Established Program to Stimulate Competitive Research (EPSCoR) Collaborations for Optimizing Research Ecosystems…</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 18:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WASP-193b, a giant planet with a density similar to that of cotton candy</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240514141403.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Astronomers have just discovered WASP-193b, an extraordinarily low-density giant planet orbiting a distant Sun-like star.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:14:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF announces a new EPSCoR Track-1 award to combat climate change in Kentucky</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-new-epscor-track-1-award-combat</link><description>The Commonwealth of Kentucky will receive $20 million from the U.S. National Science Foundation through the Established Program to Stimulate Competitive Research (EPSCoR). This program aims to support U.S. states and territories, also known as EPSCoR…</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Young whale's journey highlights threats facing ocean animals</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240514141354.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>A young whale's journey across the Mediterranean highlights the many threats facing ocean animals, researchers say.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:13:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Big data helps determine what drives disease risk</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/big-data-helps-determine-what-drives-disease-risk</link><description>Working with nearly 3,000 observations across almost 1,500 host-parasite combinations, U.S. National Science Foundation-supported researchers at Notre Dame University have found that biodiversity loss, chemical pollution, introduced species and…</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:14:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>People without an inner voice have poorer verbal memory</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240514141317.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>The vast majority of people have an ongoing conversation with themselves, an inner voice, that plays an important role in their daily lives. But between 5-10 per cent of the population do not have the same experience of an inner voice, and they find it more difficult to perform certain verbal memory tasks, new research shows.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:13:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Discovery in tomato could lead to natural pesticides</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/discovery-tomato-could-lead-natural-pesticides</link><description>Like a slightly revised version of the movie "The Parent Trap," U.S. National Science Foundation-supported researchers from Michigan State University have discovered that tomato plants have two related but separate pathways for producing acylsugars…</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 20:40:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Researchers discover the universe's oldest stars in our own galactic backyard</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240514141300.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Astronomers discovered three of the oldest stars in the universe, and they live in our own galactic neighborhood. The stars are in the Milky Way's 'halo' -- the cloud of stars that envelopes the entire main galactic disk -- and they appear to have formed between 12 and 13 billion years ago, when the very first galaxies were taking shape.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:13:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>