<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 15:53:30 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NSF appoints Micah Cheatham as chief management officer</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-appoints-micah-cheatham-chief-management</link><description>Today, the U.S. National Science Foundation is pleased to announce the appointment of Micah Cheatham as chief management officer (CMO). In this role, Cheatham will serve as principal advisor to the NSF director and deputy director on agency…</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Building materials for water-rich planets in the early solar system</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240709121817.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Age data for certain classes of meteorite have made it possible to gain new findings on the origin of small water-rich astronomical bodies in the early solar system. These planetesimals continually supplied building materials for planets -- also for the Earth, whose original material contained little water. The Earth received its actual water through planetesimals, which emerged at low temperatures in the outer solar system, as shown by computational models carried out by an international research teach with participation by earth scientists.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 17:18:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Transformers: Cooler side of the grid</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/transformers-cooler-side-grid</link><description>In a significant step towards resilient, sustainable energy, researchers at The University of Texas at Austin (UT Austin) are undertaking a groundbreaking initiative to enhance the performance and longevity of grid transformers, a critical component…</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:19:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>First local extinction in the US due to sea level rise, study suggests</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240709121814.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>The United States has lost its only stand of the massive Key Largo tree cactus in what researchers believe is the first local extinction of a species caused by sea level rise in the country.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 17:18:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Statement from NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan on the U.S. Economic Development Administration's Regional Technology and Innovation Hub awardees</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/statement-on-economic-development-admin-regional-tech-innovation</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation congratulates the U.S. Economic Development Administration (EDA) on its announcement today of its Regional Technology and Innovation Hubs (Tech Hubs). In alignment with the 'CHIPS and Science Act of 2022,' NSF and…</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ancient large kangaroo moved mainly on four legs, according to new research</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240709121711.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>A type of extinct kangaroo that lived during the Pleistocene around two and a half million to ten thousand years ago, known as the 'giant wallaby', was a poor hopper, a study has found.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 17:17:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Physicists' laser experiment excites atom's nucleus, may enable new type of atomic clock</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/physicists-laser-experiment-excites-atoms-nucleus</link><description>A team of researchers successfully raised the energy state of an atom's nucleus with a laser, which could lead to new precision measurement technology with orders of magnitude higher accuracy than today's best atomic clocks. The researchers embedded…</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 16:57:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Run screaming or slow retreat? New study advances understanding of brain responses to emotionally-charged scenes</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240709121708.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>The ability to recognize and respond to emotionally-charged situations is essential to a species' evolutionary success. A new study advances our understanding of how the brain responds to emotionally charged objects and scenes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 17:17:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A new film on baffling Baffin Bay</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/new-film-baffling-baffin-bay</link><description>A new NSF-supported documentary follows the Baffin Bay Deglacial Experiment team on its journey to investigate what happened to the Greenland Ice Sheet over 15,000 years ago Although scientists know that the Earth has seen major climate changes from…</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 22:24:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Brain neurotransmitter receptor antagonist found to prevent opioid addiction in mice</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240709121705.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>New research has found a drug that treats insomnia works to prevent the addictive effects of the morphine opioids in mice while still providing effective pain relief.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 17:17:05 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>