<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 11:02:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Predictive AI model could help forecast neurodegenerative diseases</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/predictive-ai-model-could-help-forecast-neurodegenerative</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Neurodegenerative diseases like Alzheimer's are a growing concern in the U.S., with over 7 million Americans living with Alzheimer's disease today. By...</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 16:00:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Millions of new solar system objects to be found and 'filmed in technicolor' -- studies predict</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/06/250603213454.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Astronomers have revealed new research showing that millions of new solar system objects are likely to be detected by a brand-new facility, which is e...</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 02:34:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>First direct observation of the trapped waves that shook the world in 2023</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/06/250603115015.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>A new study has finally confirmed the theory that the cause of extraordinary global tremors in September -- October 2023 was indeed two mega tsunamis ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 16:50:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists say next few years vital to securing the future of the West Antarctic Ice Sheet</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/06/250603115018.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Collapse of the West Antarctic Ice Sheet could be triggered with very little ocean warming above present-day, leading to a devastating four meters of ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 16:50:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tea, berries, dark chocolate and apples could lead to a longer life span, study shows</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/06/250603115028.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>New research has found that those who consume a diverse range of foods rich in flavonoids, such as tea, berries, dark chocolate, and apples, could low...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 16:50:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Being in nature can help people with chronic back pain manage their condition</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/06/250603115020.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Researchers asked patients, some of whom had experienced lower back pain for up to 40 years, if being in nature helped them coped better with their lo...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 16:50:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF announces new NextG wireless funding opportunity</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-new-nextg-wireless-funding-opportunity</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation today announced a new funding opportunity to support research and technology development that will improve the ne...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 14:01:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF advanced computing accelerates preeclampsia research and potential treatments</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-advanced-computing-accelerates-preeclampsia-research</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Each year, preeclampsia—a life-threatening pregnancy complication—affects nearly 1 in 25 expectant mothers in the United States. Emerging suddenly aft...</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 16:36:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Learning occurs quicker than thought, according to brain imaging</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/learning-occurs-quicker-thought-according-brain-imaging</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Researchers supported by the U.S. National Science Foundation have provided a new understanding of how and where learning occurs in the brain. The two...</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 16:30:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New tools to identify and monitor cardiovascular disease</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/new-tools-identify-monitor-cardiovascular-disease</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Cardiovascular diseases cause one death every 33 seconds in America. Diagnosing these conditions, which account for approximately 20% of all deaths an...</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 14:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>