<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 06:39:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>A remarkable fossil assemblage gets a new interpretation</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/remarkable-fossil-assemblage-gets-new-interpretation</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>A team of paleontologists recently discovered that an ancient seascape known for its diverse assemblage of exceptionally preserved fossils represents ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 18:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meteorite contains evidence of liquid water on Mars 742 million years ago</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/11/241113160829.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>An asteroid struck Mars 11 million years ago and sent pieces of the red planet hurtling through space. One of these chunks of Mars eventually crashed ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 21:08:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF names three new I-Corps Hubs expanding the National Innovation Network across the U.S.</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-names-three-new-i-corps-hubs-expanding-national</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation today announced the addition of three new NSF Innovation Corps (NSF I-Corps™) Hubs that will scale the NSF-led Na...</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 17:35:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>12,000-year-old stones may be very early evidence of wheel-like technology</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/11/241113160855.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>A collection of perforated pebbles from an archaeological site in Israel may be spindle whorls, representing a key milestone in the development of rot...</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 21:08:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Creating a buzz about bee nest symmetry</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/creating-buzz-about-bee-nest-symmetry</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Mirroring the mechanisms that make human faces and bodies — and those of many multicellular organisms — symmetrical, bee colonies build symmetrical ne...</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 16:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-72</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In a whirlwind of activity over the past two weeks, U.S. National Science Foundation Director Sethuraman Panchanathan has been at the forefront of cha...</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 14:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists discover laser light can cast a shadow</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/11/241114130211.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Researchers have found that under certain conditions, a laser beam can act like an opaque object and cast a shadow, opening new possibilities for tech...</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 18:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Faster flowing glaciers could help predict nearby volcanic activity</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/11/241113123717.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Glaciers that are within three miles of a volcano move nearly 50% quicker than average, a new study has found, which could help create early warning o...</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 17:37:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF Arecibo C3 opening moved to 2025, aligning with NSF's 75th anniversary commemorations</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-arecibo-c3-opening-moved-2025-aligning-nsfs-75th</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has announced that the official opening of the NSF Arecibo Center for Culturally Relevant and Inclusive Science E...</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 18:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anti-anxiety and hallucination-like effects of psychedelics mediated by distinct neural circuits</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/11/241114161054.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>New research suggests that it could be possible to separate treatment from hallucinations when developing new drugs based on psychedelics. The anti-an...</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 21:10:54 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>