<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:10:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NSF invites K-12 students to design their own video games and compete for Game Maker Awards</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-invites-k-12-students-design-their-own-video</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation announces the NSF Game Maker Awards "Life in 2100" competition for K-12 students. To commemorate the agency’s milestone 75th anniversary, this competition invites students to create video games that imagine life…</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 15:10:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Researchers unveil mysteries of ancient Earth</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240814170336.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>A team of researchers has made strides in understanding the formation of massif-type anorthosites, enigmatic rocks that only formed during the middle part of Earth's history. These plagioclase-rich igneous rock formations, which can cover areas as large as 42,000 square kilometers and host titanium ore deposits, have puzzled scientists for decades due to conflicting theories about their origins.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 22:03:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Studying the journey, not the destination, provides new insight into songbird migrations</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/studying-journey-into-songbird-migrations</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>New research supported by the U.S. National Science Foundation using two decades worth of data could change how scientists think about bird migrations and the interdependencies and relationships they involve. Driving any long distance usually…</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 20:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>International study detects consciousness in unresponsive patients</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240814170333.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>New research found that brain scans can detect consciousness in some patients with brain injury who are unresponsive. In the study, 241 participants with severe brain injury who do not respond when given a simple instruction were assessed with functional MRI (fMRI), electroencephalography (EEG), or both tests, while hearing instructions, such as 'imagine opening and closing your hand.' Their brain responses showed that 25 percent of participants repeatedly followed this instruction covertly over minutes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 22:03:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>This week, NSF marked the second anniversary of the "CHIPS and Science Act of 2022," signed into law on August 9, 2022. This landmark legislation has empowered NSF to accelerate innovation and build a resilient, inclusive, and productive American…</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:27:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New brain-computer interface allows man with ALS to 'speak' again</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240814170129.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>A new brain-computer interface translates brain signals into speech with up to 97 percent accuracy. Researchers implanted sensors in the brain of a man with severely impaired speech due to amyotrophic lateral sclerosis (ALS). The man was able to communicate his intended speech within minutes of activating the system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 22:01:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Radio astronomers and satellite internet provider develop new sky-sharing system</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/radio-astronomers-satellite-internet-provider</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>New techniques developed by the U.S. National Science Foundation National Radio Astronomy Observatory (NSF NRAO) and SpaceX enable radio astronomy telescopes to operate without interference from satellite transmissions. The techniques allow…</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 22:20:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Engineers conduct first in-orbit test of 'swarm' satellite autonomous navigation</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240814160728.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>With 2D cameras and space robotics algorithms, astronautics engineers have created a navigation system able to manage multiple satellites using visual data only. They just tested it in space for the first time.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 21:07:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF National Quantum Virtual Laboratory advances with first five pilot projects</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-national-quantum-virtual-laboratory-advances</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Realizing practical advantages and societal benefits from quantum-scale phenomena has been a long-sought milestone in quantum information science. The U.S. National Science Foundation today announced the initial $5 million investment across five…</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 14:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Physicists throw world's smallest disco party</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240814160717.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>A new milestone has been set for levitated optomechanics as a group of scientists observed the Berry phase of electron spins in nano-sized diamonds levitated in vacuum.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 21:07:17 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>