<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 11:04:10 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Scientists just found a hidden factor behind Earth’s methane surge</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/08/250816113528.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Roughly two-thirds of all atmospheric methane, a potent greenhouse gas, comes from methanogens. Tracking down which methanogens in which environment p...</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 04:27:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists uncover the lost shelduck that chose walking over flight</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/08/250816113526.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Scientists have uncovered an extinct shelduck from the Chatham Islands that evolved shorter wings and stronger legs, adapting to a predator-free, wind...</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 04:16:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The surprising way rising CO2 could supercharge space storms</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/08/250816113525.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Rising CO₂ levels will make the upper atmosphere colder and thinner, altering how geomagnetic storms impact satellites. Future storms could cause shar...</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 04:04:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NASA’s SWOT satellite captures Kamchatka megaquake tsunami in striking detail</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/08/250815034719.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>When a massive 8.8 magnitude earthquake struck off Russia’s Kamchatka Peninsula, NASA and CNES’s SWOT satellite captured a rare and detailed picture o...</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 17:13:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trojan horse bacteria sneak cancer-killing viruses into tumors</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/08/250816113522.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Scientists have engineered a groundbreaking cancer treatment that uses bacteria to smuggle viruses directly into tumors, bypassing the immune system a...</description><pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 15:28:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF and NVIDIA partnership enables Ai2 to develop fully open AI models to fuel U.S. scientific innovation</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-nvidia-partnership-enables-ai2-develop-fully-open-ai</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation announced a partnership with NVIDIA to develop a set of artificial intelligence models that will transform the ab...</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 13:07:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Podcast: Introducing AI to the future workforce</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/podcast-introducing-ai-future-workforce</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>A workforce fluent in AI techniques will be essential to ensure U.S. leadership in artificial intelligence continues. Jeremy Waisome, an assistant pro...</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 18:56:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF invests $29.2 million in EPSCoR Research Infrastructure collaborations for transformative impact across 11 jurisdictions</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-invests-292-million-epscor-research-infrastructure</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation (NSF) has announced six major awards through its EPSCoR Research Infrastructure Improvement Program: Focused EPSC...</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 14:55:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF invests nearly $32M to accelerate novel AI-driven approaches in protein design, strengthening the U.S. bioeconomy</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-invests-nearly-32m-accelerate-novel-ai-driven-approaches</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation Directorate for Technology, Innovation and Partnerships (NSF TIP) announced an inaugural investment of nearly $32...</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 15:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF invests in AI-ready test beds to accelerate U.S. leadership</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-invests-ai-ready-test-beds-accelerate-us-leadership</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation announced over $2 million in planning grants to support the development of artificial intelligence-ready test bed...</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 16:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>