<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 06:58:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NSF announces pilot phase and anticipated opening date of Arecibo C3 at the site of the NSF Arecibo Observatory Historic District in Puerto Rico</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-pilot-phase-anticipated-opening-date-of-arecibo</link><description>| En Español | As excitement builds for the grand opening of the new U.S. National Science Foundation Arecibo Center for Culturally Relevant and Inclusive Science Education, Computational Skills, and Community Engagement (NSF Arecibo C3), anticipated…</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 16:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Animal brain inspired AI game changer for autonomous robots</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240515164207.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>A team of researchers has developed a drone that flies autonomously using neuromorphic image processing and control based on the workings of animal brains. Animal brains use less data and energy compared to current deep neural networks running on GPUs (graphic chips). Neuromorphic processors are therefore very suitable for small drones because they don't need heavy and large hardware and batteries. The results are extraordinary: during flight the drone's deep neural network processes data up to 64 times faster and consumes three times less energy than when running on a GPU. Further developments of this technology may enable the leap for drones to become as small, agile, and smart as flying insects or birds.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 21:42:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-51</link><description>This week was full of celebrations and milestones — including recognizing NSF staff and public servants for their hard work to better the nation; celebrating teachers for their dedication to educating the next generation of scientists, engineers and…</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 22:11:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The crystallization of memory: Study reveals how practice forms new memory pathways in the brain</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240515164158.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>A new study has shown that repetitive practice not only is helpful in improving skills but also leads to profound changes in the brain's memory pathways.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 21:41:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF announces $24M investment across three EPSCoR jurisdictions</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-24m-investment-across-three-epscor</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has awarded teams from South Dakota, New Hampshire and Maine roughly $8 million each through the Established Program to Stimulate Competitive Research (EPSCoR) Collaborations for Optimizing Research Ecosystems…</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 18:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Detection of an Earth-sized exoplanet orbiting the ultracool dwarf star SPECULOOS-3</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240515122831.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Astronomers have just discovered a new Earth-sized exoplanet around SPECULOOS-3, an 'ultracool dwarf' star as small as Jupiter, twice as cold as our Sun, and located 55 light-years from Earth. After the famous TRAPPIST-1, SPECULOOS 3 is the second planetary system discovered around this type of star.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:28:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF announces a new EPSCoR Track-1 award to combat climate change in Kentucky</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-new-epscor-track-1-award-combat</link><description>The Commonwealth of Kentucky will receive $20 million from the U.S. National Science Foundation through the Established Program to Stimulate Competitive Research (EPSCoR). This program aims to support U.S. states and territories, also known as EPSCoR…</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Robots' and prosthetic hands' sense of touch could be as fast as humans</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240515122740.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Research could pave the way for a prosthetic hand and robot to be able to feel touch like a human hand. The technology could also be used to help restore lost functionality to patients after a stroke.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:27:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Big data helps determine what drives disease risk</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/big-data-helps-determine-what-drives-disease-risk</link><description>Working with nearly 3,000 observations across almost 1,500 host-parasite combinations, U.S. National Science Foundation-supported researchers at Notre Dame University have found that biodiversity loss, chemical pollution, introduced species and…</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:14:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Highly pathogenic avian flu detected in New York City wild birds</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240515122731.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>A small number of New York City wild birds carry highly pathogenic H5N1 avian influenza, according to a recent study.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:27:31 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>