<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 06:54:37 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Historic records provide new insight</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/historic-records-provide-new-insight</link><description>U.S. National Science Foundation-funded researchers recently released a new study in Ecology and Evolution o utlining their in-depth analysis of historic baleen plates, the comb structures that are used by some species of whales to filter food, from…</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 21:27:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Another intermediate-mass black hole discovered at the center of our galaxy</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240718124854.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>So far, only about ten intermediate-mass black holes have been discovered in the entire universe. The newly identified black hole causes surrounding stars in a cluster to move in an unexpectedly orderly way.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 17:48:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists discover which parts of the Amazon rainforest are most vulnerable to drought</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/scientists-discover-which-parts-amazon-rainforest</link><description>Regions of the Amazon rainforest respond to drought according to differences in local forest environments and in the properties of trees, Scott Saleska of the University of Arizona and colleagues have discovered. In the southern Amazon rainforest…</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 15:15:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Microbes found to destroy certain 'forever chemicals'</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240717162500.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>An environmental engineering team has discovered that specific bacterial species can cleave the strong fluorine-to-carbon bond certain kinds of 'forever chemical' water pollutants, offering promise for low-cost treatments of contaminated drinking water.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 21:25:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF–DOE Rubin Observatory will detect thousands of elusive brown dwarfs, unlocking Milky Way mysteries</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/rubin-observatory-will-detect-thousands-dwarfs</link><description>Too big to be planets but too small to be stars, distant brown dwarfs are a key ingredient for understanding the history of the Milky Way. These elusive objects have existed since the early universe and have remained relatively unchanged. Anticipated…</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 19:05:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Evidence for butchery of giant armadillo-like mammals in Argentina 21,000 years ago</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240717162440.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Cut marks on fossils could be evidence of humans exploiting large mammals in Argentina more than 20,000 years ago, according to a new study.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 21:24:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-58</link><description>NSF has been bustling with activity in recent weeks, achieving many significant milestones. NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan welcomed Phoenix, Arizona Mayor Kate Gallego to NSF headquarters. Their discussions centered around collaboration…</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ant insights lead to robot navigation breakthrough</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240717162408.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Have you ever wondered how insects are able to go so far beyond their home and still find their way? The answer to this question is not only relevant to biology but also to making the AI for tiny, autonomous robots. Drone-researchers felt inspired by biological findings on how ants visually recognize their environment and combine it with counting their steps in order to get safely back home. They have used these insights to create an insect-inspired autonomous navigation strategy for tiny, lightweight robots. It allows such robots to come back home after long trajectories, while requiring extremely little computation and memory (0.65 kiloByte per 100 m). In the future, tiny autonomous robots could find a wide range of uses, from monitoring stock in warehouses to finding gas leaks in industrial sites.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 21:24:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wildfire smoke is reaching almost all lakes in North America</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/wildfire-smoke-reaching-almost-all-lakes-north</link><description>Wildfire smoke, sometimes drifting across hundreds of miles, reached almost every lake in North America at least one day each year from 2019 to 2021, according to U.S. National Science Foundation- supported findings published in the journal Global…</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 17:28:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Soft, stretchy 'jelly batteries' inspired by electric eels</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240717162405.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Researchers have developed soft, stretchable 'jelly batteries' that could be used for wearable devices or soft robotics, or even implanted in the brain to deliver drugs or treat conditions such as epilepsy.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 21:24:05 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>