<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 07:56:22 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Eight or more drinks per week linked to signs of injury in the brain</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/04/250409173113.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Heavy drinkers who have eight or more alcoholic drinks per week have an increased risk of brain lesions called hyaline arteriolosclerosis, signs of br...</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 22:31:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Solid or liquid? Scientists accurately predict complex tissue changes in fruit fly embryos</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/solid-or-liquid-scientists-accurately-predict-complex-tissue</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Funded by the U.S. National Science Foundation, scientists have accurately modeled particular cellular changes in Drosophila melanogaster, or the frui...</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 13:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How much food can the world grow? International team calls for new yield potential estimates</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/04/250409155025.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Agronomists question statistical methods used to predict yield potential and 'yield gaps' for major crops. In some cases, yield potential is overestim...</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 20:50:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF expands access to advanced cloud computing for scientific research</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-expands-access-advanced-cloud-computing-scientific</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation (NSF) has awarded a $20 million grant to expand the NSF CloudBank, an initiative designed to accelerate science a...</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 14:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hopping gives this tiny robot a leg up</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/04/250409154610.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>A hopping, insect-sized robot can jump over gaps or obstacles, traverse rough, slippery, or slanted surfaces, and perform aerial acrobatic maneuvers, ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 20:46:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sink or Swim: The fate of sinking tectonic plates depends on their ancient tectonic histories</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/04/250409154835.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>New findings provide a greater understanding of plate subduction, or how tectonic plates slide beneath one another. This recycling of surface material...</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 20:48:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prehistoric rhinos lived in super-herds</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/04/250409154833.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Rhinos that flourished across much of North America 12 million years ago gathered in huge herds, according to a new study.</description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 20:48:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quantum quasiparticle could make future quantum computers more reliable</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/quantum-quasiparticle-could-make-future-quantum-computers</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Supported by the U.S. National Science Foundation, physicists have revealed the presence of a previously unobserved type of subatomic phenomenon calle...</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tiny lenses grown from bacteria and enzymes may help doctors see inside cells</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/tiny-lenses-grown-bacteria-enzymes-may-help-doctors-see</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>A team of researchers supported by the U.S. National Science Foundation has successfully made self-growing microlenses using bacteria and enzymes foun...</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 21:44:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Conserving the White Oak Tree: Critical for timber and distilling industries</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/conserving-white-oak-tree-critical-timber-distilling</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>A group of researchers from the University of Kentucky, The University of Tennessee and Indiana University, including those supported by the U.S. Nati...</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>