<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 06:40:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NSF announces $20 million investment in quantum nanofabrication infrastructure</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-20-million-investment-quantum</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation (NSF) announced a nearly $20 million award that will support the construction of a nanoscale fabrication facility at the University of Colorado Boulder to accelerate the co-design and development of atomic…</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 19:36:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prying open the AI black box</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240621122906.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Meet SQUID, a new computational tool. Compared with other genomic AI models, SQUID is more consistent, reduces background noise, and can yield better predictions regarding critical mutations. The new system aims to bring scientists closer to their findings' true medical implications.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 17:29:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Democratizing data: Discovering data use and value for research and policy</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/democratizing-data-discovering-data-use-value</link><description>Data access and discovery continue to be topics of great interest across the federal data ecosystem. The National Center for Science and Engineering Statistics (NCSES) within the U.S. National Science Foundation supported a pilot study seeking to…</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 16:09:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Iron meteorites hint that our infant solar system was more doughnut than dartboard</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240620194009.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Iron meteorites are remnants of the metallic cores of the earliest asteroids in our solar system. Iron meteorites contain refractory metals, such as iridium and platinum, that formed near the sun but were transported to the outer solar system. New research shows that for this to have happened, the protoplanetary disk of our solar system had to have been doughnut-shaped because the refractory metals could not have crossed the large gaps in a target-shaped disk of concentric rings. The paper suggests that the refractory metals moved outward as the protoplanetary disk rapidly expanded, and were trapped in the outer solar system by Jupiter.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 00:40:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Collaborative approaches improve materials informatics workforce training</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/collaborative-approaches-improve-materials</link><description>A wide range of innovative products, from biomedical implants to aerospace composites, come from research in materials informatics (MI) — the combination of machine learning, artificial intelligence and computational methodologies with materials…</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 17:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Supermassive black hole appears to grow like a baby star</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240620152335.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Supermassive black holes pose unanswered questions for astronomers around the world, not least 'How do they grow so big?' Now, an international team of astronomers has discovered a powerful rotating, magnetic wind that they believe is helping a galaxy's central supermassive black hole to grow. The swirling wind, revealed with the help of the ALMA telescope in nearby galaxy ESO320-G030, suggests that similar processes are involved both in black hole growth and the birth of stars.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 20:23:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shipworms still hold some sea-crets</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/shipworms-still-hold-some-sea-crets</link><description>Although they have been known to mariners for centuries — having aided in shipwrecking Columbus and sinking parts of the Spanish Armada — scientists have not been able to determine how shipworms digest wood, until now. Sometimes known as "termites of…</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 14:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Walking brings huge benefits for low back pain</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240620152321.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Adults with a history of low back pain went nearly twice as long without a recurrence of their back pain if they walked regularly, a world-first study has found.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 20:23:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-56</link><description>This week, NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan highlighted NSF’s commitment to innovation and STEM advancements through several key events. The Director joined Senator Shaheen in a conversation on Capitol Hill with New Hampshire business leaders to…</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 19:53:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sweat health monitor measures levels of disease markers</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240620152311.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>A wearable health monitor can reliably measure levels of important biochemicals in sweat during physical exercise. The 3D-printed monitor could someday provide a simple and non-invasive way to track health conditions and diagnose common diseases, such as diabetes, gout, kidney disease or heart disease. The monitor was able to accurately monitor the levels of volunteers' glucose, lactate and uric acid as well as the rate of sweating during exercise.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 20:23:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>