<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 06:53:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Why does the United States have the most tornadoes in the world?  Scientists find new answers.</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/why-does-united-states-have-most-tornadoes-world</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>The central and eastern regions of the United States are the hotspots for Earth's most damaging and frequent tornadoes, scientists have found. In fact, the U.S. has the most tornadoes of any country in the world, but why? In a study published in…</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 17:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Super-black wood can improve telescopes, optical devices and consumer goods</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240730140539.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>Thanks to an accidental discovery, researchers have created a new super-black material that absorbs almost all light, opening potential applications in fine jewelry, solar cells and precision optical devices.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 19:05:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-60</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>This week, NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan participated in a series of pivotal discussions and events, underscoring U.S. National Science Foundation’s role at the forefront of scientific innovation and workforce development in the United States…</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 18:12:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What no one has seen before -- simulation of gravitational waves from failing warp drive</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240730134858.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Physicists have been exploring the theoretical possibility of spaceships driven by compressing the four-dimensional spacetime for decades. Although this so-called 'warp drive' originates from the realm of science fiction, it is based on concrete descriptions in general relativity. A new study takes things a step further -- simulating the gravitational waves such a drive might emit if it broke down.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 18:48:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF funds over $50M in new partnerships to broaden participation in materials science</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-funds-over-50m-new-partnerships-broaden</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation is announcing $50 million in Partnerships for Research and Education in Materials (PREM) awards to 15 collaborative research projects nationwide to expand participation and access to materials science-focused…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 14:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The corona is weirdly hot: Parker Solar Probe rules out one explanation</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240730134746.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>By diving into the sun's corona, NASA's Parker Solar Probe has ruled out S-shaped bends in the sun's magnetic field as a cause of the corona's searing temperatures.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 18:47:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jumping on the jumping gene bandwagon to speed up plant breeding</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/jumping-jumping-gene-bandwagon-speed-plant</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Getting a new variety of corn, tomato, soybean or other crop to market can be a long and costly effort, with breeders working to ensure the eventual product has the right mix of genetics that will let it withstand change, produce large amounts of…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 18:48:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NASA data shows July 22, 2024 was Earth's hottest day on record</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240729173444.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>July 22, 2024, was the hottest day on record, according to a NASA analysis of global daily temperature data. July 21 and 23 of this year also exceeded the previous daily record, set in July 2023. These record-breaking temperatures are part of a long-term warming trend driven by human activities, primarily the emission of greenhouse gases.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 22:34:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Making strides in understanding decision making</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/making-strides-understanding-decision-making</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Decisions, decisions. Life is full of decisions, from what to have for breakfast to where to work. To make each one, a series of mechanisms in the brain must be engaged. Understanding those mechanisms is an important area of neuroscience. To help…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 17:19:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Winter breeding offers lifeline for monarch butterflies in Northern California</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240729173441.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>Monarch butterflies in Northern California are adapting to a changing climate by embracing an unexpected strategy: breeding in the winter. The shift could be key to the survival of the iconic insect, according to a new study.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 22:34:41 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>