<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 12:32:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NSF awards $42.4M in new grants to support the future of semiconductors</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-awards-42-4m-new-grants-support-future-semiconductors</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Today, the U.S. National Science Foundation, in partnership with Ericsson, Intel Corporation, Micron Technology and Samsung, announced $42.4 million i...</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 15:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Plant-derived secondary organic aerosols can act as mediators of plant-plant interactions</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240913105324.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>A new study reveals that plant-derived secondary organic aerosols (SOAs) can act as mediators of plant-plant interactions. This research was conducted...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 15:53:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF–DOE Rubin Observatory will reveal the faint light from sources of gravitational waves, neutrinos and more</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-doe-rubin-observatory-will-reveal-faint-light-sources</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Astronomy has always relied on light to convey information about the universe. But capturing photons — such as those from visible light or radio waves...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 16:32:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Folded or cut, this lithium-sulfur battery keeps going</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240913105258.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Most rechargeable batteries that power portable devices, such as toys, handheld vacuums and e-bikes, use lithium-ion technology. But these batteries c...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 15:52:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Purple bacteria offer path to more sustainable plastic</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/purple-bacteria-offer-path-more-sustainable-plastic</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>There's hardly a more ubiquitous substance than plastic. It's everywhere in the environment, from soil to air to water, and it's in our bodies. Accord...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 16:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bacteria work together to thrive in difficult conditions</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240913105250.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>In a new study, researchers have determined through both statistical analysis and in experiments that soil pH is a driver of microbial community compo...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 15:52:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Water temperature at Australia's Great Barrier Reef reaches hottest in 400 years</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/water-temperature-australias-great-barrier-reef-hottest-in-400-years</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Warming ocean waters have led to mass coral bleaching events in Australia's Great Barrier Reef (GBR) and are threatening the future of this UNESCO Wor...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 14:02:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ignore antifungal resistance in fungal disease at your peril, warn top scientists</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240913003332.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Without immediate action, humanity will potentially face further escalation in resistance in fungal disease, a group of scientists from the around the...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 05:33:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Astronomers create first detailed map of sun's coronal magnetic fields</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/astronomers-create-first-detailed-map-suns-coronal-magnetic</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Researchers at the U.S. National Science Foundation National Solar Observatory have successfully mapped the magnetic fields of the sun's atmospheric c...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 15:08:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Huge gamma-ray burst collection 'rivals 250-year-old Messier catalog'</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240913003326.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Hundreds of gamma-ray bursts (GRBs) have been recorded as part of an enormous global effort so extensive it 'rivals the catalog of deep-sky objects cr...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 05:33:26 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>