<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 06:39:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Woolly mammoth chromosomes reconstructed using fossilized sample</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/woolly-mammoth-chromosomes-reconstructed</link><description>An international team of scientists assembled the woolly mammoth's genetic code using fossilized chromosomes from a 52,000-year-old carcass discovered in Siberian permafrost. The mammoth became freeze-dried on death, preserving the 3D structure of…</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 21:16:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Insight into one of life's earliest ancestors revealed in new study</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240712124116.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Researchers have shed light on Earth's earliest ecosystem, showing that within a few hundred million years of planetary formation, life on Earth was already flourishing.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 17:41:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF announces groundbreaking Leadership-Class Computing Facility project</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-groundbreaking-computing-facility</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has begun construction on the Leadership-Class Computing Facility (LCCF), a cutting-edge facility led by the Texas Advanced Computing Center (TACC) at The University of Texas at Austin (UT Austin) that will…</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How the 'heart and lungs' of a galaxy extend its life</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240712124039.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Galaxies avoid an early death because they have a 'heart and lungs' which effectively regulate their 'breathing' and prevent them growing out of control, a new study suggests. If they didn't, the universe would have aged much faster than it has and all we would see today is huge 'zombie' galaxies teeming with dead and dying stars. That's according to a new study that investigates one of the great mysteries of the Universe -- why galaxies are not as large as astronomers would expect.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 17:40:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF appoints Micah Cheatham as chief management officer</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-appoints-micah-cheatham-chief-management</link><description>Today, the U.S. National Science Foundation is pleased to announce the appointment of Micah Cheatham as chief management officer (CMO). In this role, Cheatham will serve as principal advisor to the NSF director and deputy director on agency…</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Forest carbon storage has declined across much of the Western U.S., likely due to drought and fire</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240711215622.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Forests have been embraced as a natural climate solution, due to their ability to soak up carbon dioxide from the atmosphere as they grow, locking it up in their trunks, branches, leaves, and roots. But a new study confirms widespread doubts about the potential for most forests in the Western US to help curb climate change. The paper analyzed trends in carbon storage across the American West from 2005 to 2019.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 02:56:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Transformers: Cooler side of the grid</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/transformers-cooler-side-grid</link><description>In a significant step towards resilient, sustainable energy, researchers at The University of Texas at Austin (UT Austin) are undertaking a groundbreaking initiative to enhance the performance and longevity of grid transformers, a critical component…</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:19:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'A history of contact': Geneticists are rewriting the narrative of Neanderthals and other ancient humans</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240711215541.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Using genomes from 2,000 living humans as well as three Neanderthals and one Denisovan, an international team mapped the gene flow between the hominin groups over the past quarter-million years.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 02:55:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Statement from NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan on the U.S. Economic Development Administration's Regional Technology and Innovation Hub awardees</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/statement-on-economic-development-admin-regional-tech-innovation</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation congratulates the U.S. Economic Development Administration (EDA) on its announcement today of its Regional Technology and Innovation Hubs (Tech Hubs). In alignment with the 'CHIPS and Science Act of 2022,' NSF and…</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A stealth fungus has decimated North American bats but scientists may be a step closer to treating white-nose syndrome</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240711215526.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>An invasive fungus that colonizes the skin of hibernating bats with deadly consequences is a stealthy invader that uses multiple strategies to slip into the small mammals' skin cells and quietly manipulate them to aid its own survival. The fungus, which causes the disease white-nose syndrome, has devastated several North American species over the last 18 years.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 02:55:26 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>