<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 11:36:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Studying cold fog in mountainous terrains</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/studying-cold-fog-mountainous-terrains</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>When air temperatures drop to 0 degrees Celsius or below, cold fog can form and disguise a landscape, posing challenges for drivers and pilots. Cold f...</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 21:02:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When the past meets the future: Innovative drone mapping unlocks secrets of Bronze Age 'mega fortress' in the Caucasus</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/01/250108144140.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>An academic has used drone mapping to investigate a 3000-year-old 'mega fortress' in the Caucasus mountains, revealing details that re-shape understan...</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 19:41:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists devise new method to detect permanent distortions in space-time left by massive supernova explosions</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/scientists-devise-new-method-detect-permanent-distortions</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Scientists have presented a new way to detect permanent distortions in the fabric of space-time predicted to be caused by certain supernovae explosion...</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 22:36:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF congratulates recipients of the prestigious National Medal of Science and National Medal of Technology and Innovation awards</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-congratulates-recipients-prestigious-national-medal</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>President Joe Biden revealed the newest honorees of the recipients of the National Medal of Science and the National Medal of Technology and Innovatio...</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 19:03:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paper-based sensors may lead to rapid detection of heart attacks</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/paper-based-sensors-may-lead-rapid-detection-heart-attacks</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>When individuals experience acute myocardial infarction, also known as a heart attack, time is precious. Detection and diagnosis of a heart attack hav...</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 17:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rethinking population management in zoos</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/01/250108144318.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Until now, contraception has been the method of choice for zoos to avoid surplus animals. Researchers are now calling for a paradigm shift: zoos could...</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 19:43:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>One of the youngest ever pilots takes the helm of a 60-year-old deep-sea exploring vehicle</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/one-youngest-ever-pilots-takes-helm-60-year-old-deep-sea</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>The Wood Holes Oceanographic Institution (WHOI) recently announced the newest human-occupied vehicle (HOV) Alvin pilot, Kaitlyn Beardshear. Beardshear...</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 14:07:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Electrohydraulic wearable devices create unprecedented haptic sensations</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/01/250108144220.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Scientists have invented compact wearable devices that deliver rich, expressive, and pleasant tactile sensations that go far beyond the buzzing vibrat...</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 19:42:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How deep sleep clears a mouse's mind, literally</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/01/250108143735.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>A good night's sleep does more than just help you feel rested--it might literally clear your mind. A new study shows how deep sleep may wash away wast...</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 19:37:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Evolutionary biology: Ants can hold a grudge</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/01/250108144025.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Evolutionary biologists are investigating the extent to which ants learn from past experiences. After being attacked by ants from a particular nest, a...</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 19:40:25 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>