<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 06:53:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Process by which COVID-19 latches onto and enters human cells is revealed</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/process-which-covid-19-latches-enters-human-cells</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>A team led by researchers with the U.S. National Science Foundation Physics Frontiers Center for Theoretical Biological Physics at Rice University have provided a new atomic-level understanding of how coronaviruses, including the virus that causes…</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 19:16:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ancient DNA reveals Indigenous dog lineages found at Jamestown, Virginia</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240816173937.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Previous scientific studies have indicated that North American dog lineages were replaced with European ones between 1492 and the present day. To better understand the timing of this replacement, researchers sequenced mitochondrial DNA from archaeological dogs. Their findings suggest a complex social history of dogs during the early colonial period.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 22:39:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tropical glaciers now smallest in 11,700 years, scientists find</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/tropical-glaciers-now-smallest-11700-years</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Tropical glaciers, which are especially at risk from climate warming, have melted rapidly in recent decades. The question, scientists say, is how much? Researchers funded by the U.S. National Science Foundation studied exposed bedrock at the edges of…</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 19:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tracking down the asteroid that sealed the fate of the dinosaurs</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240816123943.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>The asteroid that led to the extinction of the dinosaurs 66 million years ago probably came from the outer solar system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 17:39:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF invites K-12 students to design their own video games and compete for Game Maker Awards</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-invites-k-12-students-design-their-own-video</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation announces the NSF Game Maker Awards "Life in 2100" competition for K-12 students. To commemorate the agency’s milestone 75th anniversary, this competition invites students to create video games that imagine life…</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 15:10:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Right on schedule: Physicists use modeling to forecast a black hole's feeding patterns with precision</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240816121552.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>The dramatic dimming of a light source ~ 870 million light years away from Earth confirms the accuracy of a detailed model.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 17:15:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Studying the journey, not the destination, provides new insight into songbird migrations</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/studying-journey-into-songbird-migrations</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>New research supported by the U.S. National Science Foundation using two decades worth of data could change how scientists think about bird migrations and the interdependencies and relationships they involve. Driving any long distance usually…</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 20:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>It's a rave: Underground acoustics amplify soil health</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240816121531.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Barely audible to human ears, healthy soils produce a cacophony of sounds in many forms -- a bit like an underground rave concert of bubble pops and clicks. Special recordings made by ecologists show this chaotic mixture of soundscapes can be a measure of the diversity of tiny living animals in the soil, which create sounds as they move and interact with their environment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 17:15:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>This week, NSF marked the second anniversary of the "CHIPS and Science Act of 2022," signed into law on August 9, 2022. This landmark legislation has empowered NSF to accelerate innovation and build a resilient, inclusive, and productive American…</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:27:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rethinking the dodo</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240816121523.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Researchers are setting out to challenge our misconceptions about the Dodo, one of the most well-known but poorly understood species of bird. Researchers have undertaken the most comprehensive review of the taxonomy of the Dodo and its closest relative, the Rodriguez Island Solitaire.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 17:15:23 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>