<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 14:47:36 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>'Cells to Galaxies' unites astronomers, medical imaging experts to advance both fields</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/cells-galaxies-unites-astronomers</link><description>In May 2024, experts from the U.S. National Science Foundation National Radio Astronomy Observatory (NSF NRAO) and the medical imaging field presented at the International Society for Magnetic Resonance in Medicine conference on the surprising…</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 15:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Would astronauts' kidneys survive a roundtrip to Mars?</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240611130413.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>The structure and function of the kidneys is altered by space flight, with galactic radiation causing permanent damage that would jeopardise any mission to Mars, according to a new study led by researchers from UCL.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 18:04:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Synthetic platelets stanch bleeding, promote healing using advanced materials</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/synthetic-platelets-stanch-bleeding-promote-healing</link><description>A research team has developed synthetic platelets that can stop bleeding and enhance healing at the site of an injury. They demonstrated that the synthetic platelets work well in some animals but have not yet begun clinical trials in humans. The…</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 15:03:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trash-sorting robot mimics complex human sense of touch</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240611130406.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Researchers are breaking through the difficulties of robotic recognition of various common, yet complex, items. Their layered sensor is equipped with material detection at the surface and pressure sensitivity at the bottom, with a porous middle layer sensitive to thermal changes. An efficient cascade classification algorithm rules out object types in order, from easy to hard, starting with simple categories like empty cartons before moving on to orange peels or scraps of cloth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 18:04:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-54</link><description>NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan traveled to Interlaken, Switzerland, to join international partners for the Global Research Council's (GRC) annual meeting. GRC aims to promote long-term multilateral research and collaboration across continents…</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 20:32:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How did a satellite galaxy of the Milky Way come to be?</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240611130335.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Crater 2, located approximately 380,000 light years from Earth, is one of the largest satellite galaxies of the Milky Way. Extremely cold and with slow-moving stars, Crater 2 has low surface brightness. How this galaxy originated remains unclear. A team of physicists now offers an explanation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 18:03:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF enhances research security with new TRUST proposal assessment process</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-enhances-research-security-new-trust-proposal</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has announced a new risk mitigation process, the Trusted Research Using Safeguards and Transparency (TRUST) framework, which will guide the agency in assessing grant proposals for potential national security risks…</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 15:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lone Star State: Tracking a low-mass star as it speeds across the Milky Way</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240610171015.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Astronomers have discovered a rare hypervelocity L subdwarf star racing through the Milky Way. More remarkably, this star may be on a trajectory that causes it to leave the Milky Way altogether.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 22:10:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Widely used climate theory doesn't 'ring' true, according to new tree data</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/widely-used-climate-theory-doesnt-ring-true</link><description>New data on over 1,500 trees across nearly 1,000 sites shows that an existing theory of how individuals within a species will respond to a changing climate might not be true. The data, in the form of tree rings from an aridland pine, contradicts the…</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 21:00:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Brain's structure hangs in 'a delicate balance'</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240610170956.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Researchers examined anatomy of neurons from humans, mice and fruit flies. They discovered that the cellular structure of the brain is at a critical point, poised between two phases. New insights could help design computational models of the brain's complexity.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 22:09:56 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>