<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 15:28:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Widely used climate theory doesn't 'ring' true, according to new tree data</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/widely-used-climate-theory-doesnt-ring-true</link><description>New data on over 1,500 trees across nearly 1,000 sites shows that an existing theory of how individuals within a species will respond to a changing climate might not be true. The data, in the form of tree rings from an aridland pine, contradicts the…</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 21:00:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A technique for more effective multipurpose robots</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240603172233.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>MIT researchers developed a technique to combine robotics training data across domains, modalities, and tasks using generative AI models. They create a combined strategy from several different datasets that enables a robot to learn to perform new tasks in unseen environments.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 22:22:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF, NEH and partner funding agencies from seven countries announce the winners of the Canada-led 2023 International Joint Initiative for Research on Climate Change Adaptation and Mitigation competition</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-neh-partner-funding-agencies-seven-countries</link><description>Today, the U.S. National Science Foundation and the National Endowment of the Humanities (NEH) joined partner funding agencies from Brazil, Canada, Germany, Norway, South Africa, Switzerland and the United Kingdom in announcing the awardees for the…</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 16:15:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Altered carbon points toward sustainable manufacturing</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240603114419.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Researchers develop a vastly more productive way to convert carbon dioxide into useful materials and compounds.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 16:44:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mountain building linked to major extinction event half a billion years ago</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/mountain-building-linked-major-extinction-event</link><description>As life on Earth rapidly expanded a little over 500 million years ago during the "Cambrian explosion," Earth had tectonic plates slowly crashing into each other, building mountains and starting a series of unfortunate events that led to a mass…</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 22:57:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The embryo assembles itself</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240603114353.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Biological processes depend on puzzle pieces coming together and interacting. Under specific conditions, these interactions can create something new without external input. This is called self-organization, as seen in a school of fish or a flock of birds. Interestingly, the mammalian embryo develops similarly. Scientists now introduce a mathematical framework that analyzes self-organization from a single cell to a multicellular organism.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 16:43:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF and DOE partner on new internship opportunity in clean hydrogen energy</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-doe-partner-new-internship-opportunity-clean</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation and the Department of Energy, through its Office of Energy Efficiency and Renewable Energy (EERE), have initiated a joint training and professional development opportunity for NSF-supported graduate students in…</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 18:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Thawing permafrost: Not a climate tipping element, but nevertheless far-reaching impacts</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240603114326.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Permafrost soils store large quantities of organic carbon and are often portrayed as a critical tipping element in the Earth system, which, once global warming has reached a certain level, suddenly and globally collapses. Yet this image of a ticking timebomb, one that remains relatively quiet until, at a certain level of warming, it goes off, is a controversial one among the research community. Based on the scientific data currently available, the image is deceptive, as an international team has shown in a recently released study. According to their findings, there is no single global tipping point; rather, there are numerous local and regional ones, which 'tip' at different times, producing cumulative effects and causing the permafrost to thaw in step with climate change.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 16:43:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Climate change will make it harder to see the forest for the trees</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/climate-change-will-make-it-harder-see-forest</link><description>Individual trees can't move to escape climate change, and new U.S. National Science Foundation-supported research shows that species will be limited in their ability to migrate via seed dispersal and other methods because of a lack of symbiotic fungi…</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 14:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Groundbreaking progress in quantum physics: How quantum field theories decay and fission</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240603114324.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>An international research team has sparked interest in the scientific community with results in quantum physics. In their current study, the researchers reinterpret the Higgs mechanism, which gives elementary particles mass and triggers phase transitions, using the concept of 'magnetic quivers.'</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 16:43:24 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>