<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:39:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-54</link><description>NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan traveled to Interlaken, Switzerland, to join international partners for the Global Research Council's (GRC) annual meeting. GRC aims to promote long-term multilateral research and collaboration across continents…</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 20:32:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oral insulin drops offer relief for diabetes patients</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240605162742.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Diabetes rates continue to rise. Scientists have now created a pain-free drug delivery method to help people with diabetes manage the disease and maintain their health more easily. Researchers have developed oral insulin drops that when placed under the tongue are quickly and efficiently absorbed by the body, potentially replacing the need for insulin injections.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 21:27:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF enhances research security with new TRUST proposal assessment process</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-enhances-research-security-new-trust-proposal</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has announced a new risk mitigation process, the Trusted Research Using Safeguards and Transparency (TRUST) framework, which will guide the agency in assessing grant proposals for potential national security risks…</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 15:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AIs are irrational, but not in the same way that humans are</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240605162628.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Large Language Models behind popular generative AI platforms like ChatGPT gave different answers when asked to respond to the same reasoning test and didn't improve when given additional context, finds a new study.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 21:26:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Widely used climate theory doesn't 'ring' true, according to new tree data</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/widely-used-climate-theory-doesnt-ring-true</link><description>New data on over 1,500 trees across nearly 1,000 sites shows that an existing theory of how individuals within a species will respond to a changing climate might not be true. The data, in the form of tree rings from an aridland pine, contradicts the…</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 21:00:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blood sausages and yak milk: Bronze Age cuisine of Mongolian nomads unveiled</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240605162547.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Bronze cauldrons were used by the inhabitants of the Mongolian steppe around 2,700 years ago to process animal blood and milk. This is shown by a protein analysis of archaeological finds from this period.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 21:25:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF, NEH and partner funding agencies from seven countries announce the winners of the Canada-led 2023 International Joint Initiative for Research on Climate Change Adaptation and Mitigation competition</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-neh-partner-funding-agencies-seven-countries</link><description>Today, the U.S. National Science Foundation and the National Endowment of the Humanities (NEH) joined partner funding agencies from Brazil, Canada, Germany, Norway, South Africa, Switzerland and the United Kingdom in announcing the awardees for the…</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 16:15:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Poor quality diet makes our brains sad</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240605162519.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Eating a poor quality diet might lead to brain changes that are associated with depression and anxiety. This is according to a first-of-its-kind study into the brain chemistry and structure, and diet quality of 30 volunteers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 21:25:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mountain building linked to major extinction event half a billion years ago</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/mountain-building-linked-major-extinction-event</link><description>As life on Earth rapidly expanded a little over 500 million years ago during the "Cambrian explosion," Earth had tectonic plates slowly crashing into each other, building mountains and starting a series of unfortunate events that led to a mass…</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 22:57:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI approach elevates plasma performance and stability across fusion devices</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240605162441.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Fusion researchers have successfully deployed machine learning methods to suppress harmful plasma edge instabilities without sacrificing plasma performance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 21:24:41 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>