<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 09:53:40 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-66</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>This week, NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan engaged in discussions and announcements that underscored the agency's commitment to advancing researc...</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 20:30:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mars' missing atmosphere could be hiding in plain sight</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240925143940.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>New research suggests Mars' missing atmosphere -- which dramatically diminished 3.5 billion years ago -- could be locked in the planet's clay-covered ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 19:39:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Single-dose gene therapy is potentially life-changing for adults with hemophilia B</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240925172115.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Adults with hemophilia B saw their number of bleeding episodes drop by an average of 71 percent after a single infusion of gene therapy, according to ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 22:21:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Drone footage provides new insight into gray whales' acrobatic feeding behavior</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240925143959.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Drone footage is offering new insight into the acrobatics undertaken by gray whales foraging in the waters off the coast of Oregon.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 19:39:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A renovated aircraft for atmospheric sciences is ready for action</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/renovated-aircraft-atmospheric-sciences-ready-action</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>The newly updated U.S. National Science Foundation (NSF) University of Wyoming (UW) King Air Research Aircraft (King Air) is set to fly its first rese...</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 21:00:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>5 areas where NSF funding is enhancing undergraduate STEM participation at Hispanic-serving institutions</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/5-areas-where-nsf-funding-enhancing-undergraduate-stem</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>In the U.S., just over 21% of the undergraduate student body identified as Hispanic in 2021. Nearly 63% of those students were enrolled at Hispanic-se...</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 14:27:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Brazilian fossils reveal jaw-dropping discovery in mammal evolution</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240925123653.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>The discovery of new cynodont fossils from southern Brazil by a team of palaeontologists has led to a significant breakthrough in understanding the ev...</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 17:36:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF and philanthropic partners invest more than $18M to prioritize ethical and societal considerations in the creation of emerging technologies</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-philanthropic-partners-invest-more-18m-prioritize</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation announced an inaugural investment of more than $18 million to 44 multidisciplinary, multi-sector teams across the...</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 19:03:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How special is the Milky Way Galaxy?</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240925144014.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>The SAGA Survey just published three new research articles that provide us with new insights into the uniqueness of our own Milky Way Galaxy after com...</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 19:40:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What tiny marine organisms eat can affect how the deep ocean stores carbon</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/what-tiny-marine-organisms-eat-can-affect-how-deep-ocean</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>The dietary preferences of bacteria that eat organic molecules called lipids can affect how carbon dioxide from the ocean's surface moves to the deep ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 14:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>