<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 12:03:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>A new film on baffling Baffin Bay</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/new-film-baffling-baffin-bay</link><description>A new NSF-supported documentary follows the Baffin Bay Deglacial Experiment team on its journey to investigate what happened to the Greenland Ice Sheet over 15,000 years ago Although scientists know that the Earth has seen major climate changes from…</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 22:24:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Organic material from Mars reveals the likely origin of life's building blocks</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240701232841.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Two samples from Mars together deliver clear evidence of the origin of Martian organic material. The study presents solid evidence for a prediction made over a decade ago that could be key to understanding how organic molecules, the foundation of life, were first formed here on Earth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 04:28:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deep-sea discovery opens up ocean of potential</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/deep-sea-discovery-opens-ocean-potential</link><description>New research by U.S. National Science Foundation-funded scientists making use of NSF facilities has provided insight into how related ocean creatures have adapted to live in vastly different environments. The study may also provide new knowledge…</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 20:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A prosthesis driven by the nervous system helps people with amputation walk naturally</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240701162227.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>With a new surgical intervention and neuroprosthetic interface, researchers restored a natural walking gait in people with amputations below the knee. Seven patients were able to walk faster, avoid obstacles, and climb stairs more naturally than people with a traditional amputation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:22:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF awards $35M for networks to transform research capacity and competitiveness</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-awards-35m-networks-transform-research</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has awarded $35 million through the Established Program to Stimulate Competitive Research (EPSCoR) Research Incubators for STEM Excellence Research Infrastructure Improvement (E-RISE RII) to boost research…</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New and improved camera inspired by the human eye</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240701162221.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Computer scientists have invented a camera mechanism that improves how robots see and react to the world around them. Inspired by how the human eye works, their innovative camera system mimics the tiny involuntary movements used by the eye to maintain clear and stable vision over time.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:22:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF launches new investment to accelerate the transition of privacy-enhancing technologies to practice</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-launches-new-investment-accelerate-transition</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation yesterday published a new investment to advance privacy-enhancing technologies (PETs) and promote their use to solve real-world problems. The Privacy-Preserving Data Sharing in Practice (PDaSP) program, which…</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 15:20:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Self-assembling, highly conductive sensors could improve wearable devices</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240701162218.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>To advance soft robotics, skin-integrated electronics and biomedical devices, researchers have developed a 3D-printed material that is soft and stretchable -- traits needed for matching the properties of tissues and organs -- and that self-assembles. Their approach employs a process that eliminates many drawbacks of previous fabrication methods, such as less conductivity or device failure, the team said.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:22:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Physicists create first-ever Bose-Einstein condensate made of molecules</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/physicists-create-first-ever-bose-einstein</link><description>A team of physicists has successfully created a unique quantum state of matter called a Bose-Einstein condensate (BEC) out of molecules. The team is led by Sebastian Will at Columbia University, who received a U.S. National Science Foundation Faculty…</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 20:53:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dampening the 'seeds' of hurricanes</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240701162212.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Increased atmospheric moisture may alter critical weather patterns over Africa, making it more difficult for the predecessors of many Atlantic hurricanes to form, according to a new study.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:22:12 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>