<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:50:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NSF and USDA join forces to boost innovation in agricultural robotics</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-usda-join-forces-boost-innovation-agricultural</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation and the U.S. Department of Agriculture's National Institute of Food and Agriculture (USDA NIFA) are teaming up to advance foundational research in agricultural robotics. The agencies are issuing a new Dear…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Human activities have an intense impact on Earth's deep subsurface fluid flow</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/04/240424182458.htm</link><description>Hydrologists predict human-induced underground fluid fluxes to rise with climate change mitigation strategies like carbon sequestration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 23:24:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New center supported by NSF will catalyze data-driven insights in molecular and cellular biosciences</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/new-center-supported-nsf-will-catalyze-data-driven</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has made a $20 million award to support the creation of the National Synthesis Center for Emergence in the Molecular and Cellular Sciences (NCEMS). The center will combine vast amounts of available data on…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 14:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Holographic displays offer a glimpse into an immersive future</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/04/240424111558.htm</link><description>Researchers have invented a new optical element that brings us one step closer to mixing the real and virtual worlds in an ordinary pair of eyeglasses using high-definition 3D holographic images.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:15:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF honors 3 outstanding early-career researchers with the Alan T. Waterman Award</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-honors-3-outstanding-early-career-researchers</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation honored three researchers with the Alan T. Waterman Award, the nation's highest honor for early-career scientists and engineers. The 2024 recipients: Muyinatu A. Lediju Bell, a biomedical engineer at Johns Hopkins…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This salt battery harvests osmotic energy where the river meets the sea</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/04/240424111549.htm</link><description>Estuaries -- where freshwater rivers meet the salty sea -- are great locations for birdwatching and kayaking. In these areas, waters containing different salt concentrations mix and may be sources of sustainable, 'blue' osmotic energy. Researchers report creating a semipermeable membrane that harvests osmotic energy from salt gradients and converts it to electricity. The new design had an output power density more than two times higher than commercial membranes in lab demonstrations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:15:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF invests $90M in innovative national scientific cyberinfrastructure for transforming STEM education</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-invests-90m-innovative-national-scientific</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation announced today a strategic investment of $90 million over five years in SafeInsights, a unique national scientific cyberinfrastructure aimed at transforming learning research and STEM education. Funded through…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:30:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Making diamonds at ambient pressure</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/04/240424111504.htm</link><description>Researchers have grown diamonds under conditions of 1 atmosphere pressure and at 1025 degrees Celsius using a liquid metal alloy composed of gallium, iron, nickel, and silicon, thus breaking the existing paradigm. The discovery of this new growth method opens many possibilities for further basic science studies and for scaling up the growth of diamonds in new ways.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:15:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-49</link><description>This week, US National Science Foundation Director worked to strengthen pathways into STEM and expand the agency’s reach in communities across the nation and world. At the Arctic Encounter Symposium, Director Panchanathan took center stage alongside…</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 20:37:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eruption of mega-magnetic star lights up nearby galaxy</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/04/240424111501.htm</link><description>While ESA's satellite INTEGRAL was observing the sky, it spotted a burst of gamma-rays -- high-energy photons -- coming from the nearby galaxy M82. Only a few hours later, ESA's XMM-Newton X-ray space telescope searched for an afterglow from the explosion but found none. An international team realized that the burst must have been an extra-galactic flare from a magnetar, a young neutron star with an exceptionally strong magnetic field.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:15:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>