<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 06:58:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Widely used climate theory doesn't 'ring' true, according to new tree data</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/widely-used-climate-theory-doesnt-ring-true</link><description>New data on over 1,500 trees across nearly 1,000 sites shows that an existing theory of how individuals within a species will respond to a changing climate might not be true. The data, in the form of tree rings from an aridland pine, contradicts the…</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 21:00:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Giant viruses found on Greenland ice sheet</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240604184205.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Giant viruses found on the Greenland ice sheet probably regulate the growth of snow algae on the ice by infecting them. Knowing how to control these viruses could help us reduce the rate of ice-melt.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 23:42:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF, NEH and partner funding agencies from seven countries announce the winners of the Canada-led 2023 International Joint Initiative for Research on Climate Change Adaptation and Mitigation competition</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-neh-partner-funding-agencies-seven-countries</link><description>Today, the U.S. National Science Foundation and the National Endowment of the Humanities (NEH) joined partner funding agencies from Brazil, Canada, Germany, Norway, South Africa, Switzerland and the United Kingdom in announcing the awardees for the…</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 16:15:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Using AI to decode dog vocalizations</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240604132204.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Have you ever wished you could understand what your dog is trying to say to you? Researchers are exploring the possibilities of AI, developing tools that can identify whether a dog's bark conveys playfulness or aggression.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 18:22:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mountain building linked to major extinction event half a billion years ago</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/mountain-building-linked-major-extinction-event</link><description>As life on Earth rapidly expanded a little over 500 million years ago during the "Cambrian explosion," Earth had tectonic plates slowly crashing into each other, building mountains and starting a series of unfortunate events that led to a mass…</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 22:57:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Human activity contributed to woolly rhinoceros' extinction</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240604132202.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Researchers have discovered sustained hunting by humans prevented the woolly rhinoceros from accessing favourable habitats as Earth warmed following the Last Ice Age.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 18:22:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF and DOE partner on new internship opportunity in clean hydrogen energy</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-doe-partner-new-internship-opportunity-clean</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation and the Department of Energy, through its Office of Energy Efficiency and Renewable Energy (EERE), have initiated a joint training and professional development opportunity for NSF-supported graduate students in…</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 18:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summer droughts in Northern hemisphere increasingly likely as seasonal streamflows change</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240604132128.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Declining snowfall is changing the seasonal patterns of streamflow throughout the Northern hemisphere boosting chances of water shortages in the summer, scientists have found.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 18:21:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Climate change will make it harder to see the forest for the trees</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/climate-change-will-make-it-harder-see-forest</link><description>Individual trees can't move to escape climate change, and new U.S. National Science Foundation-supported research shows that species will be limited in their ability to migrate via seed dispersal and other methods because of a lack of symbiotic fungi…</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 14:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Some countries could meet their total electricity needs from floating solar panels</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240604132107.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Floating solar photovoltaic panels could supply all the electricity needs of some countries, new research has shown. The researchers calculated the daily electrical output for floating photovoltaics (FPV) on nearly 68,000 lakes and reservoirs around the world, using available climate data for each location.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 18:21:07 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>