<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:43:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NSF announces groundbreaking Leadership-Class Computing Facility project</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-groundbreaking-computing-facility</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has begun construction on the Leadership-Class Computing Facility (LCCF), a cutting-edge facility led by the Texas Advanced Computing Center (TACC) at The University of Texas at Austin (UT Austin) that will…</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hydrogen flight looks ready for take-off with new advances</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240711111519.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>The possibility of hydrogen-powered flight means greater opportunities for fossil-free travel, and the technological advances to make this happen are moving fast. New studies show that almost all air travel within a 750-mile radius (1200 km) could be made with hydrogen-powered aircraft by 2045, and with a novel heat exchanger currently in development, this range could be even further.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:15:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF appoints Micah Cheatham as chief management officer</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-appoints-micah-cheatham-chief-management</link><description>Today, the U.S. National Science Foundation is pleased to announce the appointment of Micah Cheatham as chief management officer (CMO). In this role, Cheatham will serve as principal advisor to the NSF director and deputy director on agency…</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dark matter in dwarf galaxy tracked using stellar motions</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240711111354.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>The qualities and behavior of dark matter, the invisible 'glue' of the universe, continue to be shrouded in mystery. Though galaxies are mostly made of dark matter, understanding how it is distributed within a galaxy offers clues to what this substance is, and how it's relevant to a galaxy's evolution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:13:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Transformers: Cooler side of the grid</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/transformers-cooler-side-grid</link><description>In a significant step towards resilient, sustainable energy, researchers at The University of Texas at Austin (UT Austin) are undertaking a groundbreaking initiative to enhance the performance and longevity of grid transformers, a critical component…</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:19:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>First ever 3D reconstruction of 52,000-year-old woolly mammoth chromosomes thanks to serendipitously freeze-dried skin</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240711111343.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>An international research team has assembled the genome and 3D chromosomal structures of a 52,000-year-old woolly mammoth -- the first time such a feat has been achieved for any ancient DNA sample. The fossilized chromosomes, which are around a million times longer than most ancient DNA fragments, provide insight into how the mammoth's genome was organized within its living cells and which genes were active within the skin tissue from which the DNA was extracted. This unprecedented level of structural detail was retained because the mammoth underwent freeze-drying shortly after it died, which meant that its DNA was preserved in a glass-like state.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:13:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Statement from NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan on the U.S. Economic Development Administration's Regional Technology and Innovation Hub awardees</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/statement-on-economic-development-admin-regional-tech-innovation</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation congratulates the U.S. Economic Development Administration (EDA) on its announcement today of its Regional Technology and Innovation Hubs (Tech Hubs). In alignment with the 'CHIPS and Science Act of 2022,' NSF and…</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Creativity starts in the cradle, new research shows</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240710195507.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>New research indicates that babies can begin grasping complex language and ideas.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 00:55:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Physicists' laser experiment excites atom's nucleus, may enable new type of atomic clock</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/physicists-laser-experiment-excites-atoms-nucleus</link><description>A team of researchers successfully raised the energy state of an atom's nucleus with a laser, which could lead to new precision measurement technology with orders of magnitude higher accuracy than today's best atomic clocks. The researchers embedded…</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 16:57:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A new species of extinct crocodile relative rewrites life on the Triassic coastline</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240710195436.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>The surprising discovery of a new species of extinct crocodile relative from the Triassic Favret Formation of Nevada, USA, rewrites the story of life along the coasts during the first act of the Age of Dinosaurs. The new species Benggwigwishingasuchus eremicarminis reveals that while giant ichthyosaurs ruled the oceans, the ancient crocodile kin known as pseudosuchian archosaurs ruled the shores across the Middle Triassic globe between 247.2 and 237 million years ago.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 00:54:36 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>