<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 06:40:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>5 areas where NSF funding is enhancing undergraduate STEM participation at Hispanic-serving institutions</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/5-areas-where-nsf-funding-enhancing-undergraduate-stem</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In the U.S., just over 21% of the undergraduate student body identified as Hispanic in 2021. Nearly 63% of those students were enrolled at Hispanic-se...</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 14:27:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Long ago, but not so different</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/long-ago-not-so-different</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>In a new study, a team of U.S. National Science Foundation-supported researchers suggests that 4 billion years ago, plate tectonics likely looked clos...</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 14:53:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists design new drug to fight malaria</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240926144907.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>A team has designed a new drug against malaria and identified its mechanism of action.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 19:49:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How are pronouns processed in the memory-region of our brain?</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240927173201.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>A new study shows how individual brain cells in the hippocampus respond to pronouns. 'This may help us unravel how we remember what we read.'</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 22:32:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF and Quad partners launch AI-ENGAGE to encourage collaboration on emerging technologies and agriculture</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-quad-partners-launch-ai-engage-encourage-collaboration</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation, Japan Science and Technology Agency (JST), Indian Council of Agricultural Research (ICAR), and Commonwealth Scie...</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 17:50:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Researchers discover new bacterium that causes gut immunodeficiency</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240926144904.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Researchers have discovered a new bacterium that weakens the immune system in the gut, potentially contributing to certain inflammatory and infectious...</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 19:49:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Babies born after fertility treatment have higher risk of heart defects, study suggests</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240927173121.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>The risk of being born with a major heart defect is 36% higher in babies who were conceived after assisted reproductive technology, such as in vitro f...</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 22:31:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF partners with the U.S. Department of Education to improve outcomes in elementary science education</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-partners-us-department-education-improve-outcomes</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation is providing half of $15 million in funding to establish the new Center for Advancing Elementary Science through ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 18:35:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>U.S. National Science Foundation and Department of Commerce announce a new $30M funding opportunity, funded by the CHIPS &amp; Science Act, to prepare talent for semiconductor jobs nationwide</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-department-commerce-announce-30m-funding-opportunity</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>The Network Coordination Hub for the National Network for Microelectronics Education will establish and operate regional nodes to offer consistent, ri...</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 20:42:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Return of the elephants seals: From a few to thousands</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240927173545.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>A new international study has revealed the genetic impact of hunting in northern elephant seals. The research shows that this species narrowly escaped...</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 22:35:45 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>