<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 06:58:36 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NSF-backed SECURE Center will support research security, international collaboration</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-backed-secure-center-will-support-research</link><description>Today, the U.S. National Science Foundation announced a five-year $67 million investment establishing the Safeguarding the Entire Community of the U.S. Research Ecosystem (SECURE) ($50 million to University of Washington and $17 million to Texas A&amp;M…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 11:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Drawing water from dry air</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240723182005.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>A prototype device harvests drinking water from the atmosphere, even in arid places.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 23:20:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When lightning strikes, check for wind turbines</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/when-lightning-strikes-check-wind-turbines</link><description>Minutes after lightning lit the dark evening sky in the middle of a blizzard, a team of seven students and researchers rapidly unzipped a bright yellow bag the size of a small car to release a giant white balloon. This daring feat was part of a U.S…</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 19:15:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>3D-printed microstructure forest facilitates solar steam generator desalination</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240723123507.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Faced with the world's impending freshwater scarcity, researchers turned to solar steam generators, which are emerging as a promising device for seawater desalination. The team sought design inspiration from trees and harnessed the potential of 3D printing. They present technology for producing efficient SSGs for desalination and introduces a novel method for printing functional nanocomposites for multi-jet fusion. Their SSGs were inspired by plant transpiration and are composed of miniature tree-shaped microstructures, forming an efficient, heat-distributing forest.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 17:35:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF announces new AI test beds initiative to advance safety and security of AI technologies</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-new-ai-test-beds-initiative-advance</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation announces the launch of a new initiative that will invest in the development of artificial intelligence-ready test beds, a critical infrastructure designed to propel responsible AI research and innovation forward…</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 18:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Astrophysicists uncover supermassive blackhole/dark matter connection in solving the 'final parsec problem'</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240722175905.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Researchers have found a link between some of the largest and smallest objects in the cosmos: supermassive black holes and dark matter particles. Their new calculations reveal that pairs of supermassive black holes (SMBHs) can merge into a single larger black hole because of previously overlooked behavior of dark matter particles, proposing a solution to the longstanding 'final parsec problem' in astronomy.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 22:59:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF announces $77.8M investment to build climate resilience capacity across 21 EPSCoR jurisdictions</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-77-8m-investment-build-epscor</link><description>Today, the U.S. National Science Foundation announced a $77.8 million investment in 14 projects through the Established Program to Stimulate Competitive Research (EPSCoR). Spanning 50 institutions across 21 jurisdictions, this investment aims to…</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 16:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Converting captured carbon to fuel: Study assesses what's practical and what's not</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240722155154.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>A new analysis sheds light on major shortfalls of a recently proposed approach to capture CO2 from air and directly convert it to fuel using electricity. The authors also provide a new, more sustainable, alternative.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 20:51:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF awards inaugural TRAILBLAZER grants for groundbreaking engineering ideas</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-awards-inaugural-trailblazer-grants</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has announced the first grants in its Trailblazer Engineering Impact Award (TRAILBLAZER) program, a new $18-million activity to enable researchers with established records of creativity and paradigm-shifting…</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 14:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Breakthrough in skeletal muscle regeneration</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240722155152.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>In a finding that opens the door to the development of targeted therapies for various muscle disorders, newly published research identifies key mechanisms of skeletal muscle regeneration and growth of muscles following resistance exercise.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 20:51:52 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>