<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:01:36 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Most distant supernova: James Webb sees a star explode at cosmic dawn</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/12/251228074453.htm</link><image>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image><description>Scientists have detected the most distant supernova ever seen, exploding when the universe was less than a billion years old. The event was first sign...</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:27:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The deep ocean has a missing link and scientists finally found it</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/12/251228074505.htm</link><image>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image><description>Scientists have uncovered why big predators like sharks spend so much time in the ocean’s twilight zone. The answer lies with mid-sized fish such as t...</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 13:41:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mini brains reveal clear brain signals of schizophrenia and bipolar disorder</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/12/251228074451.htm</link><image>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image><description>Tiny lab-grown brains are offering an unprecedented look at how schizophrenia and bipolar disorder disrupt neural activity. Researchers found distinct...</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 12:44:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ancient wolves could only have reached this island by boat</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/12/251227004151.htm</link><image>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image><description>Scientists have uncovered ancient wolf remains on a small Baltic island where wolves could only have been brought by humans. These animals weren’t dog...</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:44:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mars dust storms are crackling with electricity</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/12/251226045319.htm</link><image>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image><description>Mars isn’t just dusty—it crackles with electricity. Scientists discovered that dust devils can generate tiny electric sparks, captured for the first t...</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:42:05 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>