<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 07:16:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Saturn's moon Titan could harbor life, but only a tiny amount, study finds</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/04/250407172910.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Despite its uniquely rich inventory of organic molecules, Saturn's largest moon, Titan, may be able to support only a minuscule amount of biomass, if ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 22:29:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tiny lenses grown from bacteria and enzymes may help doctors see inside cells</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/tiny-lenses-grown-bacteria-enzymes-may-help-doctors-see</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>A team of researchers supported by the U.S. National Science Foundation has successfully made self-growing microlenses using bacteria and enzymes foun...</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 21:44:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Researchers use AI to improve diagnosis of drug-resistant infections</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/04/250407173027.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Scientists have developed an artificial intelligence-based method to more accurately detect antibiotic resistance in deadly bacteria such as tuberculo...</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 22:30:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Researchers discover why plastic sheds dangerous fragments</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/04/250407172923.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>The world is littered with trillions of micro- and nanoscopic pieces of plastic. These can be smaller than a virus -- just the right size to disrupt c...</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 22:29:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The lush past of the world's largest desert</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/04/250407114252.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>The vast desert of the Arabian Peninsula was not always an arid landscape. A recent study reveals that this region was once home to a vast lake and ri...</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 16:42:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chatbot opens computational chemistry to nonexperts</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/04/250407172921.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>A web platform uses a chatbot to enable any chemist -- including undergraduate chemistry majors -- to configure and execute complex quantum mechanical...</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 22:29:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Conserving the White Oak Tree: Critical for timber and distilling industries</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/conserving-white-oak-tree-critical-timber-distilling</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>A group of researchers from the University of Kentucky, The University of Tennessee and Indiana University, including those supported by the U.S. Nati...</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ultrathin conductor developed for nanoelectronics could be better than copper</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/ultrathin-conductor-developed-nanoelectronics-could-be</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>With multiple grants and research infrastructure provided by the U.S. National Science Foundation, researchers have shown that a newly developed mater...</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 18:25:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chainmail-like polymer could be the future of body armor</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/chainmail-polymer-could-be-future-body-armor</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Researchers supported by grants and instrumentation provided by the U.S. National Science Foundation have created the first 2D polymer material that m...</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 19:34:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New method to keep protein-based drugs stable without refrigeration</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/new-method-keep-protein-based-drugs-stable-without</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>A team of researchers led by the recipient of a U.S. National Science Foundation Faculty Early Career Development grant has developed a new storage me...</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 16:28:30 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>