<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 16:15:33 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Cloudy with a chance of climate predictions</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/cloudy-chance-climate-predictions</link><description>Whether they're fluffy, bright or ominous, clouds are key to regulating Earth's energy and water cycles. Two sets of U.S. National Science Foundation-supported researchers recently published findings to help scientists better understand what's…</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 21:15:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paleontology: New fossil fish genus discovered</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240613140915.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Paleontologists have identified a new genus of fossil goby, revealing evolutionary secrets of a lineage that stretches back millions of years.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 19:09:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Cells to Galaxies' unites astronomers, medical imaging experts to advance both fields</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/cells-galaxies-unites-astronomers</link><description>In May 2024, experts from the U.S. National Science Foundation National Radio Astronomy Observatory (NSF NRAO) and the medical imaging field presented at the International Society for Magnetic Resonance in Medicine conference on the surprising…</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 15:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>6,000 years ago, men and women had equal access to resources</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240613140756.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Using isotope geochemistry, scientists have uncovered new information about the Barmaz necropolis in Valais (Switzerland): 14% of the people buried 6,000 years ago at this site were not locals. What's more, the study suggests that this Middle Neolithic agropastoral society -- one of the oldest known in the western part of Switzerland -- was relatively egalitarian. The isotope ratios of carbon, nitrogen and sulphur contained in the bones reveal that all members of the community, including people from elsewhere, had access to the same food resources.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 19:07:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Synthetic platelets stanch bleeding, promote healing using advanced materials</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/synthetic-platelets-stanch-bleeding-promote-healing</link><description>A research team has developed synthetic platelets that can stop bleeding and enhance healing at the site of an injury. They demonstrated that the synthetic platelets work well in some animals but have not yet begun clinical trials in humans. The…</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 15:03:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ancient ocean slowdown warns of future climate chaos</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240613140748.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>When it comes to the ocean's response to global warming, we're not in entirely uncharted waters. A new study shows that episodes of extreme heat in Earth's past caused the exchange of waters from the surface to the deep ocean to decline.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 19:07:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-54</link><description>NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan traveled to Interlaken, Switzerland, to join international partners for the Global Research Council's (GRC) annual meeting. GRC aims to promote long-term multilateral research and collaboration across continents…</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 20:32:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nanosized blocks spontaneously assemble in water to create tiny floating checkerboards</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240613140320.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Researchers have engineered nanosized cubes that spontaneously form a two-dimensional checkerboard pattern when dropped on the surface of water. The work presents a simple approach to create complex nanostructures through a technique called self-assembly.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 19:03:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF enhances research security with new TRUST proposal assessment process</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-enhances-research-security-new-trust-proposal</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has announced a new risk mitigation process, the Trusted Research Using Safeguards and Transparency (TRUST) framework, which will guide the agency in assessing grant proposals for potential national security risks…</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 15:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dolphins with elevated mercury levels in Florida and Georgia</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240613140133.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Scientists found elevated mercury levels in dolphins in the U.S. Southeast. The highest levels were found in dolphins in Florida's St. Joseph and Choctawhatchee Bays. Researchers study dolphins because they are considered a sentinel species for oceans and human health. Like us, they are high up in the food chain, live long lives, and share certain physiological traits. Some of their diet is most vulnerable to mercury pollution and is also eaten by people.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 19:01:33 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>