<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 01:28:08 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Long ago, but not so different</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/long-ago-not-so-different</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In a new study, a team of U.S. National Science Foundation-supported researchers suggests that 4 billion years ago, plate tectonics likely looked clos...</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 14:53:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>5 areas where NSF funding is enhancing undergraduate STEM participation at Hispanic-serving institutions</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/5-areas-where-nsf-funding-enhancing-undergraduate-stem</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>In the U.S., just over 21% of the undergraduate student body identified as Hispanic in 2021. Nearly 63% of those students were enrolled at Hispanic-se...</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 14:27:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>U.S. National Science Foundation and Department of Commerce announce a new $30M funding opportunity, funded by the CHIPS &amp; Science Act, to prepare talent for semiconductor jobs nationwide</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-department-commerce-announce-30m-funding-opportunity</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>The Network Coordination Hub for the National Network for Microelectronics Education will establish and operate regional nodes to offer consistent, ri...</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 20:42:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>These fish use legs to taste the seafloor</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240926132111.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Sea robins are unusual animals with the body of a fish, wings of a bird, and walking legs of a crab. Now, researchers show that the legs of the sea ro...</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 18:21:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF and Quad partners launch AI-ENGAGE to encourage collaboration on emerging technologies and agriculture</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-quad-partners-launch-ai-engage-encourage-collaboration</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation, Japan Science and Technology Agency (JST), Indian Council of Agricultural Research (ICAR), and Commonwealth Scie...</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 17:50:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Weekend warrior' physical activity may help protect against more than 200 diseases</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240926132037.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Compared with inactivity, a weekend warrior pattern of exercise (concentrating most moderate-to-vigorous physical activity in one to two days during t...</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 18:20:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A method of 'look twice, forgive once' can sustain social cooperation</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240926132048.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Using mathematical modeling, researchers found a way to maintain cooperation without relying on complex norms or institutions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 18:20:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF partners with the U.S. Department of Education to improve outcomes in elementary science education</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-partners-us-department-education-improve-outcomes</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation is providing half of $15 million in funding to establish the new Center for Advancing Elementary Science through ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 18:35:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This rocky planet around a white dwarf resembles Earth -- 8 billion years from now</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240926132019.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>A 2020 microlensing event was caused by a planetary system with an Earth-like planet and brown dwarf. The star type was uncertain. The team has determ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 18:20:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists design new drug to fight malaria</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240926144907.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>A team has designed a new drug against malaria and identified its mechanism of action.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 19:49:07 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>