<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 10:58:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Scientists just mapped how the body rejects pig organs—and how to stop it</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/06/250630073445.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Scientists have achieved an unprecedented look into how the human immune system attacks a transplanted pig kidney, using spatial molecular imaging to ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 06:10:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Citizen scientists spot rare exploding star in real-time</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/07/250701030209.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Citizen scientists using the Kilonova Seekers platform spotted a stellar flash 2,500 times brighter than before, allowing astronomers to identify the ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 09:24:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ancient DNA reveals leprosy hit the Americas long before colonization</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/06/250630073438.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Leprosy’s tale stretches from 5,000-year-old skeletons in Eurasia to a startling 4,000-year-old case in Chile, revealing that the rare strain Mycobact...</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 13:07:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JWST unlocks 10-billion-year mystery of how galaxies shape themselves</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/06/250629033347.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Using the James Webb Space Telescope, scientists spotted thin and thick disks in galaxies as far back as 10 billion years ago—something never seen bef...</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 11:43:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists just found a sugar switch that protects your brain from Alzheimer's</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/06/250630073442.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Scientists have uncovered a surprising sugar-related mechanism inside brain cells that could transform how we fight Alzheimer’s and other dementias. I...</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 15:04:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chemical process more efficiently converts carbon dioxide to methanol, a chemical used in manufacturing and a potential fuel</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/chemical-process-more-efficiently-converts-carbon-dioxide</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>A new chemical process funded by the U.S. National Science Foundation has produced methanol — a type of alcohol essential for manufacturing many commo...</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 14:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Superconducting material stabilized at everyday pressure, another step toward real-world applications</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/superconducting-material-stabilized-everyday-pressure</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>U.S. National Science Foundation-funded researchers have stabilized a composite material in a superconducting state at ambient or normal, everyday pre...</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 15:19:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF invests $25.5M in research to drive new U.S. manufacturing technologies and talent pipelines</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-invests-255m-research-drive-new-us-manufacturing</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has announced a $25.5 million investment to support fundamental research and workforce development aimed at enabl...</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 15:07:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF Graduate Research Fellow's work on light contributes to nanodot breakthrough</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-graduate-research-fellows-work-light-contributes-nanodot</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Americans spend a lot of time on their screens. The images on those screens are made of pixels — tiny dots that represent a single point of color. Sci...</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 13:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ever-changing universe revealed in first imagery from NSF-DOE Vera C. Rubin Observatory</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/first-imagery-nsf-doe-vera-c-rubin-observatory</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>The NSF-DOE Vera C. Rubin Observatory, a major new scientific facility jointly funded by the U.S. National Science Foundation and the U.S. Department ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 16:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>