<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 07:24:39 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Scientists discover which parts of the Amazon rainforest are most vulnerable to drought</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/scientists-discover-which-parts-amazon-rainforest</link><description>Regions of the Amazon rainforest respond to drought according to differences in local forest environments and in the properties of trees, Scott Saleska of the University of Arizona and colleagues have discovered. In the southern Amazon rainforest…</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 15:15:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nature-based solutions to disaster risk from climate change are cost effective</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240716151252.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>A new global assessment of scientific literature finds that nature-based solutions (NbS) are an economically effective method to mitigate risks from a range of disasters -- from floods and hurricanes to heatwaves and landslides -- which are only expected to intensify as Earth continues to warm.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:12:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF–DOE Rubin Observatory will detect thousands of elusive brown dwarfs, unlocking Milky Way mysteries</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/rubin-observatory-will-detect-thousands-dwarfs</link><description>Too big to be planets but too small to be stars, distant brown dwarfs are a key ingredient for understanding the history of the Milky Way. These elusive objects have existed since the early universe and have remained relatively unchanged. Anticipated…</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 19:05:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How astronomers are using pulsars to observe evidence of dark matter</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240716151238.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Tantalizing evidence of potential dark matter objects has been detected with the help of the Universe's 'timekeepers'. These pulsars -- neutron stars which rotate and emit lighthouse-like beams of radio waves that rapidly sweep through space -- were used to identify mysterious hidden masses. Pulsars earned their nickname because they send out electromagnetic radiation at very regular intervals, ranging from milliseconds to seconds, making them extremely accurate timekeepers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:12:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wildfire smoke is reaching almost all lakes in North America</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/wildfire-smoke-reaching-almost-all-lakes-north</link><description>Wildfire smoke, sometimes drifting across hundreds of miles, reached almost every lake in North America at least one day each year from 2019 to 2021, according to U.S. National Science Foundation- supported findings published in the journal Global…</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 17:28:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sun-like stars found orbiting hidden companions</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240716151150.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Astronomers have uncovered what appear to be 21 neutron stars in orbit around stars like our Sun. The discovery is surprising because it is not clear how a star that exploded winds up next to a star like our Sun.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:11:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seasonal shifts: Phenology events at the bottom of the world</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/seasonal-shifts-phenology-events-bottom-world</link><description>Climate change has affected more than the planet's temperature. As climate change has become more influential, seasonal event timing has fluctuated. Flower blooms are harder to predict, and animal migration schedules have shifted. These events, known…</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 16:41:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New analysis of Cassini data yields insights into Titan's seas</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240716122705.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>A new study of radar experiment data from the Cassini-Huygens mission to Saturn has yielded fresh insights related to the makeup and activity of the liquid hydrocarbon seas near the north pole of Titan, the largest of Saturn's 146 known moons.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 17:27:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Woolly mammoth chromosomes reconstructed using fossilized sample</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/woolly-mammoth-chromosomes-reconstructed</link><description>An international team of scientists assembled the woolly mammoth's genetic code using fossilized chromosomes from a 52,000-year-old carcass discovered in Siberian permafrost. The mammoth became freeze-dried on death, preserving the 3D structure of…</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 21:16:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bizarre 'garden sprinkler-like' jet is spotted shooting out of neutron star</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240716122625.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>A strange 'garden sprinkler-like' jet coming from a neutron star has been pictured for the first time. The S-shaped structure is created as the jet changes direction due to the wobbling of the disc of hot gas around the star -- a process called precession, which has been observed with black holes but, until now, never with neutron stars.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 17:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>