<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 06:47:39 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Climate change will make it harder to see the forest for the trees</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/climate-change-will-make-it-harder-see-forest</link><description>Individual trees can't move to escape climate change, and new U.S. National Science Foundation-supported research shows that species will be limited in their ability to migrate via seed dispersal and other methods because of a lack of symbiotic fungi…</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 14:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Editing without 'cutting': Molecular mechanisms of new gene-editing tool revealed</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240529144235.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>New research has determined the spatial structure of various processes of a novel gene-editing tool called 'prime editor.' Functional analysis based on these structures also revealed how a 'prime editor' could achieve reverse transcription, synthesizing DNA from RNA, without 'cutting' both strands of the double helix. Clarifying these molecular mechanisms contributes greatly to designing gene-editing tools accurate enough for gene therapy treatments.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:42:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-53</link><description>From testifying in front of the Senate Committee on Commerce, Science, and Transportation hearing to celebrating new graduates entering the STEM enterprise, this week NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan reinforced the significance of the agency's…</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 22:30:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Acute sense of touch helps hummingbirds hover near a flower without bumping into it</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240529144222.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Hummingbird flight mechanics have been well studied but far less is known about how their sense of touch helps them sip nectar from a flower without bumping into it. Most of what scientists know about how touch is processed in the brain comes from studies on mammals, but bird brains are very different from mammal brains. New research shows that touch and air pressure on the wings and legs activate specific clusters of neurons in two regions of the forebrain to create a map of their body, which may help hummingbirds make nuanced adjustments to flight.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:42:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Navajo Technical University partners with NSF center, creating new opportunities in materials research and education</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/navajo-technical-university-partners-nsf-center</link><description>A partnership that began in 2017 between Navajo Technical University (NTU) and the U.S. National Science Foundation Materials Research Science and Engineering Center at Harvard University is providing Navajo students with new opportunities to pursue…</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 17:30:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Complete X and Y chromosome sequences of living great ape species determined</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240529144220.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Newly generated, complete genomes for the sex chromosomes of six primate species may inform conservation of these endangered species and shed light on sex-related genetic diseases in both humans and our closest living relatives.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:42:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF invests $36M in computing projects that promise to maximize performance, reduce energy demands</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-invests-36m-computing-projects-promise</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation is awarding $36 million to three projects selected for their potential to revolutionize computing and make significant impacts in reducing the carbon footprint of the lifecycle of computers. Funding for the…</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 17:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Moon orbiting 'dinky' asteroid is actually two tiny moons stuck together</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240529144217.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>The moon orbiting the asteroid Dinkinesh is actually two tiny moons stuck together. Collectively called 'Selam,' the two moonlets bring new insight into the complex processes behind planetary formation and evolution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:42:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-52</link><description>On May 16, U.S. National Science Foundation Director Sethuraman Panchanathan, alongside Former Chair of the National Science Board Chair Dan Reed, testified to the House Committee on Science, Space and Technology Subcommittee on Research and…</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 18:25:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The case of the missing black holes</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240529144206.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Researchers have applied the well-understood and highly verified quantum field theory, usually applied to the study of the very small, to a new target, the early universe. Their exploration led to the conclusion that there ought to be far fewer miniature black holes than most models suggest, though observations to confirm this should soon be possible. The specific kind of black hole in question could be a contender for dark matter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:42:06 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>