<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 11:00:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Winds of change: James Webb Space Telescope reveals elusive details in young star systems</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/10/241007115547.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Planet-forming disks, maelstroms of gas and dust swirling around young stars, are nurseries that give rise to planetary systems, including our solar s...</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 16:55:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF, NIH and FDA support research in digital twin technology for biomedical applications</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-nih-fda-support-research-digital-twin-technology</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation, in collaboration with the National Institutes of Health (NIH) and the Food and Drug Administration (FDA), has aw...</description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 21:08:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF congratulates laureates of the 2024 Nobel Prize in physiology or medicine</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-congratulates-laureates-2024-nobel-prize-physiology-medicine</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation congratulates Victor Ambros and Gary Ruvkun for their Nobel Prize in physiology or medicine. Their breakthrough d...</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 22:39:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Researchers confront new US and global challenges in vaccinations of adults</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/10/241007115102.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Over the past decade, decreasing vaccination rates now threaten the huge beneficial impacts of vaccinations in the U.S. and globally. Researchers disc...</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 16:51:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists discover a secret to regulating our body clock, offering new approach to end jet lag</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/10/241007115447.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Scientists have discovered the secret to regulating our internal clock. They identified that this regulator sits right at the tail end of Casein Kinas...</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 16:54:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Antarctic 'greening' at dramatic rate</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/10/241007115554.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Vegetation cover across the Antarctic Peninsula has increased more than tenfold over the last four decades, new research shows.</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 16:55:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Creating the largest, most comprehensive picture of neural connections to date</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/creating-largest-most-comprehensive-picture-neural</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Flip a switch on the wall, and it turns on a light across the room through a simple circuit. Now add 140,000 other switches and try and figure out whi...</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 15:31:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-68</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation Director Sethuraman Panchanathan had a dynamic week as he met with domestic and international partners to emphasi...</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 19:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Autobiographical memory in the digital age: Our lives in the mirror of our data</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/10/241007115253.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Never before have people recorded more information about their lives than today. But what does this mean for the way we remember our lives and how we ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 16:52:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MRR: Taking a groundbreaking technology from basic research to commercialization</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/mrr-taking-groundbreaking-technology-basic-research</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>The development of a cutting-edge technique to monitor and control chemical reactions in real time has the potential to transform pharmaceutical manuf...</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 15:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>