<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 07:25:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Cloudy with a chance of climate predictions</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/cloudy-chance-climate-predictions</link><description>Whether they're fluffy, bright or ominous, clouds are key to regulating Earth's energy and water cycles. Two sets of U.S. National Science Foundation-supported researchers recently published findings to help scientists better understand what's…</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 21:15:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pacific coast gray whales have gotten 13% shorter in the past 20-30 years, Oregon State study finds</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240612173127.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Gray whales that spend their summers feeding in the shallow waters off the Pacific Northwest coast have undergone a significant decline in body length since around the year 2000, a new study found.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 22:31:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Cells to Galaxies' unites astronomers, medical imaging experts to advance both fields</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/cells-galaxies-unites-astronomers</link><description>In May 2024, experts from the U.S. National Science Foundation National Radio Astronomy Observatory (NSF NRAO) and the medical imaging field presented at the International Society for Magnetic Resonance in Medicine conference on the surprising…</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 15:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Western agricultural communities need water conservation strategies to adapt to future shortages</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240612173119.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>The Western U.S. is heavily reliant on mountain snowpacks and their gradual melt for water storage and supply, and climate change is expected to upend the reliability of this natural process. Many agricultural communities in this part of the country are examining ways to adapt to a future with less water, and new research shows that a focus on supplementing water supply by expanding reservoir capacity won't be enough to avert future water crises.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 22:31:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Synthetic platelets stanch bleeding, promote healing using advanced materials</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/synthetic-platelets-stanch-bleeding-promote-healing</link><description>A research team has developed synthetic platelets that can stop bleeding and enhance healing at the site of an injury. They demonstrated that the synthetic platelets work well in some animals but have not yet begun clinical trials in humans. The…</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 15:03:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NASA's Roman mission gets cosmic 'sneak peek' from supercomputers</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240612173107.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Researchers used supercomputers to create nearly 4 million simulated images depicting the cosmos.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 22:31:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-54</link><description>NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan traveled to Interlaken, Switzerland, to join international partners for the Global Research Council's (GRC) annual meeting. GRC aims to promote long-term multilateral research and collaboration across continents…</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 20:32:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Swimming microrobots deliver cancer-fighting drugs to metastatic lung tumors in mice</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240612173104.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Engineers have developed microscopic robots, known as microrobots, capable of swimming through the lungs to deliver cancer-fighting medication directly to metastatic tumors. This approach has shown promise in mice, where it inhibited the growth and spread of tumors that had metastasized to the lungs, thereby boosting survival rates compared to control treatments.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 22:31:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF enhances research security with new TRUST proposal assessment process</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-enhances-research-security-new-trust-proposal</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has announced a new risk mitigation process, the Trusted Research Using Safeguards and Transparency (TRUST) framework, which will guide the agency in assessing grant proposals for potential national security risks…</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 15:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What the geologic record reveals about how oceans were oxygenated 2.3 billion years ago</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240612140903.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Geochemists used thallium isotopes to track the rise and fall of free oxygen on Earth between 2.5 and 2.2 billion years ago, the process that enabled life as we know it.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 19:09:03 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>