<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 15:12:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>A renovated aircraft for atmospheric sciences is ready for action</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/renovated-aircraft-atmospheric-sciences-ready-action</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>The newly updated U.S. National Science Foundation (NSF) University of Wyoming (UW) King Air Research Aircraft (King Air) is set to fly its first rese...</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 21:00:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Abrupt intensification of northern wildfires due to future permafrost thawing</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240924123046.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Climate scientists and permafrost experts show that, according to new climate computer model simulations, global warming will accelerate permafrost th...</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 17:30:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-66</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>This week, NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan engaged in discussions and announcements that underscored the agency's commitment to advancing researc...</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 20:30:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Another Franklin expedition crew member has been identified</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240924123035.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>The skeletal remains of a senior officer of Sir John Franklin's 1845 Northwest Passage expedition have been identified using DNA and genealogical anal...</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 17:30:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF and philanthropic partners invest more than $18M to prioritize ethical and societal considerations in the creation of emerging technologies</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-philanthropic-partners-invest-more-18m-prioritize</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation announced an inaugural investment of more than $18 million to 44 multidisciplinary, multi-sector teams across the...</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 19:03:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Atmospheric blocking slows ocean-driven melting of Greenland's largest glacier tongue</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240924123033.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Northeast Greenland is home to the 79 N Glacier -- the country's largest floating glacier tongue, but also one seriously threatened by global warming:...</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 17:30:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Atmospheric Rivers Shape Arctic Moisture</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/atmospheric-rivers-shape-arctic-moisture</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Atmospheric rivers cross the planet. These large, narrow sections of Earth's atmosphere carry moisture from the tropics to the poles. A recently publi...</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 15:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Astronomers catch a glimpse of a uniquely inflated and asymmetric exoplanet</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240924123003.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Astronomers have observed the atmosphere of a hot and uniquely inflated exoplanet using NASA's James Webb Space Telescope.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 17:30:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Researchers track plasma creation using novel ultra-fast laser method</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/researchers-track-plasma-creation-using-novel-ultra-fast</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>A team of researchers supported by the U.S. National Science Foundation has developed a new method of tracking the ultra-fast heat progression in warm...</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 18:02:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The heart of the question: Who can get Medicare-covered weight loss medicine?</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240923184938.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>With Medicare now covering semaglutide for people with obesity and cardiovascular disease who don't have diabetes, a study looks at who that might inc...</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 23:49:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>