<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 06:47:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Jumping on the jumping gene bandwagon to speed up plant breeding</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/jumping-jumping-gene-bandwagon-speed-plant</link><description>Getting a new variety of corn, tomato, soybean or other crop to market can be a long and costly effort, with breeders working to ensure the eventual product has the right mix of genetics that will let it withstand change, produce large amounts of…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 18:48:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New groups of methane-producing organisms in Yellowstone</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240724171548.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>The team verified that microbes found in Yellowstone National Park hot springs produce methane to grow.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 22:15:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Making strides in understanding decision making</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/making-strides-understanding-decision-making</link><description>Decisions, decisions. Life is full of decisions, from what to have for breakfast to where to work. To make each one, a series of mechanisms in the brain must be engaged. Understanding those mechanisms is an important area of neuroscience. To help…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 17:19:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dark matter flies ahead of normal matter in mega galaxy cluster collision</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240724171512.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Astronomers have untangled a messy collision between two massive clusters of galaxies in which the clusters' vast clouds of dark matter have decoupled from the so-called normal matter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 22:15:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>U.S. National Science Foundation and Department of Commerce partner to advance semiconductor workforce development</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-doc-partner-to-advance-semiconductor</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation and the CHIPS for America Research and Development Office within the National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST), a bureau of the U.S. Department of Commerce (DOC), signed a memorandum of understanding…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 15:28:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Saharan dust regulates hurricane rainfall</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240724171436.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>New research underscores the close relationship between dust plumes transported from the Sahara Desert in Africa, and rainfall from tropical cyclones along the U.S. Gulf Coast and Florida.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 22:14:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF-backed SECURE Center will support research security, international collaboration</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-backed-secure-center-will-support-research</link><description>Today, the U.S. National Science Foundation announced a five-year $67 million investment establishing the Safeguarding the Entire Community of the U.S. Research Ecosystem (SECURE) ($50 million to University of Washington and $17 million to Texas A&amp;M…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 11:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Neuroscientists discover brain circuitry of placebo effect for pain relief</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240724123119.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Researchers have discovered a novel pain control pathway that links the cingulate cortex in the front of the brain, through the pons region of the brainstem, to cerebellum in the back of the brain.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 17:31:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When lightning strikes, check for wind turbines</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/when-lightning-strikes-check-wind-turbines</link><description>Minutes after lightning lit the dark evening sky in the middle of a blizzard, a team of seven students and researchers rapidly unzipped a bright yellow bag the size of a small car to release a giant white balloon. This daring feat was part of a U.S…</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 19:15:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Researchers record images and data of a shark experiencing a boat strike</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240724123103.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Researchers have captured what they believe is the first ever video of a shark or any large marine animal being struck by a boat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 17:31:03 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>