<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 07:00:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NSF and USDA join forces to boost innovation in agricultural robotics</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-usda-join-forces-boost-innovation-agricultural</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation and the U.S. Department of Agriculture's National Institute of Food and Agriculture (USDA NIFA) are teaming up to advance foundational research in agricultural robotics. The agencies are issuing a new Dear…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Long snouts protect foxes when diving headfirst in snow</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/04/240429165819.htm</link><description>When hunting for mice in winter, red and arctic fox are known to plunge headfirst at speeds of 2-4 meters per second, but their sharp noses reduce the impact force in snow and protect them from injury, according to a new study.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 21:58:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New center supported by NSF will catalyze data-driven insights in molecular and cellular biosciences</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/new-center-supported-nsf-will-catalyze-data-driven</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has made a $20 million award to support the creation of the National Synthesis Center for Emergence in the Molecular and Cellular Sciences (NCEMS). The center will combine vast amounts of available data on…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 14:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gemini south reveals origin of unexpected differences in giant binary stars</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/04/240429133558.htm</link><description>Astronomers have confirmed that differences in binary stars' composition can originate from chemical variations in the cloud of stellar material from which they formed. The results help explain why stars born from the same molecular cloud can possess different chemical composition and host different planetary systems, as well as pose challenges to current stellar and planet formation models.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 18:35:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF honors 3 outstanding early-career researchers with the Alan T. Waterman Award</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-honors-3-outstanding-early-career-researchers</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation honored three researchers with the Alan T. Waterman Award, the nation's highest honor for early-career scientists and engineers. The 2024 recipients: Muyinatu A. Lediju Bell, a biomedical engineer at Johns Hopkins…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Experimental type 1 diabetes drug shelters pancreas cells from immune system attack</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/04/240429133540.htm</link><description>Scientists say that an experimental monoclonal antibody drug called mAb43 appears to prevent and reverse the onset of clinical type 1 diabetes in mice, and in some cases, to lengthen the animals' lifespan.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 18:35:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF invests $90M in innovative national scientific cyberinfrastructure for transforming STEM education</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-invests-90m-innovative-national-scientific</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation announced today a strategic investment of $90 million over five years in SafeInsights, a unique national scientific cyberinfrastructure aimed at transforming learning research and STEM education. Funded through…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:30:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>More plants on the menu of ancient hunter-gatherers</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/04/240429115900.htm</link><description>It has long been thought that meat played an important role in the diet of hunter-gatherers before the Neolithic transition. However, due to the scarcity of well-preserved human remains from Paleolithic sites, little information exists about the dietary habits of pre-agricultural human groups. A new study challenges this notion by presenting compelling isotopic evidence of a strong preference for plants among 15,000-year-old hunter-gatherers from Morocco. This is the first time a significant amount of plant consumption has been measured for a pre-agricultural population, shedding new light on the dietary practices of ancient human societies.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 16:59:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-49</link><description>This week, US National Science Foundation Director worked to strengthen pathways into STEM and expand the agency’s reach in communities across the nation and world. At the Arctic Encounter Symposium, Director Panchanathan took center stage alongside…</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 20:37:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fixin' to be flexitarian: Scrap fish and invasive species can liven up vegetables</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/04/240429103026.htm</link><description>Greening the way we eat needn't mean going vegetarian. A healthy, more realistic solution is to adopt a flexitarian diet where seafoods add umami to 'boring' vegetables. A gastrophysicist puts mathematical equations to work in calculating the umami potential of everything from seaweed and shrimp paste to mussels and mackerel.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 15:30:26 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>