<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 07:25:32 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NSF announces a new EPSCoR Track-1 award to combat climate change in Kentucky</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-new-epscor-track-1-award-combat</link><description>The Commonwealth of Kentucky will receive $20 million from the U.S. National Science Foundation through the Established Program to Stimulate Competitive Research (EPSCoR). This program aims to support U.S. states and territories, also known as EPSCoR…</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI systems are already skilled at deceiving and manipulating humans</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240510111440.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Many artificial intelligence (AI) systems have already learned how to deceive humans, even systems that have been trained to be helpful and honest. Researchers describe the risks of deception by AI systems and call for governments to develop strong regulations to address this issue as soon as possible.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 16:14:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Big data helps determine what drives disease risk</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/big-data-helps-determine-what-drives-disease-risk</link><description>Working with nearly 3,000 observations across almost 1,500 host-parasite combinations, U.S. National Science Foundation-supported researchers at Notre Dame University have found that biodiversity loss, chemical pollution, introduced species and…</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:14:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ONe novae stellar explosion may be source of our phosphorus</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240510111431.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Astronomers have proposed a new theory to explain the origin of phosphorus, one of the elements important for life on Earth. The theory suggests a type of stellar explosion known as ONe novae as a major source of phosphorus.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 16:14:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Discovery in tomato could lead to natural pesticides</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/discovery-tomato-could-lead-natural-pesticides</link><description>Like a slightly revised version of the movie "The Parent Trap," U.S. National Science Foundation-supported researchers from Michigan State University have discovered that tomato plants have two related but separate pathways for producing acylsugars…</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 20:40:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How the brain is flexible enough for a complex world (without being thrown into chaos)</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240510111409.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Many neurons exhibit 'mixed selectivity,' meaning they can integrate multiple inputs and participate in multiple computations. Mechanisms such as oscillations and neuromodulators recruit their participation and tune them to focus on the relevant information.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 16:14:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF-led National AI Research Resource Pilot awards first round access to 35 projects in partnership with DOE</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-led-national-ai-research-resource-pilot-awards</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation and the Department of Energy are thrilled to announce the first 35 projects that will be supported with computational time through the National Artificial Intelligence Research Resource (NAIRR) Pilot, marking a…</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Squeezed by neighbors, planet glows with molten lava</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240509155528.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Astrophysicists discovered that an exoplanet is covered with so many active volcanoes that seen from a distance it would take on a fiery, glowing-red hue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 20:55:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-50</link><description>This week, Sethuraman Panchanathan, director of the U.S. National Science Foundation, has been actively forwarding science, education and engineering initiatives through meaningful collaborations with congressional leaders and NSF researchers. His…</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 22:19:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A fragment of human brain, mapped in exquisite detail</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240509155503.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Researchers have created the largest synaptic-resolution, 3D reconstruction of a piece of human brain to date, showing in vivid detail each cell and its web of neural connections in a piece of human temporal cortex about half the size of a rice grain.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 20:55:03 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>