<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 14:10:03 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NSF announces 4 new Engineering Research Centers focused on biotechnology, manufacturing, robotics and sustainability</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-4-new-engineering-research-centers-0</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Engineering innovations transform our lives and energize the economy. The U.S. National Science Foundation announces a five-year investment of $104 million, with a potential 10-year investment of up to $208 million, in four new NSF Engineering…</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 15:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Humpbacks are among animals who manufacture and wield tools</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240820221814.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Researchers suggest a new designation of the humpback whales they study: tool wielders. Researchers have known that humpback whales create "bubble-nets" to hunt, but they have learned that the animals don't just create the bubble-nets; they manipulate this unique tool in a variety of ways to maximize their food intake in Alaskan feeding grounds.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 03:18:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The disappearing mountains and hungry volcano</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/disappearing-mountains-hungry-volcano</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Once upon a time, the Teton Range, a 40-mile-long mountain range in the northern Rocky Mountains, may have extended much longer than it does now. A U.S. National Science Foundation-funded team thinks it might know what happened to it. The team, led…</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 13:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Red and processed meat consumption associated with higher type 2 diabetes risk, study of two million people finds</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240820221808.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Meat consumption, particularly consumption of processed meat and unprocessed red meat, is associated with a higher type 2 diabetes risk, an analysis of data from 1.97 million participants.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 03:18:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Unfrozen layers in dryland permafrost are unexpected source of methane</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/unfrozen-layers-dryland-permafrost-are-unexpected</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Permafrost is permanently frozen soil in the coldest areas of the planet. Although it has trapped organic carbon from the remains of plants and animals that died and froze thousands of years ago, rising temperatures are thawing the soil, releasing…</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 21:47:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New view of North Star reveals spotted surface</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240820124556.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>High-resolution images show large spots on the surface of Polaris.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 17:45:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF awards $38M to strengthen research infrastructure, build partnerships and improve STEM workforce development</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-awards-38m-strengthen-research-infrastructure</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has awarded researchers in Maine, Mississippi, New Mexico, Puerto Rico and Rhode Island roughly $38 million through the Established Program to Stimulate Competitive Research (EPSCoR), which promotes the…</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 16:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Explanation found for X-ray radiation from black holes</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240820124514.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Researchers have succeeded in something that has been pursued since the 1970s: explaining the X-ray radiation from the black hole surroundings. The radiation originates from the combined effect of the chaotic movements of magnetic fields and turbulent plasma gas.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 17:45:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>U.S. National Science Foundation, Paul G. Allen Family Foundation double investment in science-driven conservation projects</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/us-national-science-foundation-paul-g-allen-family</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation and the Paul G. Allen Family Foundation are investing $16 million across 10 projects that will conduct basic science with direct conservation applications to benefit species and ecosystems. The projects are…</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 15:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fossil hotspots in Africa obscure a more complete picture of human evolution</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240820124505.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>A new study shows how the mismatch between where fossils are preserved and where humans likely lived may influence our understanding of early human evolution.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 17:45:05 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>