<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 06:38:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Lakes in marginalized communities sampled less, study finds</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/lakes-marginalized-communities-sampled-less-study-finds</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Water is essential for all forms of life — humans included — and understanding the quality of available water is critical to knowing where to drink, s...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 20:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New AI can ID brain patterns related to specific behavior</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240909175239.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Scientists have developed a new AI algorithm that can separate brain patterns related to a particular behavior. This work promises to improve brain-co...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 22:52:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-64</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>This week, NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan met with representatives from Australia, including Doug Hilton, CEO of CSIRO, Dharmini Robertson, U.S....</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 22:09:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Formation of super-Earths is limited near metal-poor stars</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240909160254.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>In a new study, astronomers report novel evidence regarding the limits of planet formation, finding that after a certain point, planets larger than Ea...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 21:02:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A window into the body: groundbreaking technique makes skin transparent</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/window-into-body-invisible-skin</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Researchers have developed a new way to see organs within a body by rendering overlying tissues transparent to visible light. The counterintuitive pro...</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 19:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New research sinks an old theory for the doldrums, a low-wind equatorial region that stranded sailors for centuries</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240909160244.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>During the Age of Sail, sailors riding the trade winds past the equator dreaded becoming stranded in the doldrums, a meteorologically distinct region ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 21:02:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weather anomaly experienced in the McMurdo Dry Valleys</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/weather-anomaly-experienced-mcmurdo-dry-valleys</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>The McMurdo Dry Valleys are a unique region of Antarctica, nearly devoid of snow and ice. An atmospheric river event in March 2022 led to record warm ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 15:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Artificial muscles propel a robotic leg to walk and jump</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240909113111.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Researchers have developed a robotic leg with artificial muscles. Inspired by living creatures, it jumps across different terrains in an agile and ene...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 16:31:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nothing to 'shrub' about: How plant coverage is affecting the Arctic carbon cycle</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nothing-shrub-about-how-plant-coverage-affecting-arctic</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Researchers at Columbia University's Department of Earth and Environment Science have discovered new implications for the Arctic carbon cycle in the f...</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 19:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Out-of-body' research could lead to new ways to promote social harmony</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/09/240909113039.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Out-of-body experiences, such as near-death experiences, can have a 'transformative' effect on people's ability to experience empathy and connect with...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 16:30:39 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>