<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 12:05:07 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NSF awards $35M for networks to transform research capacity and competitiveness</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-awards-35m-networks-transform-research</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has awarded $35 million through the Established Program to Stimulate Competitive Research (EPSCoR) Research Incubators for STEM Excellence Research Infrastructure Improvement (E-RISE RII) to boost research…</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Solar technology: Innovative light-harvesting system works very efficiently</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240626152221.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Researchers are reporting progress on the road to more efficient utilization of solar energy: They have developed an innovative light-harvesting system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 20:22:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF launches new investment to accelerate the transition of privacy-enhancing technologies to practice</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-launches-new-investment-accelerate-transition</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation yesterday published a new investment to advance privacy-enhancing technologies (PETs) and promote their use to solve real-world problems. The Privacy-Preserving Data Sharing in Practice (PDaSP) program, which…</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 15:20:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Almonds, pottery, wood help date famed Kyrenia shipwreck</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240626152136.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Researchers have identified the likeliest timeline of the famous Hellenistic-era Kyrenia shipwreck, discovered and recovered off the north coast of Cyprus in the 1960s.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 20:21:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Physicists create first-ever Bose-Einstein condensate made of molecules</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/physicists-create-first-ever-bose-einstein</link><description>A team of physicists has successfully created a unique quantum state of matter called a Bose-Einstein condensate (BEC) out of molecules. The team is led by Sebastian Will at Columbia University, who received a U.S. National Science Foundation Faculty…</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 20:53:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How do our memories last a lifetime? New study offers a biological explanation</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240626152118.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>A new study by a team of international researchers has uncovered a biological explanation for long-term memories. It centers on the discovery of the role of a molecule, KIBRA, that serves as a 'glue' to other molecules, thereby solidifying memory formation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 20:21:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI-powered underwater robots revolutionize marine conservation, NSF-funded researchers lead the charge</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/ai-powered-underwater-robots-revolutionize-marine</link><description>The underwater environment, covering nearly 80% of the planet, is critical in maintaining ecological balance and supporting human well-being. Effective conservation relies on thoroughly understanding underwater species distribution and ecosystem…</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 16:33:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shocked quartz reveals evidence of historical cosmic airburst</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240626152057.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Researchers continue to expand the case for the Younger Dryas Impact hypothesis. The idea proposes that a fragmented comet smashed into the Earth's atmosphere 12,800 years ago, causing a widespread climatic shift that, among other things, led to the abrupt reversal of the Earth's warming trend and into an anomalous near-glacial period called the Younger Dryas.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 20:20:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Creating a diverse and inclusive AI research community is the goal of new NSF awards</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/creating-diverse-inclusive-ai-research-community</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation is excited to announce a new round of ExpandAI awards dedicated to fostering diversity and inclusion within the artificial intelligence research community. In collaboration with the departments of Homeland…</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 16:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pillars of creation star in new visualization from NASA's Hubble and Webb telescopes</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240626152053.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Made famous in 1995 by NASA's Hubble Space Telescope, the Pillars of Creation in the heart of the Eagle Nebula have captured imaginations worldwide with their arresting, ethereal beauty. Now, NASA has released a new 3D visualization of these towering celestial structures using data from NASA's Hubble and James Webb space telescopes. This is the most comprehensive and detailed multiwavelength movie yet of these star-birthing clouds.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 20:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>