<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 06:58:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>A thorny problem, a genetic answer</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/thorny-problem-genetic-answer</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Every rose has its thorn. Or rather, every rose has its prickle, a sharp projection of the plant's skin that can serve as a deterrent to herbivores but also makes cultivating roses and other plants more difficult. New research supported by the U.S…</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 19:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Retreat of tropical glaciers foreshadows changing climate's effect on the global ice</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240801165624.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>As they are in many places around the globe, glaciers perched high in the Andes Mountains are shrinking. Now, researchers have uncovered evidence that the high-altitude tropical ice fields are likely smaller than they've been at any time since the last ice age ended 11,700 years ago.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 21:56:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Astronomers uncover new phenomenon in growth dynamics of supermassive black hole</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/astronomers-uncover-new-phenomenon-growth-dynamics</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Scientists at the U.S. National Science Foundation National Radio Astronomy Observatory (NSF NRAO), along with an international team of astronomers, have uncovered a new cosmic mechanism in the complex dynamics of supermassive black holes — one that…</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 13:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When it comes to DNA replication, humans and baker's yeast are more alike than different</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240801142240.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>Humans and baker's yeast have more in common than meets the eye, including an important mechanism that helps ensure DNA is copied correctly, reports a pair of studies. The findings visualize for the first time a molecular complex -- called CTF18-RFC in humans and Ctf18-RFC in yeast -- that loads a 'clamp' onto DNA to keep parts of the replication machinery from falling off the DNA strand.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 19:22:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Garden to table: Turning a backyard plant into a mainstream crop</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/garden-table-turning-backyard-plant-mainstream</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>It looks like a cherry tomato wrapped in a paper lantern, but in fact it's called a groundcherry. Little-known beyond gardeners and farmers, the groundcherry has quietly produced fruit across North America for centuries. Now it's emerging from…</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 17:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Climate change may lead to shifts in vital Pacific Arctic fisheries</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240801121934.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Commercially important marine fish and invertebrate species will likely shift northwards under a warmer climate, according to new research.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 17:19:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why does the United States have the most tornadoes in the world?  Scientists find new answers.</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/why-does-united-states-have-most-tornadoes-world</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>The central and eastern regions of the United States are the hotspots for Earth's most damaging and frequent tornadoes, scientists have found. In fact, the U.S. has the most tornadoes of any country in the world, but why? In a study published in…</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 17:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Engineering researchers crack the code to boost solar cell efficiency and durability</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240801121900.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>Photovoltaic (PV) technologies, which convert light into electricity, are increasingly applied worldwide to generate renewable energy. Researchers have now developed a molecular treatment that significantly enhances the efficiency and durability of perovskite solar cells. Their breakthrough will potentially accelerate the large-scale production of this clean energy.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 17:19:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-60</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>This week, NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan participated in a series of pivotal discussions and events, underscoring U.S. National Science Foundation’s role at the forefront of scientific innovation and workforce development in the United States…</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 18:12:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Judging your own happiness could backfire</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240801121840.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>Judging how happy you are could backfire and negatively impact life satisfaction and psychological well-being, according to new research.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 17:18:40 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>