<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 23:45:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Clinical trial reveals twice-yearly injection to be 96% effective in HIV prevention</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/11/241127191937.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Recent results from a recent clinical trial indicate that a twice-yearly injection of Lenacapavir offers an overall 96% reduced risk of acquiring HIV....</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 00:19:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Researchers call for sustainable governance as groundwater resources become scarce</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/researchers-call-sustainable-governance-groundwater</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>In recent decades, the Western United States has faced a mounting environmental crisis: the depletion of groundwater resources. This pressing issue, d...</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 18:05:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-73</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan spent the week commemorating NSF's leading efforts in strengthening partnerships and supporting research empoweri...</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 19:36:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>First new treatment for asthma attacks in 50 years</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/11/241127191934.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>A recent trial finds an injection given during some asthma and COPD attacks is more effective than the current treatment of steroid tablets, reducing ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 00:19:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-74</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan had a productive week traveling abroad, connecting with international counterparts, exploring opportunities for g...</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 19:14:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF announces funding opportunity to train and expand the U.S. workforce across a range of key technologies</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-funding-opportunity-train-expand-us-workforce</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>The NSF ExLENT program offers all Americans opportunities to gain the skills needed to succeed in key technologies and prepare them to enter the workf...</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 18:40:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Satellite evidence bolsters case that climate change caused mass elephant die-off</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/11/241129120944.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>A new study has provided further evidence that the deaths of 350 African elephants in Botswana during 2020 were the result of drinking from water hole...</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 17:09:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A fossil first: Scientists find 1.5-million-year-old footprints of two different species of human ancestors at same spot</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/11/241128200732.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>More than a million years ago, on a hot savannah teeming with wildlife near the shore of what would someday become Lake Turkana in Kenya, two complete...</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 01:07:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A novel method to shed light on heat waves</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/novel-method-shed-light-heat-waves</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>A U.S. National Science Foundation-supported researcher developed a machine learning model that uses data stored in paleoclimate archives, such as tre...</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 19:58:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coral adaptation unlikely to keep pace with global warming</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/11/241128200737.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Coral adaptation to ocean warming and marine heatwaves will likely be overwhelmed without rapid reductions of global greenhouse gas emissions, accordi...</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 01:07:37 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>