<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 16:33:37 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NSF and USDA join forces to boost innovation in agricultural robotics</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-usda-join-forces-boost-innovation-agricultural</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation and the U.S. Department of Agriculture's National Institute of Food and Agriculture (USDA NIFA) are teaming up to advance foundational research in agricultural robotics. The agencies are issuing a new Dear…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fixin' to be flexitarian: Scrap fish and invasive species can liven up vegetables</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/04/240429103026.htm</link><description>Greening the way we eat needn't mean going vegetarian. A healthy, more realistic solution is to adopt a flexitarian diet where seafoods add umami to 'boring' vegetables. A gastrophysicist puts mathematical equations to work in calculating the umami potential of everything from seaweed and shrimp paste to mussels and mackerel.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 15:30:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New center supported by NSF will catalyze data-driven insights in molecular and cellular biosciences</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/new-center-supported-nsf-will-catalyze-data-driven</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has made a $20 million award to support the creation of the National Synthesis Center for Emergence in the Molecular and Cellular Sciences (NCEMS). The center will combine vast amounts of available data on…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 14:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>T. Rex not as smart as previously claimed</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/04/240429103020.htm</link><description>Dinosaurs were likely as smart as reptiles but not as intelligent as monkeys.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 15:30:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF honors 3 outstanding early-career researchers with the Alan T. Waterman Award</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-honors-3-outstanding-early-career-researchers</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation honored three researchers with the Alan T. Waterman Award, the nation's highest honor for early-career scientists and engineers. The 2024 recipients: Muyinatu A. Lediju Bell, a biomedical engineer at Johns Hopkins…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Probing the effects of interplanetary space on asteroid Ryugu</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/04/240429102816.htm</link><description>Samples reveal evidence of changes experienced by the surface of asteroid Ryugu, some probably due to micrometeoroid bombardment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 15:28:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF invests $90M in innovative national scientific cyberinfrastructure for transforming STEM education</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-invests-90m-innovative-national-scientific</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation announced today a strategic investment of $90 million over five years in SafeInsights, a unique national scientific cyberinfrastructure aimed at transforming learning research and STEM education. Funded through…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:30:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Test reveals mice think like babies</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/04/240426165208.htm</link><description>Are mice clever enough to be strategic? A neuroscientist who studies learning in humans and animals, and who has long worked with mice, wondered why rodents often performed poorly in tests when they knew how to perform well. With a simple experiment, and by acting as 'a little bit of a mouse psychologist,' he and his team figured it out.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 21:52:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-49</link><description>This week, US National Science Foundation Director worked to strengthen pathways into STEM and expand the agency’s reach in communities across the nation and world. At the Arctic Encounter Symposium, Director Panchanathan took center stage alongside…</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 20:37:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New circuit boards can be repeatedly recycled</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/04/240426165151.htm</link><description>Researchers have developed a new PCB that performs on par with traditional materials and can be recycled repeatedly with negligible material loss. Researchers used a solvent that transforms a type of vitrimer -- a cutting-edge class of polymer -- into a jelly-like substance without damage, allowing solid components to be plucked out for reuse or recycling. With these 'vPCBs' (vitrimer printed circuit boards), researchers recovered 98% of the vitrimer and 100% of the glass fiber.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 21:51:51 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>