<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 06:56:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Collaborative approaches improve materials informatics workforce training</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/collaborative-approaches-improve-materials</link><description>A wide range of innovative products, from biomedical implants to aerospace composites, come from research in materials informatics (MI) — the combination of machine learning, artificial intelligence and computational methodologies with materials…</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 17:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Large wildfires create weather that favors more fire</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240618115618.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>A new study shows soot from large wildfires in California traps sunlight, making days warmer and drier than they ought to be.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 16:56:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shipworms still hold some sea-crets</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/shipworms-still-hold-some-sea-crets</link><description>Although they have been known to mariners for centuries — having aided in shipwrecking Columbus and sinking parts of the Spanish Armada — scientists have not been able to determine how shipworms digest wood, until now. Sometimes known as "termites of…</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 14:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Astronomers see a massive black hole awaken in real time</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240618115433.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>In late 2019 the previously unremarkable galaxy SDSS1335+0728 suddenly started shining brighter than ever before. To understand why, astronomers have used data from several space and ground-based observatories, including the European Southern Observatory's Very Large Telescope (ESO's VLT), to track how the galaxy's brightness has varied. In a study out today, they conclude that they are witnessing changes never seen before in a galaxy -- likely the result of the sudden awakening of the massive black hole at its core.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 16:54:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-56</link><description>This week, NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan highlighted NSF’s commitment to innovation and STEM advancements through several key events. The Director joined Senator Shaheen in a conversation on Capitol Hill with New Hampshire business leaders to…</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 19:53:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bedtime battles: 1 in 4 parents say their child can't go to sleep because they're worried or anxious</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240617173714.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>One in four parents describe getting their young child to bed as difficult -- and these parents are less likely to have a bedtime routine, more likely to leave on a video or TV show, and more likely to stay with their child until they're asleep.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 22:37:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A deeper look into where the really big one could occur</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/deeper-look-where-really-big-one-could-occur</link><description>For the first time, NSF-funded researchers revealed a detailed look at the potential for a major earthquake off the coasts of southern British Columbia, Washington, Oregon and northern California. The new study characterizes the Cascadia Subduction…</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 17:28:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>An earthquake changed the course of the Ganges: Could it happen again?</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240617173557.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>A major earthquake 2,500 years ago caused one of the largest rivers on Earth to abruptly change course, according to a new study. The previously undocumented quake rerouted the main channel of the Ganges River in what is now densely populated Bangladesh, which remains vulnerable to big quakes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 22:35:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trouble dead ahead: Acidifying oceans harm tropical corals</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/trouble-dead-ahead-acidifying-oceans-harm-tropical</link><description>The French Polynesian island Moorea is the most beautiful isle in the world, some say. Its lagoons are surrounded by reefs dominated by Porites corals. These corals and other calcifying marine species are the world's primary reef-builders. Therein…</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 16:35:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Direct evidence found for dairy consumption in the Pyrenees in the earliest stages of the Neolithic</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240617173552.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>A study on the remains of the Chaves and Puyascada caves, both located in the province of Huesca, Spain, yields the first direct proof of the consumption and processing of dairy products in the Pyrenees already at the start of the Neolithic period, approximately 7,500 years ago, as well as the consumption of pig. The results lead to doubts about the belief that these products were first used much later in the Pyrenean mountain range.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 22:35:52 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>