<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:41:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NSF announces $24M investment across three EPSCoR jurisdictions</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-24m-investment-across-three-epscor</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has awarded teams from South Dakota, New Hampshire and Maine roughly $8 million each through the Established Program to Stimulate Competitive Research (EPSCoR) Collaborations for Optimizing Research Ecosystems…</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 18:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2023 was the hottest summer in two thousand years</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240514141249.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Researchers have found that 2023 was the hottest summer in the Northern Hemisphere in the past two thousand years, almost four degrees warmer than the coldest summer during the same period.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:12:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF announces a new EPSCoR Track-1 award to combat climate change in Kentucky</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-new-epscor-track-1-award-combat</link><description>The Commonwealth of Kentucky will receive $20 million from the U.S. National Science Foundation through the Established Program to Stimulate Competitive Research (EPSCoR). This program aims to support U.S. states and territories, also known as EPSCoR…</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Today's world: Fastest rate of carbon dioxide rise over the last 50,000 years</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240513150512.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Today's rate of atmospheric carbon dioxide increase is 10 times faster than at any other point in the past 50,000 years, researchers have found through a detailed chemical analysis of ancient Antarctic ice.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 20:05:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Big data helps determine what drives disease risk</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/big-data-helps-determine-what-drives-disease-risk</link><description>Working with nearly 3,000 observations across almost 1,500 host-parasite combinations, U.S. National Science Foundation-supported researchers at Notre Dame University have found that biodiversity loss, chemical pollution, introduced species and…</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:14:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Like dad and like mum...all in one plant</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240513150437.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Scientists have established a system to generate clonal sex cells in tomato plants and used them to design the genomes of offspring. The fertilization of a clonal egg from one parent by a clonal sperm from another parent led to plants containing the complete genetic information of both parents.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 20:04:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Discovery in tomato could lead to natural pesticides</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/discovery-tomato-could-lead-natural-pesticides</link><description>Like a slightly revised version of the movie "The Parent Trap," U.S. National Science Foundation-supported researchers from Michigan State University have discovered that tomato plants have two related but separate pathways for producing acylsugars…</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 20:40:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What makes a memory? It may be related to how hard your brain had to work</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240513105202.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>The human brain filters through a flood of experiences to create specific memories. Why do some of the experiences in this deluge of sensory information become 'memorable,' while most are discarded by the brain? A computational model and behavioral study developed by Yale scientists suggests a new clue to this age-old question, they report in the journal Nature Human Behavior.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 15:52:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF-led National AI Research Resource Pilot awards first round access to 35 projects in partnership with DOE</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-led-national-ai-research-resource-pilot-awards</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation and the Department of Energy are thrilled to announce the first 35 projects that will be supported with computational time through the National Artificial Intelligence Research Resource (NAIRR) Pilot, marking a…</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Plant virus treatment shows promise in fighting metastatic cancers in mice</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240513105128.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>An experimental treatment made from a plant virus is effective at protecting against a broad range of metastatic cancers in mice, shows a new study. The treatment, composed of nanoparticles fashioned from the cowpea mosaic virus -- a virus that infects black-eyed pea plants -- showed remarkable success in improving survival rates and suppressing the growth of metastatic tumors across various cancer models, including colon, ovarian, melanoma and breast cancer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 15:51:28 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>