<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 06:43:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Collaborative approaches improve materials informatics workforce training</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/collaborative-approaches-improve-materials</link><description>A wide range of innovative products, from biomedical implants to aerospace composites, come from research in materials informatics (MI) — the combination of machine learning, artificial intelligence and computational methodologies with materials…</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 17:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Titan's lakes may be shaped by waves</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240619143731.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Geologists studied Titan's shorelines and showed through simulations that coastlines of the moon's methane- and ethane-filled seas have likely been shaped by waves. Until now, scientists have found indirect and conflicting signs of wave activity, based on Cassini images of Titan's surface.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 19:37:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shipworms still hold some sea-crets</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/shipworms-still-hold-some-sea-crets</link><description>Although they have been known to mariners for centuries — having aided in shipwrecking Columbus and sinking parts of the Spanish Armada — scientists have not been able to determine how shipworms digest wood, until now. Sometimes known as "termites of…</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 14:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>At least one in four US residential yards exceed new EPA lead soil level guideline</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240619143719.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Roughly one in four U.S. households have soil exceeding the new U.S. Environmental Protection Agency's lead screening levels of 200 parts per million (ppm), halved from the previous level of 400 ppm, a new study found. For households with exposure from multiple sources, the EPA lowered the guidance to 100 ppm; nearly 40% of households exceed that level, the study also found.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 19:37:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-56</link><description>This week, NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan highlighted NSF’s commitment to innovation and STEM advancements through several key events. The Director joined Senator Shaheen in a conversation on Capitol Hill with New Hampshire business leaders to…</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 19:53:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jupiter's great red spot is not the same one Cassini observed in 1600s</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240619143717.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Jupiter's iconic Great Red Spot has persisted for at least 190 years and is likely a different spot from the one observed by the astronomer Giovanni Domenico Cassini in 1665, a new study reports. The Great Red Spot we see today likely formed because of an instability in the planet's intense atmospheric winds, producing a long, persistent atmospheric cell, the study also finds.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 19:37:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A deeper look into where the really big one could occur</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/deeper-look-where-really-big-one-could-occur</link><description>For the first time, NSF-funded researchers revealed a detailed look at the potential for a major earthquake off the coasts of southern British Columbia, Washington, Oregon and northern California. The new study characterizes the Cascadia Subduction…</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 17:28:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Non-native plants and animals expanding ranges 100 times faster than native species</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240619143655.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>An international team of scientists has recently found that non-native species are expanding their ranges many orders of magnitude faster than native ones, in large part due to inadvertent human help. Even seemingly sedentary non-native plants are moving at three times the speed of their native counterparts in a race where, because of the rapid pace of climate change and its effect on habitat, speed matters. To survive, plants and animals need to be shifting their ranges by 3.25 kilometers per year just to keep up with the increasing temperatures and associated climactic shifts -- a speed that native species cannot manage without human help.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 19:36:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trouble dead ahead: Acidifying oceans harm tropical corals</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/trouble-dead-ahead-acidifying-oceans-harm-tropical</link><description>The French Polynesian island Moorea is the most beautiful isle in the world, some say. Its lagoons are surrounded by reefs dominated by Porites corals. These corals and other calcifying marine species are the world's primary reef-builders. Therein…</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 16:35:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Researchers create new class of materials called 'glassy gels'</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240619143556.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Researchers have created a new class of materials called 'glassy gels' that are very hard and difficult to break despite containing more than 50% liquid. Coupled with the fact that glassy gels are simple to produce, the material holds promise for a variety of applications.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 19:35:56 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>