<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 16:58:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>When the only thing you can eat can kill you, having more gene copies can help</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/when-only-thing-you-can-eat-can-kill-you-having-more-gene</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>According to research supported by the U.S. National Science Foundation, gene duplications being selected over evolutionary time — not the specializat...</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 17:47:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Far out' blazar discovery suggests early universe had more supermassive black holes than previously thought</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/far-out-blazar-discovery-suggests-early-universe-had-more</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Scientists have discovered the most distant and therefore oldest blazar ever seen. Labeled J0410–0139, the blazar is at the center of a galaxy 12.9 bi...</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 20:29:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Migration memory: How caribou adapt to changing winter conditions</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/migration-memory-how-caribou-adapt-changing-winter</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>U.S. National Science Foundation-supported research shows that caribou will optimize their migration path based on their collective memories. Caribou ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 17:39:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Protein protects biological nitrogen fixation from oxidative stress</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/01/250115165045.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>A research team has discovered how the 'Shethna protein II' protects the nitrogen-fixing enzyme nitrogenase from damage. The oxygen sensor protein cou...</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 21:50:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This fast and agile robotic insect could someday aid in mechanical pollination</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/01/250115165102.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>New insect-scale microrobots can fly more than 100 times longer than previous versions. The new bots, also significantly faster and more agile, could ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 21:51:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coyote genes may show urban evolution at work</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/01/250115164909.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>A new study outlines the ways by which city life may be shaping the evolution of urban coyotes, the highly adaptable carnivores spotted in alleyways f...</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 21:49:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-77</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>This week, NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan began the new year by strengthening strategic global partnerships and commemorating the groundbreaking...</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 19:30:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chasing sparks: Unraveling a 50-year-old X-ray mystery</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/chasing-sparks-unraveling-50-year-old-x-ray-mystery</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>A U.S. National Science Foundation-supported team recently solved an enduring physics enigma, revealing new information about how X-rays form during t...</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 17:31:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This quasar may have helped turn the lights on for the universe</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/01/250115164904.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Astronomers have detected an intensely brightening and dimming quasar that may help explain how some objects in the early universe grew at a highly ac...</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 21:49:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Researchers make comfortable materials that generate power when worn</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/01/250115165051.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Researchers have demonstrated new wearable technologies that both generate electricity from human movement and improve the comfort of the technology f...</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 21:50:51 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>