<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 07:11:07 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-53</link><description>From testifying in front of the Senate Committee on Commerce, Science, and Transportation hearing to celebrating new graduates entering the STEM enterprise, this week NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan reinforced the significance of the agency's…</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 22:30:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Charge your laptop in a minute or your EV in 10? Supercapacitors can help</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240524171435.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Imagine if your dead laptop or phone could charge in a minute or if an electric car could be fully powered in 10 minutes. New research could lead to such advances.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 22:14:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Navajo Technical University partners with NSF center, creating new opportunities in materials research and education</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/navajo-technical-university-partners-nsf-center</link><description>A partnership that began in 2017 between Navajo Technical University (NTU) and the U.S. National Science Foundation Materials Research Science and Engineering Center at Harvard University is providing Navajo students with new opportunities to pursue…</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 17:30:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI headphones let wearer listen to a single person in a crowd, by looking at them just once</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240524171429.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Engineers have developed an artificial intelligence system that lets someone wearing headphones look at a person speaking for three to five seconds to 'enroll' them. The system then plays just the enrolled speaker's voice in real time, even as the pair move around in noisy environments.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 22:14:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF invests $36M in computing projects that promise to maximize performance, reduce energy demands</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-invests-36m-computing-projects-promise</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation is awarding $36 million to three projects selected for their potential to revolutionize computing and make significant impacts in reducing the carbon footprint of the lifecycle of computers. Funding for the…</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 17:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Theory and experiment combine to shine a new light on proton spin</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240524171421.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Nuclear physicists have long been working to reveal how the proton gets its spin. Now, a new method that combines experimental data with state-of-the-art calculations has revealed a more detailed picture of spin contributions from the very glue that holds protons together.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 22:14:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-52</link><description>On May 16, U.S. National Science Foundation Director Sethuraman Panchanathan, alongside Former Chair of the National Science Board Chair Dan Reed, testified to the House Committee on Science, Space and Technology Subcommittee on Research and…</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 18:25:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Caterpillars can detect their predators by the static electricity they emit</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240524115312.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Caterpillars respond defensively to electric fields similar to those emitted by their natural predators, scientists have found.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 16:53:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Largest camera ever built arrives at Rubin Observatory in Chile</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/largest-camera-ever-built-arrives-rubin</link><description>The 3200-megapixel Legacy Survey of Space and Time (LSST) Camera, the groundbreaking instrument at the core of the NSF-DOE Vera C. Rubin Observatory, has arrived at the observatory site on Cerro Pachón in Chile. The U.S. National Science Foundation…</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 15:44:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Imperceptible sensors made from 'electronic spider silk' can be printed directly on human skin</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240524115309.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Researchers have developed a method to make adaptive and eco-friendly sensors that can be directly and imperceptibly printed onto a wide range of biological surfaces, whether that's a finger or a flower petal.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 16:53:09 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>