<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:24:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Metformin’s secret brain pathway revealed after 60 years</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250910000256.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Metformin, long trusted for diabetes, turns out to work in the brain too. By shutting down Rap1 in the hypothalamus, the drug lowers blood sugar more ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:18:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists finally solve the mystery of ghostly halos on the ocean floor</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250910000244.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Barrels dumped off Southern California decades ago have been found leaking alkaline waste, not just DDT, leaving behind eerie white halos and transfor...</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 05:02:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The invisible plastic threat you can finally see</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250910000240.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Researchers in Germany and Australia have created a simple but powerful tool to detect nanoplastics—tiny, invisible particles that can slip through sk...</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 06:49:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sweat and food stains vanish under blue light</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250909031515.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Forget harsh bleach—scientists have discovered that powerful blue LED light can erase yellow stains from sweat, food, and oils without harming delicat...</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 05:13:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Don’t toss cannabis leaves. Scientists just found rare compounds inside</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250910000258.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Scientists at Stellenbosch University have uncovered a rare class of plant compounds, flavoalkaloids, in Cannabis leaves for the first time. Using adv...</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 12:10:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF National Quantum Virtual Laboratory speeds into the design phase</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-national-quantum-virtual-laboratory-speeds-design-phase</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation National Quantum Virtual Laboratory (NSF NQVL) is coming into sharper focus with the selection of the first four ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 15:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF announces funding to establish the National AI Research Resource Operations Center</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-funding-establish-national-ai-research</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation today announced a new solicitation to establish a National Artificial Intelligence Research Resource Operations C...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 15:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF expanding national AI infrastructure with new data systems and resources</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-expanding-national-ai-infrastructure-new-data-systems</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation today announced two major advancements in America's AI infrastructure: the launch of the Integrated Data Systems ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF announces new funding opportunities to advance AI education and build the STEM workforce of the future</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-new-funding-opportunities-advance-ai-education</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has announced two new Dear Colleague Letters (DCL) and one program solicitation that implement key elements of th...</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 20:03:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF and NVIDIA partnership enables Ai2 to develop fully open AI models to fuel U.S. scientific innovation</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-nvidia-partnership-enables-ai2-develop-fully-open-ai</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation announced a partnership with NVIDIA to develop a set of artificial intelligence models that will transform the ab...</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 13:07:12 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>