<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 11:02:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Fitness trackers are failing millions — this fix could change everything</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/06/250620030423.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Fitness trackers often fail people with obesity by underestimating their energy burn, leading to discouraging results and misguided health data. A sci...</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 08:04:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>One shot to stop HIV: MIT's bold vaccine breakthrough</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/06/250619090853.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Researchers from MIT and Scripps have unveiled a promising new HIV vaccine approach that generates a powerful immune response with just one dose. By c...</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 14:08:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Microscopic heist: How lung bacteria forge weapons to steal iron and survive</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/06/250619035515.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Researchers investigating the enigmatic and antibiotic-resistant Pandoraea bacteria have uncovered a surprising twist: these pathogens don't just pose...</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 08:55:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Massive thread of hot gas found linking galaxies — and it’s 10 times the mass of the Milky Way</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/06/250619035510.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Astronomers have uncovered a colossal, searing-hot filament of gas linking four galaxy clusters in the Shapley Supercluster a discovery that could fin...</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 08:55:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How life endured the Snowball Earth: Evidence from Antarctic meltwater ponds</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/06/250619090850.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>During Earth's ancient Snowball periods, when the entire planet was wrapped in ice, life may have endured in tiny meltwater ponds on the surface of eq...</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 14:08:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF ZEUS becomes the most powerful laser in the U.S.</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-zeus-becomes-most-powerful-laser-us</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation Zettawatt-Equivalent Ultrashort pulse laser System (NSF ZEUS) laser facility at the University of Michigan now ha...</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 14:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sparking curiosity in the future semiconductor workforce</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/sparking-curiosity-future-semiconductor-workforce</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>The United States semiconductor industry is projected to have between 60,000 and 100,000 unfilled jobs by 2030. As the need for semiconductor technici...</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 14:00:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Training AI to see more like humans</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/training-ai-see-more-humans</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>At Brown University, an innovative new project is revealing that teaching artificial intelligence to perceive things more like people may begin with s...</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 14:00:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Light from dawn of the universe observed by Earth-based telescopes</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/light-dawn-universe-observed-earth-based-telescopes</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>For the first time, scientists have used Earth-based telescopes funded by the U.S. National Science Foundation to look back over 13 billion years and ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 11:58:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Researchers discover microplastics at all ocean depths</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/researchers-discover-microplastics-all-ocean-depths</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Researchers with support from the U.S. National Science Foundation published a global benchmark of microplastic distribution in the ocean, revealing t...</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 14:00:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>