<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 07:04:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Mountain building linked to major extinction event half a billion years ago</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/mountain-building-linked-major-extinction-event</link><description>As life on Earth rapidly expanded a little over 500 million years ago during the "Cambrian explosion," Earth had tectonic plates slowly crashing into each other, building mountains and starting a series of unfortunate events that led to a mass…</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 22:57:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Ugly' fossil places extinct saber-toothed cat on Texas coast</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240530182207.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>This fossil looks like a lumpy, rounded rock with a couple of exposed teeth that are a little worse for wear, having been submerged and tumbled along the floor of the Gulf of Mexico for thousands of years before washing up on a beach. But when it was X-rayed a doctoral student saw there was more to the fossil that met the eye: a hidden canine tooth that had not yet erupted from the jaw bone. It was just what researchers needed to identify the fossil as belonging to a Homotherium, a genus of large cat that roamed much of the Earth for millions of years.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 23:22:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF and DOE partner on new internship opportunity in clean hydrogen energy</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-doe-partner-new-internship-opportunity-clean</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation and the Department of Energy, through its Office of Energy Efficiency and Renewable Energy (EERE), have initiated a joint training and professional development opportunity for NSF-supported graduate students in…</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 18:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Medium and mighty: Intermediate-mass black holes can survive in globular clusters</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240530182143.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>New research demonstrated a possible formation mechanism of intermediate-mass black holes in globular clusters, star clusters that could contain tens of thousands or even millions of tightly packed stars. The first ever star-by-star massive cluster-formation simulations revealed that sufficiently dense molecular clouds, the 'birthing nests' of star clusters, can give birth to very massive stars that evolve into intermediate-mass black holes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 23:21:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Climate change will make it harder to see the forest for the trees</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/climate-change-will-make-it-harder-see-forest</link><description>Individual trees can't move to escape climate change, and new U.S. National Science Foundation-supported research shows that species will be limited in their ability to migrate via seed dispersal and other methods because of a lack of symbiotic fungi…</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 14:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>People are altering decomposition rates in waterways</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240530182119.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Humans may be accelerating the rate at which organic matter decomposes in rivers and streams on a global scale, according to a new study. That could pose a threat to biodiversity in waterways around the world and increase the amount of carbon in Earth's atmosphere, potentially exacerbating climate change. The study is the first to combine a global experiment and predictive modeling to illustrate how human impacts to waterways may contribute to the global climate crisis.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 23:21:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-53</link><description>From testifying in front of the Senate Committee on Commerce, Science, and Transportation hearing to celebrating new graduates entering the STEM enterprise, this week NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan reinforced the significance of the agency's…</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 22:30:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Historic iceberg surges offer insights on modern climate change</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240530182110.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>A great armada entered the North Atlantic, launched from the cold shores of North America. But rather than ships off to war, this force was a fleet of icebergs. And the havoc it wrought was to the ocean current itself. The future of the Atlantic circulation will be determined by a tug-o-war between Greenland's decreasing ice flux and its increasing freshwater runoff.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 23:21:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Navajo Technical University partners with NSF center, creating new opportunities in materials research and education</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/navajo-technical-university-partners-nsf-center</link><description>A partnership that began in 2017 between Navajo Technical University (NTU) and the U.S. National Science Foundation Materials Research Science and Engineering Center at Harvard University is providing Navajo students with new opportunities to pursue…</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 17:30:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists develop visual tool to help people group foods based on their levels of processing</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240530182042.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Scientists studying ultra-processed foods have created a new tool for assessing the rewarding and reinforcing properties of foods that make up 58 percent of calories consumed in the United States. The foods have been linked to a wide range of negative health outcomes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 23:20:42 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>