<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 07:20:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Prolific potholes in the prairie star in award-winning short film</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/prolific-potholes-prairie-star-award-winning-short</link><description>Most of us think potholes are something to avoid. However, some potholes are worth protecting. The U.S. National Science Foundation is funding researchers to study prairie pothole wetlands, which are ecologically and economically important, but under…</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 14:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sleep resets brain connections -- but only for first few hours</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240501125828.htm</link><description>During sleep, the brain weakens the new connections between neurons that had been forged while awake -- but only during the first half of a night's sleep, according to a new study.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 17:58:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF and NIH partner on internship opportunity in biomedical engineering</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-nih-partner-internship-opportunity-biomedical</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation and the National Institutes of Health's National Institute of Biomedical Imaging and Bioengineering (NIBIB) have initiated a joint research training opportunity through the NSF Non-Academic Research Internships…</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 17:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists identify new brain circuit in mice that controls body's inflammatory reactions</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240501125818.htm</link><description>The brain can direct the immune system to an unexpected degree, capable of detecting, ramping up and tamping down inflammation, shows a new study in mice.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 17:58:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF and USDA join forces to boost innovation in agricultural robotics</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-usda-join-forces-boost-innovation-agricultural</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation and the U.S. Department of Agriculture's National Institute of Food and Agriculture (USDA NIFA) are teaming up to advance foundational research in agricultural robotics. The agencies are issuing a new Dear…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A 'cosmic glitch' in gravity</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240501125809.htm</link><description>Researchers have discovered a potential 'cosmic glitch' in the universe's gravity, explaining its strange behavior on a cosmic scale.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 17:58:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New center supported by NSF will catalyze data-driven insights in molecular and cellular biosciences</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/new-center-supported-nsf-will-catalyze-data-driven</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has made a $20 million award to support the creation of the National Synthesis Center for Emergence in the Molecular and Cellular Sciences (NCEMS). The center will combine vast amounts of available data on…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 14:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists work out the effects of exercise at the cellular level</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240501125227.htm</link><description>The health benefits of exercise are well known but new research shows that the body's response to exercise is more complex and far-reaching than previously thought. In a study on rats, a team of scientists has found that physical activity causes many cellular and molecular changes in all 19 of the organs they studied in the animals.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 17:52:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF honors 3 outstanding early-career researchers with the Alan T. Waterman Award</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-honors-3-outstanding-early-career-researchers</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation honored three researchers with the Alan T. Waterman Award, the nation's highest honor for early-career scientists and engineers. The 2024 recipients: Muyinatu A. Lediju Bell, a biomedical engineer at Johns Hopkins…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Earth-like environment likely on ancient Mars</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240501100729.htm</link><description>A research team using the ChemCam instrument onboard NASA's Curiosity rover discovered higher-than-usual amounts of manganese in lakebed rocks within Gale Crater on Mars, which indicates that the sediments were formed in a river, delta, or near the shoreline of an ancient lake.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 15:07:29 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>