<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 02:04:10 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>A new film on baffling Baffin Bay</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/new-film-baffling-baffin-bay</link><description>A new NSF-supported documentary follows the Baffin Bay Deglacial Experiment team on its journey to investigate what happened to the Greenland Ice Sheet over 15,000 years ago Although scientists know that the Earth has seen major climate changes from…</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 22:24:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Self-assembling, highly conductive sensors could improve wearable devices</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240701162218.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>To advance soft robotics, skin-integrated electronics and biomedical devices, researchers have developed a 3D-printed material that is soft and stretchable -- traits needed for matching the properties of tissues and organs -- and that self-assembles. Their approach employs a process that eliminates many drawbacks of previous fabrication methods, such as less conductivity or device failure, the team said.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:22:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deep-sea discovery opens up ocean of potential</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/deep-sea-discovery-opens-ocean-potential</link><description>New research by U.S. National Science Foundation-funded scientists making use of NSF facilities has provided insight into how related ocean creatures have adapted to live in vastly different environments. The study may also provide new knowledge…</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 20:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dampening the 'seeds' of hurricanes</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240701162212.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Increased atmospheric moisture may alter critical weather patterns over Africa, making it more difficult for the predecessors of many Atlantic hurricanes to form, according to a new study.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:22:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF awards $35M for networks to transform research capacity and competitiveness</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-awards-35m-networks-transform-research</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has awarded $35 million through the Established Program to Stimulate Competitive Research (EPSCoR) Research Incubators for STEM Excellence Research Infrastructure Improvement (E-RISE RII) to boost research…</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Layers of carbonate provide insight into the world of the ancient Romans</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240701131824.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Archaeologists face a major challenge when they intend to acquire information about buildings or facilities of which only ruins remain. This was a particular challenge for the remnants of the Roman water mills in Barbegal in Southern France, dating back to the 2nd century CE. This unique industrial complex consisted of 16 water wheels placed in parallel rows. Little could at first be deduced about the site from these now scant ruins -- except that the wheels were supplied by an aqueduct that brought water from the surrounding hills. Researchers have now unraveled the history of the mill complex using calcium carbonate deposits that are now stored in the Archaeological Museum of Arles. These deposits had formed towards the end of the roughly 100-year operational life of the Barbegal water mills on the sides and base of the wooden supply system that conveyed the water to the wheels.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:18:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF launches new investment to accelerate the transition of privacy-enhancing technologies to practice</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-launches-new-investment-accelerate-transition</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation yesterday published a new investment to advance privacy-enhancing technologies (PETs) and promote their use to solve real-world problems. The Privacy-Preserving Data Sharing in Practice (PDaSP) program, which…</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 15:20:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Largest ever genetic study of age of puberty in girls shows links with weight gain</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240701131723.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Genes can indirectly influence the age at which girls have their first period by accelerating weight gain in childhood, a known risk factor for early puberty. Other genes can directly affect age of puberty, some with profound effects.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:17:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Physicists create first-ever Bose-Einstein condensate made of molecules</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/physicists-create-first-ever-bose-einstein</link><description>A team of physicists has successfully created a unique quantum state of matter called a Bose-Einstein condensate (BEC) out of molecules. The team is led by Sebastian Will at Columbia University, who received a U.S. National Science Foundation Faculty…</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 20:53:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sixty-million-year-old grape seeds reveal how the death of the dinosaurs may have paved the way for grapes to spread</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240701131719.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Scientists discovered the oldest fossil grapes in the Western Hemisphere, which help show how after the death of the dinosaurs, grapes spread across the world.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:17:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>