<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 06:59:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NSF funds over $50M in new partnerships to broaden participation in materials science</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-funds-over-50m-new-partnerships-broaden</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation is announcing $50 million in Partnerships for Research and Education in Materials (PREM) awards to 15 collaborative research projects nationwide to expand participation and access to materials science-focused…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 14:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New drug shows promise in clearing HIV from brain</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240725193914.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>An experimental drug originally developed to treat cancer may help clear HIV from infected cells in the brain, according to a new study. By targeting infected cells in the brain, drug may clear virus from hidden areas that have been a major challenge in HIV treatment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 00:39:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jumping on the jumping gene bandwagon to speed up plant breeding</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/jumping-jumping-gene-bandwagon-speed-plant</link><description>Getting a new variety of corn, tomato, soybean or other crop to market can be a long and costly effort, with breeders working to ensure the eventual product has the right mix of genetics that will let it withstand change, produce large amounts of…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 18:48:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chemical analyses find hidden elements from renaissance astronomer Tycho Brahe's alchemy laboratory</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240725154836.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Danish Tycho Brahe was most famous for his contributions to astronomy. However, he also had a well-equipped alchemical laboratory where he produced secret medicines for Europe's elite.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 20:48:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Making strides in understanding decision making</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/making-strides-understanding-decision-making</link><description>Decisions, decisions. Life is full of decisions, from what to have for breakfast to where to work. To make each one, a series of mechanisms in the brain must be engaged. Understanding those mechanisms is an important area of neuroscience. To help…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 17:19:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nitrogen emissions have a net cooling effect: But researchers warn against a climate solution</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240725154823.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>An international team of researchers has found that nitrogen emissions from fertilizers and fossil fuels have a net cooling effect on the climate. But they warn increasing atmospheric nitrogen has further damaging effects on the environment, calling for an urgent reduction in greenhouse gas emissions to halt global warming.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 20:48:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>U.S. National Science Foundation and Department of Commerce partner to advance semiconductor workforce development</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-doc-partner-to-advance-semiconductor</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation and the CHIPS for America Research and Development Office within the National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST), a bureau of the U.S. Department of Commerce (DOC), signed a memorandum of understanding…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 15:28:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Zealand's flightless birds are retreating to moa refuges</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240725154812.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Researchers have found New Zealand's endangered flightless birds are seeking refuge in the locations where six species of moa last lived before going extinct.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 20:48:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF-backed SECURE Center will support research security, international collaboration</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-backed-secure-center-will-support-research</link><description>Today, the U.S. National Science Foundation announced a five-year $67 million investment establishing the Safeguarding the Entire Community of the U.S. Research Ecosystem (SECURE) ($50 million to University of Washington and $17 million to Texas A&amp;M…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 11:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Warming has more impact than cooling on Greenland's 'firn'</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240725154739.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>A new study finds disproportionate effects of temperature shifts on an icy glacier layer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 20:47:39 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>