<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 11:08:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Light from dawn of the universe observed by Earth-based telescopes</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/light-dawn-universe-observed-earth-based-telescopes</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>For the first time, scientists have used Earth-based telescopes funded by the U.S. National Science Foundation to look back over 13 billion years and ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 11:58:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Magnetic mayhem at the sun’s poles: First images reveal a fiery mystery</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/06/250616040223.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>For the first time in history, we re seeing the Sun from an angle no one ever has: from above and below its poles. Thanks to the European Space Agency...</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 09:02:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Single psilocybin trip delivers two years of depression relief for cancer patients</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/06/250616040215.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Psilocybin, the active ingredient in magic mushrooms, might just revolutionize how depression and anxiety are treated in cancer patients. In a groundb...</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 09:02:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Your brain has a hidden beat — and smarter minds sync to it</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/06/250616040220.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>When we focus, switch tasks, or face tough mental challenges, the brain starts to sync its internal rhythms, especially in the midfrontal region. A ne...</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 09:02:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Researchers discover microplastics at all ocean depths</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/researchers-discover-microplastics-all-ocean-depths</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Researchers with support from the U.S. National Science Foundation published a global benchmark of microplastic distribution in the ocean, revealing t...</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 14:00:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Galactic mystery: Why massive stars struggle to form in the Milky Way's center</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/06/250615023033.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>At the heart of our galaxy lies a cosmic puzzle: although the Galactic Center is packed with star-making material, massive stars form there surprising...</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 07:30:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tiny wasp’s shocking reproductive trick may transform global agriculture</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/06/250615021307.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Aphid-hunting wasps can reproduce with or without sex, challenging previous assumptions. This unique flexibility could boost sustainable pest control ...</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 07:13:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cholesterol crystal formation captured on video for first time, may lead to more effective treatments for high cholesterol</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/cholesterol-crystal-formation-captured-video-first-time-may</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>With support from the U.S. National Science Foundation, researchers at the University of Houston have captured the dynamics of microscopic cholesterol...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 17:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Predictive AI model could help forecast neurodegenerative diseases</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/predictive-ai-model-could-help-forecast-neurodegenerative</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Neurodegenerative diseases like Alzheimer's are a growing concern in the U.S., with over 7 million Americans living with Alzheimer's disease today. By...</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 16:00:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF announces new NextG wireless funding opportunity</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-new-nextg-wireless-funding-opportunity</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation today announced a new funding opportunity to support research and technology development that will improve the ne...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 14:01:39 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>