<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 12:07:30 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NSF appoints Micah Cheatham as chief management officer</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-appoints-micah-cheatham-chief-management</link><description>Today, the U.S. National Science Foundation is pleased to announce the appointment of Micah Cheatham as chief management officer (CMO). In this role, Cheatham will serve as principal advisor to the NSF director and deputy director on agency…</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fresh wind blows from historical supernova</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240705101157.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>A mysterious remnant from a rare type of supernova recorded in 1181 has been explained for the first time. Two white dwarf stars collided, creating a temporary 'guest star,' now labeled supernova (SN) 1181, which was recorded in historical documents in Japan and elsewhere in Asia. However, after the star dimmed, its location and structure remained a mystery until a team pinpointed its location in 2021. Now, through computer modeling and observational analysis, researchers have recreated the structure of the remnant white dwarf, a rare occurrence, explaining its double shock formation. They also discovered that high-speed stellar winds may have started blowing from its surface within just the past 20-30 years. This finding improves our understanding of the diversity of supernova explosions, and highlights the benefits of interdisciplinary research, combining history with modern astronomy to enable new discoveries about our galaxy.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 15:11:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Transformers: Cooler side of the grid</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/transformers-cooler-side-grid</link><description>In a significant step towards resilient, sustainable energy, researchers at The University of Texas at Austin (UT Austin) are undertaking a groundbreaking initiative to enhance the performance and longevity of grid transformers, a critical component…</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:19:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists discover new T cells and genes related to immune disorders</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240704201557.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Researchers have discovered several rare types of helper T cells that are associated with immune disorders such as multiple sclerosis, rheumatoid arthritis, and even asthma. The discoveries were made possible by a newly developed technology they call ReapTEC. The new T cell atlas is publicly available and should help in the development of new drug therapies for immune-mediated diseases.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 01:15:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Statement from NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan on the U.S. Economic Development Administration's Regional Technology and Innovation Hub awardees</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/statement-on-economic-development-admin-regional-tech-innovation</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation congratulates the U.S. Economic Development Administration (EDA) on its announcement today of its Regional Technology and Innovation Hubs (Tech Hubs). In alignment with the 'CHIPS and Science Act of 2022,' NSF and…</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The dawn of the Antarctic ice sheets</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240704201554.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>In recent years global warming has left its mark on the Antarctic ice sheets. The 'eternal' ice in Antarctica is melting faster than previously assumed, particularly in West Antarctica more than East Antarctica. The root for this could lie in its formation, as an international research team has now discovered: sediment samples from drill cores combined with complex climate and ice-sheet modelling show that permanent glaciation of Antarctica began around 34 million years ago -- but did not encompass the entire continent as previously assumed, but rather was confined to the eastern region of the continent (East Antarctica).</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 01:15:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Physicists' laser experiment excites atom's nucleus, may enable new type of atomic clock</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/physicists-laser-experiment-excites-atoms-nucleus</link><description>A team of researchers successfully raised the energy state of an atom's nucleus with a laser, which could lead to new precision measurement technology with orders of magnitude higher accuracy than today's best atomic clocks. The researchers embedded…</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 16:57:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Moon 'swirls' could be magnetized by unseen magmas</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240703131824.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Mysterious, light-colored swirls on Moon's surface could be rocks magnetized by magma activity underground, laboratory experiments confirm.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:18:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A new film on baffling Baffin Bay</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/new-film-baffling-baffin-bay</link><description>A new NSF-supported documentary follows the Baffin Bay Deglacial Experiment team on its journey to investigate what happened to the Greenland Ice Sheet over 15,000 years ago Although scientists know that the Earth has seen major climate changes from…</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 22:24:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A breakthrough in inexpensive, clean, fast-charging batteries</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240703131808.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Scientists have created an anode-free sodium solid-state battery. This brings the reality of inexpensive, fast-charging, high-capacity batteries for electric vehicles and grid storage closer than ever.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:18:08 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>