<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 01:36:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Radio astronomers and satellite internet provider develop new sky-sharing system</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/radio-astronomers-satellite-internet-provider</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>New techniques developed by the U.S. National Science Foundation National Radio Astronomy Observatory (NSF NRAO) and SpaceX enable radio astronomy telescopes to operate without interference from satellite transmissions. The techniques allow…</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 22:20:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Millions of years for plants to recover from global warming</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240809135943.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Catastrophic volcanic eruptions that warmed the planet millions of years ago shed new light on how plants evolve and regulate climate. Researchers reveal the long-term effects of disturbed natural ecosystems on climate in geological history and its implications for today.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 18:59:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF National Quantum Virtual Laboratory advances with first five pilot projects</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-national-quantum-virtual-laboratory-advances</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Realizing practical advantages and societal benefits from quantum-scale phenomena has been a long-sought milestone in quantum information science. The U.S. National Science Foundation today announced the initial $5 million investment across five…</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 14:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Potential new approach to enhancing stem-cell transplants</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240809135941.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>A discovery may boost the effectiveness of stem-cell transplants, commonly used for patients with cancer, blood disorders, or autoimmune diseases caused by defective stem cells, which produce all the body's different blood cells.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 18:59:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Massive genes allow golden algae to synthesize its toxin</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/massive-genes-allow-golden-algae-synthesize-its</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>The toxic golden alga, Prymnesium parvum, can cause mass mortality events involving fish, including the environmental disaster that impacted the Oder River in Europe in 2022, killing half the river's fish population. Now, NSF-supported researchers…</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 19:27:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Largest protein yet discovered builds algal toxins</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240809135939.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>While seeking to unravel how marine algae create their chemically complex toxins, scientists have discovered the largest protein yet identified in biology. Uncovering the biological machinery the algae evolved to make its intricate toxin also revealed previously unknown strategies for assembling chemicals, which could unlock the development of new medicines and materials.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 18:59:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF invests $7.6M in educational projects to build a skilled semiconductor manufacturing workforce in partnership with Intel Corporation</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-invests-76m-educational-projects-build-skilled</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Today, the U.S. National Science Foundation and Intel Corporation announced a $7.6 million investment in six projects to advance equitable STEM education and training opportunities that strengthen the nation's semiconductor workforce. This investment…</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Study reveals ways in which 40Hz sensory stimulation may preserve brain's 'white matter'</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240809135936.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Scientists report that gamma frequency light and sound stimulation preserves myelination in mouse models and reveal molecular mechanisms that may underlie the benefit.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 18:59:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Celebrating two years of “Chips and Science”</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/celebrating-two-years-chips-science</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>NSF unleashed critical investments to support use-inspired research and innovation in key technology areas and to support solutions to pressing national, societal and geostrategic challenges, as articulated in the “CHIPS and Science Act of 2022.” The…</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bacteria encode hidden genes outside their genome--do we?</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240809135927.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>A 'loopy' discovery in bacteria is raising fundamental questions about the makeup of our own genome -- and revealing a potential wellspring of material for new genetic therapies.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 18:59:27 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>