<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 06:57:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Three million years ago, our ancestors were vegetarian</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/01/250117112232.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Human ancestors like Australopithecus -- which lived around 3.5 million years ago in southern Africa -- ate very little to no meat, according to new r...</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 16:22:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The universe is expanding too fast to fit theories: Hubble tension in crisis</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/01/250117161235.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>The Universe really seems to be expanding fast. Too fast, even. A new measurement confirms what previous -- and highly debated -- results had shown: T...</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 21:12:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NASA's Hubble traces hidden history of Andromeda galaxy</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/01/250117171319.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>In the years following the launch of NASA's Hubble Space Telescope, astronomers have tallied over 1 trillion galaxies in the universe. But only one ga...</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 22:13:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Astrophysicists reveal structure of 74 exocomet belts orbiting nearby stars in landmark survey</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/01/250117112405.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Astrophysicists have imaged a large number of exocomet belts around nearby stars, and the tiny pebbles within them. The crystal-clear images show ligh...</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 16:24:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Insights into how populations conform or go against the crowd</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/01/250117171309.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Cultural traits -- the information, beliefs, behaviors, customs, and practices that shape the character of a population -- are influenced by conformit...</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 22:13:09 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>