<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 11:05:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>A hit of dopamine tells baby birds when their song practice is paying off</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/03/250325191424.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>By watching the ebb and flow of the brain's chemical signals, researchers are beginning to disentangle the molecular mechanisms underlying the intrins...</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:14:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fluorescent caves could explain how life persists in extraterrestrial environments</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/03/250325120148.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Deep below the Earth's surface, rock and mineral formations lay hidden with a secret brilliance. Under a black light, the chemicals fossilized within ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 17:01:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Postpartum female preference for cooler temperatures linked to brain changes</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/03/250325141530.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Mothers experience major metabolic adaptations during pregnancy and lactation to support the development and growth of the new life. Although many met...</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 19:15:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hydrophilic coating makes for unflappable golf balls</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/03/250325120145.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>The condition of the grass on a golf course can drastically skew the chances of a winning putt regardless of a player's skill. Now, a coating that soa...</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 17:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Low-sugar' vaccine can provide broad immunity against coronavirus variants</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/03/250325120154.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Early animal studies show that a single vaccine could protect the recipient from different variants of the coronaviruses that cause COVID-19, the flu ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 17:01:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chainmail-like polymer could be the future of body armor</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/chainmail-polymer-could-be-future-body-armor</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Researchers supported by grants and instrumentation provided by the U.S. National Science Foundation have created the first 2D polymer material that m...</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 19:34:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Unique skeletal tissue may enable new regenerative medical treatments</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/unique-skeletal-tissue-may-enable-new-regenerative-medical</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Supported by multiple grants from the U.S. National Science Foundation, researchers have comprehensively characterized the properties of a unique type...</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 16:25:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New method to keep protein-based drugs stable without refrigeration</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/new-method-keep-protein-based-drugs-stable-without</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>A team of researchers led by the recipient of a U.S. National Science Foundation Faculty Early Career Development grant has developed a new storage me...</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 16:28:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cutting-edge air quality monitoring strengthens public health nationwide</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/cutting-edge-air-quality-monitoring-strengthens-public</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>The fires that devastated many in Los Angeles in January 2025 not only scarred the landscape but also changed the air. A day after the Eaton fire burn...</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 15:20:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF-DOE Vera C. Rubin Observatory installs LSST Camera on telescope</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-doe-vera-c-rubin-observatory-installs-lsst-camera</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>NSF-DOE Vera C. Rubin Observatory, funded by the U.S. National Science Foundation and the U.S. Department of Energy’s Office of Science, has achieved ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 15:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>