<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 11:43:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Leopard spots and protein nanoclusters: How pattern rules could advance muscular dystrophy treatment</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/leopard-spots-protein-nanoclusters-how-pattern-rules-could</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Although a leopard cannot change its spots, new research funded by the U.S. National Science Foundation uses the principles that govern patterns like ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 13:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ancient Andes society used hallucinogens to strengthen social order</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/05/250505170814.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Snuff tubes uncovered at Chavin de Huantar in Peru reveal how leaders used mystical experiences to cement their power.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 22:08:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Black tea and berries could contribute to healthier aging</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/05/250505121914.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Higher intakes of black tea, berries, citrus fruits and apples could help to promote healthy aging, new research has found.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 17:19:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Big problem for fusion energy solved</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/05/250505170827.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>A new shortcut can help engineers design leak-proof magnetic confinement systems for fusion reactors 10 times as fast as the gold standard method, wit...</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 22:08:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Specialized sponge recycles minerals from stormwater for reuse in agriculture and other industries</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/specialized-sponge-recycles-minerals-stormwater-reuse</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Funded by multiple grants from the U.S. National Science Foundation, researchers created a functional sponge that can soak up certain pollutants from ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 15:44:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New study informs fire prevention strategies to save lives and property</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/new-study-informs-fire-prevention-strategies-save-lives</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>U.S. National Science Foundation-supported research shows that fires in populated areas are three times more likely to lead to premature deaths than w...</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 13:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gorilla study reveals complex pros and cons of friendship</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/05/250505170816.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Friendship comes with complex pros and cons -- possibly explaining why some individuals are less sociable, according to a new study of gorillas.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 22:08:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A long and ongoing look at the secrets of human longevity and healthy aging</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/05/250505171023.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Researchers participating in the Cilento Initiative on Aging Outcomes or CIAO study will gather in Acciaroli (Pollica-Cilento) Salerno, Italy to revie...</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 22:10:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From electronic bugs to real ones, methods for listening provide insights into communication and hearing</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/electronic-bugs-real-ones-methods-listening-provide-insights</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>A new study by U.S. National Science Foundation-funded researchers on how members of the animal world sense and react to sounds provides insight into ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 14:33:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In extreme conditions, heat does not flow between materials. It bounces off.</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/extreme-conditions-heat-does-not-flow-between-materials-it</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>A new study supported by the U.S. National Science Foundation shows, for the first time, how heat moves — or rather, doesn't — between materials in a ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 18:51:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>