<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 08:43:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NSF appoints Micah Cheatham as chief management officer</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-appoints-micah-cheatham-chief-management</link><description>Today, the U.S. National Science Foundation is pleased to announce the appointment of Micah Cheatham as chief management officer (CMO). In this role, Cheatham will serve as principal advisor to the NSF director and deputy director on agency…</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Creativity starts in the cradle, new research shows</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240710195507.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>New research indicates that babies can begin grasping complex language and ideas.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 00:55:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Transformers: Cooler side of the grid</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/transformers-cooler-side-grid</link><description>In a significant step towards resilient, sustainable energy, researchers at The University of Texas at Austin (UT Austin) are undertaking a groundbreaking initiative to enhance the performance and longevity of grid transformers, a critical component…</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:19:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A new species of extinct crocodile relative rewrites life on the Triassic coastline</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240710195436.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>The surprising discovery of a new species of extinct crocodile relative from the Triassic Favret Formation of Nevada, USA, rewrites the story of life along the coasts during the first act of the Age of Dinosaurs. The new species Benggwigwishingasuchus eremicarminis reveals that while giant ichthyosaurs ruled the oceans, the ancient crocodile kin known as pseudosuchian archosaurs ruled the shores across the Middle Triassic globe between 247.2 and 237 million years ago.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 00:54:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Statement from NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan on the U.S. Economic Development Administration's Regional Technology and Innovation Hub awardees</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/statement-on-economic-development-admin-regional-tech-innovation</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation congratulates the U.S. Economic Development Administration (EDA) on its announcement today of its Regional Technology and Innovation Hubs (Tech Hubs). In alignment with the 'CHIPS and Science Act of 2022,' NSF and…</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Combination treatment can increase human insulin-producing cells in vivo</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240710195355.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>In preclinical studies, a team of researchers report new findings on a therapeutic combination that regenerated human insulin-producing beta cells, providing a possible new treatment for diabetes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 00:53:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Physicists' laser experiment excites atom's nucleus, may enable new type of atomic clock</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/physicists-laser-experiment-excites-atoms-nucleus</link><description>A team of researchers successfully raised the energy state of an atom's nucleus with a laser, which could lead to new precision measurement technology with orders of magnitude higher accuracy than today's best atomic clocks. The researchers embedded…</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 16:57:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lion with nine lives breaks record with longest swim in predator-infested waters</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240710195340.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>A record-breaking swim by two lion brothers across a predator-infested African river has been documented in a new study. The researchers say the 1km swim is another example of iconic wildlife species having to make tough decisions to find homes and mates in a human-dominated world.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 00:53:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A new film on baffling Baffin Bay</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/new-film-baffling-baffin-bay</link><description>A new NSF-supported documentary follows the Baffin Bay Deglacial Experiment team on its journey to investigate what happened to the Greenland Ice Sheet over 15,000 years ago Although scientists know that the Earth has seen major climate changes from…</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 22:24:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mars likely had cold and icy past, new study finds</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240710195336.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>The question of whether Mars ever supported life has captivated the imagination of scientists and the public for decades. Central to the discovery is gaining insight into the past climate of Earth's neighbor: was the planet warm and wet, with seas and rivers much like those found on our own planet? Or was it frigid and icy, and therefore potentially less prone to supporting life as we know it? A new study finds evidence to support the latter by identifying similarities between soils found on Mars and those of Canada's Newfoundland, a cold subarctic climate.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 00:53:36 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>