<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 02:37:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>A deeper look into where the really big one could occur</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/deeper-look-where-really-big-one-could-occur</link><description>For the first time, NSF-funded researchers revealed a detailed look at the potential for a major earthquake off the coasts of southern British Columbia, Washington, Oregon and northern California. The new study characterizes the Cascadia Subduction…</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 17:28:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tiny New Zealand bird delivers a lesson in birdsong evolution</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240614141847.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Scientists are rethinking the evolution of vocal learning in birds. New Zealand's smallest bird, the rifleman or titipounamu, may have a rudimentary version of the talent possessed by parrots, hummingbirds and songbirds.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 19:18:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trouble dead ahead: Acidifying oceans harm tropical corals</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/trouble-dead-ahead-acidifying-oceans-harm-tropical</link><description>The French Polynesian island Moorea is the most beautiful isle in the world, some say. Its lagoons are surrounded by reefs dominated by Porites corals. These corals and other calcifying marine species are the world's primary reef-builders. Therein…</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 16:35:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sharks have depleted functional diversity compared to the last 66 million years</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240614141824.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>New research has found that sharks retained high levels of functional diversity for most of the last 66 million years, before steadily declining over the last 10 million years to its lowest value in the present day.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 19:18:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF and AACC announce 2024 Community College Innovation Challenge winners</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-aacc-2024-community-college-winners</link><description>Today, the U.S. National Science Foundation, in partnership with the American Association of Community Colleges (AACC), announced the three winning teams of the 2024 Community College Innovation Challenge (CCIC). The annual competition seeks to…</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:49:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Infectious H5N1 influenza virus in raw milk rapidly declines with heat treatment</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240614141822.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>The amount of infectious H5N1 influenza viruses in raw milk rapidly declined with heat treatment in laboratory research. However, small, detectable amounts of infectious virus remained in raw milk samples with high virus levels when treated at 72 degrees Celsius (161.6 degrees Fahrenheit) for 15 seconds -- one of the standard pasteurization methods used by the dairy industry. The authors of the study stress, however, that their findings reflect experimental conditions in a laboratory setting and are not identical to large-scale industrial pasteurization processes for raw milk.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 19:18:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cloudy with a chance of climate predictions</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/cloudy-chance-climate-predictions</link><description>Whether they're fluffy, bright or ominous, clouds are key to regulating Earth's energy and water cycles. Two sets of U.S. National Science Foundation-supported researchers recently published findings to help scientists better understand what's…</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 21:15:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pair plasmas found in deep space can now be generated in the lab</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240613161155.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Researchers have experimentally generated high-density relativistic electron-positron pair-plasma beams by producing two to three orders of magnitude more pairs than previously reported.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:11:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Cells to Galaxies' unites astronomers, medical imaging experts to advance both fields</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/cells-galaxies-unites-astronomers</link><description>In May 2024, experts from the U.S. National Science Foundation National Radio Astronomy Observatory (NSF NRAO) and the medical imaging field presented at the International Society for Magnetic Resonance in Medicine conference on the surprising…</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 15:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists preserve DNA in an amber-like polymer</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240613161153.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>With their 'T-REX' method, researchers developed a glassy, amber-like polymer that can be used for long-term storage of DNA, such as entire human genomes or digital files such as photos.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:11:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>