<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 15:17:10 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NSF partners with Micron and GlobalFoundries to invest in semiconductor workforce development at minority-serving institutions</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-partners-micron-globalfoundries-invest</link><description>Today, the U.S. National Science Foundation announced a new partnership with Micron Technology, Inc., and GlobalFoundries (GF) to increase access to equitable education and develop the next generation of a diverse, semiconductor-ready science…</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 14:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Drug-like inhibitor shows promise in preventing flu</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240521132302.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Currently available flu medications only target the virus after it has already established an infection, but what if a drug could prevent infection in the first place? Now, scientists have designed drug-like molecules to do just that, by thwarting the first stage of influenza infection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 18:23:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Statement by Director Sethuraman Panchanathan on NSF ranking in Best Places to Work in the Federal Government</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/statement-director-panchanathan-nsf-ranking-best-places-work</link><description>I am pleased to announce that the U.S. National Science Foundation has again been recognized among the 2023 Best Places to Work in the Federal Government®. NSF ranked No. 8 among mid-sized agencies as featured in a special edition released today by…</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 15:10:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cosmic rays illuminate the past</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240521124720.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Researchers have for the first time been able to pin down a prehistoric settlement of early farmers in northern Greece dating back more than 7,000 years to the year. For this they combined annual growth ring measurements on wooden building elements with the sudden spike of cosmogenic radiocarbon in 5259 BC. This provides a reliable chronological reference point for many other archaeological sites in Southeast Europe.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 17:47:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF planning major infrastructure overhaul to support future research in South Pole</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-planning-major-infrastructure-overhaul-support</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation released the draft of its South Pole Station Master Plan (SPSMP), which will inform investments planned under the NSF Antarctic Infrastructure Recapitalization program and ensure that the mission and priorities of…</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 14:39:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Complete Stellar Collapse: Unusual star system proves that stars can die quietly</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240521124700.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>University of Copenhagen astrophysicists help explain a mysterious phenomenon, whereby stars suddenly vanish from the night sky. Their study of an unusual binary star system has resulted in convincing evidence that massive stars can completely collapse and become black holes without a supernova explosion.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 17:47:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF announces pilot phase and anticipated opening date of Arecibo C3 at the site of the NSF Arecibo Observatory Historic District in Puerto Rico</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-pilot-phase-anticipated-opening-date-of-arecibo</link><description>| En Español | As excitement builds for the grand opening of the new U.S. National Science Foundation Arecibo Center for Culturally Relevant and Inclusive Science Education, Computational Skills, and Community Engagement (NSF Arecibo C3), anticipated…</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 16:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Researchers discover hidden step in dinosaur feather evolution</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240521124309.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Scientists discover 'zoned development' in dinosaur skin, with zones of reptile-style scales and zones of bird-like skin with feathers. A new dinosaur skin fossil has been found to be composed of silica -- the same as glass.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 17:43:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-51</link><description>This week was full of celebrations and milestones — including recognizing NSF staff and public servants for their hard work to better the nation; celebrating teachers for their dedication to educating the next generation of scientists, engineers and…</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 22:11:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Warming climate intensifies flash droughts worldwide</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240521124249.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Sudden, severe dry spells known as flash droughts are rising in intensity around the world, with a notable exception in mountainous Central Asia, where flash drought extent is shrinking, according to new research. Heat and changes to precipitation patterns caused by a warming climate are driving these trends, the study found.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 17:42:49 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>