<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 15:49:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NSF National Quantum Virtual Laboratory advances with first five pilot projects</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-national-quantum-virtual-laboratory-advances</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Realizing practical advantages and societal benefits from quantum-scale phenomena has been a long-sought milestone in quantum information science. The U.S. National Science Foundation today announced the initial $5 million investment across five…</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 14:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Study reveals ways in which 40Hz sensory stimulation may preserve brain's 'white matter'</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240809135936.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Scientists report that gamma frequency light and sound stimulation preserves myelination in mouse models and reveal molecular mechanisms that may underlie the benefit.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 18:59:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Massive genes allow golden algae to synthesize its toxin</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/massive-genes-allow-golden-algae-synthesize-its</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>The toxic golden alga, Prymnesium parvum, can cause mass mortality events involving fish, including the environmental disaster that impacted the Oder River in Europe in 2022, killing half the river's fish population. Now, NSF-supported researchers…</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 19:27:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bacteria encode hidden genes outside their genome--do we?</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240809135927.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>A 'loopy' discovery in bacteria is raising fundamental questions about the makeup of our own genome -- and revealing a potential wellspring of material for new genetic therapies.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 18:59:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF invests $7.6M in educational projects to build a skilled semiconductor manufacturing workforce in partnership with Intel Corporation</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-invests-76m-educational-projects-build-skilled</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Today, the U.S. National Science Foundation and Intel Corporation announced a $7.6 million investment in six projects to advance equitable STEM education and training opportunities that strengthen the nation's semiconductor workforce. This investment…</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Greenland mega-tsunami led to week-long oscillating fjord wave</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240809135909.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>In September 2023, a megatsunami in remote eastern Greenland sent seismic waves around the world, piquing the interest of the global research community. The event created a week-long oscillating wave in Dickson Fjord, according to a new report in The Seismic Record.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 18:59:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF promotes the transition to a circular economy in advanced materials</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-promotes-transition-circular-economy-advanced</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation, in partnership with Australia's national science agency, Commonwealth Scientific and Industrial Research Organisation (CSIRO), are investing in solutions that will accelerate the transition of materials…</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New technology uses light to engrave erasable 3D images</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240809135709.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Researchers invented a technique that uses a specialized light projector and a photosensitive chemical additive to imprint two- and three-dimensional images inside any polymer. The light-based engraving remains in the polymer until heat or light are applied, which erases the image and makes it ready to use again. The technology is intended for any situation where having detailed, precise visual data in a compact and easily customizable format could be critical, such as planning surgeries and developing architectural designs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 18:57:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Celebrating two years of “Chips and Science”</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/celebrating-two-years-chips-science</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>NSF unleashed critical investments to support use-inspired research and innovation in key technology areas and to support solutions to pressing national, societal and geostrategic challenges, as articulated in the “CHIPS and Science Act of 2022.” The…</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Record-breaking recovery of rocks that originated in Earth's mantle could reveal secrets of planet's history</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240809135650.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Scientists have recovered the first long section of rocks that originated in the Earth's mantle, the layer below the crust and the planet's largest component. The rocks will help unravel the mantle's role in the origins of life on Earth, the volcanic activity generated when it melts, and how it drives the global cycles of important elements such as carbon and hydrogen. .</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 18:56:50 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>