<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 02:02:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-53</link><description>From testifying in front of the Senate Committee on Commerce, Science, and Transportation hearing to celebrating new graduates entering the STEM enterprise, this week NSF Director Sethuraman Panchanathan reinforced the significance of the agency's…</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 22:30:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI headphones let wearer listen to a single person in a crowd, by looking at them just once</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240524171429.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Engineers have developed an artificial intelligence system that lets someone wearing headphones look at a person speaking for three to five seconds to 'enroll' them. The system then plays just the enrolled speaker's voice in real time, even as the pair move around in noisy environments.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 22:14:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Navajo Technical University partners with NSF center, creating new opportunities in materials research and education</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/navajo-technical-university-partners-nsf-center</link><description>A partnership that began in 2017 between Navajo Technical University (NTU) and the U.S. National Science Foundation Materials Research Science and Engineering Center at Harvard University is providing Navajo students with new opportunities to pursue…</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 17:30:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Key role of plant-bacteria communication for the assembly of a healthy plant microbiome supporting sustainable plant nutrition</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240523205054.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>In an interdisciplinary study, researchers discovered that symbiotic bacteria communicate with legume plants through specific molecules and that this communication influences which bacteria grow near the plant roots. The findings provide insights into how plants and soil bacteria form beneficial partnerships for nutrient uptake and resilience. These results are a step towards understanding how communication between plants and soil bacteria can lead to specific beneficial associations providing plants with nutrients.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 01:50:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF invests $36M in computing projects that promise to maximize performance, reduce energy demands</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-invests-36m-computing-projects-promise</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation is awarding $36 million to three projects selected for their potential to revolutionize computing and make significant impacts in reducing the carbon footprint of the lifecycle of computers. Funding for the…</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 17:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Birth of universe's earliest galaxies observed for first time</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240523153708.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Researchers have now seen the formation of three of the earliest galaxies in the universe, more than 13 billion years ago. The sensational discovery contributes important knowledge about the universe.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 20:37:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-52</link><description>On May 16, U.S. National Science Foundation Director Sethuraman Panchanathan, alongside Former Chair of the National Science Board Chair Dan Reed, testified to the House Committee on Science, Space and Technology Subcommittee on Research and…</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 18:25:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists map networks regulating gene function in the human brain</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240523153702.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>A consortium of researchers has produced the largest and most advanced multidimensional maps of gene regulation networks in the brains of people with and without mental disorders. These maps detail the many regulatory elements that coordinate the brain's biological pathways and cellular functions. The research used postmortem brain tissue from over 2,500 donors to map gene regulation networks across different stages of brain development and multiple brain-related disorders.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 20:37:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Largest camera ever built arrives at Rubin Observatory in Chile</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/largest-camera-ever-built-arrives-rubin</link><description>The 3,200-megapixel Legacy Survey of Space and Time (LSST) camera, the groundbreaking instrument at the core of the NSF-DOE Vera C. Rubin Observatory, has arrived at the observatory site on Cerro Pachón in Chile. The U.S. National Science Foundation…</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 15:44:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Birdsong and human voice built from same genetic blueprint</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240523153629.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Humans have been long fascinated by bird song and the cacophony of other avian sounds -- from coos and honks to quacks and peeps. But little is known about how the unique vocal organ of birds -- the syrinx -- varies from species to species or its deeper evolutionary origins. A trio of recent studies is changing that. The studies include high-resolution anatomical scans of syrinxes from hummingbirds and ostriches -- the world's smallest and largest bird species -- and the discovery that the syrinx and larynx, the vocal organ of reptiles and mammals, including humans, share the same developmental programming.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 20:36:29 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>