<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 06:56:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NSF invites K-12 students to design their own video games and compete for Game Maker Awards</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-invites-k-12-students-design-their-own-video</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation announces the NSF Game Maker Awards "Life in 2100" competition for K-12 students. To commemorate the agency’s milestone 75th anniversary, this competition invites students to create video games that imagine life…</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 15:10:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Brain wiring is guided by activity even in very early development</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240815185851.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>In humans, the process of learning is driven by different groups of cells in the brain firing together. For instance, when the neurons associated with the process of recognizing a dog begin to fire in a coordinated manner in response to the cells that encode the features of a dog -- four legs, fur, a tail, etc. -- a young child will eventually be able to identify dogs going forward. But brain wiring begins before humans are born, before they have experiences or senses like sight to guide this cellular circuitry. How does that happen?</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 23:58:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Studying the journey, not the destination, provides new insight into songbird migrations</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/studying-journey-into-songbird-migrations</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>New research supported by the U.S. National Science Foundation using two decades worth of data could change how scientists think about bird migrations and the interdependencies and relationships they involve. Driving any long distance usually…</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 20:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cleaning up the aging brain: Scientists restore brain's trash disposal system</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240815124156.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Scientists have restored the brain's waste-clearing process in aging mice, offering potential new treatment for Alzheimer's and Parkinson's using existing drugs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 17:41:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>This week, NSF marked the second anniversary of the "CHIPS and Science Act of 2022," signed into law on August 9, 2022. This landmark legislation has empowered NSF to accelerate innovation and build a resilient, inclusive, and productive American…</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:27:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zebrafish use surprising strategy to regrow spinal cord</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240815124154.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>A new study maps out a detailed atlas of all the cells involved in regenerating the zebrafish spinal cord. In an unexpected finding, the researchers showed that survival and adaptability of the severed neurons themselves is required for full spinal cord regeneration. Surprisingly, the study showed that stem cells capable of forming new neurons play a complementary role but don t lead the process.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 17:41:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Radio astronomers and satellite internet provider develop new sky-sharing system</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/radio-astronomers-satellite-internet-provider</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>New techniques developed by the U.S. National Science Foundation National Radio Astronomy Observatory (NSF NRAO) and SpaceX enable radio astronomy telescopes to operate without interference from satellite transmissions. The techniques allow…</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 22:20:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Intelligent soft robotic clothing for automatic thermal adaptation in extreme heat</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240815124142.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>As global warming intensifies, people increasingly suffer from extreme heat. For those working in a high-temperature environment indoors or outdoors, keeping thermally comfortable becomes particularly crucial. A team has now developed thermally-insulated and breathable soft robotic clothing that can automatically adapt to changing ambient temperatures, thereby helping to ensure worker safety in hot environments.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 17:41:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF National Quantum Virtual Laboratory advances with first five pilot projects</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-national-quantum-virtual-laboratory-advances</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Realizing practical advantages and societal benefits from quantum-scale phenomena has been a long-sought milestone in quantum information science. The U.S. National Science Foundation today announced the initial $5 million investment across five…</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 14:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why do plants wiggle? New study provides answers</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/08/240815124139.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Decades after his voyage on the HMS Beagle, Charles Darwin became fascinated by why plants move as they grow -- spinning and twisting into corkscrews. Now, more than 150 years later, a new study may have solved the riddle.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 17:41:39 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>