<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>BUscience</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from BUscience, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 06:48:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>A volcano erased an island’s plants. Their DNA revealed how life starts over</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250915202828.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Volcanic eruptions on the remote island of Nishinoshima repeatedly wipe the land clean, giving scientists a rare chance to study life’s earliest stage...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 04:33:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Strange ‘leopard spots’ in a Mars rock could be the strongest hint of life yet</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250916032210.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>NASA’s Perseverance rover has delivered its most compelling clue yet in the search for life on Mars. A rock sample called “Sapphire Canyon,” taken fro...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 08:31:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hubble just revealed the fiery heart of the Cigar Galaxy</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250915205900.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Behind the dusty clouds of the Cigar Galaxy lies a dazzling powerhouse of star formation, where stars are being born ten times faster than in the Milk...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 02:07:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stress measured in hair could predict depression and anxiety in children</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250915202834.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Researchers from the University of Waterloo discovered that measuring long-term stress through children’s hair samples can reveal early signs of menta...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 07:47:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists just found the “master switch” for plant growth</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250915202831.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Scientists at Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory have cracked open the secrets of plant stem cells, mapping key genetic regulators in maize and Arabidopsis...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 07:28:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF invests $6.2 million in EPSCoR Research Fellows</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-invests-62-million-epscor-research-fellows</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation is investing $6.2 million in 24 exceptional researchers who have been selected as NSF Established Program to Stim...</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 15:00:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF National Quantum Virtual Laboratory speeds into the design phase</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-national-quantum-virtual-laboratory-speeds-design-phase</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation National Quantum Virtual Laboratory (NSF NQVL) is coming into sharper focus with the selection of the first four ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 15:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF announces funding to establish the National AI Research Resource Operations Center</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-funding-establish-national-ai-research</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation today announced a new solicitation to establish a National Artificial Intelligence Research Resource Operations C...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 15:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF expanding national AI infrastructure with new data systems and resources</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-expanding-national-ai-infrastructure-new-data-systems</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation today announced two major advancements in America's AI infrastructure: the launch of the Integrated Data Systems ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF announces new funding opportunities to advance AI education and build the STEM workforce of the future</title><link>https://www.nsf.gov/news/nsf-announces-new-funding-opportunities-advance-ai-education</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has announced two new Dear Colleague Letters (DCL) and one program solicitation that implement key elements of th...</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 20:03:56 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>