<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 11:55:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NSF-led National AI Research Resource Pilot awards first round access to 35 projects in partnership with DOE</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-led-national-ai-research-resource-pilot-awards</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation and the Department of Energy are thrilled to announce the first 35 projects that will be supported with computational time through the National Artificial Intelligence Research Resource (NAIRR) Pilot, marking a…</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Did a magnetic field collapse trigger the emergence of animals?</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240503135331.htm</link><description>Researchers uncovered compelling evidence that Earth's magnetic field was in a highly unusual state when the macroscopic animals of the Ediacaran Period -- 635 to 541 million years ago -- diversified and thrived. Their study raises the question of whether these fluctuations in Earth's ancient magnetic field led to shifts in oxygen levels that may have been crucial to the proliferation of life forms millions of years ago.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 18:53:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan (May 3, 2024)</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-may-3-2024</link><description>This week, Sethuraman Panchanathan, director of the U.S. National Science Foundation, has been actively forwarding science, education and engineering initiatives through meaningful collaborations with congressional leaders and NSF researchers. His…</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 22:19:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ice shelves fracture under weight of meltwater lakes</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240503135322.htm</link><description>Heavy pooling meltwater can fracture ice, potentially leading to ice shelf collapse.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 18:53:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rubin Observatory's newly coated mirror will reflect the ever-changing universe with unparalleled completeness</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/rubin-observatorys-newly-coated-mirror-will</link><description>The Vera C. Rubin Observatory, a research facility under construction in Chile and funded by the U.S. National Science Foundation and the U.S. Department of Energy's Office of Science, achieved a major milestone on April 27, 2024, with the successful…</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 15:44:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stretchable e-skin could give robots human-level touch sensitivity</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240503111943.htm</link><description>A stretchy electronic skin could equip robots and other devices with the same softness and touch sensitivity as human skin, opening up new possibilities to perform tasks that require a great deal of precision and control of force.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 16:19:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF and industry partners announce sustainable polymer research funding opportunity</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-industry-partners-announce-sustainable-polymer</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has launched a $9.5 million research funding opportunity in partnership with BASF, Dow, IBM, PepsiCo Inc. and Procter &amp; Gamble Co. Sustainable Polymers Enabled by Emerging Data Analytics (SPEED) is part of NSF's…</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 18:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Gap' in carbon removal: Countries' plans to remove CO2 not enough</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240503111933.htm</link><description>New research suggests that countries' current plans to remove CO2 from the atmosphere will not be enough to comply with the 1.5 C warming limit set out under the Paris Agreement.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 16:19:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New NSF grant targets large language models and generative AI, exploring how they work and implications for societal impacts</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/new-nsf-grant-targets-large-language-models</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has announced a grant of $9 million to Northeastern University for research to investigate how large language models (LLMs) and generative AI operate, focusing on the computing process called deep inference and AI…</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists track 'doubling' in origin of cancer cells</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240502141250.htm</link><description>Working with human breast and lung cells, scientists say they have charted a molecular pathway that can lure cells down a hazardous path of duplicating their genome too many times, a hallmark of cancer cells.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 19:12:50 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>