<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 06:57:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NSF invests $36M in computing projects that promise to maximize performance, reduce energy demands</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-invests-36m-computing-projects-promise</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation is awarding $36 million to three projects selected for their potential to revolutionize computing and make significant impacts in reducing the carbon footprint of the lifecycle of computers. Funding for the…</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 17:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Birth of universe's earliest galaxies observed for first time</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240523153708.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Researchers have now seen the formation of three of the earliest galaxies in the universe, more than 13 billion years ago. The sensational discovery contributes important knowledge about the universe.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 20:37:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-52</link><description>On May 16, U.S. National Science Foundation Director Sethuraman Panchanathan, alongside Former Chair of the National Science Board Chair Dan Reed, testified to the House Committee on Science, Space and Technology Subcommittee on Research and…</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 18:25:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists map networks regulating gene function in the human brain</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240523153702.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>A consortium of researchers has produced the largest and most advanced multidimensional maps of gene regulation networks in the brains of people with and without mental disorders. These maps detail the many regulatory elements that coordinate the brain's biological pathways and cellular functions. The research used postmortem brain tissue from over 2,500 donors to map gene regulation networks across different stages of brain development and multiple brain-related disorders.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 20:37:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Largest camera ever built arrives at Rubin Observatory in Chile</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/largest-camera-ever-built-arrives-rubin</link><description>The 3,200-megapixel Legacy Survey of Space and Time (LSST) camera, the groundbreaking instrument at the core of the NSF-DOE Vera C. Rubin Observatory, has arrived at the observatory site on Cerro Pachón in Chile. The U.S. National Science Foundation…</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 15:44:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Study explains why the brain can robustly recognize images, even without color</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240523153624.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>New research offers a possible explanation for how the brain learns to identify both color and black-and-white images. The researchers found evidence that early in life, when the retina is unable to process color information, the brain learns to distinguish objects based on luminance, rather than color.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 20:36:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF partners with Micron and GlobalFoundries to invest in semiconductor workforce development at minority-serving institutions</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-partners-micron-globalfoundries-invest</link><description>Today, the U.S. National Science Foundation announced a new partnership with Micron Technology, Inc., and GlobalFoundries (GF) to increase access to equitable education and develop the next generation of a diverse, semiconductor-ready science…</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 14:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A promising approach to develop a birth control pill for men</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240523153614.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Researchers show in animal models that a novel, non-hormonal sperm-specific approach offers a promising option for reversible human male contraception.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 20:36:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Statement by Director Sethuraman Panchanathan on NSF ranking in Best Places to Work in the Federal Government</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/statement-director-panchanathan-nsf-ranking-best-places-work</link><description>I am pleased to announce that the U.S. National Science Foundation has again been recognized among the 2023 Best Places to Work in the Federal Government®. NSF ranked No. 8 among mid-sized agencies as featured in a special edition released today by…</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 15:10:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Intriguing nearby world sized between Earth, Venus</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/05/240523153445.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Astronomers have discovered a planet between the sizes of Earth and Venus only 40 light-years away.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 20:34:45 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>