<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 06:45:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>A new film on baffling Baffin Bay</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/new-film-baffling-baffin-bay</link><description>A new NSF-supported documentary follows the Baffin Bay Deglacial Experiment team on its journey to investigate what happened to the Greenland Ice Sheet over 15,000 years ago Although scientists know that the Earth has seen major climate changes from…</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 22:24:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Analysis suggests 2021 Texas abortion ban resulted in increase in infant deaths in state in year after law went into effect</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240627174235.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Researchers use statistical modeling to estimate infant deaths expected if one of the country's most stringent state abortion laws had not been enacted. The study estimates that infant deaths in Texas increased more than expected in the year following the state's 2021 ban on abortion in early pregnancy, especially among infants with congenital anomalies.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 22:42:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deep-sea discovery opens up ocean of potential</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/deep-sea-discovery-opens-ocean-potential</link><description>New research by U.S. National Science Foundation-funded scientists making use of NSF facilities has provided insight into how related ocean creatures have adapted to live in vastly different environments. The study may also provide new knowledge…</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 20:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The density difference of sub-Neptunes finally deciphered</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240627172226.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>The majority of stars in our galaxy are home to planets. The most abundant are the sub-Neptunes, planets between the size of Earth and Neptune. Calculating their density poses a problem for scientists: depending on the method used to measure their mass, two populations are highlighted, the dense and the less dense. Is this due to an observational bias or the physical existence of two distinct populations of sub-Neptunes? Recent work argues for the latter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 22:22:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF awards $35M for networks to transform research capacity and competitiveness</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-awards-35m-networks-transform-research</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has awarded $35 million through the Established Program to Stimulate Competitive Research (EPSCoR) Research Incubators for STEM Excellence Research Infrastructure Improvement (E-RISE RII) to boost research…</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Antarctic ice shelves hold twice as much meltwater as previously thought</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240627172211.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Slush -- water-soaked snow -- makes up more than half of all meltwater on the Antarctic ice shelves during the height of summer, yet is poorly accounted for in regional climate models. The findings could have profound implications for ice shelf stability and sea level rise.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 22:22:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF launches new investment to accelerate the transition of privacy-enhancing technologies to practice</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-launches-new-investment-accelerate-transition</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation yesterday published a new investment to advance privacy-enhancing technologies (PETs) and promote their use to solve real-world problems. The Privacy-Preserving Data Sharing in Practice (PDaSP) program, which…</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 15:20:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Last surviving woolly mammoths were inbred but not doomed to extinction</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240627172101.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>The last population of woolly mammoths was isolated on Wrangel Island off the coast of Siberia 10,000 years ago, when sea levels rose and cut the mountainous island off from the mainland. A new genomic analysis reveals that the isolated mammoths, who lived on the island for the subsequent 6,000 years, originated from at most 8 individuals but grew to 200--300 individuals within 20 generations. The researchers report that the Wrangel Island mammoths' genomes showed signs of inbreeding and low genetic diversity but not to the extent that it can explain their ultimate (and mysterious) extinction.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 22:21:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Physicists create first-ever Bose-Einstein condensate made of molecules</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/physicists-create-first-ever-bose-einstein</link><description>A team of physicists has successfully created a unique quantum state of matter called a Bose-Einstein condensate (BEC) out of molecules. The team is led by Sebastian Will at Columbia University, who received a U.S. National Science Foundation Faculty…</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 20:53:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Common plastics could passively cool and heat buildings with the seasons</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/06/240627172053.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>By restricting radiant heat flows between buildings and their environment to specific wavelengths, coatings engineered from common materials can achieve energy savings and thermal comfort that goes beyond what traditional building envelopes can achieve.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 22:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>