<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 15:43:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NSF and USDA join forces to boost innovation in agricultural robotics</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-usda-join-forces-boost-innovation-agricultural</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation and the U.S. Department of Agriculture's National Institute of Food and Agriculture (USDA NIFA) are teaming up to advance foundational research in agricultural robotics. The agencies are issuing a new Dear…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Climate change could become the main driver of biodiversity decline by mid-century</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/04/240425161518.htm</link><description>Global biodiversity has declined between 2% and 11% during the 20th century due to land-use change alone, according to a large multi-model study. Projections show climate change could become the main driver of biodiversity decline by the mid-21st century.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 21:15:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New center supported by NSF will catalyze data-driven insights in molecular and cellular biosciences</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/new-center-supported-nsf-will-catalyze-data-driven</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation has made a $20 million award to support the creation of the National Synthesis Center for Emergence in the Molecular and Cellular Sciences (NCEMS). The center will combine vast amounts of available data on…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 14:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Food in sight? The liver is ready!</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/04/240425161504.htm</link><description>What happens in the body when we are hungry and see and smell food? A team of researchers has now been able to show in mice that adaptations in the liver mitochondria take place after only a few minutes. Stimulated by the activation of a group of nerve cells in the brain, the mitochondria of the liver cells change and prepare the liver for the adaptation of the sugar metabolism. The findings could open up new avenues for the treatment of type 2 diabetes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 21:15:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF honors 3 outstanding early-career researchers with the Alan T. Waterman Award</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-honors-3-outstanding-early-career-researchers</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation honored three researchers with the Alan T. Waterman Award, the nation's highest honor for early-career scientists and engineers. The 2024 recipients: Muyinatu A. Lediju Bell, a biomedical engineer at Johns Hopkins…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>With hybrid brains, these mice smell like a rat</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/04/240425131554.htm</link><description>Mice lacking an olfactory system have had their sense of smell restored with neurons from rats, the first time scientists have successfully integrated the sensory apparatus of one species into another.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 18:15:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF invests $90M in innovative national scientific cyberinfrastructure for transforming STEM education</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-invests-90m-innovative-national-scientific</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation announced today a strategic investment of $90 million over five years in SafeInsights, a unique national scientific cyberinfrastructure aimed at transforming learning research and STEM education. Funded through…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:30:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How do birds flock? Researchers do the math to reveal previously unknown aerodynamic phenomenon</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/04/240425131416.htm</link><description>How do birds fly in a coordinated and seemingly effortless fashion? Part of the answer lies in precise, and previously unknown, aerodynamic interactions, reports a team of mathematicians. Its breakthrough broadens our understanding of wildlife, including fish, who move in schools, and could have applications in transportation and energy.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 18:14:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This week with NSF Director Panchanathan</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/week-nsf-director-panchanathan-49</link><description>This week, US National Science Foundation Director worked to strengthen pathways into STEM and expand the agency’s reach in communities across the nation and world. At the Arctic Encounter Symposium, Director Panchanathan took center stage alongside…</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 20:37:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Human activities have an intense impact on Earth's deep subsurface fluid flow</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/04/240424182458.htm</link><description>Hydrologists predict human-induced underground fluid fluxes to rise with climate change mitigation strategies like carbon sequestration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 23:24:58 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>