<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 03:02:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NSF funds over $50M in new partnerships to broaden participation in materials science</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-funds-over-50m-new-partnerships-broaden</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation is announcing $50 million in Partnerships for Research and Education in Materials (PREM) awards to 15 collaborative research projects nationwide to expand participation and access to materials science-focused…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 14:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Dancing molecules' heal cartilage damage</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240726193211.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>New therapy uses synthetic nanofibers to mimic the natural signaling of a protein that is crucial for cartilage formation and maintenance. Researchers found that intensifying the motion of molecules within the nanofibers led to more components needed for regeneration. After just four hours, the treatment activated the gene expression necessary to generate cartilage. Therapy could be used to treat osteoarthritis, which affects nearly 530 million people worldwide.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 00:32:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jumping on the jumping gene bandwagon to speed up plant breeding</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/jumping-jumping-gene-bandwagon-speed-plant</link><description>Getting a new variety of corn, tomato, soybean or other crop to market can be a long and costly effort, with breeders working to ensure the eventual product has the right mix of genetics that will let it withstand change, produce large amounts of…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 18:48:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New understanding of fly behavior has potential application in robotics, public safety</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240726113422.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Scientists have identified an automatic behavior in flies that helps them assess wind conditions -- its presence and direction -- before deploying a strategy to follow a scent to its source. The fact that they can do this is surprising -- can you tell if there's a gentle breeze if you stick your head out of a moving car? Flies aren't just reacting to an odor with a preprogrammed response: they are responding in context-appropriate manner. This knowledge potentially could be applied to train more sophisticated algorithms for scent-detecting drones to find the source of chemical leaks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 16:34:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Making strides in understanding decision making</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/making-strides-understanding-decision-making</link><description>Decisions, decisions. Life is full of decisions, from what to have for breakfast to where to work. To make each one, a series of mechanisms in the brain must be engaged. Understanding those mechanisms is an important area of neuroscience. To help…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 17:19:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lampreys possess a 'jaw-dropping' evolutionary origin</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240726113343.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Lampreys are one of only two living jawless vertebrates Jaws are formed by a key stem cell population called the neural crest New research reveals the gene regulatory changes that may explain morphological differences between jawed and jawless vertebrates.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 16:33:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>U.S. National Science Foundation and Department of Commerce partner to advance semiconductor workforce development</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-doc-partner-to-advance-semiconductor</link><description>The U.S. National Science Foundation and the CHIPS for America Research and Development Office within the National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST), a bureau of the U.S. Department of Commerce (DOC), signed a memorandum of understanding…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 15:28:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Researchers develop state-of-the-art device to make artificial intelligence more energy efficient</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240726113337.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>Engineering researchers have demonstrated a state-of-the-art hardware device that could reduce energy consumption for artificial intelligent (AI) computing applications by a factor of at least 1,000.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 16:33:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF-backed SECURE Center will support research security, international collaboration</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-backed-secure-center-will-support-research</link><description>Today, the U.S. National Science Foundation announced a five-year $67 million investment establishing the Safeguarding the Entire Community of the U.S. Research Ecosystem (SECURE) ($50 million to University of Washington and $17 million to Texas A&amp;M…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 11:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New drug shows promise in clearing HIV from brain</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/07/240725193914.htm</link><image_url>https://www.sciencedaily.com/images/scidaily-logo-rss.png</image_url><description>An experimental drug originally developed to treat cancer may help clear HIV from infected cells in the brain, according to a new study. By targeting infected cells in the brain, drug may clear virus from hidden areas that have been a major challenge in HIV treatment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 00:39:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>