<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Fitness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from Fitness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 12:46:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>From 2 Members to 500: 8th Day Gym Celebrates 15 Years as a CrossFit Affiliate</title><link>https://barbend.com/8th-day-gym-celebrates-15-years-of-crossfit/</link><image>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image><description>Fifteen years ago, when most people had never heard of CrossFit, Joe Cebulski finished his athletic career as a decathlete and decided to take a risk ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Iain Valliere’s 5 Tips to Build a Pro-Bodybuilder-Sized Back</title><link>https://barbend.com/iain-vallieres-5-tips-pro-bodybuilder-sized-back/</link><image>https://www.youtube.com/embed/2NBfGFYW0MU</image><description>The back is the largest and most complex muscle group in the body. While it plays a significant role in aesthetics and performance, many people train ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Train With Caution — These Exercises Are Dangerous</title><link>https://barbend.com/train-with-caution-dangerous-exercises/</link><image>https://www.youtube.com/embed/yVkfYIFim1o</image><description>Many gym-goers probably know which exercises have bad reputations. Do those movements deserve to perish, or can some be beneficial for certain goals? ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is Fitness Influencer Gracie Collis’ Weekly Glute Hypertrophy Programming Up to Snuff?</title><link>https://barbend.com/gracie-collis-weekly-glute-hypertrophy-programming/</link><image>https://www.youtube.com/embed/Fh6f4y92GzU</image><description>While many want full, firm butts that look aesthetic in legwear, the glutes are more than just show muscles. They drive hip movement, maintain body al...</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Strava App Review (2025): A Powerful Platform That Stretches Beyond Running and Cycling</title><link>https://barbend.com/strava-app-review/</link><image>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image><description>According to Amanda Capritto, certified personal trainer, “Virtually everyone can benefit from a fitness app, even those with years upon years of trai...</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 16:00:36 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>