<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 01:07:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Governments Could Stop Inflating if They Wanted — But They Won’t</title><link>https://discernmoney.com/governments-could-stop-inflating-if-they-wanted-but-they-wont/</link><description>The post Governments Could Stop Inflating if They Wanted — But They Won’t appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 04:27:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Remember Us': How To Fight Media Bombholing</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/03/remember_us_how_to_fight_media_bombholing_622854.html</link><description>A couple years ago the journalist Matt Taibbi came up with a telling new term for the way the media works in our time: bombholing. Bombholing is the practice of publishing wild and unsubstantiated stories in the press, then sending those same stories down the memory hole when they turn out to be false. Then the media hits viewers with a new "bombshell," which makes people forget the old "bombshell." Viewers are led "from mania to mania."</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 22:26:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>9 deaths in mass overdose incident in Austin involving dozens: 'One of the worst we've seen'</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/9-deaths-in-mass-overdose-incident-in-austin-involving-dozens-one-of-the-worst-we-ve-seen-2668156822.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52171403&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C66%2C0%2C66</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52171403&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C66%2C0%2C66" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52171403&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;coordinates=151,0,151,0 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg%3Fid%3D52171403%26width%3D1200%26height%3D800%26coordinates%3D151%2C0%2C151%2C0%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Austin law enforcement says that a &lt;a href="https://www.kxan.com/news/local/austin/multiple-hand-to-hand-transactions-arrest-warrant-provides-more-details-in-austin-overdose-surge/" target="_blank"&gt;mass overdose incident&lt;/a&gt; is to blame for nine deaths and nearly 80 suspected overdoses over the last week in downtown Austin. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Austin Police Department said that officers and the Austin-Travis County EMS began to respond to numerous reports of overdoses on Monday. The wave subsided after several days but ended up taking the lives of nine people and leading to dozens overdosing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Law enforcement officials and non-profit organizations tried to battle the mass overdose incident by distributing Narcan and informing at-risk residents of the bad batch of drugs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Emergency responders said they attended to 36 suspected overdoses on Monday and 27 on Tuesday, with 7 more on Wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Christa Stedman, the public information officer for Austin-Travis County EMS, said in &lt;a href="https://www.kxan.com/news/overdose-surge-2-detained-after-70-overdoses-multiple-deaths-in-austin/" target="_blank"&gt;a media briefing&lt;/a&gt; that the distribution of Narcan had unquestionably saved lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We've seen in just a couple of days the numbers dramatically decline, that's a great thing, and I think that speaks to the incredible work that both our community help paramedic team and our partners have done in essentially flooding the city with Narcan."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lily Hughs of the Texas Harm Reduction Alliance said that her team of volunteers had been out in the community trying to get the word out about the bad batch of drugs so that users could avoid the threat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hughes said they also offered training for drug users who wanted to learn how to use Narcan. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We took extra time to do training and talk them through, and made sure every single person we talked to knew what was going on," she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EMS said they had handed out about 400 doses of Narcan while the THRA said they had handed out about 100 doses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Austin police later said that they had detained two persons of interest related to the overdoses. One of those suspects was identified as 55-year-old Johnny Lee Wright, who was charged with unlawful possession of a firearm by a felon. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A second person who was unidentified was arrested on a charge of possession of a controlled substance. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investigators said they identified Wright and another person through the use of high resolution cameras that recorded Wright allegedly handing off narcotics to users after having received them from the unidentified suspect. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Police said that Wright and the second person were “known by officers who regularly worked the downtown area as narcotics dealers." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Here's a news report about the incident:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 04:37:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dean Phillips becomes first House Democrat to call on Rep. Cuellar to resign after indictment</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/dean-phillips-first-house-democrat-call-dem-rep-cuellar-resign-indictment</link><description>Rep. Dean Phillips was the first House Democrat to call on colleague Rep. Henry Cuellar, also a Democrat, to resign after his bribery and conspiracy indictment Friday.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 02:58:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jeffrey Epstein’s ‘Black Book’ With 221 Additional High-Profile Names Is Being Sold to a Secret Bidder</title><link>https://nypost.com/2024/05/03/us-news/jeffrey-epstein-black-book-with-221-names-to-sell-at-auction/</link><description>The post Jeffrey Epstein’s ‘Black Book’ With 221 Additional High-Profile Names Is Being Sold to a Secret Bidder appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 04:00:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Our Overreach vs. Russia Is Alienating the World</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/03/our_overreach_vs_russia_is_alienating_the_world_622466.html</link><description>Since Russia launched its full-scale war on Ukraine more than two years ago, the West has desperately sought ways to punish Russia without harming...</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 22:23:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nancy Pelosi, Al Gore, and others awarded Presidential Medal of Freedom</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/nancy-pelosi-al-gore-and-others-awarded-presidential-medal-of-freedom-2668155183.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52171355&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C171</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52171355&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C171" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52171354&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0,0,0,171 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg%3Fid%3D52171354%26width%3D1200%26height%3D600%26coordinates%3D0%2C0%2C0%2C171%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Joe Biden &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aqBVADKnNzM" target="_blank"&gt;honored&lt;/a&gt; multiple figures with the Presidential Medal of Freedom during a ceremony on Friday, including Democratic Rep. Nancy Pelosi of California, who previously served as speaker of the House and was the first and only woman ever to serve in that role. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Biden &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/live/aqBVADKnNzM?si=50C2fEEEz-prerol&amp;amp;t=1044" target="_blank"&gt;predicted&lt;/a&gt; that Pelosi will go down in history as the greatest House speaker.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It is with great appreciation that I accept the Presidential Medal of Freedom from our great and patriotic President of the United States Joe Biden," Pelosi said in a &lt;a href="https://pelosi.house.gov/news/press-releases/pelosi-statement-receiving-presidential-medal-freedom" target="_blank"&gt;statement&lt;/a&gt;. "Freedom was the vision of our founders, has been the goal of our men and women in uniform, and is our promise to our children. It is with reverence for freedom and respect for all who have received it that I am deeply honored and forever grateful. Thank you, President Biden."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Democratic Rep. Adam Schiff of California congratulated Pelosi in a &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/RepAdamSchiff/status/1786537778668261779" target="_blank"&gt;tweet&lt;/a&gt;, calling the award "a fitting honor for the greatest Speaker of all time."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;         —  (@)        &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/RepAdamSchiff/status/1786537778668261779"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Former Vice President Al Gore, who is known for promoting climate alarmism ideology, also received the Presidential Medal of Freedom on Friday. Gore, a Democrat, lost the 2000 presidential election to Republican candidate George W. Bush. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;John Kerry, who has previously served as special presidential envoy for climate under Biden, secretary of state under Barack Obama, and as a U.S. senator, also received the medal. Kerry, a Democrat, lost the 2004 presidential election to Bush.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former New York City Mayor Michael Bloomberg was also one of the award recipients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In all, there were 19 people &lt;a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/briefing-room/statements-releases/2024/05/03/president-biden-announces-recipients-of-the-presidential-medal-of-freedom-2/" target="_blank"&gt;honored&lt;/a&gt; with the award on Friday, though the medal was being posthumously awarded in some cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 03:15:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Border Patrol sector stops hundreds of Chinese illegal immigrants in just two days as numbers soar</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/border-patrol-sector-stops-hundreds-chinese-illegal-immigrants-just-two-days-numbers-soar</link><description>The San Diego Border Patrol Sector has seen a surge in migrants from China, encountering more nationals in two days than the entire border did in FY 21.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 00:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Limit Your Kids’ Screen Time — Here’s How</title><link>https://www.movieguide.org/news-articles/how-to-help-your-children-manage-their-screen-time.html</link><description>The post Limit Your Kids’ Screen Time — Here’s How appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 03:57:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>American Aid Alone Won't Save Ukraine</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/03/american_aid_alone_wont_save_ukraine_622870.html</link><description>To survive, Kyiv must build new brigades-and force Moscow to negotiate.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 22:23:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Surveillance video captures man sexually assaulting 81-year-old woman with dementia in California</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/surveillance-video-captures-man-sexually-assaulting-81-year-old-woman-with-dementia-in-california-2668155114.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52171360&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C310</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52171360&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C310" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52171360&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0,0,0,310 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg%3Fid%3D52171360%26width%3D1200%26height%3D600%26coordinates%3D0%2C0%2C0%2C310%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The family of an elderly woman with dementia &lt;a href="https://www.foxla.com/news/81-year-old-women-with-alzheimers-sexually-assaulted-in-pacoima-home-family-says" target="_blank"&gt;released&lt;/a&gt; video of her sexual assault in order to help police identify the suspect and arrest him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The horrendous abuse unfolded on Monday at about 6:45 p.m. at the woman's apartment in Pacoima in southern California.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The video shows the man entering the home of the 81-year-old woman after she answered the door, according to the family. He then went and checked the other rooms before returning and assaulting the woman, and making her perform sex acts on him. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The victim's son-in-law spoke to KABC-TV about the execrable incident but wanted his face blurred to protect his identity and that of the victim.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The video catches him doing things that I wouldn't wish on anyone," said the victim's relative. "There's a lot of elderly people in the community. This guy needs to be off the streets. It's probably not the first time and it won't be the last time he's done this, or will do this."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He said that the family had set up the camera so that no one could see it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The camera in the living room is pretty hidden and we hid it from her," the son-in-law explained. "To avoid her from trying to turn it off. And he never saw that camera in the living room."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Friday afternoon, Los Angeles Police detectives&lt;a href="https://abc7.com/lapd-searching-for-sex-assault-suspect-in-pacoima-victim-has-dementia/14757161/" target="_blank"&gt; told KABC&lt;/a&gt; they were able to identify and arrest a suspect. They said he was still in the area near the apartment complex where the woman lived. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The son-in-law &lt;a href="https://www.foxla.com/news/81-year-old-women-with-alzheimers-sexually-assaulted-in-pacoima-home-family-says" target="_blank"&gt;told KTTV-TV&lt;/a&gt; that the woman had been diagnosed with early onset dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We think it’s pretty much progressed to Alzheimer’s already," he added. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The son-in-law said they were alerted to the incident when his wife noticed her mother was up later than usual. When they rewound the recording, they were stunned by seeing the assault. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The son-in-law told KTTV that he had a suspicion about who the attacker was. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"He’s known to be a lurker. He lurks around the area," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He added that without the recording, they would have never known what happened because the woman doesn't remember the incident due to her medical illness. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Police said that they are investigating the incident as attempted rape. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Here's the report of the assault:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;! &lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 02:35:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fox News Politics: Mr. Broke It</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/fox-news-politics-mr-broke-it</link><description>The latest updates from the 2024 campaign trail, exclusive interviews and more Fox News politics content</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 22:53:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Now This is How You Deal With Pro Hamas Terror Sympathizers! Team USA! [VIDEO]</title><link>https://rumble.com/v4t26do-now-this-is-how-you-deal-with-pro-hamas-terror-sympathizers-team-usa.html</link><description>The post Now This is How You Deal With Pro Hamas Terror Sympathizers! Team USA! [VIDEO] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 03:56:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Columbia Protesters Backed Themselves Into a Corner</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/03/columbia_protesters_backed_themselves_into_a_corner_622856.html</link><description>Yesterday afternoon, Columbia University's campus felt like it would in the hours before a heat wave breaks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 22:21:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mark Ham​ill of 'Star Wars' fame visits White House, says he asked Biden if he could call him 'Joebi-Wan Kenobi'</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/mark-ham-ill-of-star-wars-fame-visits-white-house-says-he-asked-biden-if-he-could-call-him-joebi-wan-kenobi-2668155043.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52171309&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C101%2C0%2C71</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52171309&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C101%2C0%2C71" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52171308&amp;amp;width=2000&amp;amp;height=1500&amp;amp;coordinates=77,0,35,0 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg%3Fid%3D52171308%26width%3D2000%26height%3D1500%26coordinates%3D77%2C0%2C35%2C0%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Actor Mark Hamill of "Star Wars" fame, who has been an outspoken supporter of President Joe Biden, met with the president on Friday before appearing at the White House press briefing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hamill said that he called Biden "Mr. President," but Biden said Hamill could call him Joe. Hamill said he asked if he could call the president "Joebi-Wan Kenobi." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hamill has previously posted the eyebrow-raising &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/mark-hamill-best-president-ever" target="_blank"&gt;claim&lt;/a&gt; on social media that "Joe Biden is the best president we've ever had." &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But while he has high praise for Biden, he has &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/MarkHamill/status/1761120030895517770?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1761120030895517770%7Ctwgr%5Ef08a1a81d5b8e854c07d4574b872a5896e97d25d%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theblaze.com%2Fr%2Fentryeditor%2F2668154677publish" target="_blank"&gt;called&lt;/a&gt; it the "understatement of the century," to describe Donald Trump as the nation's worst president ever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;         —  (@)        &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/MarkHamill/status/1761120030895517770"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;"May The First Not Quench Your Thirst For Biden's Re-election!" Hamill &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/MarkHamill/status/1785842788023591097" target="_blank"&gt;tweeted&lt;/a&gt; on Wednesday, May 1, adding the hashtag "#BidenHarris2024." &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"May The Second Biden Administration Be As Productive and Successful As The 1st," he &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/MarkHamill/status/1786088763241779248" target="_blank"&gt;wrote&lt;/a&gt; on Thursday May 2.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;         —  (@)        &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/MarkHamill/status/1786088763241779248"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;On Friday, May 3rd, Hamill &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/MarkHamill/status/1786375698455667141" target="_blank"&gt;tweeted&lt;/a&gt;, "May The Third Be Absurd That The Guy Who Tried To Steal A Fair Election Is Allowed To Run Again."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier this year, on March 5, he &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/MarkHamill/status/1765093771170238470" target="_blank"&gt;tweeted&lt;/a&gt;, "I voted for four more years of an orange-free Oval Office." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;         —  (@)        &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/MarkHamill/status/1765093771170238470"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;In an apparent play on Hamill's Friday White House visit and press briefing appearance, the Babylon Bee, a satire site, &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/TheBabylonBee/status/1786504113099886751" target="_blank"&gt;posted&lt;/a&gt; a piece titled, "Mark Hamill Joins Death Star Press Conference To Say What A Good Job He Thinks The Emperor Is Doing."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;         —  (@)        &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/TheBabylonBee/status/1786504113099886751"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 02:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prosecutors repeatedly reference Trump’s Access Hollywood scandal after judge ruled tape itself 'prejudicial'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/prosecutors-repeatedly-reference-trumps-access-hollywood-scandal-judge-ruled-tape-itself-prejudicial</link><description>New York prosecutors continue to heavily reference the infamous leaked Access Hollywood tape capturing Trump's crude comments about women despite judge deeming the tape itself prejudicial.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 22:45:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Democrat Hellhole DC: Random Bullets Fired Into High School, Graze Student’s Head</title><link>https://dailycaller.com/2024/05/03/stray-bullet-grazes-students-head-dunbar-high-school-washington-dc/</link><description>The post Democrat Hellhole DC: Random Bullets Fired Into High School, Graze Student’s Head appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 03:55:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Normal Students Get Screwed</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/03/normal_students_get_screwed_622977.html</link><description>Elite universities went to war against fraternities and fun while indulging Hamas-admiring collectives, and the students have noticed</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 22:17:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>13-year-old student says she was attacked by adults on school bus and she was suspended for defending herself</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/13-year-old-student-says-she-was-attacked-by-adults-on-school-bus-and-she-was-suspended-for-defending-herself-2668154835.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52171137&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C269</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52171137&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C269" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52171137&amp;amp;width=1245&amp;amp;height=700&amp;amp;coordinates=0,0,0,145 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg%3Fid%3D52171137%26width%3D1245%26height%3D700%26coordinates%3D0%2C0%2C0%2C145%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 13-year-old girl says she was attacked by adults related to a bull at a Texas school, but the district decided to suspend the victim after she fought back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The girl, who didn't want to be identified, &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/texas/news/adults-attack-13-year-old-on-denton-isd-school-bus/" target="_blank"&gt;told KTVT-TV that&lt;/a&gt; she had heard rumors that a new girl at Bettye Myers Middle School in Denton wanted to fight with her. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She said she went to school officials, including a counselor and an assistant principal. She said they told her that they had spoken to the other girl, but it didn't help the situation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She says that when she got on the school bus to go home, the girl attacked her. Then she realized the girl's mother had also joined the fight when she called her "mom" during the fight. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I was scared," she said to KTVT with tears in her eyes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Video shows the assault on the school bus with other students standing around recording the incident and not intervening at all. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I guess one of the women came and put me in a choke hold on the bus," she added. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She says that the women followed the bus to her stop and attacked her again. Video from the second altercation shows her being knocked to the ground and beaten. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The girl says she was able to call her mother during the attack. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I heard my baby scream out," said her mother to KTVT. "And no one did anything."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She's upset at the actions of the bus driver, who appeared to do nothing to prevent the fight and drove away while the girl was being attacked the second time. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Had he locked the door, called for help, waited for the police to arrive. Those grown adults wouldn't have been able to get on a bus, assault my child, and they wouldn't been able to follow the bus and continue assaulting her," she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The girl says she is traumatized because of the attacks. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I can't walk to the store anymore. I have to look and watch every time when I see a white car," she said. "And I have to be on watch everywhere I go. Because of you."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She also says that school officials suspended her for three days for her response, but she says she was simply defending herself. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A spokesperson for the Denton police told KTVT that they are taking the incident seriously and expect an update about the case soon. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The victim and her mother said that they are leaning on their faith to deal with the aftermath of the violence. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I had to sit up at night crying about it, asking God why. But I also pray for them cause my mom taught me, just because they did you wrong, it's all for a reason. It's all for purpose," said the 13-year-old girl. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The other night when she said, 'Mom, let's pray.' And she grabbed my hand and began to pray for them, I'm like, 'Okay, you know... she's going to be all right,'" said the mother. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Here's the news report about the incident:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;! &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 01:35:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nancy Pelosi, John Kerry, other Biden allies awarded Presidential Medal of Freedom</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/nancy-pelosi-john-kerry-biden-allies-awarded-presidential-medal-freedom</link><description>President Biden awarded 19 individuals with the United States' highest civilian award, the Presidential Medal of Freedom, on Friday — including many Democratic allies.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 22:12:50 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>