<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 01:04:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Privileged Karen at LAX Screams at Airport Workers About Missing Flight . . . She Was at the Wrong Terminal [VIDEO]</title><link>https://rumble.com/v4s0kfc-privileged-karen-at-lax-screams-at-airport-workers-about-missing-flight...-.html</link><description>The post Privileged Karen at LAX Screams at Airport Workers About Missing Flight . . . She Was at the Wrong Terminal [VIDEO] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 05:32:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bitter Fruits of Bidenomics--Inflation Rising, Growth Slowing</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/27/bitter_fruits_of_bidenomics--inflation_rising_growth_slowing_622542.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 14:53:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Harvard Protesters Raise Palestinian Flags On University Building, In Spot Reserved For The American Flag</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/harvard-protesters-raise-palestinian-flags-on-university-building-in-spot-reserved-for-the-american-flag-2667983101.html</link><image_url>https://freebeacon.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/IMG_7482.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://freebeacon.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/IMG_7482.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anti-Israel protesters at Harvard University raised Palestinian flags on campus Saturday evening in a spot typically reserved for the American flag. Harvard protesters hoisted three Palestinian flags over the Harvard Yard encampment, where students have been sleeping in tents since Wednesday. The flags were raised on poles attached to University Hall–where Harvard usually flies the […]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://freebeacon.com/campus/harvard-protesters-raise-palestinian-flags-on-university-building-in-spot-reserved-for-the-american-flag/"&gt;Harvard Protesters Raise Palestinian Flags On University Building, In Spot Reserved For The American Flag&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://freebeacon.com"&gt;Washington Free Beacon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 02:33:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Washington chooses its wars; Ukraine and Israel have made the cut despite opposition on right and left</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/washington-dc-chooses-wars-ukraine-israel-have-made-the-cut</link><description>History will judge whether the United States' involvement in wars in the Ukraine and Middle East was justified, just as it judged U.S. involvement in Central America or war in Iraq.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 22:42:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Iran’s Nightmares</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/irans-nightmares/</link><description>(VDH)—Details of the recent limited Israeli retaliatory strike against Iranian anti-aircraft missile batteries at Isfahan are still sketchy. But nonetheless, we can draw some conclusions. Israel’s small volley of missiles hit their intended targets, to the point of zeroing in on the very launchers designed to stop such incoming ordnance. The target was near the […]
The post Iran’s Nightmares appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 05:28:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A First Lady Who Deserves a Second Look</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/25/a_first_lady_who_deserves_a_second_look_622483.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 14:52:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Terrifying' interrogation': American faces 12 years in Turks and Caicos prison after 4 rounds of hunting ammo found in his luggage</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/terrifying-interrogation-american-faces-12-years-in-turks-and-caicos-prison-after-4-rounds-of-hunting-ammo-found-in-his-luggage-2667959143.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.png?id=52121532&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C44%2C0%2C76</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.png?id=52121532&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C44%2C0%2C76" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.png?id=52121531&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0,0,0,120 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.png%3Fid%3D52121531%26width%3D1200%26height%3D600%26coordinates%3D0%2C0%2C0%2C120%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;An American man's dream vacation has turned into a nightmare. He is now facing 12 years in a &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/tag/turks-and-caicos" target="_blank"&gt;Turks and Caicos&lt;/a&gt; prison after four rounds of hunting ammunition were found in his luggage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Ryan Watson, 40, was looking for rest and relaxation when he went on a tropical vacation with his wife to the Caribbean island of Turks and Caicos. However, Watson said that he had been subjected to "terrifying interrogation" and exorbitant living fees after Turks and Caicos authorities discovered four rounds of hunting ammo in his luggage. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watson and his wife traveled to Turks and Caicos in early April to celebrate friends' 40th birthdays. On April 12, security at the Howard Hamilton International Airport found four rounds of ammo "unknowingly left in a duffel bag from a deer hunting trip," according to a &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/tag/gofundme" target="_blank"&gt;GoFundMe&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/help-bring-the-watson-family-home-detained-abroad" target="_blank"&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; made on behalf of the family.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The couple – from Oklahoma – were able to get through security with the ammo at their local Will Rogers World Airport. The TSA is currently reviewing protocols at Will Rogers World Airport to determine how the ammunition was able to sneak through security. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"TSA is conducting a review at OKC, which was the originating airport," the Transportation Security Administration  said in a statement. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ryan and Valerie Watson were both charged with possession of ammunition – a charge that carries a minimum of 12 years in prison in Turks &amp; Caicos.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watson told the &lt;a href="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-13355193/Ryan-Watson-Turks-Caicos-Interrogation-cops-bullets.html?ns_mchannel=rss&amp;amp;ns_campaign=1490&amp;amp;ito=1490" target="_blank"&gt;Daily Mail&lt;/a&gt; that he and his wife were subjected to a "terrifying interrogation" after their arrest. He added, "It was all pretty intimidating."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Valerie told &lt;a href="https://www.nbcboston.com/investigations/consumer/turks-caicos-ammunition-arrests/3347412/" target="_blank"&gt;WBTS-TV&lt;/a&gt;, "When I heard that, I immediately was terrified because I was like, we can't both be in prison for 12 years. We have kids at home. And this is such an innocent mistake that we didn't even know we weren't – we didn't even know it was there. So yeah, my immediate thought was our kids and them being, you know, parentless for, for that long."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, the charges were dropped against Valerie Watson – an elementary school teacher. She has since returned to Oklahoma to be with her children. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oklahoma Gov. Kevin Stitt – a Republican – sent a &lt;a href="https://okcfox.com/resources/pdf/7832a444-83d4-42d1-b849-1d8f384ef476-Watson_Letter_SIGNED_4_16_2024.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;letter&lt;/a&gt; to the Turks and Caicos Islands government in an attempt to "vouch" for Watson and have him released.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The Watsons are upstanding members of their community and the State of Oklahoma, and I can assure you countless others stand willing to confirm their high moral characters," Stitt &lt;a href="https://www.newson6.com/story/662bcdbb62c4390646d10016/gov-stitt-writes-letter-vouching-for-oklahoma-couple-arrested-in-turks-and-caicos-#:~:text=I%20am%20writing%20to%20vouch,confirm%20their%20high%20moral%20characters." target="_blank"&gt;wrote&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"First and foremost, the Watsons are devoted parents," Stitt said. "Their two young children, Van and Ellie, need their parents home without delay. Mr. and Mrs. Watson would never intentionally break the law. Again, they are unwavering in moral character, reliable neighbors, and devoted community members."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stitt concluded, "Like many in Oklahoma, Mr. Watson is an avid outdoorsman. We learn to safely use and transport firearms from a young age. To the extent Mr. Watson possessed ammunition, it would have been due to an inadvertent oversight, not an intentional attempt to break the law. The Watsons are great Oklahomans, and their children and community need them home soon."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After spending nearly two weeks in detention, Watson paid a $15,000 bond to be released from jail, &lt;a href="https://www.tcipolice.tc/u-s-visitor-charged-with-possession-of-ammunition/" target="_blank"&gt;according&lt;/a&gt; to the Royal Turks &amp; Caicos Islands Police Force. His release has conditions, including surrendering his passport and not being able to leave the country. He also must check in with local authorities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Forced to reside in Turks and Caicos has been costly for Watson. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watson has reportedly been staying at a $500-a-night AirBnB with the financial assistance help of his in-laws. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the time of publication, the GoFundMe campaign had raised nearly $210,000 for the Watson family to assist him with legal fees and provide money for his living expenses. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watson's next court appearance is scheduled for June 7.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;        American tourist faces prison in Turks and Caicos over ammo found in luggage                        &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XdJ0EPPT4ws&amp;amp;list=RDNSXdJ0EPPT4ws&amp;amp;start_radio=1" target="_blank"&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 22:38:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Justice Thomas raised crucial question about legitimacy of special counsel's prosecution of Trump</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/justice-thomas-raised-crucial-question-about-legitimacy-special-counsels-prosecution-trump</link><description>Supreme Court Justice Clarence Thomas raised a question Thursday that goes to the heart of Special Counsel Jack Smith's charges against former President Donald Trump.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 22:13:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Houston Restaurant Employee Accused of Putting His Genitals in Food Items, Possessing Child Porn</title><link>https://discern.tv/houston-restaurant-employee-accused-of-putting-his-genitals-in-food-items-possessing-child-porn/</link><description>The post Houston Restaurant Employee Accused of Putting His Genitals in Food Items, Possessing Child Porn appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 05:03:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Noncompete Deals Good or Bad? Probably Both</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/27/are_noncompete_deals_good_or_bad_probably_both_622596.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 14:52:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Like a freight train': Videos show widespread destruction as tornadoes ravage Nebraska and Iowa, more storms pose perilous threats</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/like-a-freight-train-videos-show-widespread-destruction-as-tornadoes-ravage-nebraska-and-iowa-more-storms-pose-perilous-threats-2667959141.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52121081&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C57</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52121081&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C57" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52121058&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0,28,0,29 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg%3Fid%3D52121058%26width%3D1200%26height%3D600%26coordinates%3D0%2C28%2C0%2C29%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Parts of Nebraska and Iowa were ravaged by powerful tornadoes on Friday. Weather experts predict that new storms could bring even more destruction to the Midwest region. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hundreds of homes and businesses were damaged or destroyed by the ferocity of the storm's fury, especially in a suburb of Omaha, Nebraska. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;         —  (@)        &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/JordanHallWX/status/1784203738195869854"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;On Saturday, residents of Elkhorn were sifting through the rubble after a tornado decimated the area. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We watched it touch down like 200 yards over there and then we took shelter,” &lt;a href="https://www.wwnytv.com/2024/04/27/tornadoes-collapse-buildings-level-homes-nebraska-iowa/" target="_blank"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; Pat Woods – who lives in Elkhorn. "We could hear it coming through. When we came up, our fence was gone and we looked to the northwest and the whole neighborhood's gone.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kim Woods, Pat's wife, added, “The whole neighborhood just to the north of us is pretty flattened.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason Sunday – a resident of Elkhorn in Omaha – told &lt;a href="https://www.ketv.com/article/elkhorn-family-rebuild-after-tornado/60623274" target="_blank"&gt;KETV&lt;/a&gt;, "We saw it coming from the southwest, and when it got too close for comfort, we headed downstairs quickly. We were in the downstairs bathtub, and it was just like the movie said, it was like a freight train."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three people were hurt with non-life-threatening injuries when a tornado caused an industrial building to collapse in Nebraska’s Lancaster County. There were 70 people inside, but they were able to be evacuated. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Omaha police Lt. Neal Bonacci said and police and firefighters were going door-to-door to help residents. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;         —  (@)        &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/accuweather/status/1784256122792153109"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Nebraska Gov. Jim Pillen toured the area worst affected by the tornadoes in his state. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pillen &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/TeamPillen/status/1784019473973817673" target="_blank"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; on the X social media platform: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;Suzanne and I extend our deepest prayers to all those impacted by today's storms. I have ordered that state resources be made available to assist with the emergency response and to support local first responders as they assess the damage. Nebraskans are tough, resilient people, and our neighbors and communities will rally around affected families and businesses to assist them. Nebraskans are no strangers to severe weather and, as they have countless times before, Nebraskans will help Nebraskans to rebuild.&lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt;         —  (@)        &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/TeamPillen/status/1784259650981900618"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;In Iowa, the small towns of Minden and Harlan were some of the hardest hit by the destructive tornadoes. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt;         —  (@)        &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/WeatherNation/status/1784008957314379980"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt;         —  (@)        &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/accuweather/status/1784218036414689351"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;There were nearly 80 reports of tornadoes on Friday across five states that were corroborated by weather service data and storm chaser recordings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There have been several reports of injuries but thankfully no fatalities have been reported.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More updates on the severe weather in the Midwest:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Four people in Iowa's Pottawattamie County suffered storm-related injuries and needed medical attention, according to county emergency management officials.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pottawattamie County, home to approximately 90,000 residents, witnessed damage to roughly 120 homes and businesses, with varying degrees of destruction reported, emergency officials stated. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;In Omaha, two individuals received minor injuries following a tornado in the Elkhorn area on Friday. Omaha Police Chief Todd Schmaderer credited the city and county's effective warning systems for mitigating further casualties, stressing the the benefits of early alerts.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Iowa Gov. Kim Reynolds issued a disaster proclamation to aid storm recovery efforts in Pottawattamie County following the tornado that ravaged Minden.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Emergency responders in Nebraska's Shelby and Douglas counties reported significant property damage from multiple tornadoes on Friday. Residents were forced to evacuate due to the storm's devastation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Texas witnessed at least two tornadoes on Friday afternoon, as captured in social media footage.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt; Threats of severe weather – including damaging winds, possible flooding, and large hail – are in play for Nebraska, Texas, Oklahoma, and Iowa on Saturday and Sunday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than 50 million people are under the threat of severe weather on Saturday. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Approximately 18 million people across Nebraska, Iowa, and Texas, are under flood watches until Sunday afternoon, according to the National Weather Service&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There were tornado warnings issued for the Midwest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A tornado watch has been &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/NWStornado/status/1784263952236745002" target="_blank"&gt;issued&lt;/a&gt; for parts of Kansas and Nebraska until 7 p.m. CDT.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;        More than a dozen tornadoes touch down across Texas, Oklahoma and Nebraska                        &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0eApcbd-dkg" target="_blank"&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 21:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GOP Rep. Bill Posey won't seek re-election, endorses former Florida Senate President as replacement</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/gop-rep-bill-posey-wont-seek-re-election-endorses-former-florida-senate-president-as-replacement</link><description>Florida GOP Rep. Bill Posey announced that he would not be seeking re-election on Friday, continuing on to endorse former Florida Senate President Mike Haridopolos as his replacement.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 18:57:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mike Lindell on the Importance of Protecting Your Wealth with Precious Metals [Ad]</title><link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OYzVkTmfVLU</link><description>The post Mike Lindell on the Importance of Protecting Your Wealth with Precious Metals [Ad] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 04:47:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amid the Chaos, America's Elite Campuses Can't Educate</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/25/amid_the_chaos_americas_elite_campuses_cant_educate_622488.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 14:52:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Florida school failed to address 'ticking time bomb' teen who brutally beat his teacher over a Nintendo Switch</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/florida-school-failed-to-address-ticking-time-bomb-teen-who-brutally-beat-his-teacher-over-a-nintendo-switch-2667948880.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.png?id=52120965&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C3%2C0%2C4</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.png?id=52120965&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C3%2C0%2C4" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.png?id=52120965&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;coordinates=215,0,216,0 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.png%3Fid%3D52120965%26width%3D1200%26height%3D800%26coordinates%3D215%2C0%2C216%2C0%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;A large autistic Florida teenager who &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/blaze-news-original-a-dozen-disturbing-instances-when-students-got-brutally-violent-with-teachers" target="_blank"&gt;violently beat his teacher's aid unconscious&lt;/a&gt; over a video game was reportedly a "ticking time bomb," the boy's attorneys said in a petition filed against the student's school earlier this week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brendan Depa's legal team blamed the Flagler County School District for not meeting the boy's needs before the attack, which took place in February 2023, according to the &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2024/04/27/us-news/florida-teen-brendan-depa-files-petition-blaming-flagler-county-school-district-in-teachers-aid-assault/?utm_campaign=nypost&amp;amp;utm_medium=social&amp;amp;utm_source=twitter" target="_blank"&gt;New York Post&lt;/a&gt;. The &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/naydich-beating-school-brendan-depa" target="_blank"&gt;brutal attack&lt;/a&gt; left paraprofessional Joan Naydich with five broken ribs, a severe concussion, and hearing loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a consequence, Depa now faces up to 30 years in prison after pleading no contest to the beatdown that was caught on camera inside the school building. However, the boy's attorneys claim that the incident only happened because the district committed a series of violations resulting in "significant harm" to the teen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The district should be held to account for its failures which have forever changed the trajectory of this young man’s life,” the petition states, which was obtained by &lt;a href="https://flaglerlive.com/depa-lawsuit/#google_vignette" target="_blank"&gt;Flagler Live&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not only did the attorneys blame the school district, but they also suggested that Naydich asked for her own beating after she reprimanded Depa in front of his classmates. She proceeded to threaten to take away his Nintendo Switch that ultimately turned into a verbal fight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Afterward, Depa spit on Naydich. The paraprofessional left the classroom to report him for assault, prompting him to follow her and launch the horrific attack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The school did not seem to have any control over B.D. and B.D. was allowed to do whatever he wanted with little to no intervention or consequences,” the petition stated, adding that the school had a responsibility to intervene.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“To allow B.D. to continue to escalate only led to the incident where the paraprofessional was harmed and B.D. was arrested,” the petition went on. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Had these issues been addressed in real time, B.D. would not have harmed the paraprofessional and would not have been arrested and facing significant time incarcerated.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“B.D. was a ticking time bomb,” the petition added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Depa's legal team — who also said the teen failed to receive education while he was behind bars — is requesting "compensatory education" and payment for his admittance into a behavioral therapeutic school for students with disorders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Depa is set to appear in court on Wednesday for sentencing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 20:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump endorses GOP Utah Senate candidate looking to replace Romney: 'He will be a GREAT Senator'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-endorses-gop-utah-senate-candidate-looking-replace-romney-great-senator</link><description>Former President Donald Trump endorsed Trent Staggs, a Republican looking to replace retiring Sen. Mitt Romney, R-Utah., in Utah's GOP primary race for the Senate.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 18:02:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NYPD Chief Blasts AOC for Her Criticism of the Department in Clearing Columbia Encampment</title><link>https://pjmedia.com/rick-moran/2024/04/27/nypd-cheif-blasts-rep-ocasio-cortez-for-her-criticism-of-the-department-in-clearing-columbia-encampment-n4928560</link><description>The post NYPD Chief Blasts AOC for Her Criticism of the Department in Clearing Columbia Encampment appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 04:46:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Arizona Indictments Come at the Worst Time for Trump</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/27/arizona_indictments_come_at_the_worst_time_for_trump_622582.html</link><description>The Supreme Court should focus on the crimes Donald Trump's allies are accused of committing when it rules on the</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 14:40:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘I’d Even Take Biden Over Junior’: Donald Trump Exchanges Broadsides With RFK Jr.</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/id-even-take-biden-over-junior-donald-trump-exchanges-broadsides-with-rfk-jr-2667944758.html</link><image_url>https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/GettyImages-2107855017-scaled.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/GettyImages-2107855017-scaled.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;'His Views on Vaccines are FAKE, as is everything else about his Candidacy'</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 19:35:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'NO EVIDENCE': Biden mocked for stretching the truth on shock jock Howard Stern's show</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/no-evidence-biden-mocked-stretching-truth-shock-jock-howard-sterns-show</link><description>Media outlets and conservative commentators piled on President Biden for stretching the truth during a Friday interview with radio host Howard Stern.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 17:11:24 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>