<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:15:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Former MIT Researcher Who Killed Yale Graduate Student Sentenced to 35 Years in Prison</title><link>https://www.theepochtimes.com/us/former-mit-researcher-who-killed-yale-graduate-student-sentenced-to-35-years-in-prison-5635813?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=TheLibertyDaily</link><description>The post Former MIT Researcher Who Killed Yale Graduate Student Sentenced to 35 Years in Prison appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:15:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Heavily Outspent in Swing States</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2024/04/23/realclearpolitics_biden_talks_abortion_in_florida_biden_campaign_outspends_trump_papua_new_guinea_reacts_to_the_legend_of_uncle_bosie.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:00:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FACT CHECK: Image Of Rocket Attack Is From 2015, Not A Recent Rocket Attack From Iraq</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/fact-check-image-of-rocket-attack-is-from-2015-not-a-recent-rocket-attack-from-iraq-2667867915.html</link><image_url>https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/ISIS-e1657634333194.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/ISIS-e1657634333194.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A post shared on social media purportedly shows an image of a recent missile attack from Iraqi forces on a U.S. military base. Five Rockets Fired From Iraq Towards U.S. Military Base In Syria | Sahara Reporters https://t.co/SvtgJts1bn pic.twitter.com/1LCRCN8lQz — Sahara Reporters (@SaharaReporters) April 21, 2024 Verdict: False The claim is inaccurate. The photo dates back to […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:02:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>LA mayor break-in suspect was 'targeting' Bass, Gascon says: 'He was looking for her'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/la-mayor-break-suspect-was-targeting-bass-gascon-says-he-was-looking-her</link><description>Los Angeles District Attorney George Gascon says the man accused of breaking into the official mayoral residence did so specifically to target Mayor Karen Bass.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:07:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Megyn Kelly Goes Off on MSNBC/NBC for the Sanctimonious Behavior Over ‘Checkbook Journalism’ [VIDEO]</title><link>https://rumble.com/v4r6uu5-megyn-kelly-goes-off-on-msnbcnbc-for-the-sanctimonious-behavior-over-checkb.html</link><description>The post Megyn Kelly Goes Off on MSNBC/NBC for the Sanctimonious Behavior Over ‘Checkbook Journalism’ [VIDEO] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:15:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bob Kraft a Good Fit for Elizabeth Warren's Seat</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/24/bob_kraft_a_good_fit_for_elizabeth_warrens_seat_622416.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 12:42:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Columbia President Shafik Extends Deadline To Clear Encampment: 12 AM, 8 AM, 48 Hours</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/columbia-president-shafik-extends-deadline-to-clear-encampment-12-am-8-am-48-hours-2667867769.html</link><image_url>https://freebeacon.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/pro-palestinian-protests-continue-at-columbia-university-in-new-york-c-scaled-e1713965393951.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://freebeacon.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/pro-palestinian-protests-continue-at-columbia-university-in-new-york-c-scaled-e1713965393951.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Columbia University president Minouche Shafik set a midnight deadline for student protesters to clear the unauthorized tent encampment that has plagued campus—only to push that deadline back twice, first to 8 a.m. and then 48 hours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://freebeacon.com/campus/columbia-president-shafik-extends-deadline-to-clear-encampment-12-am-8-am-48-hours/"&gt;Columbia President Shafik Extends Deadline To Clear Encampment: 12 AM, 8 AM, 48 Hours&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://freebeacon.com"&gt;Washington Free Beacon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:50:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WATCH: Online videos expose how human traffickers are sneaking illegal migrants into US</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/online-videos-expose-how-human-traffickers-sneaking-illegal-migrants-into-us</link><description>Videos being published on social media show a smuggler's journey into the U.S. with a group of illegal immigrants from the Mexican side of the border.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:04:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Campuses Are a Time Bomb Ticking on America</title><link>https://spectator.org/the-campuses-are-a-time-bomb-ticking-on-america/</link><description>The post The Campuses Are a Time Bomb Ticking on America appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:47:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>School Chaplains Law Crosses a Sacred Line</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/24/school_chaplains_law_crosses_a_sacred_line_622415.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 12:39:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A civil rights lawsuit exposes anarcho-tyranny in action</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/a-civil-rights-lawsuit-exposes-anarcho-tyranny-in-action-2667867935.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/overview-of-the-sheetz-store-in-prince-william-county.jpg?id=52080956&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C102%2C0%2C25</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/overview-of-the-sheetz-store-in-prince-william-county.jpg?id=52080956&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C102%2C0%2C25" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/overview-of-the-sheetz-store-in-prince-william-county.jpg?id=52080956&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;coordinates=66,0,0,0 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/overview-of-the-sheetz-store-in-prince-william-county.jpg%3Fid%3D52080956%26width%3D1200%26height%3D800%26coordinates%3D66%2C0%2C0%2C0%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Federal officials have leveled &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxbusiness.com/politics/biden-admin-hits-sheetz-convenience-store-chain-lawsuit-campaign-stop" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;a discrimination lawsuit&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; at the Sheetz convenience store chain&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; alleging &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;the company’s use of criminal background checks as a screening mechanism for employees&lt;/span&gt; falls afoul of Title VII of the Civil Rights Act of 1964&lt;span&gt;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Although Joe &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Biden&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;’s&lt;/span&gt; Department of Justice &lt;span&gt;says it &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;do&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;es&lt;/span&gt; not believe the company inten&lt;span&gt;ded&lt;/span&gt; to discriminate, the fact that minority applicants are more likely to have criminal records places Sheetz &lt;span&gt;outside of the law.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This action may seem absurd, but the lawsuit fits well within the logic of existing civil rights law and its standard of “disparate impact.” Sheetz employs a common screening method to protect its customers and employees’ safety, yet the Biden administration has made it clear that criminals’ rights hold more importance. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Progressives did not want a world that removed racial preferences. They wanted a world that actively used racial preferences to reshape American institutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The civil rights regime that rules the United States reckons that skin color trumps all other concerns and has made a safe, high-trust society illegal, punishing the average law-abiding citizen in the name of equality. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most Americans think of the Civil Rights Act as the piece of legislation that ended legal discrimination in the United States but do not understand how the relevant body of law has mutated over the years.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The original language of the law was vague and allowed for radical interpretations that have led to the rise of a legal leviathan that reaches into every part of American life. The average person would assume civil rights law simply prevents a business from openly denying an individual employment due to his race, but the truth is far more complicated. The Supreme Court's decision in &lt;em&gt;Griggs v. Duke Power Co. &lt;/em&gt;(1971) introduced the language of disparate impact, and that change has warped every institution in the United States. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Under disparate impact, the employer does not need to make any conscious decision to discriminate in order to violate the law. In the original case, the justices decided that if minority applicants reliably scored lower on aptitude or IQ tests, then the use of those tests to screen potential employees broke the law even if the employer had no intent to discriminate.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Removing intent as a factor made any difference in outcomes for racial groups count as evidence of discrimination. The Civil Rights Act of 1991 made the change official, leading to college degrees becoming the only acceptable way for businesses to screen would-be hires. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most Americans would enthusiastically endorse the idea that we should evaluate every individual on their merits, but the creation of a standard like disparate impact exposes the falsehood that civil rights law merely aimed to give each person an equal shot.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether we like it or not, differences between groups reliably emerge across different domains, and using objective standards will naturally reflect those differences. Progressives did not want a world that removed racial preferences. They wanted a world that actively used racial preferences to reshape American institutions. A standard like disparate impact does not reduce racial preference but instead increases the salience of race to the point that companies must hire less qualified or even dangerous employees to fill a &lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;de facto&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt; racial quota system. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Warping reality to meet an artificial ideological goal is always dangerous and often leads to disastrous results. The justification for banning basic aptitude and IQ tests was based on utopian thinking at best and cynical political calculation at worst. It has resulted in the explosion of extreme college debt and a leftist monopoly on employment credentials in the United States.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The relentless expansion of the ideology at the heart of civil rights law always meant that it would eventually need to be applied to criminal records. Some minority groups commit crimes at a significantly higher rate and therefore have a much higher likelihood of being excluded from employment by a background check. Those on the left attribute this fact to racism, but they find it hard to disagree with the data itself. People can and will argue endlessly over the causal factors, but just as with aptitude tests, the intention of the employer does not matter. If any difference in results occurs, even with the use of objective measures, it is a violation of the law. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is how our current ruling class uses civil rights law to implement a system of anarcho-tyranny. A government under anarcho-tyranny ignores serious violations of law like theft and violent assault and instead seeks to criminalize the behavior of normal, law-abiding citizens whom it views as the greatest threat to its power. This tactic is designed to remove the organic mechanisms most communities use to create safety and order and keep the population in a constant state of fear.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With the most basic tools of order stripped away, citizens are compelled to grant the government increased levels of power in the hope it will be used to reinstate a safe and healthy status quo. Instead, the regime uses power to reward its client classes. This tactic is particularly effective at keeping the middle class from organizing and opposing a regime that deploys the &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/columns/opinion/macintyre-permanent-revolution-and-the-total-state" target="_self"&gt;&lt;u&gt;classic strategy of high and low versus middle&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to eliminate competition and expand its power. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Any civilization without a death wish would understand that keeping its customers and employees safe by screening applicants for criminal records is a commonsense move. Society is better when our public spaces are run by trustworthy individuals who have, at the very least, demonstrated an ability to refrain from violating the law.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the Biden administration wants to send a chilling message to any corporation that would value safety and order above the perverse, race-obsessed ideology of the civil rights regime. Our malicious Justice Department is unfairly targeting responsible employers with harsh laws while letting violent criminals off easily, which threatens public safety. To end the madness and restore order, this country must take back the excessive control the civil rights authorities have over all American institutions. &lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chip Roy raises alarms about George Soros' purchase of radio giant Audacy</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/chip-roy-raises-alarms-george-soros-purchase-major-radio-company</link><description>Rep. Chip Roy is raising alarms about billionaire George Soros' recent acquisition of a major network of radio stations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:30:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>People Sound off on AOC’s Condemnation of Police Enforcing the Law Against Protesters</title><link>https://twitchy.com/fuzzychimp/2024/04/23/aoc-condemns-police-presence-on-columbia-campus-n2395454</link><description>The post People Sound off on AOC’s Condemnation of Police Enforcing the Law Against Protesters appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:47:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Slavery Reparations in California?</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/24/slavery_reparations_in_california_622391.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 12:37:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New York Times to Americans: Embrace Big Brother, he’s watching anyway</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/new-york-times-to-americans-embrace-big-brother-hes-watching-anyway-2667867722.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52080939&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C198%2C0%2C199</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52080939&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C198%2C0%2C199" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52080939&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;coordinates=128,0,129,0 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg%3Fid%3D52080939%26width%3D1200%26height%3D800%26coordinates%3D128%2C0%2C129%2C0%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2024/04/21/opinion/fisa-section-702-fbi-privacy.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;New York Times published an op-ed&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;the&lt;/span&gt; other day &lt;span&gt;in defense of warrantless government surveillance titled &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;“&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Government Surveillance Keeps Us Safe.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;”&lt;/span&gt; Big Brother himself &lt;span&gt;couldn&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;’&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;t&lt;/span&gt; have &lt;span&gt;come up with&lt;/span&gt; a better title.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The piece begins with this claim: “This is an extraordinarily dangerous time for the United States and our allies.” Let me start here by asking New York Times editors, &lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;why&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt; this is a such an extraordinarily dangerous time for the United States and our allies. You said that Donald Trump was going to destroy peace on earth. He instead brought us closer to peace. He did things that I never thought could be accomplished in my lifetime. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Congress, including 30 Republicans, voted that Fourth Amendment rights do not matter. They put your rights in the backseat to bureaucratic expediency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You said that if Trump recognized Jerusalem as the capitol of Israel, we would break out into war. The opposite happened. We were forging historic peace accords. So, why are we in an extraordinarily difficult place? I think that’s important to answer before you offer a solution. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Permit me to make a few obvious points. Our economy is out of control. Who was it that caused that? Morgan Stanley came out and said we have two years to take care of our debt or we’re done for. Two years! Do you think we’re turning the corner on that one? Do you think the next election will change that? Do you think that our current government even cares about that? No. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We pulled out of Afghanistan and showed the world that we were absolutely insane. Then, we encouraged a war and are paying for a war in Ukraine. Then, we sent money to Iran and said, “You’re off the hook with us. Just pinkie promise that you won’t do anything.” And it did! What a shock.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The people who caused this problem cannot fix the problem because they don’t recognize that &lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;they&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt; are the problem. Who was it, exactly, New York Times, who has neglected our national debt, our economy, and has funded foreign wars to the precipice of World War III? It certainly wasn’t Donald Trump.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The op-ed goes on:  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;Israel’s unpreparedness on Oct. 7 shows that even powerful nations can be surprised in catastrophic ways. Fortunately, Congress, in a rare bipartisan act, voted early Saturday to reauthorize a key intelligence power that provides critical information on hostile states and threats ranging from terrorism to fentanyl trafficking.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yes, powerful nations can be surprised in catastrophic ways. But catastrophic things can happen to powerful nations that are not surprising at all. For instance, every American knows right now that we have an open border. If the Times was serious about catastrophic things happening in the United States, it would be paying attention to our open borders. It would call on Congress and the president to seal it off and make sure that only people we could vet could come into the United States. But it's not serious. It's using the crisis for its own benefit. Never let a good crisis go to waste, right? It is using the crisis to distort and control.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The op-ed, of course, takes jabs at “ignorant” people like you and me who have raised concerns about the bill: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;Civil libertarians argued that the surveillance bill erodes Americans’ privacy rights and pointed to examples when American citizens got entangled in investigations. Importantly, the latest version of the bill adds dozens of legal safeguards around the surveillance in question — the most expansive privacy reform to the legislation in its history. &lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;That's because the bill does erode Americans' privacy rights. Congress just keeps on giving the executive branch more power. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The piece continues: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;At the center of the debate is the Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Act. Originally passed in 1978, it demanded that investigators gain an order from a special court to surveil foreign agents inside the United States. Collecting the communications of foreigners abroad did not require court approval. That line blurred in the digital age. Many foreign nationals rely on American providers such as Google and Meta, which route or store data in the United States, raising questions as to whether the rules apply to where the targets are or where their data is collected…&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;In 2008, Congress addressed that conundrum with Section 702. Instead of requiring the government seek court orders for each foreign target, that provision requires yearly judicial approval of the rules that govern the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;program as a whole&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Do you have a problem with foreign targets? I don’t. This is not even what we’re talking about. Why does the New York Times believe it’s important to explain that part? Because I don’t think anyone has a problem with it. People like me who are concerned about Section 702 don’t have an issue with targeting foreign threats. That’s not partisan. That is common sense.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The issue at stake is the targeting of American citizens by consequence. The op-ed writers don’t merely say this is “inevitable in today's globalized world.” They insist it “can be vital for U.S. security.” So, in other words, you can do nothing about it anyway. You better just accept the fact that your digital communication can be searched and seized without a warrant.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In fact, the op-ed makes the claim that “requiring such a warrant would have been unnecessary and unwise. Getting a FISA court order is bureaucratically cumbersome and would slow down investigations.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well, we wouldn’t want to slow anything down! If someone has a brush with somebody under FBI investigation without their knowledge, let’s just throw ’em in jail. Let’s cut through the bureaucratic nightmare of the Constitution. If your rights take a backseat to bureaucratic expediency, that’s just something you will have to deal with. It’s all for the sake of the “greater good,” safety, security, and government efficiency.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To the ire of our bureaucratic states, it turns out you do have rights. In this specific case, you have the right to not be subject to unreasonable searches and seizures. It's called the Fourth Amendment. But now, your Congress, including 30 Republicans, voted that your Fourth Amendment rights do not matter. They put your rights in the backseat to bureaucratic expediency. They swore to “defend the Constitution of the United States against all enemies, foreign and domestic.” If they continue to sacrifice your rights on the altar of federal bureaucracy, does that not make them the enemies they swore to protect you against? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Want more from Glenn Beck? Get Glenn's &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://nam11.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Flinks.glennbeck.com%2Fjoin%2F51r%2Fsignup-theblaze&amp;amp;data=05%7C01%7Ckbradford%40glennbeck.com%7C5ae07c10bf6c4596860f08dbdbd1d647%7Cdb443f8476654a1aa56554a55f8e24d5%7C1%7C0%7C638345466535332907%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C3000%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=94gGMSRVSXsBpcLcopUmJLBrXDcb%2BGLLqjgBLipx53U%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;FREE email newsletter&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt; with his latest insights, top stories, show prep and more delivered to your inbox.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Supreme Court set to hear arguments over emergency room abortion access in states' rights challenge</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/supreme-court-set-hear-arguments-emergency-room-abortion-access-states-rights-challenge</link><description>The contentious issue of abortion has returned to the Supreme Court, with the justices prepared on Wednesday to weigh a states rights challenge over hospital emergency room access to the procedure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:30:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Warns That a Strong Dollar Is a “Total Disaster” for the American Economy</title><link>https://www.theepochtimes.com/business/donald-trump-warns-strong-dollar-total-disaster-for-us-economy-5635981?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=TheLibertyDaily</link><description>The post Trump Warns That a Strong Dollar Is a “Total Disaster” for the American Economy appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:46:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Rot In U.S. Academia Extends To Most of Every Faculty</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/24/the_rot_in_us_academia_extends_to_most_of_every_faculty_622398.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 12:37:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FACT CHECK: No, Ali Khamenei Did Not Appear On Forbes Cover</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/fact-check-no-ali-khamenei-did-not-appear-on-forbes-cover-2667867393.html</link><image_url>https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/GettyImages-80855707-scaled-e1611328453385.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/GettyImages-80855707-scaled-e1611328453385.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An image shared on Facebook claims Iran’s Supreme Ayatollah Ali Khamenei appeared on Forbes cover. Verdict: False There is no evidence that Khamenei appeared on the cover of Forbes. Fact Check: Israel struck Iran on April 19, though refrained from a larger attack in order to avoid a larger scale war between the two nations, according to […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:20:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Newsom ignoring California crises to promote himself in pro-abortion campaign, GOP lawmakers say</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/newsom-ignoring-california-crises-promote-himself-pro-abortion-campaign-gop-lawmakers-say</link><description>California Republicans torched Gavin Newsom for his national abortion rights ad Monday while the state faces crises they say requires the Democrat governor's attention.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:29:37 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>