<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 00:44:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Massive Crowd of American Patriots Gathered in Front of Trump Tower to Show Their Support [VIDEO]</title><link>https://rumble.com/v4yq6du-massive-crowd-of-american-patriots-continues-to-grow-in-front-of-trump-towe.html</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>The post Massive Crowd of American Patriots Gathered in Front of Trump Tower to Show Their Support [VIDEO] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 03:46:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Election a Referendum on Dems' Abuse of Justice System</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/31/election_a_referendum_on_dems_abuse_of_justice_system_624744.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 20:07:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump turns conviction into cash, spotlights record fundraising in wake of guilty verdict</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-turns-conviction-cash-spotlights-record-fundraising-guilty-verdict</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>Trump campaign announces haul of $52.8 million in fundraising in the 24 hours after the former president was found guilty on all counts in his criminal trial.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 02:38:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Attorneys Rip Judge Merchan on CNN for Throwing the Constitution “Out a Window” With His Ludicrous Jury Instructions</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/attorneys-rip-judge-merchan-cnn-throwing-constitution-window/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>(DCNF)—Defense attorney Randy Zelin and former Trump attorney Tim Parlatore said on Friday that Judge Juan Merchan violated the U.S. Constitution with his instructions to the jury in former President Donald Trump’s trial. Merchan instructed the jury that it is not a requirement for them to be in unanimous agreement about what “other crime” Trump […] The post Attorneys Rip Judge Merchan on CNN for Throwing the Constitution “Out a Window” With His Ludicrous Jury Instructions appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 03:44:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Faces Big Trouble in Virginia</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/30/biden_faces_big_trouble_in_virginia_624572.html</link><description>States previously considered out of reach for former President Trump may now be in play. One of the most intriguing is Virginia.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 20:01:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kansas Constitution doesn't include right to vote: state high court majority</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/kansas-constitution-doesnt-include-right-vote-state-high-court-majority</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>The Kansas Supreme Court released a majority opinion Friday suggesting that the state Constitution's Bill of Rights does not include a right to vote.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 01:49:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Emboldened by the “Hush Money” Verdict, Jack Smith Repeats His Request for a Trump Gag Order in Classified Documents Case</title><link>https://justthenews.com/government/courts-law/jack-smith-repeats-request-trump-gag-order-classified-documents-case</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>The post Emboldened by the “Hush Money” Verdict, Jack Smith Repeats His Request for a Trump Gag Order in Classified Documents Case appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 03:44:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Can Biden Seize the Lifeline This Verdict Gives Him?</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/31/can_biden_seize_the_lifeline_this_verdict_gives_him_624742.html</link><description>The incumbent president is badly behind - but now he has a chance to woo disenchanted Republicans who can't bear Donald's stink says Guardian columnist Jonathan Freedland</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 20:00:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vermont Gov. Scott vetoes 'safe injection site' proposal</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/vermont-gov-scott-vetoes-safe-injection-site-proposal</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>Republican Vermont Gov. Phil Scott has vetoed the Democratic Legislature's proposal to create a pilot "safe injection site" for drug users in Burlington.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 01:27:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>President Donald J. Trump: “We’re Going to FIGHT” [VIDEO]</title><link>https://rumble.com/v4yoxcz-president-donald-j-trump-were-going-to-fight.html</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>The post President Donald J. Trump: “We’re Going to FIGHT” [VIDEO] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 03:44:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Case for Bernie Sanders Retiring From the Senate</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/31/the_case_for_bernie_sanders_retiring_from_the_senate_624605.html</link><description>To suggest every older candidate or public servant retire would be rank ageism. But Ibelieve Sanders had an opportunity here to set an important example.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 19:55:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GOP's Murkowski laments Trump's 'baggage' following guilty verdict</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/gops-murkowski-laments-trumps-baggage-following-guilty-verdict</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>Sen. Lisa Murkowski, R-Alaska, was one of the last Republicans to comment on former President Trump's conviction, but did not reveal her thoughts on it.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 23:49:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Defense Attorney Tells CNN There’s a “Great Likelihood” of Trump Overturning the Verdict on Numerous “Issues”</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/defense-attorney-tells-cnn-theres-great-likelihood-trump/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>(DCNF)—Criminal defense attorney Michael O’Mara asserted Friday there is a strong chance of former President Donald Trump’s legal team overturning the guilty verdict against him in his New York trial. A jury in Manhattan convicted Trump in the case brought by Democratic District Attorney Alvin Bragg on all 34 counts of falsifying business records. CNN […] The post Defense Attorney Tells CNN There’s a “Great Likelihood” of Trump Overturning the Verdict on Numerous “Issues” appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 03:44:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maine Issuing Licenses to Individuals With Bogus SSNs</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/30/maine_issuing_licenses_to_individuals_with_bogus_ssns_624642.html</link><description>A police department in southern Maine is seeing an uptick in the number of driver's licenses issued by the Bureau of Motor Vehicles (BMV) to individuals using the social security number 999-99-9999. We've seen an uptick in [BMV] using 999-99-9999 for social security numbers, wrote Darcie L. Valido, the Assistant Director of Operations for Sanford</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 19:38:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Soros heir urges Democrats to hammer Trump as 'convicted felon at every opportunity'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/soros-heir-urges-democrats-hammer-trump-convicted-felon-every-opportunity</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>George Soros' son urged Democrats to wield Trump's conviction against him, constantly referring to him as a "convicted felon," ahead of the election.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 22:34:58 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>