<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 07:11:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>CBDCs, BRICS, and De-Dollarization Efforts Accelerate Ahead of a Possible Return of Trump</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/cbdcs-brics-de-dollarization-efforts-accelerate-ahead-possible/</link><description>Note: The information provided by The Liberty Daily or any related communications is for informational purposes only and should not be considered as financial advice. We do not provide personalized investment, financial, or legal advice. The Liberty Daily benefits from purchases made through our sponsors. The slow and steady push for de-dollarization across the globe […]
The post CBDCs, BRICS, and De-Dollarization Efforts Accelerate Ahead of a Possible Return of Trump appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 12:03:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>US Pays Little Attention to Latin America. China Moves In</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/08/us_pays_little_attention_to_latin_america_china_moves_in_623267.html</link><description>To fight China's growing influence, the U.S. must increase economic engagement in Latin America Opinion</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 04:20:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New mothers need what modern medicine neglects</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/new-mothers-need-what-modern-medicine-neglects-2668209569.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52202477&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C310</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52202477&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C310" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52202477&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;coordinates=0,0,0,140 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg%3Fid%3D52202477%26width%3D1200%26height%3D800%26coordinates%3D0%2C0%2C0%2C140%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;I refer to the period of time following the birth of my first kid as my trial by fire.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;New motherhood thrust me into an awkward phase rivaled only by puberty. Three months postpartum, my skin suddenly erupted in deep, sore, bleeding, disfiguring cystic acne that covered my entire face. My hair, once red, curly, and plentiful, turned dark and fell out in handfuls, leaving bald patches not only in the normal spots at the temple but throughout my whole scalp. My whole body seemed to swell, even six months postpartum. That following year, I had two miscarriages. Everything felt as if it were falling apart — because it was!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If one thing unites every postpartum tradition across the world, it is female-to-female care. In case anyone needs reminding: Having a baby is a uniquely female experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This unfortunate experience inspired curiosity: What’s wrong with me? Is this normal? Was it always like this? For everyone? How could human civilization sustain itself if every child born means its mother not only endures hell through the pains of birth but also permanent, disfiguring ill health? Where’s the bliss I was promised? What am I missing? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On one hand, maternal sacrifice is built into the very fabric of reality. The built-in difficulty is a fact that must be confronted with fortitude; it also &lt;a href="https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/pdf/10.1080/14681990412331297974#:~:text=Perhaps%20after%20human%20childbirth%2C%20vasopressin,loss%20of%20interest%20in%20sex." target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;bonds us to our children&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. But how much is too much? At what point does heroic fortitude become stubborn foolhardiness? At what point is it permissible to look around and wonder if the suffering you endure is the result of some easily remedied ignorance or injustice — and so, warrants a solution? At what point is it permissible to seek help? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;At what point is it permissible to seek help?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt; The fact that this question is something I regularly consider reflects how very &lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;American&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt; I am to the core — proudly! That attitude is what has made America the greatest commercial republic in all of human history. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ours is an implicitly industrious — liberal, independence-prizing — mode of operation. This doesn’t translate perfectly over to the domestic world, especially not the particular moment in time that is postpartum. It took my health crumbling completely to realize that motherhood wasn’t something I could approach with white-knuckled ambitions of singular success. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;"Foolish the doctor who despises the knowledge acquired by the ancients." — Hippocrates&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today in America, we do not hold any formal, ritualized postpartum tradition. The average American woman is discharged from the hospital within 48 hours of birth, and she is compelled by her employer to return to work after two weeks. The average American family lives far from relatives. The average American neighbor doesn’t know what’s going on next door. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are more likely to survive than our forebears, but far less likely to continue having children. TikTok is saturated with mom content describing the intense loneliness American women feel in the exile of motherhood. As Tim Carney points out in his recent book, "&lt;a href="https://helenroy.substack.com/p/family-unfriendly-how-our-culture" target="_blank"&gt;Family Unfriendly&lt;/a&gt;," neither the infrastructure nor the culture of modern America is conducive to domestic harmony. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;History informs us of alternatives. Contra the modern attitude toward motherhood, childbirth, independence, the nature of the female body, and what matters in life, every civilized pre-industrial society held strict traditional rules — prohibitions &lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt; requirements — for women and their relatives to abide by during the period of time following childbirth. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These rules carved out a time and space for mothers and their babies to convalesce, physically and spiritually, for all the ways they were uniquely vulnerable. It was also thought — across cultures! — that the preservation of a woman’s health during postpartum would prefigure good health in menopause.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The medical literature holds that the involution of the uterus after childbirth takes approximately six weeks. This concept is not unlike what is found in the Bible; in the Old Testament, women were considered “impure” for 40 days after the birth of a boy and 80 days after the birth of a girl. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Impurity,” in this case, is not a matter of spiritual degradation, as the English translation may suggest. It is a matter of &lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;ritual separation&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt; of human blood from the sanctuary of the temple. A woman bleeds as long as her uterus is returning to normal size. For most women, that means she’s bleeding, or is at risk of hemorrhage, for at least six weeks. Ancient Jews held a ritual “purification” of women 40 days after birth. Early Christians upheld and elaborated on that tradition through what is known now as “&lt;a href="https://www.irishfamilyhistorycentre.com/article/churching/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;the churching of women&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In "&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/First-Forty-Days-Essential-Nourishing/dp/B08ZBM2RZV" target="_blank"&gt;The First Forty Days: The Essential Art of Nourishing the New Mother&lt;/a&gt;," Heng Ou, a Chinese-American mother, describes the ancient Chinese tradition of &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/national/health-science/i-tried-the-chinese-practice-of-sitting-the-month-after-childbirth/2017/01/06/54517ee0-ad0b-11e6-a31b-4b6397e625d0_story.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;zuoyuezi&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, “sitting the month,” where after a baby is born, the mother’s mother, grandmother, or an aunt moves in to nourish her, manage her home, and keep her warm following childbirth.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Mexico, the traditional &lt;a href="https://www.babycenter.com/baby/postpartum-health/bringing-back-the-hispanic-tradition-of-cuarentena-after-chi_10346386" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;cuarentena&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; requires women to avoid cold showers, drink lots of hot soups and milk, wear a postpartum &lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;faja&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, and be fully clothed with pants, socks, and a sweater. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To the &lt;a href="https://www.healthhub.sg/live-healthy/malay_confinement_practices#:~:text=During%20confinement%2C%20some%20new%20mums,to%20keep%20the%20body%20warm." target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Malays&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a birth is regarded as a gift bestowed by God. New mothers are often cared for by their mothers or mothers-in-law. During Malay confinement, new mothers will bathe in warm water that has been boiled with lemongrass and ginger to promote circulation in the body. They practice post-natal massage to tighten and tone muscles around the abdomen, revitalize their energy, and improve circulation. The Malays also originated &lt;a href="https://www.orchardbirths.com/belly-binding#:~:text=Bengkung%20Belly%20Binding%20is%20considered,more%20popular%20in%20the%20US." target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;bengkung&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; belly binding, a tradition of wrapping the abdominal muscles to bring the musculature of the waist back together after birth — a practice that has recently become popular in Western crunchy and celebrity circles. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;"The march of science and technology does not imply growing intellectual complexity in the lives of most people. It often means the opposite." — Thomas Sowell&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No such acknowledgement of change, of vulnerability, or of status is built into American women's initiation into motherhood. Modernity — modern technology, including clean water systems, antibiotics, ultrasound, and to an extent, standardized systems of care — enables our historically excellent survival rate. What a luxury that we have forgotten how high infant and maternal mortality has been in the past! But what did modern society exchange, however indirectly or unintentionally, for lower infant and maternal mortality?  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps it was intergenerational interdependence for a sense of certainty. Wisdom for intelligence. Community for commodity. The critical function of midwives, grandmothers, and sisters-in-law — tending vulnerable, familial women and children — has been almost universally outsourced to the medical profession. But the medical profession optimizes for efficiency, reducing the lying-in period to the minimum amount of time necessary to ensure that mom and baby aren’t going to die. That becomes the new standard of care. The tradition of a month of rest became not just optional; it was forgotten entirely. Basic survival is a fine goal — but is it sufficient if our ultimate purpose is to promote true human flourishing? And are the apparent trade-offs we’ve made &lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;actually &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;mutually exclusive?  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was lucky, comparatively: There was no office to which I needed to return days postpartum, my husband has always been attentive and loving, and my child and I were both born into an era of maternal and neonatal &lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;survival&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. Still, I suffered as a consequence of chronic sleeplessness, stress, and nutrient deficiency. My symptoms seemed to indicate a chronic inflammation issue that is basically illegible to Western medical professionals. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What was behind the chronic stress? If I can be honest: loneliness, anxiety, ignorance, and stubborn resistance to true rest. Critically, I lacked the company of a more experienced woman to show me the ropes. My birth trauma had convinced me my baby would die if I ever lost sight of her. The internet didn’t help. I hadn’t met my friends yet. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here is where my Americanness helped me after initially hurting me: Having reached my threshold for suffering, I prayed and resolved that I’d develop a better system for the next time I gave birth, and set forth testing several practices and products cobbled together from the various folk traditions I mentioned already. I asked: What principles of postpartum care are &lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;universally recognized&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The regulatory agencies may lag when it comes to innovation, but there are factions of the scientific community that are catching up to the ancestral wisdom by systematically verifying its efficacy. Doctors like Aviva Romm have inspired a new generation of practitioners to take herbal medicine seriously, and the studies coming out about the effectiveness of herbs such as &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC5376420/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;holy basil&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, used in common folk postpartum care are promising. Discovering Dr. Romm was life-changing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The following postpartum principles helped me not only maintain but improve my health, sanity, hair, and skin after my second and third children were born. It’s never been easy, but never again did I experience the cold exile of isolation, exhaustion, hormonal chaos, and depression that haunted the first year of my first daughter’s life. These are where I’d start if I could go back in time. I hope they help you, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Female Friendship&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“A woman's function is laborious, but because it is gigantic, not because it is minute. I will pity Mrs. Jones for the hugeness of her task; I will never pity her for its smallness." — G.K. Chesterton&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If one thing unites every postpartum tradition across the world, it is female-to-female care. In case anyone needs reminding: Having a baby is a uniquely female experience. Husbands should be intensely interested and supportive of their wives’ needs, but there are things they cannot know and solutions they cannot intuit because of the limitations of their experience. In so many ways, postpartum begins a new season of formation, and you will need a teacher. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Find female friends.&lt;/em&gt; Find surrogate (not literally) mothers if yours doesn’t live nearby or is otherwise disposed. If you’re expecting, new to a place, and you have the money, invest in a postpartum doula, night nurse, or mother’s helper. There are some apps now, including Peanut, where you can search to meet buddies, but I think the best kind of friendships happen when you cannot choose your precise qualifications for what you think you like in someone. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Church communities often (not always) provide some kind of preformed social connections — and a shared worldview upon which new connections can be forged. Hobby groups can’t guarantee ideological uniformity, but participation in one at least signifies that the participant values the human experience more than scrolling TikTok endlessly in their spare time — that’s a red pill of its own. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crunchy Facebook mom groups may be another good place to go spelunking for friends. Start your own group message and let people know when you’re heading to the gym or the park or wherever. The key is to tap into and make yourself useful within existing networks of women; even if you don’t find your bestie on the first shot, you will learn more about what, and who, is out there. If your efforts are fruitful, these will be the women that talk you through dark days, bring you food, babysit your kids, become godparents to your kids, and watch your kids grow up. &lt;em&gt;Love them well.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Seclusion, not isolation&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“We live, in fact, in a world starved for solitude, silence, and private: and therefore starved for meditation and true friendship.” — C. S. Lewis&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Bouncing back” — the vapid expectation that women “be back in their pre-pregnancy jeans” within the month — is mirrored by the expectation that immediately after the pains of childbirth have passed, the new mother is as emotionally and mentally sharp as ever. Clinical postpartum depression and anxiety aside, this is an amazingly ignorant expectation, and it requires its witting or unwitting believers to also believe the “mind in a vat” account of human nature: The mind and body are easily and completely distinguishable, the latter easily overcome by the former. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Historically speaking, postpartum convalescence was about much more than the body, since the body was never understood as totally distinct from the mind. In order to protect one’s peace, new mothers should remain sequestered from strangers, outsiders, and, truly, anyone they do not trust. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even some traditionalist circles seem to do progressivism with extra steps in this regard, with some women returning to Latin mass within 48 hours of giving birth. Recovery is not a competition. Though it’s rarely articulated and difficult to dig up historically, there &lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt; a robust tradition of postpartum rest for Christian mothers. &lt;em&gt;Do not allow yourself to be made to feel guilty or extravagant for taking your forty days of seclusion if you can arrange your life in such a way that it’s possible.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Warmth&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another simple and universal truth of traditional postpartum care: for the full forty days, keep your body warm, especially your feet and belly. Wear wool socks. Never be without a blanket. Warm baths with herbs, epsom salts, regular salt, baking soda, and lavender essential oil can be lifegiving. If you get your hair wet, dry immediately with heat. I use a heating pad over the uterus which also helps with afterbirth pains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Vitamin A is for Animal&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Let food be your medicine and medicine be your food.” — Hippocrates&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Breastmilk is extremely high in vitamin A, a vitamin that the American College of Obstetricians and Gynecologists has made a point to fearmonger against because isotretinoin (a highly concentrated form of synthetic Vitamin A, sold commercially as Accutane) is teratogenic to fetuses in utero. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Generally speaking, the rules ACOG sets for pregnancy are meant to be followed postpartum. Out of an “abundance of caution,” doctors instruct nervous new moms to avoid Vitamin A. Don’t eat liver, they say; too much Vitamin A could cause birth defects. While the latter part of that statement may be strictly true, it is an embellishment bordering on a lie, the consequences of which are staggering and, though not as obviously harmful as extreme birth defects, still painful.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Weston A. Price, a dentist who studied the bone structure of indigenous versus industrial peoples in the 1930s, concluded that modern people’s abandonment of Vitamin A-rich animal protein such as organ meats has led to underdeveloped jaws, crooked teeth, and breathing issues due to structural abnormalities in the modern face. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Price discovered that the diets of healthy traditional peoples contained at least 10 times as much vitamin A as the American diet of his day. His work revealed that vitamin A is one of several fat-soluble activators present only in animal fats and necessary for the assimilation of minerals in the diet. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the pregnant and postpartum mom, vitamin A deficiency can look like cystic acne, low &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/1856040/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;progesterone&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and immune issues. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;TLDR: you need to be consuming animal products. Every ancient tradition of postpartum care abides by this principle, leaning heavily into animal proteins and fats. Raw milk is preferable because the pasteurization process removes most of the Vitamin A and enzymes from the product. Organ meats are great. You can take the liver in capsule form. Steak is great. Chicken and bone broth are great. I put gelatin in everywhere it can dissolve without detection. In my experience, animal proteins are the nutritional necessity for postpartum. No vegan diets allowed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Rest and Prayer&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;God, grant me the serenity to accept the things I cannot change, the courage to change the things I can, and the wisdom to know the difference.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you haven’t already downloaded the Hallow app, it may be a good investment for your transition from maiden to mother. There are times when the exhaustion, the frequent interruptions, and the general sense of spontaneity will interrupt all your best laid plans for a 15-minute meditative prayer. "For everything there is a season, a time for every activity under heaven. A time to be born and a time to die. A time to plant and a time to harvest." (Ecclesiastes 3:1-2)This is a time to be born; when a baby is born, so is a mother. You may need to relearn how prayer happens throughout the day. You may learn what it really means to pray without ceasing. Hallow can help. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So many of the postpartum traditions I explored were inherited from a pre-Christian culture where a certain amount of superstition about protecting the baby from things like “the evil eye” was baked in. I think the truth in that impulse is that a woman can be as spiritually vulnerable as she is physically and emotionally in the days following childbirth. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think it’s good practice to simply acknowledge this. You will power through by God’s grace, but acknowledge it. Acknowledge your need for rest, and understand that Christ invites us to rest, to &lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;abide&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt; in Him. We have to do that, even if we’ve been trained by the careerist culture never to flinch or take a break. We women especially have some things to unlearn here. It’s important to remember that we have a God-given &lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;female&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt; body and vocation to honor and uphold. &lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Barron Trump to enter politics as Florida delegate at GOP convention</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/barron-trump-enter-politics-florida-delegate-gop-convention</link><description>Barron Trump, the youngest child of former President Trump will enter the political fray for the first time when he will be an at-large delegate to the Republican National Convention.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 12:01:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Journalist Jonathan Choe Clearly Struck a Nerve as University “Activists” Doxx Him . . . With Umbrellas [VIDEO]</title><link>https://rumble.com/v4u2fw8-journalist-jonathan-choe-clearly-struck-a-nerve-as-university-activists-dox.html</link><description>The post Journalist Jonathan Choe Clearly Struck a Nerve as University “Activists” Doxx Him . . . With Umbrellas [VIDEO] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:17:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Happiness Gap Between Left and Right Isn't Closing</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/08/happiness_gap_between_left_and_right_isnt_closing_623258.html</link><description>Why is it that a substantial body of social science research finds that conservatives are happier than liberals? A partial</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 04:20:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Being ‘Triggered’ By Mother’s Day Proves The Irreplaceable Role Of Moms</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/being-triggered-by-mothers-day-proves-the-irreplaceable-role-of-moms-2668209403.html</link><image_url>https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/pexels-katya-wolf-8715584.jpeg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/pexels-katya-wolf-8715584.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img class="rm-shortcode" id="47e13" src="https://www.conservativereview.com/media-library/eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpbWFnZSI6Imh0dHBzOi8vdGhlZmVkZXJhbGlzdC5jb20vd3AtY29udGVudC91cGxvYWRzLzIwMjQvMDUvcGV4ZWxzLWthdHlhLXdvbGYtODcxNTU4NC0xMjAweDY3NS5qcGVnIiwiZXhwaXJlc19hdCI6MTc0MzExMjA4Mn0.syam08SOJpO91iZNTxj-Mrrq5rrsMXCXtNpCHPmMfps/image.jpeg" /&gt;We are watching the self-inflicted wounds of a culture that has been trying to erase motherhood for five decades, and the results are not pretty.&lt;/span&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:51:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alabama lawmakers strengthen penalties for falsely reporting a crime after Carlee Russell kidnapping hoax</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/alabama-strengthen-penalties-falsely-reporting-crime-carlee-russell-kidnapping-hoax</link><description>Falsely reporting a crime to law enforcement is one step away from becoming a felony in certain circumstances in Alabama after the bill passed the state legislature on Wednesday.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 10:45:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Violent Tornadoes Slam Southern States</title><link>https://www.toddstarnes.com/weather/violent-tornadoes-slam-southern-states/</link><description>The post Violent Tornadoes Slam Southern States appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:16:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Universities Surrender to Pro-Hamas Demonstrators</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/08/universities_surrender_to_pro-hamas_demonstrators_623243.html</link><description>By now, the pro-Hamas demonstrations that have swept American universities have become disruptive and even violent.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 04:19:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>American Families Can’t Get A Grip On Their Budgets Until Washington Fixes Its Own</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/american-families-cant-get-a-grip-on-their-budgets-until-washington-fixes-its-own-2668209388.html</link><image_url>https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/alexander-grey-8a5eJ1-mmQ-unsplash.jpeg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/alexander-grey-8a5eJ1-mmQ-unsplash.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img class="rm-shortcode" id="9679b" src="https://www.conservativereview.com/media-library/eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpbWFnZSI6Imh0dHBzOi8vdGhlZmVkZXJhbGlzdC5jb20vd3AtY29udGVudC91cGxvYWRzLzIwMjQvMDUvYWxleGFuZGVyLWdyZXktOGE1ZUoxLW1tUS11bnNwbGFzaC0xMjAweDY3NS5qcGVnIiwiZXhwaXJlc19hdCI6MTcyMzc2NDg2OH0.6YiTxmrNVao7tJKoT2wv_dM6sr9YOPt8ms4mHhKc4CY/image.jpeg" /&gt;Reports confirm Washington has created a vicious cycle for struggling families, not to mention the federal government as a whole.&lt;/span&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:50:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden national security adviser's wife launches run for House seat in key swing state</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/biden-national-security-advisers-wife-launches-run-house-seat-key-swing-state</link><description>Maggie Goodlander, a former top Biden administration official and the wife of National Security Adviser Jake Sullivan, launches a Democratic congressional campaign in battleground New Hampshire</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 10:30:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meet the 11 Republican Heroes Who Stood up Against the Swamp</title><link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2024/05/08/meet-the-11-republican-heroes-who-stood-up-against-the-swamp/</link><description>The post Meet the 11 Republican Heroes Who Stood up Against the Swamp appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:16:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden's Oval Office vs. America's Kitchen Table</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/08/bidenrsquos_oval_office_vs_americarsquos_kitchen_table_623240.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 04:19:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Toto Recall: Biden bashing in, Hamas hating still out</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/toto-recall-biden-bashing-in-hamas-hating-still-out-2668209498.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/toto-recall-biden-bashing-in-hamas-hating-still-out.jpg?id=52195996&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C171</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/toto-recall-biden-bashing-in-hamas-hating-still-out.jpg?id=52195996&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C171" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/toto-recall-biden-bashing-in-hamas-hating-still-out.jpg?id=52195996&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;coordinates=0,0,0,1 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/toto-recall-biden-bashing-in-hamas-hating-still-out.jpg%3Fid%3D52195996%26width%3D1200%26height%3D800%26coordinates%3D0%2C0%2C0%2C1%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the juiciest stories happen in the backyard of “Saturday Night Live.” It’s the Big Apple, and there’s never a dull moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consider privileged college students trashing a campus building in between chanting for violence against Jews.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s a truth-to-power moment for the Not Ready for Prime Time Players! (That’s the name given to the show’s wild and crazy cast in the ‘70s.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not exactly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“SNL” brewed the weakest comic tea possible out of the Columbia U protests. The show’s latest &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=D3sJBQpd1hc&amp;amp;t=115s" target="_blank"&gt;cold open&lt;/a&gt; followed three parents conflicted about the raging pro-Palestinian protests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Show stalwart Kenan Thompson drew a few smiles through sheer force of will. The city’s sizable Jewish population, alas, likely wasn’t amused. Nor was anyone else.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Later, during the “Weekend Update” segment, coanchor Michael Che clucked his tongue over the Columbia U violence-a-palooza.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey, it’s not happening in their studio, right?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Add it all together, and it’s the perfect symbol of “SNL” betraying its once-great legacy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Jon Stewart as ... a broken clock&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jon Stewart told the truth again. He must want an early exit from his “Daily Show” gig.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The far-left comedian riffed on President Joe Biden during a Netflix comedy special, and he couldn’t hold back about the &lt;a href="https://www.businessinsider.com/jon-stewart-trump-may-be-scary-biden-too-old-president-2024-5" target="_blank"&gt;aging leader’s, well, age&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm not saying that Biden can't contribute to society, he just shouldn't be president.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whenever Stewart steps a toe off the progressive plantation, he gets an earful. Remember the outrage when he said the COVID-19 virus likely came from ... the Wuhan Lab experimenting with viruses?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He’ll get more not-so-friendly fire again and likely revert to his “Orange Man Bad” playbook.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Kristen Stewart is ... box-office poison&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kristen Stewart loves making movies no one wants to see. Her 2020 thriller “Underwater” barely drew a crowd. Neither did “Spencer” (2021) or “Crimes of the Future” (2022). She followed them up with this year’s “Love Lies Bleeding.” The grind-house thriller leaned hard into its lesbian sex scenes, keeping some folks away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then, she pouted to the press that people were offended by her “racy” lesbian photo spread, even though she seemed like the only person paying attention to it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Voila! The film earned a pathetic $8.3 million earlier this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, she’s vowing to scare away even more fans with her next project. Her directorial debut, “The Chronology of Water,” features “incest and periods and a woman violently repossessing her voice and body,” &lt;a href="https://www.usmagazine.com/entertainment/news/kristen-stewart-says-directorial-debut-is-about-incest-and-periods/" target="_blank"&gt;she told the press.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yes, she admits audiences want to see “Jesus and dogs” on screen, but her inner artist demands more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A few more flops, and she’ll don a chastity belt and beg for a “Twilight” reunion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Michael Rapaport risks 'safety'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If Robert De Niro roasts Donald Trump for the 14th time in a week, it makes all the news outlets. Reporters can’t get enough of it, and they’ll share the quotes far and wide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If a Jewish star’s freedom of speech gets squelched? Crickets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Actor-turned-comic Michael Rapaport learned that lesson. The “Beautiful Girls” alum’s stand-up gig got canceled over the proverbial heckler’s veto. Rapaport is both Jewish and a staunch defender of Israel. That makes him a ripe target for today’s “Pro-Palestinian” mobs, who try to silence him at every turn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shockingly, said mob failed to do so &lt;a href="https://www.portlandmercury.com/comedy/2024/01/09/46971994/why-are-people-protesting-michael-rapaports-portland-comedy-shows" target="_blank"&gt;a few weeks ago in Portland&lt;/a&gt;. His luck ran out in Madison, Wisconsin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The reason? &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/media/comedian-michael-rapaport-stunned-show-allegedly-canceled-over-pro-israel-views-p-off" target="_blank"&gt;“Safety concerns.”&lt;/a&gt; AKA the “heckler’s veto” on steroids.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rapaport joins a growing list of Jewish artists canceled for their views. Author/actor Brett Gelman of “Stranger Things” fame saw &lt;a href="https://deadline.com/2024/03/stranger-things-actor-brett-gelman-signing-canceled-book-soup-safety-concerns-1235849470/" target="_blank"&gt;several bookstore appearances canceled&lt;/a&gt; this year. Jewish musician Matisyahu &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/jewish-musician-has-2-shows-canceled-after-venues-staff-reportedly-refuse-to-work-his-events-islamophobic-and-transphobic" target="_self"&gt;faced similar repercussions&lt;/a&gt; despite his peaceful mien.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If Rapaport wants to draw attention to his plight, he better start teeing off on Trump. Except that may not happen, either. The dedicated Trump critic says he &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/michael-rapaport-goes-scorched-earth-on-biden-and-progressive-democrats" target="_self"&gt;might just vote for him&lt;/a&gt; come November thanks to our feckless current leader.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The best news of the week? Disney CEO Bob Iger announces we’ll only get two to three woke superhero films a year, down from a brief high of four.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FIRST ON FOX: Biden gets boost from major health care group warning Trump poses 'threat to public health'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/biden-boost-major-healthcare-group-warning-trump-threat-public-health</link><description>A group of 48 former high-level medical officials have penned a letter pleading with Americans not to put former President Trump back in the White House.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 10:00:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dementia Joe’s Interview With Erin Burnett Is Hilarious Exercise in Childish Denial and Straight-Up Falsehood</title><link>https://redstate.com/nick-arama/2024/05/08/biden-interview-with-erin-burnet-is-hilarious-exercise-in-childish-denial-n2173936</link><description>The post Dementia Joe’s Interview With Erin Burnett Is Hilarious Exercise in Childish Denial and Straight-Up Falsehood appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:14:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Tale of Two Pictures</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/08/a_tale_of_two_pictures_623257.html</link><description>They tell an infinite number of words</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 04:19:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blaze News original: The disturbing trend of females as young as 12 who've been accused of brutal physical attacks</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/blaze-news-original-the-disturbing-trend-of-females-as-young-as-12-who-ve-been-accused-of-brutal-physical-attacks-2668209225.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/blaze-news-original-the-disturbing-trend-of-females-as-young-as-12-who-ve-been-accused-of-brutal-physical-attacks.jpg?id=52201690&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C127</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/blaze-news-original-the-disturbing-trend-of-females-as-young-as-12-who-ve-been-accused-of-brutal-physical-attacks.jpg?id=52201690&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C127" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/blaze-news-original-the-disturbing-trend-of-females-as-young-as-12-who-ve-been-accused-of-brutal-physical-attacks.jpg?id=52196884&amp;amp;width=1245&amp;amp;height=700&amp;amp;coordinates=0,0,0,47 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/blaze-news-original-the-disturbing-trend-of-females-as-young-as-12-who-ve-been-accused-of-brutal-physical-attacks.jpg%3Fid%3D52196884%26width%3D1245%26height%3D700%26coordinates%3D0%2C0%2C0%2C47%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last month, Blaze News focused on a dozen disturbing instances when students got &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/blaze-news-original-a-dozen-disturbing-instances-when-students-got-brutally-violent-with-teachers" target="_blank"&gt;brutally violent with teachers&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well, half the physical attacks we highlighted were carried out by females — two of whom were only 15 years old at the time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's so evil; how could you do that to a person? You have a mother and a father; how could you just beat a man until you take off half of his skull?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the trends Blaze News has been noticing over the last several years is the apparent increase in younger and younger kids getting charged with violent crimes — and arguably an even more surprising stat is how many of them are very young females.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We're talking age 14 — and as young as 12.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Readers of Blaze News likely recall the shocking story of a &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/girl-14-charged-with-murder" target="_blank"&gt;14-year-old girl&lt;/a&gt; who was charged as an adult with third-degree murder in connection with the brutal traffic cone beating of a 73-year-old man on a Philadelphia street well after midnight during the summer of 2022.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Officials said Gamara Mosley was seen hitting the victim twice with the traffic cone on camera and possibly another time off-camera, &lt;a href="https://www.fox29.com/news/james-lambert-death-girl-14-turns-herself-in-for-beating-death-of-73-year-old-in-north-philly-police-say" target="_blank"&gt;WTXF-TV reported&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;         —  (@)        &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/KellyRuleTV/status/1547615556861235200"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Sources &lt;a href="https://www.nbcphiladelphia.com/news/local/deadly-traffic-cone-beating-north-philadelphia/3293913/" target="_blank"&gt;told WCAU-TV&lt;/a&gt; that the victim was walking past a basketball court when he asked a group of teens why they were out so late.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's so evil; how could you do that to a person?" Elsie Stephens, the victim's older sister asked WCAU before adding, "You have a mother and a father; how could you just beat a man until you take off half of his skull?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Authorities also charged a 14-year-old male as an adult with murder in connection with the attack, but his charges were dismissed, the &lt;a href="https://archive.is/9zBsN/again?url=https://www.inquirer.com/crime/james-lambert-traffic-cone-philadelphia-charges-20240328.html#selection-1311.0-1311.319" target="_blank"&gt;Philadelphia Inquirer reported&lt;/a&gt; in March. Other kids turned themselves into police but ultimately weren't charged.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Inquirer had the following to say in regard to Mosley:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;In late February, Mosley’s case was decertified and sent to juvenile court, and she was adjudicated delinquent of murder, conspiracy, and possession of an instrument of crime, according to records. Court administrators did not respond to questions about her sentence. Mosley’s lawyer, Susan M. Lin, declined to comment.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;The following are more examples of very young female teens and preteens accused of carrying out violent acts:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Girls, 12 and 13, accused of beating disabled man to death — then walking away in a 'celebratory mood'&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three girls — one 12-year-old and two 13-year-olds — were accused of viciously beating a disabled man and leaving him for dead in a &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/tag/washington" target="_self"&gt;Washington, D.C.&lt;/a&gt;, alley in 2023. The trio allegedly walked away from the "horrific" beatdown in a "celebratory mood." Prosecutors said there is graphic video of the young girls brutally attacking 64-year-old Reggie Brown. An unknown male in his 20s initiated the assault, police said, noting the male reportedly grabbed Brown by the collar and threw him against a brick wall. According to the &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2024/03/30/us-news/three-girls-arrested-for-beating-disabled-man-to-death-on-dc-street/" target="_blank"&gt;New York Post&lt;/a&gt;, the girls were walking by at the time and one of them asked the male, "Can I fight him?” The male replied, "Yes." The girls allegedly chased Brown down an alley and threw him to the ground, after which they repeatedly kicked and stomped Brown in the head on the concrete, reportedly pulled down Brown's pants, took off his belt, and then beat him with his own belt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;8 teen girls charged with beating, stabbing to death 59-year-old man in Toronto — 3 suspects are 13 years old&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to the three 13-year-olds, police said three 14-year-old girls and two 16-year-old suspects were arrested in the December 2022 "swarming" attack. The victim was found on a street suffering from multiple stab wounds and later was pronounced dead at a hospital, ABC News said. Police said a number of weapons were recovered from the suspects, but the names of the suspects — all of whom were charged with murder — were not released due to their ages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Two 12-year-old females charged with aggravated assault in a violent attack that left 55-year-old woman unconscious and in critical condition&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Police said the victim was "assaulted to the point of unconsciousness" on a train platform in Edmonton, Alberta, and was hospitalized with significant head and facial injuries, &lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/edmonton/two-12-year-olds-charged-in-attack-at-edmonton-lrt-station-that-left-woman-in-critical-condition-1.7049430" target="_blank"&gt;CBC News said&lt;/a&gt;. The two females approached the victim who was sitting on a bench at night waiting for a train in November 2023, police said, adding that officers caught the females nearby after they fled the scene.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Gang of thugs beat 33-year-old woman unconscious on Philly street; at least 3 female suspects are 12, 13, and 14 years old&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img class="rm-shortcode" id="88c61" src="https://www.conservativereview.com/media-library/eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpbWFnZSI6Imh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnRoZWJsYXplLmNvbS9tZWRpYS1saWJyYXJ5L2ltYWdlLmpwZz9pZD01MjE5Njg3OCZhbXA7d2lkdGg9OTgwIiwiZXhwaXJlc19hdCI6MTc2Nzg0NDAyNX0.dVMmTX-g1pHMdTyoItaWA9b-HLRXcCFVzaysRCueT-E/image.jpg" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/6-suspects-ages-11-through-14-arrested-after-brutal-beating-of-woman-on-philly-street-that-left-her-unconscious" target="_blank"&gt;Blaze News noted&lt;/a&gt; in March 2023 that six suspects between the ages of 11 and 14 were in custody in connection with a &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/video-cops-on-hunt-for-8-thugs-after-woman-repeatedly-punched-stomped-until-she-lies-unconscious-on-philly-sidewalk" target="_self"&gt;brutal beating of a woman on a Philadelphia street that left her unconscious&lt;/a&gt;, police &lt;a href="https://6abc.com/center-city-attack-assault-near-hall-philadelphia-woman-assaulted-teens/12934677/" target="_blank"&gt;told WPVI-TV&lt;/a&gt;. One 14-year-old female was arrested at her home while investigators told the station there was a warrant for another 14-year-old female. According to &lt;a href="https://www.fox29.com/news/group-of-kids-11-14-charged-in-brutal-beating-of-woman-in-center-city-1-still-being-sought" target="_blank"&gt;WTXF-TV&lt;/a&gt;, at least three females — ages 12, 13, and 14 — are charged with aggravated assault, robbery, and reckless endangerment. Males were involved, too, and there were eight suspects total. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;13-year-old female charged in connection with deadly beating of 52-year-old NYC taxi driver&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 13-year-old female suspect faces gang assault and theft of service charges, &lt;a href="https://abc7ny.com/cab-driver-killed-arrest-teen-nyc/12161612/" target="_blank"&gt;WABC-TV reported&lt;/a&gt;, adding that authorities said she took part in the attack in Queens that killed 52-year-old Kutin Gyimah on Aug. 13, 2022. The suspects were accused of refusing to pay their fare and knocking Gyimah to the ground where he hit his head, the station said, adding that a 15-year-old girl and a pair of 20-year-old males previously were &lt;a href="https://abc7ny.com/nyc-taxi-cab-driver-killed-homicide/12143124/" target="_blank"&gt;charged in the attack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;4 females — all younger than 15 — accused of violently attacking 20-year-old woman they called a 'white b***h with braids'&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Police found the mob of teens in April 2022 kicking and punching the 20-year-old victim while she was on the ground near Boston's Downtown Crossing. The victim suffered a head injury and later told officers she was attacked because of her hair. &lt;a href="https://www.masslive.com/boston/2022/04/5-teens-arrested-in-downtown-crossing-attack-of-woman-wearing-braids-part-of-specific-group-of-violent-juveniles-boston-police-say.html" target="_blank"&gt;Mass Live&lt;/a&gt;, citing a police report, said the woman told officers a group of girls approached her and demeaned her as a "white bitch with braids." She reportedly told the group she identifies as Hispanic and started to walk away, but one of the teens chased her and pulled her down by her hair. Several others then allegedly joined in on the attack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Pair of 14-year-old girls accused in beating of 8-year-old boy&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two 14-year-old females and a 15-year-old female were accused in an April 2023 assault against an 8-year-old boy on a sidewalk in Bay City, &lt;a href="https://www.wnem.com/2023/04/25/police-teens-arrested-after-assaulting-8-year-old/" target="_blank"&gt;WNEM-TV reported&lt;/a&gt;. The beating was caught on video, and police said the victim suffered minor injuries and didn't need medical attention. At the time of the report, two of the three suspects had been arrested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;13-year-old female arrested, accused of brutally beating girl on school bus in attack that reportedly lasted 15 minutes&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the November 2023 physical attack caught on video, the 13-year-old victim from Acadian Middle School in Lafayette, Louisiana, was hospitalized with head trauma contusions, a broken nose, a busted lip, and an injured arm, &lt;a href="https://www.klfy.com/local/lafayette-parish/she-didnt-deserve-that-13-year-old-girl-afraid-to-go-to-school-after-beating-on-school-bus/" target="_blank"&gt;KLFY-TV reported&lt;/a&gt;. It stemmed from a thrown piece of candy intended for a little boy at a pep rally that ended up hitting another student. The victim reportedly apologized immediately, but apparently that wasn't sufficient. In addition to the female who was arrested and charged with simple assault, police charged a 12-year-old boy with simple assault as well, the station said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Females, 13 and 14, arrested after girl brutally beaten unconscious in attack at school caught on video&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The April 2022 physical attack against the 13-year-old victim took place in the cafeteria of Gulfstream Academy in Hallandale Beach, Florida, &lt;a href="https://wsvn.com/news/local/police-arrest-2-gulfstream-academy-students-accused-of-beating-up-classmate/" target="_blank"&gt;WSVN-TV reported&lt;/a&gt;, adding that that victim suffered a broken leg and a head injury. Secret Southerland, 14, appeared before a judge on charges of aggravated battery with serious bodily harm, the station said, adding that Southerland was scheduled to spend at least 21 days in jail on her felony charge. The other teen girl was charged with a misdemeanor. The victim has been scared to go back to school, WSVN said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Pair of 12-year-old females accused of torturing, beating, confining girl at sleepover — even burning her with lighters&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two 12-year-old girls were arrested in connection to an alleged violent assault on another girl in Logansport, Indiana, in late February 2022, &lt;a href="https://fox59.com/news/2-pre-teens-arrested-in-alleged-violent-assault-of-girl-at-sleepover-in-logansport/" target="_blank"&gt;WXIN-TV reported&lt;/a&gt;. Family members of the victim, a 12-year-old girl, told the station she was invited to what she believed was a sleepover with friends. Renita Contreras, the victim’s aunt, told WXIN her niece instead was "tortured, beaten, confined. Two juvenile females sat on top of her for two hours so she could not breathe, they burned her with cigarette lighters. It goes on and on." The victim also reportedly was cut on her face with a sharp object and had part of her hair shaved, the station said. One of the suspects was charged with the juvenile equivalents of criminal confinement resulting in serious bodily injury, intimidation with a deadly weapon, and battery resulting in serious bodily injury, all felonies, WXIN said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;12-year-old female charged with aggravated battery, kidnapping in attack against 13-year-old girl&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Police described a “disturbing” March 2023 assault against a 13-year-old girl at Jack and Jill Park in Albuquerque, the &lt;a href="https://www.abqjournal.com/news/local/young-siblings-tied-to-brutal-park-beating-rape-of-13-year-old/article_11274ff2-71cd-5486-b654-9a62293d6349.html" target="_blank"&gt;Albuquerque Journal reported&lt;/a&gt;. Police said the victim and her friend snuck out of a house to go to a party, after which the pair were separated, and the victim was taken to the park and “severely beaten.” The 12-year-old female suspect and two other teens were charged with aggravated battery and kidnapping, the paper said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ohio AG defends letter warning 'woke' masked anti-Israel protesters they face prison time: 'We have a society'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/ohio-ag-defends-letter-warning-woke-masked-anti-israel-protesters-they-face-prison-time-we-have-a-society</link><description>Ohio's Republican Attorney General is pushing back against 'woke' critics of his recent letter reminding anti-Israel protesters of a law that could mean prison time.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 09:00:42 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>