<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 06:59:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Election Interference: Secret Service Pushes Trump Rallies Indoors</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/election-interference-secret-service-pushes-trump-rallies-indoors/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>The United States Secret Service wants President Donald J. Trump’s presidential campaign to move their historic rallies indoors instead of doing the one job they have assigned to them. Between the failed assassination attempt against Trump and the subsequent resignation of the Secret Service’s diversity hire director, Kimberly Cheatle, the stage was set for what […] The post Election Interference: Secret Service Pushes Trump Rallies Indoors appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 11:58:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vulnerable House Dem dodges question on VP Harris' record as 'border czar': 'Don’t know who Kamala Harris is'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/vulnerable-house-dem-dodges-question-vp-harris-record-border-czar</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>Vulnerable Democrat Rep. Emilia Sykes dodged questions about Vice President Harris' record on the border when confronted shortly after endorsing her for president.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 11:00:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Senator Chuck Grassley Obtains Bodycam Footage From the Day of the Assassination Attempt [VIDEO]</title><link>https://rumble.com/v586qy3-breaking-senator-chuck-grassley-obtains-bodycam-footage-from-day-of-the-ass.html</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>The post Senator Chuck Grassley Obtains Bodycam Footage From the Day of the Assassination Attempt [VIDEO] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 11:39:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kamala Harris’ husband Doug Emhoff responds to Trump's attacks on her: 'That's all he’s got?'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/kamala-harris-husband-doug-emhoff-responds-trumps-attacks-her-thats-all-hes-got</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>Second gentleman Doug Emhoff responded after former President Trump criticized his wife, Vice President Kamala Harris, after the launch of her presidential campaign.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 10:12:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>“Absolute Brainwashing”: Former Co-Host of ‘The View’ Rips Her Old Show for “Bullying” Viewers Into Backing Heels-Up Harris</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/absolute-brainwashing-former-co-host-view-rips-her/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>(DCNF)—Elisabeth Hasselbeck, a former co-host of “The View,” ripped Whoopi Goldberg for actively “bullying” viewers into backing Kamala Harris during an appearance by White House press secretary Karine Jean-Pierre. Jean-Pierre dismissed concerns on “The View” Tuesday about whether President Joe Biden could finish his term after ending his reelection bid. Hasselbeck called the appearance a […] The post “Absolute Brainwashing”: Former Co-Host of ‘The View’ Rips Her Old Show for “Bullying” Viewers Into Backing Heels-Up Harris appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 11:38:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Steven Pinker: Young people sick and tired of being told, 'you can't say that, you can't think that' on campus</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/steven-pinker-young-people-sick-tired-being-told-you-cant-say-that-you-cant-think-that-campus</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>Dr. Steven Pinker offers a robust defense of Enlightenment values, liberalism, rationality, and market economies, while championing academic freedom on college campuses.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 10:03:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Files FEC Complaint Over Traitor Joe Transferring Campaign War Chest to Heels Up Harris</title><link>https://justthenews.com/government/federal-agencies/trump-files-fec-complaint-over-biden-transferring-campaign-chest-kamala</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>The post Trump Files FEC Complaint Over Traitor Joe Transferring Campaign War Chest to Heels Up Harris appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 11:38:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden set to address nation after pressured exit from 2024 race</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/biden-set-address-nation-following-pressured-exit-from-2024-race</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>President Biden is expected to address the nation for the first time since dropping out of the 2024 race in an address from the Oval Office on Wednesday evening.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 09:00:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mother of Hostage Releases Video of Abduction to Gaza Following October 7 Invasion</title><link>https://allisrael.com/mother-of-hostage-releases-video-of-his-abduction-to-gaza-following-october-7-invasion</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>The post Mother of Hostage Releases Video of Abduction to Gaza Following October 7 Invasion appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 11:37:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Secret Service failures during Trump rally spur concerns for Netanyahu visit, McCaul says</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/secret-service-failures-during-trump-rally-spur-concerns-netanyahu-visit-mccaul-says</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>House Foreign Affairs Committee Chairman Michael McCaul spoke with Fox News Digital after touring the site of the failed assassination attempt against former President Trump.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 09:00:37 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>