<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 07:19:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Democrat Hellhole: Bride-To-Be Shot at Her Own Bachelorette Party in DC Mass Shooting at Popular Bar [VIDEO]</title><link>https://rumble.com/v4st15r-bride-to-be-shot-at-her-own-bachelorette-party-in-dc-mass-shooting-at-popul.html</link><description>The post Democrat Hellhole: Bride-To-Be Shot at Her Own Bachelorette Party in DC Mass Shooting at Popular Bar [VIDEO] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 10:40:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How We Kept College Radicals in Check in Florida</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/01/how_we_kept_college_radicals_in_check_in_florida_622810.html</link><description>America's academic leaders seem powerless only because they've spent decades promoting the ideologies now on such brutal and ugly display.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 04:10:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Poll: More Than 8 In 10 Americans Don’t Trust Corporate Media To Report Facts</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/poll-more-than-8-in-10-americans-dont-trust-corporate-media-to-report-facts-2668130005.html</link><image_url>https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/9434755558_639a3453ab_k-e1714598950284.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/9434755558_639a3453ab_k-e1714598950284.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img class="rm-shortcode" id="3162f" src="https://www.conservativereview.com/media-library/eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpbWFnZSI6Imh0dHBzOi8vdGhlZmVkZXJhbGlzdC5jb20vd3AtY29udGVudC91cGxvYWRzLzIwMjQvMDUvOTQzNDc1NTU1OF82MzlhMzQ1M2FiX2stMTIwMHg2NzUuanBnIiwiZXhwaXJlc19hdCI6MTcyNjYwNjMzNX0.GAMLuVCvqzJJ-S4Xr3pKFg1LXjUgPx39rthBdoMmusM/image.jpg" /&gt;Overwhelming majorities of Americans have lost their trust in the media to accurately report the news, according to a new poll out Wednesday.&lt;/span&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 12:13:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Matt Gaetz blasts House antisemitism legislation as ‘ridiculous hate speech bill’</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/matt-gaetz-blasts-house-antisemitism-legislation-ridiculous-hate-speech-bill</link><description>Congressman Matt Gaetz railed against the House’s antisemitism legislation on Wednesday, saying that some excerpts of the Bible would meet this bill’s definition of antisemitism.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 12:13:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Starbucks Is in Trouble</title><link>https://discern.tv/starbucks-is-in-trouble/</link><description>The post Starbucks Is in Trouble appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 10:33:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden's Worst-Case Economic Scenario Unfolding at Worst Time</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/01/bidenrsquos_worst-case_economic_scenario_unfolding_at_worst_time_622829.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 04:10:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Don’t save Democrats from their own campus disaster</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/dont-save-democrats-from-their-own-campus-disaster-2668129907.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52155119&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C120</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52155119&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C120" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img class="rm-shortcode" id="47268" src="https://www.conservativereview.com/media-library/eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpbWFnZSI6Imh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnRoZWJsYXplLmNvbS9tZWRpYS1saWJyYXJ5L2ltYWdlLmpwZz9pZD01MjE1NTExOSZhbXA7d2lkdGg9OTgwIiwiZXhwaXJlc19hdCI6MTczMzg0MzMwOX0.6AEjVuDReeRjNNnCWMd5cC28roUTfeo_66gcNWnGeEk/image.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;My dear conservative friends, we need to have a talk. This is more of an intervention than anything else. You must stop protecting institutions that are committed to destroying your way of life. The university system hates you. It always has. It will continue to hate you until it is dismantled brick by brick and replaced with something else. Something better. The universities will just never be into you, and if two factions of the left want to destroy themselves while shutting down college campuses, that’s what we in politics like to call a win.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You don’t need to ride to the rescue. You aren’t the white knight in this scenario. Just grab some popcorn and enjoy the show; I promise this will work out in your favor if you let it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Red-state governors should maintain the safety of those under their care but otherwise leave leftists to their own devices. Let those factions fight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Protests surrounding the Hamas terror attack on October 7 in Gaza and the subsequent response by Israel have now raged on college campuses across the country for weeks. The establishment left is nominally pro-Israel due to a legacy attachment to the nation and the need to maintain a healthy relationship with major donors. The more radical leftist vanguard has drunk deeply from the well of wokeness and made the natural connection between anti-European decolonization rhetoric and Israel, which it now identifies as a white colonial oppressor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jews have been stalwart Democratic voters for a long time and have avoided being dropped to the bottom of the party’s oppression hierarchy, but that arrangement is now being called into question by other members of the coalition. The left has imported and elevated a generation of immigrants who feel no attachment to America’s past relationship with Israel, and many in the vanguard come from cultures that are openly hostile to the Jewish nation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The progressive coalition has always been tenuous, and October 7 created an eruption across the most critical fault line that has manifested as an intra-leftist civil war playing out on college campuses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most opposing political parties would recognize this as a gift from on high. The Republicans, on the other hand, have several specific hang-ups that compel them to solve this problem for their opponents.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The conservative impulse to protect institutions is an admirable one. In a healthy society, institutions are the formal structures that help to enshrine a culture’s values and transmit them to the next generation. But American society is not healthy, and the long march through the institutions perpetrated by the left has installed a hostile ideology deep into the heart of the university system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;College campuses are not places of learning where promising young minds develop the leadership skills necessary to forge a brighter future. These institutions are progressive seminaries where students go deeply into debt to learn how to hate their parents, religion, and nation. This ideological poison is then distributed through every major corporation, piece of entertainment, and news headline as college graduates take their places as leaders and managers throughout society.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conservatives have complained for decades that the public schools are hostile indoctrination centers designed to secure leftist hegemony, but when the pandemic shut down these enemy institutions, conservatives became the most vocal proponents of reopening them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The same dynamic is currently playing itself out on university campuses. Conservatives may complain about the education system, but they are ultimately defenders of the status quo and would rather see these institutions continue to operate, even if they are calling for the literal destruction of the United States.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Part of this response is linked to the natural and admirable conservative impulse toward order. Conservatives recoil at the idea of violence and intimidation on these campuses, and where Republican governors are in charge, they should absolutely protect the physical safety of all students.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But there is also an impulse among many Republican politicians to punish public criticism of Israel, and this is a serious problem.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The right has spent endless hours mocking the leftist ideas of hate speech and safe spaces, but now many GOP politicians are suddenly obsessed with implementing exactly those policies. Governors like Greg Abbott of Texas and Kevin Stitt of Oklahoma, for example, have come out in favor of cracking down on “hate speech” and anti-Semitism in the wake of these protests. It is becoming hard not to notice that most of these politicians took no action as anti-white rhetoric and demonstrations dominated academia for the last decade, to the point where that ideology has now made its way into several best-selling books.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Democrats are already facing a critical election in which they must run a deeply unpopular dementia patient against a former president who maintains a strong base of support despite being hit with an endless barrage of fake criminal charges. The very last thing the left wanted was a civil war on college campuses that exposed the disastrous contradictions at the heart of its coalition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The only thing that could possibly rescue the Democrats from this nightmare scenario would be footage of Republican governors sending in police to violently silence protesters. This would bail out the establishment and allow mainstream liberals to put the woke vanguard in its place while pointing at the GOP as the real enemy, a unifying symbol of authority to hate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know the gut instinct of the right is to snatch defeat from the jaws of victory, but the GOP must sit on its hands and let this play out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Try for a moment to imagine any scenario where two factions inside the right are destroying each other and humiliating themselves in an election year and the left dives on that grenade for conservatives. You can’t, because it would never happen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Again, red-state governors should maintain the safety of those under their care but otherwise leave leftists to their own devices. Let those factions fight. In the worst-case scenario, some kids don’t get to attend Hate America 101. And the best case? Things get so bad that the Democratic coalition rends itself asunder while desperate parents plead for the right to reform the university system from the ground up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am begging you, my conservative allies, take the easy win just this once.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ernst leads Senate GOP demanding Biden 'cease planning' Gaza refugee acceptance</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/ernst-leads-senate-gop-demanding-biden-cease-planning-gaza-refugee-acceptance</link><description>Sen. Joni Ernst, R-Iowa, led Republicans in a letter to President Biden, demanding he stop planning to authorize the acceptance of Palestinian refugees from Gaza into the U.S.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:00:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Herculean Task: Trump Will Have to Drag All of These Republican Establishment Candidates Over the Finish Line</title><link>https://revolver.news/2024/05/herculean-task-trump-will-again-have-to-drag-republican-establishment-candidates-over-the-finish-line/</link><description>The post Herculean Task: Trump Will Have to Drag All of These Republican Establishment Candidates Over the Finish Line appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 10:21:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>November Will Hinge on the Youth Vote</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/01/november_will_hinge_on_the_youth_vote_622828.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 04:10:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Left’s Phony ‘Fake Electors’ Crusade Ramps Up As 2024 Election Draws Closer</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/the-lefts-phony-fake-electors-crusade-ramps-up-as-2024-election-draws-closer-2668129772.html</link><image_url>https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Trumpprofile-scaled-e1714593367211.jpeg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Trumpprofile-scaled-e1714593367211.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img class="rm-shortcode" id="e080a" src="https://www.conservativereview.com/media-library/eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpbWFnZSI6Imh0dHBzOi8vdGhlZmVkZXJhbGlzdC5jb20vd3AtY29udGVudC91cGxvYWRzLzIwMjQvMDUvVHJ1bXBwcm9maWxlLXNjYWxlZC1lMTcxNDU5MzM2NzIxMS0xMjAweDY3NS5qcGVnIiwiZXhwaXJlc19hdCI6MTc2MzQ5NTQ5MX0.Qyec8FR2Xaa-V_Z9QxzqqVc2t09do77_fmPm9YEmfWg/image.jpeg" /&gt;The litigious left has run into some problems trying to sell its legally flawed narrative that alternate electors for Trump tried to overthrow  the 2020 election.&lt;/span&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NY v Trump to resume with gag order hearing after Trump fined $9K, threatened with jail time</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/ny-v-trump-resume-gag-order-hearing-trump-fined-9k-threatened-jail-time</link><description>The judge presiding over Trump’s criminal trial will hold a hearing to consider the remaining alleged gag order violations after fining Trump $9,000 and threatening jail time.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 09:00:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Former NFL Player Paul Blair Says the Pulpit in America Has Been Asleep Since WWII [VIDEO]</title><link>https://rumble.com/v4ssq2e-fomer-nfl-player-paul-blair-says-the-pulpit-in-america-has-been-asleep-sinc.html</link><description>The post Former NFL Player Paul Blair Says the Pulpit in America Has Been Asleep Since WWII [VIDEO] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 10:20:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Takes Aim at Trump-Era Tax Cuts</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/01/biden_takes_aim_at_trump-era_tax_cuts_622804.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 04:10:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How popular primaries foil conservatives and protect the uniparty</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/how-popular-primaries-foil-conservatives-and-protect-the-uniparty-2668129771.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/how-popular-primaries-foil-conservatives-and-protect-the-uniparty.jpg?id=52154221&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C72%2C0%2C73</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/how-popular-primaries-foil-conservatives-and-protect-the-uniparty.jpg?id=52154221&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C72%2C0%2C73" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/how-popular-primaries-foil-conservatives-and-protect-the-uniparty.jpg?id=52154221&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;coordinates=180,0,180,0 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/how-popular-primaries-foil-conservatives-and-protect-the-uniparty.jpg%3Fid%3D52154221%26width%3D1200%26height%3D800%26coordinates%3D180%2C0%2C180%2C0%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Letting the masses decide the party’s nominee for down-ballot offices is tantamount to letting the elites and special interests decide the outcome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are stuck with a uniparty because incumbents are rarely defeated in district races and are almost never defeated in primaries for statewide offices — including senator and governor. The only way to change the party in one election cycle is by transitioning from popular primaries to representative conventions where high-information delegates may separate the frauds from dedicated conservatives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Money can buy you name ID in popular primaries, but it can’t buy you love from highly informed delegates and precinct captains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If Utah would only return the glory to its convention system, it would stand as a model for the nation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Republicans have liberal governors ruining red states. This is why we only hear about the successes of Ron DeSantis in Florida and few others. Western red states — from Utah and Idaho to Wyoming and North Dakota — are full of progressive Republicans. It is practically impossible for insurgent candidates to raise enough money to win statewide elections, and it is essentially unheard of to knock out a sitting governor in a primary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And yet, if Utah’s convention had been the final deciding election for the nomination, Governor Spencer Cox would not only have been defeated, but he would also have lost by a 2-1 margin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;GOP delegates met on Saturday for the Utah nominating convention and selected state Representative Phil Lyman as the party’s nominee for governor with 67.5% of the vote. The delegates are so much better informed about the issues, true records, and motivations of each candidate that a sitting governor without a known scandal only received a third of the vote from the delegates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sadly, in recent years, the party has gutted the power of the convention by allowing the loser to collect signatures and head to a popular primary, which is decisive. Cox has already qualified for the GOP primary on June 25 by gathering 28,000 signatures. Can you imagine the sort of party we would have if the convention delegates had the final say&lt;em&gt; in every red state&lt;/em&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thus far, however, we have failed to knock off a single House incumbent in a primary. Had the convention results been binding, 1st District Rep. Blake Moore would have been booted. He was defeated by 10 points in the final round of voting by political novice Paul Miller, who criticized Blake’s votes for the spending bills. Miller would never stand a chance in a popular primary, and unfortunately Blake has collected enough signatures for the primary. As vice chairman of the House Republican Conference, Moore is the seventh-ranking Republican member and will have infinite money to run a campaign full of oleaginous political ads misrepresenting himself as a conservative.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In District 2, incumbent Republican Celeste Maloy was edged out by former Green Beret Colonel Colby Jenkins. Maloy was a congressional staffer who took over for her moderate Republican boss, former Rep. Chris Stewart, and has voted with leadership. Jenkins was endorsed by Senator Mike Lee, himself a product of convention success. Lee is one of the few people to successfully knock off a long-standing incumbent Republican from the right because in 2010 the convention was still decisive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And speaking of the open Senate race, Trent Staggs beat out Rep. John Curtis by a 2-1 margin at the convention for the nomination to replace Mitt Romney. Again, Staggs would never have had the ability to crush a sitting congressman in an open primary, although he does have a boost from Trump and his network. Ironically, &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/04/24/us/politics/mitt-romney-utah-senate.html#:~:text=On%20Saturday%2C%20after%20a%20raucous,at%20the%20foes%20of%20liberty.%E2%80%9D" target="_blank"&gt;Mitt Romney also lost the convention&lt;/a&gt; in 2018 to Mike Kennedy, a member of the legislature, but was able to advance to a popular primary, where his war chest and superior name ID won the day with low-information voters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's unclear whether these insurgent candidates can carry their momentum into the primaries, but the convention demonstrates that meaningful party change requires moving away from popular primaries.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The problem is that although most Republican voters have similar expectations for their candidates, they are often unaware of the specific records and associations of their particular Republican representatives. Every Republican, particularly in conservative districts, runs broadly on conservative talking points. The one with the most money and name ID espousing those talking points usually emerges as the winner, but more often he is a creature of the uniparty engaged in perfidious campaigning to disguise the truth. Money can buy you name ID in popular primaries, but it can’t buy you love from highly informed delegates and precinct captains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Popular primaries were an innovation of the Progressive Era over a century ago, and now we know why. They ensure that no matter who wins the general election, the progressive always comes out on top.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dem senator leads bipartisan effort to strengthen Taiwan supply chain amid China threat</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/dem-senator-leads-bipartisan-effort-strengthen-taiwan-supply-chain-china-threat</link><description>Sen. Jacky Rosen led a bipartisan group of senators to introduce a bill that would evaluate Taiwan's resilience and strengthen the island's supply chain security.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 09:00:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>China Is Buying US Food Supply Chain</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/china-is-buying-us-food-supply-chain/</link><description>(Activist Post)—Most Americans are not aware of the multiple threats China is posing in America now. China is waging a different kind of war as shown in Unrestricted Warfare: China’s Master Plan to Destroy America. Fortunately, a growing number of Americans are waking up and sounding the alarm! Kristi Noem is the Governor of South Dakota. She […]
The post China Is Buying US Food Supply Chain appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 10:17:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Want To Know How To Reduce Gun Crime? Look at Detroit</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/01/want_to_know_how_to_reduce_gun_crime_look_at_detroit_622806.html</link><description>Last year, Detroit saw its fewest homicides since 1966. Here's how it did it - and how other cities can do the same.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 04:10:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blaze News original: The surprising companies accused of helping sexual exploitation — and how to protect your children online</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/blaze-news-original-the-surprising-companies-accused-of-helping-sexual-exploitation-and-how-to-protect-your-children-online-2668129427.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/blaze-news-original-the-surprising-companies-accused-of-helping-sexual-exploitation-and-how-to-protect-your-children-online.jpg?id=52131081&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C65%2C0%2C108</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/blaze-news-original-the-surprising-companies-accused-of-helping-sexual-exploitation-and-how-to-protect-your-children-online.jpg?id=52131081&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C65%2C0%2C108" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/blaze-news-original-the-surprising-companies-accused-of-helping-sexual-exploitation-and-how-to-protect-your-children-online.jpg?id=52131079&amp;amp;width=1245&amp;amp;height=700&amp;amp;coordinates=0,12,0,29 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/blaze-news-original-the-surprising-companies-accused-of-helping-sexual-exploitation-and-how-to-protect-your-children-online.jpg%3Fid%3D52131079%26width%3D1245%26height%3D700%26coordinates%3D0%2C12%2C0%2C29%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;You might be surprised to learn which digital entities are accused of facilitating, enabling, and even profiting from sexual abuse and exploitation online.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last month, the National Center on Sexual Exploitation released &lt;a href="https://endsexualexploitation.org/dirty-dozen-list-2024/" target="_blank"&gt;its annual “Dirty Dozen” list&lt;/a&gt;, a campaign bringing attention to entities and companies it believes are complicit in sexual exploitation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This year’s list includes the following entities and the NCOSE's reasoning for including them:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://endsexualexploitation.org/apple/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Apple&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;: "This Big Tech titan refuses to scan for child sex abuse material, hosts dangerous apps with deceptive age ratings and descriptions, and won’t default safety features for teens."&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://endsexualexploitation.org/cash-app/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Cash App&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;: "This peer-to-peer payment app appeals to pimps, predators, and pedophiles looking for a covert way to conduct criminal activity."&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://endsexualexploitation.org/cda-230/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Section 230 of the Communications Decency Act&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;: "The Greatest Enabler of Online Sexual Exploitation. Misinterpretations of Communications Decency Act Section 230 grant Big Tech blanket immunity for any and all types of abuses they facilitate."&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://endsexualexploitation.org/cloudflare/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Cloudflare&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;: "Providing a platform for sex buyers and traffickers. Cloudflare says it wants to build a better internet. So why does it provide services to some of the most prolific prostitution forums and deepfake sites?"&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://endsexualexploitation.org/discord/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Discord&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;: "This platform is popular with predators seeking to groom kids and with creeps looking to create, trade, or find sexually abusive content of children and unsuspecting adults."&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://endsexualexploitation.org/linkedin/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;: "LinkedIn legitimizes Pornhub and other exploitative enterprises by giving them a platform, overlooks deepfake tool promotion, and is rampant with sexual harassment against women."&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://endsexualexploitation.org/meta/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Meta&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;: "Meta’s launch of end-to-end encryption, open-sourced AI, and virtual reality are unleashing new worlds of exploitation."&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://endsexualexploitation.org/github/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Github&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;: "The vast majority of deepfakes, 'nudify' apps, and AI-generated child sex abuse content originate on this platform owned by the world’s richest company."&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://endsexualexploitation.org/reddit/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Reddit&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;: "Child sex abuse material, sex trafficking, and image-based sexual abuse hide in plain sight among endless pornography subreddits allowed on this platform."&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://endsexualexploitation.org/roblox/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Roblox&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;: "Roblox treats child protection like a game. Among the avatars, blocks, and buildings, kids are exposed to predators, rape-themed games, and age-inappropriate content like sex parties."&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://endsexualexploitation.org/spotify/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Spotify&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;: "Sexually explicit images, sadistic content, and networks trading child sex abuse material on its platform prove Spotify is out of tune with basic child safety measures and moderation practices."&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://endsexualexploitation.org/telegram/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Telegram&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;: "Messaging app Telegram serves as a safe haven for criminal communities across the globe. Sexual torture rings, sextortion gangs, deepfake bots, and more all thrive on an alarming scale."&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;What is immediately obvious about the list is that children and teenagers use these applications and programs every day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Children are, therefore, being exposed to the dangers of sexual exploitation through these entities, according to the NCOSE, an alarming phenomenon that validates the thesis of psychologist Jonathan Haidt’s newest book, “The Anxious Generation.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His central idea &lt;a href="https://www.afterbabel.com/p/anxious-generation-pre-order" target="_blank"&gt;goes like this&lt;/a&gt;: “We have overprotected children in the real world and underprotected them in the virtual world.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That our children face an onslaught of digital dangers in an increasingly technological world raises an important question: How can parents protect their children in our digital world?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you asked Haidt for his prescription to the problem, he would counsel you not to buy your children a smartphone until they begin high school. And social media? Don’t let them use it before age 16 — at the earliest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Others believe the dangers that screens and social media pose are too great for any child because, after all, a person's brain won't complete its development until one's mid-20s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But experts who spoke with Blaze News made it clear: This is not an issue parents can ignore because the well-being of your family and the lives of your children are at stake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We have a distorted view of the creepy guy in the van picking up our kids on the way to the playground or the fear of a child climbing too high on the tree," Lina Nealon, vice president and director of corporate advocacy at NCOSE, told Blaze News.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"But then we give them this very dangerous device with very little oversight or even understanding of the dangers that are literally in the palm of their hands," she warned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Blaze News reached out to each of the companies listed above. None provided a response to NCOSE's allegations.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The problem is vast&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mental health challenges like anxiety, depression, bullying, suicidal ideations, addictions, and exploitation — those are just some of the problems with the digital world. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the unique challenge with the digital world is that social media and digital technologies are designed to hook users by hijacking their brain chemistry to keep them scrolling without understanding the consequences of such behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"They are dangerous by their very design because their profit is made by facilitating those connections and making people stay online," Nealon said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This online world is not only dangerous for you, according to Nealon, but your children are particularly vulnerable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"First of all, there are very little limitations and protections for children online from being accessed by adults in general — adult strangers and certainly predatory adults," she explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Teenagers, they are built to seek connection and meet. They want to meet new people. They want to know where they fit into the world. And so these companies — Instagram and Snapchat and TikTok — create this environment where it is very easy," she said. "It's not only easy for predators to access kids, but they're creating the very environment that makes kids more susceptible to sexual abuse and exploitation."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Through connection, likes, and shares, social media companies tap into the vulnerabilities of children, Nealon explained — and make them even more vulnerable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"These platforms are actually reducing the self-esteem and self-worth of these children, and then they are allowing predators and adults to access them to see what they're doing, to see those vulnerabilities, to actually interact with them," she said. "So, from that perspective, it's very dangerous."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What is most alarming, Nealon told Blaze News, is that social media and digital companies do not have an incentive to protect your children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's their very business model to put these kids at risk," she said. "I would say that they themselves are predators in a sense because they are preying on our children and their vulnerabilities for profit."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How to protect your family&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thankfully, all is not lost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can protect your family and children from the harms of the digital world — but it requires intentionality and sacrifice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;1. Educate yourself and your children&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Melanie Hempe, &lt;a href="https://screenstrong.org/" target="_blank"&gt;founder of ScreenStrong&lt;/a&gt;, said the most important step to protect your family from the dangers of the digital world is to educate yourself and your family.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Get educated and understand how kids are different from adults," Hempe told Blaze News. "The way an adult uses a screen is very different from the way a child uses a screen. We tend to think our kids are just little adults — and that's not true. They don't have impulse control. They're high-risk takers, and they're going to be searching for novelty even more than we are."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sheer power of digital technology is exactly why parents need to be educated, Hempe explained, so that they "know how to harness the power."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm telling you: You pay now or you pay later, but someone will pay. And most of the time, our kids are the ones paying," she warned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nealon delivered a similar warning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Be educated and keep up with the trends and what's happening," she said. "There's so much research out there ... and I think the less digital, the healthier your kids will be."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;2. Cultivate a community of shared values&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Engaging in conversations with other adults where your children are — such as school, church, and friends' houses — is critical to protect them from the harms of the digital world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Having conversations with adults where your children are going to be — at school, at church, in activities and youth groups — we are constantly shocked at how even leadership, people who are supposed to be caring for children, don't understand even some of the basic risks of the technology they may be using and actually encouraging kids to use," Nealon told Blaze News.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's critical to have those conversations when your child is going elsewhere because you can have all of the safety features at home. You can have the conversations, you can be very vigilant," she explained. "But, of course, they're out there in the world, and you hope that your children will make the right decisions — but they're also children."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"So, we need to make sure that the other adults that we put in their care are also paying attention and know and can also be sure that they're doing what they can to minimize the risks to the kids," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hempe agreed that cultivating community is necessary when seeking the proper relationship with screens and the digital world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's hard to be alone and doing this on your own, especially when you have kids — they want to play with other kids who are not on Fortnite all day," she said. "You want your kids to be around other kids who have the same values and that are shooting for the high bar like you are."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;3. Internet filters&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you choose to let your children use digital technology, consider installing software on devices that filter what they will be able to see and access.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Make use of technology that's out there to protect your kids online," Nealon advised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Companies like &lt;a href="https://www.bark.us/" target="_blank"&gt;Bark&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://canopy.us/" target="_blank"&gt;Canopy&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.covenanteyes.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Covenant Eyes&lt;/a&gt; have built solutions for parents looking for filtering software. The benefit of these technologies is that you can limit what your children can access (i.e., harmful content) while still allowing them to use the internet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;4. Be a coach&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;When it comes to technology and your family, Hempe said parents need to be a coach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"They need us to be like a coach," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"My daughter was in gymnastics for years, and I learned so much about coaching," she explained. "I learned the coach has to be present when a child is doing something that's kind of dangerous. The coach has to be there. The coach can't be in the other room. And she learned that, 'Hey, I need my coach right here to spot me.' That's how it is with screens: We have to be there to spot our kids."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hempe said it's not about being "controlling" or "legalistic." But she warned that giving children unfettered access to technology not only exposes them to the harms of the digital world — like screen addictions and sexual exploitation — but it's like letting your children drive a Mack truck on the interstate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"They're not going to be safe on the highway when they're 10 years old driving the Mack truck," she explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Tools, not toys&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The truth is that technology is not going anywhere. In less than 20 years' time, we've gone from the iPhone to AI, and Gen Z cannot fathom a life without social media or the digital world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is up to parents, then, to take serious the relationship their family will have to technology. Exploitation, digital addictions, and attachment dysfunctions are just some of the ramifications that parents are now facing because of technology, screens, and social media.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When discerning how to move forward with technology, remember this one principle from Hempe: Screens are a "tool — not a toy."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you can remember that, Hempe promised you will figure out how to raise children in a digital world, all while protecting your family from the built-in harms of the technology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden admin ripped by experts as antisemitism gets 'worse' over past 6 months: 'Should have seen it coming'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/biden-admin-ripped-by-experts-as-antisemitism-gets-worse-over-past-6-months-should-have-seen-it-coming</link><description>The Biden administration is facing criticism for the way it has handled antisemitism over the past 6 months as anti-Israel protests have swept across colleges nationwide.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 09:00:29 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>