<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 09:25:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Chaos Erupts When Tennessee Passes Bill to Protect Students With Armed Teachers</title><link>https://www.redvoicemedia.com/2024/04/chaos-erupts-when-tennessee-passes-bill-to-protect-students-with-armed-teachers-videos/</link><description>The post Chaos Erupts When Tennessee Passes Bill to Protect Students With Armed Teachers appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 13:34:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Heavily Outspent in Swing States</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2024/04/23/realclearpolitics_biden_talks_abortion_in_florida_biden_campaign_outspends_trump_papua_new_guinea_reacts_to_the_legend_of_uncle_bosie.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:00:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FACT CHECK: No, Ali Khamenei Did Not Appear On Forbes Cover</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/fact-check-no-ali-khamenei-did-not-appear-on-forbes-cover-2667867393.html</link><image_url>https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/GettyImages-80855707-scaled-e1611328453385.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/GettyImages-80855707-scaled-e1611328453385.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An image shared on Facebook claims Iran’s Supreme Ayatollah Ali Khamenei appeared on Forbes cover. Verdict: False There is no evidence that Khamenei appeared on the cover of Forbes. Fact Check: Israel struck Iran on April 19, though refrained from a larger attack in order to avoid a larger scale war between the two nations, according to […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:20:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump rising in pivotal state as key Dem constituency sours on Biden</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-rising-pivotal-state-key-dem-constituency-sours-biden</link><description>Many members of the Dearborn, Michigan, community told Fox News Digital they are so dissatisfied with President Biden that may support former President Trump in November.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 13:30:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ron Paul Reveals the Final Nail in America’s Coffin [VIDEO]</title><link>https://rumble.com/v4r9mro-ron-paul-reveals-the-final-nail-in-americas-coffin.html</link><description>The post Ron Paul Reveals the Final Nail in America’s Coffin [VIDEO] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 12:36:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bob Kraft a Good Fit for Elizabeth Warren's Seat</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/24/bob_kraft_a_good_fit_for_elizabeth_warrens_seat_622416.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 12:42:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A-list olds boost Biden; Netflix toasts journo we'd 'Rather' forget</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/a-list-olds-boost-biden-netflix-toasts-journo-we-d-rather-forget-2667867150.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52080089&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C164</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52080089&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C164" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52080089&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0,0,0,164 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg%3Fid%3D52080089%26width%3D1200%26height%3D600%26coordinates%3D0%2C0%2C0%2C164%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;CBS’ Dan Rather &lt;a href="https://www.mentalfloss.com/article/570208/dan-rather-courage-controversy" target="_blank"&gt;ended his nightly telecasts&lt;/a&gt; in the mid 2000s with the word “courage.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An online news site just &lt;a href="https://www.thewrap.com/paste-taylor-swift-tortured-poets-department-review-author-fans/" target="_blank"&gt;posted a negative Taylor Swift review&lt;/a&gt; without a byline, fearing the Swifties’ wrath.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We’ve come a long way, baby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not only do today’s journalists cover for President Joe Biden’s mental decline, they can’t even stand up to pre-teens on social media.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then again, the CBS anchor is back in the news despite the endless shadow &lt;a href="https://www.powerlineblog.com/archives/2009/08/024384.php" target="_blank"&gt;RatherGate cast on his career&lt;/a&gt;. Netflix will debut “Rather” May 1, by all accounts a fawning documentary covering his days in journalism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s like tackling the life of O.J. Simpson and downplaying the whole "murder trial" thing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s not even the first time Hollywood pretended Rather didn’t attempt to rig the 2004 presidential election. Remember “Truth?” The 2015 film cast Robert Redford as Rather, suggesting he had the Texas National Guard story dead to rights all along.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Working title: “Fake but Accurate: The Movie!”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then again, maybe you don’t remember it. “Truth” made a microscopic $2 million at the U.S. box office.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;SNL pulls its punches ... again&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Saturday Night Live” has nothing to say about the anti-Israel protests raging across college campuses. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The closest the once-mighty show got to the topic was mocking the three Ivy League presidents’ D.C. testimony, but &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ep-OnsDieFQ&amp;amp;t=137s" target="_blank"&gt;that sketch&lt;/a&gt; targeted the GOP’s Elise Stefanik more harshly than the morally warped trio.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SNL still may have predicted today’s campus chaos ... nine years ago. The &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_L2fazw5Y9k" target="_blank"&gt;older sketch&lt;/a&gt; has Dakota Johnson playing a young woman getting dropped off to college for the first time by her teary-eyed dad (Taran Killam):&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They exchange pleasantries and, after she leaves the car, an ISIS truck swings by and picks her up. The ISIS soldiers fire off their weapons and say, “Death to America!”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sound familiar?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Too bad we need the Wayback Machine for SNL to speak truth to power ...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Maher speaks truth to power ... for now&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bill Maher has been swatting woke crazies on his HBO showcase for the last few years. Nothing new there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last week, Maher took it a step farther. A Neil Armstrong-sized step. He:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;praised Gov. Ron DeSantis for calling out Disney’s grooming practices,&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;attacked his fellow liberals for ignoring the latter point,&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;decried Drag Queen Story Hour in no uncertain terms, and&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;slammed Disney for its “not-so-secret gay agenda.”&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Did Rush Limbaugh come back to life in Maher’s body? Is the comedian gunning for Trump’s VP slot?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No. He just can’t stand to see the modern left devolve into a cult-like party.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conservatives aren’t locking arms around their new best chum. Some say Maher’s rhetoric is a pose, a feint to draw a few right-leaning fans. Others argue he’ll still vote for President Biden over Donald Trump.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Either way, no one in mainstream pop culture is saying what Maher is, and he’s reaching an audience that may, sadly, tune out a Limbaugh successor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, yeah, Maher matters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Hollywood gets box office bellyache&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;The box office is making studio executives as nervous as Morgan Wallen’s PR team. The numbers are way down this month, and upcoming titles like “The Latest Planet of the Apes Movie No One Asked For” won’t help.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then there’s this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Spider-Man 2” released in 2004, hit theaters anew this year and became the &lt;a href="https://www.worldofreel.com/blog/2024/4/23/sam-raimis-spider-man-2-was-2-at-the-domestic-box-office-yesterday-with-805k" target="_blank"&gt;number 2 movie at the box office April 22&lt;/a&gt;, beaten only by “Civil War.” It gets worse. The Spidey sequel was shown in fewer than 500 theaters, while most new releases get 2,000-4,000 screens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People would rather watch an old movie they’ve already seen than spanking new flicks like “Abigail,” “Money Man” or “The Ministry of Ungentlemanly Warfare.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Better buy Tums in bulk, Tinseltown.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;Mark Hamill goes full Jedi mind-trick &lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Star Wars” alum Mark Hamill declared on X that &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/MarkHamill/status/1782499294731485478?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1782499294731485478%7Ctwgr%5Eafb5625812ba4a09a3327085632a33cdcc33dd6a%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.breitbart.com%2Fentertainment%2F2024%2F04%2F23%2Fmark-hamill-joe-biden-the-best-president-weve-ever-had%2F" target="_blank"&gt;Joe Biden is the best American president. Ever&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s hoping his intervention goes as planned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The same holds for Michael Douglas. The Oscar-winning actor, when pressed on the fact that our president (81) is roughly his own age (79), responded by saying Biden is “sharp as a tack.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thoughts and prayers for our elderly A-listers.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mississippi Senate and House haggle over Medicaid expansion as session nears end</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/mississippi-senate-house-haggle-medicaid-expansion-session-nears-end</link><description>The Mississippi House proposed expanding Medicaid coverage to people who earn up to 138% of the federal poverty level, while the Senate advocated for a slower approach.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 12:18:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Analysts Continue Seeing $3,000 Gold Ahead . . . With a Twist</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/analysts-continue-seeing-3000-gold-ahead-twist/</link><description>Note: The information provided by The Liberty Daily or any related communications is for informational purposes only and should not be considered as financial advice. We do not provide personalized investment, financial, or legal advice. The Liberty Daily benefits from purchases made through our sponsors. Financial analysts and economists have been predicting gold prices continuing […]
The post Analysts Continue Seeing $3,000 Gold Ahead . . . With a Twist appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 12:35:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>School Chaplains Law Crosses a Sacred Line</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/24/school_chaplains_law_crosses_a_sacred_line_622415.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 12:39:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From quiet caucus member to House speaker: The Mike Johnson story</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/from-quiet-caucus-member-to-house-speaker-the-mike-johnson-story-2667867134.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/from-quiet-caucus-member-to-house-speaker-the-mike-johnson-story.jpg?id=52080186&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C171</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/from-quiet-caucus-member-to-house-speaker-the-mike-johnson-story.jpg?id=52080186&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C171" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/from-quiet-caucus-member-to-house-speaker-the-mike-johnson-story.jpg?id=52080186&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0,0,0,171 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/from-quiet-caucus-member-to-house-speaker-the-mike-johnson-story.jpg%3Fid%3D52080186%26width%3D1200%26height%3D600%26coordinates%3D0%2C0%2C0%2C171%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Meet the Double Agent Who Now Controls House Conservatives,” the headline reads.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The spy’s mission was simple,” the story begins. “Gain their trust, become one of them, and eventually take them over.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The article claims to describe “the perfect mole” — a “clean-cut” politician “hungry for power and influence.” The subject: Republican Rep. Mike Johnson of Louisiana. The twist: It was written in November 2018 — five years before Johnson rose to become the unlikely speaker of a deeply divided Republican House.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It turns out that the ambitious Louisianan’s careful presentation could conceal more than one play at a time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Published in the left-wing Daily Beast, the story's reporter used interviews with multiple Republican colleagues &lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/meet-the-double-agent-who-now-controls-house-conservatives" target="_blank"&gt;to paint Johnson&lt;/a&gt; as an ambitious politician who downplayed his relationship with the conservative House Freedom Caucus in order to gain the acceptance, and the eventual chairmanship, of the powerful Republican Study Committee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“For two years,” Andrew Desiderio wrote, “he was groomed and positioned, never denouncing but never formally affiliating with the Freedom Caucus and all the while getting closer and closer to his goal of total control over conservative Republicans in the House. And it worked.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of course, it’s easy to see the story in a different light now that Johnson has climbed the ladder to the top of his conference and used his authority &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/columns/opinion/mike-johnson-betrays-border-security-for-more-foreign-aid" target="_self"&gt;to cut deals with Democrats&lt;/a&gt;, most recently selling out border security to send more than $60 billion to Ukraine over the objections of a majority of his own party.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It turns out that the ambitious Louisianan’s careful presentation could conceal more than one play at a time. Today, Johnson is effectively the &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/columns/opinion/welcome-to-the-united-states-house-of-parliament" target="_self"&gt;head of a center-left coalition government&lt;/a&gt;, having passed every important spending bill of his tenure with Democrats’ support, and even relying on Democrats to protect him from being ousted from the speakership by the GOP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s always more difficult to discern motives than it might seem, and much of what happens in Washington, D.C., is significantly closer to an episode of “Veep” than an episode of “House of Cards.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There wasn’t some grand strategy here,” one current Freedom Caucus member told me, waving away theories that Johnson had kept a friendly distance from the caucus to protect his potential path to leadership. “He’s contended, and others have, that it was strategic, but that’s revisionist history.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Johnson’s socially conservative credentials were solid before he took the speakership. He has the right friends, including his fellow Louisianan Tony Perkins, president of the Family Research Council, and he once took a lot of the right stances — but could be counted on to vote with leadership when pressure mounted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Republican leadership demanded a yes vote on the National Defense Authorization Act that signed women up for the draft, for example, Johnson, then a member of the powerful House Armed Services Committee, voted yes. When leadership asked members to bust budget caps for Biden’s 2023 budget, he voted yes. When leadership wanted to pass a farm bill with all the handouts it entailed, he was a yes. The list goes on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I think he’s mobilized by a belief that to some degree he’s called by God to be there to lead,” the Freedom Caucus member, who asked not to be named to speak freely, explained. “To do the things that he believes he needs to do, like fund Ukraine, like cut deals to get bills funded, and yes, move up and use those conservative credentials to effectively have the conservative movement be behind him and to try to leverage that. But meanwhile, we’re doing whatever the defense world wants us to do: Reauthorize FISA, bust caps, fund foreign aid.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The speaker,” the congressman continued, “is who he is. This is someone who’s been upfront that he wanted to get funding to Ukraine, he was upfront about not wanting to have a shutdown. At the end of the day, he’s going to value and prize those types of things ... at the expense of the difficult kind of leadership that it takes in Washington.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“How does it feel to be a RINO?” one member of the Republican Main Street Caucus &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/2024/04/21/ukraine-aid-mike-johnson-house-speaker/" target="_blank"&gt;reportedly joked&lt;/a&gt; to Johnson when the speaker met with the more liberal group of lawmakers April 17. He was working at the time to gain Republican allies for his $95 billion foreign aid package. Johnson, the Washington Post reported, responded with “a simultaneous shrug, awkward chuckle, and a gentle pump of his fist.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The speaker is “someone who can forgive himself for lying because he thinks it’s for a higher purpose,” a senior conservative staffer who worked closely with Johnson in 2018 explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“He has an exceptional capacity for self-justification.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Five years ago, it seems, Mike Johnson’s colleagues understood the kind of man they were dealing with. Neither side realized where those attributes would take him.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 13:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>George Santos ends congressional run less than 2 months into independent campaign</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/george-santos-ends-congressional-run-less-than-2-months-independent-campaign</link><description>Former congressman George Santos announced Tuesday he is suspending his independent commission against Republican Rep. Nick LaLota for New York's 1st congressional distict.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 12:06:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HIV mRNA “Vaccines” Continue to Fail in Clinical Trials</title><link>https://discernreport.com/hiv-mrna-vaccines-continue-to-fail-in-clinical-trials/</link><description>The post HIV mRNA “Vaccines” Continue to Fail in Clinical Trials appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 12:03:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Slavery Reparations in California?</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/24/slavery_reparations_in_california_622391.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 12:37:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wednesday Western: 'Sunset in the West' (1950)</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/wednesday-western-sunset-in-the-west-1950-2667866889.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/wednesday-western-sunset-in-the-west-1950.jpg?id=52079834&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C20%2C0%2C218</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/wednesday-western-sunset-in-the-west-1950.jpg?id=52079834&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C20%2C0%2C218" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/wednesday-western-sunset-in-the-west-1950.jpg?id=52079834&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0,20,0,218 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/wednesday-western-sunset-in-the-west-1950.jpg%3Fid%3D52079834%26width%3D1200%26height%3D600%26coordinates%3D0%2C20%2C0%2C218%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today, I'd like to focus on an important staple of the genre: the mediocre Western. These are often my favorites. They’re not John Ford or Sergio Leone, but sometimes that’s a relief.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I mean, just listen to this:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;        Sunset In The West - Roy Rogers (1950)                        &lt;a href="https://youtu.be/hb7FRvUQsMI?si=sBi_JSzUwT_OR2ie" target="_blank"&gt;youtu.be&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sometimes, you want to put your feet up and take a load off. That's when you turn to Roy Rogers, the original Rhinestone Cowboy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I love this movie. Adore it. When I’m having a bad day, it’s either Roy Rogers or John Wayne and Robert Mitchum in "El Dorado."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There’s a plot. I’m &lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;sure&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt; there is. But it doesn’t make a whole lot of sense. Almost like the script was written by AI. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But it doesn't matter. Show me some gun fights, some horse chases, some ups and downs. Tell me how to feel with the music and the characters’ reactions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And some humor, like the hiccuping barber who shaves the guy’s wig. Haha. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The spontaneous musical scenes are fantastic. So perfectly unnatural. Very dated. And thank God for that, to have a perfect timestamp on a supposedly insignificant moment in the grand scheme of things. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I love it when Westerns spontaneously burst into lynching scenes, when townspeople spontaneously form into a murderous group of persecutors. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But, come on, this is "Sunset in the West." The good guy is going to win. And he'll do it in style on his “we fit like a glove” palomino, Trigger. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We watch these kinds of Westerns because sometimes it just doesn’t feel right to see the innocents die. Sometimes you can’t stomach the &lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;hint&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt; of a thought of a lovely little child losing candy, let alone winding up in the scummy depths of a well (as in Budd Boetticher's &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=V_nJEMSKXjM" target="_blank"&gt;"The Tall T"&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This isn’t a lazy entry, per se. But, in many ways, it ought to be. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What does the title "Sunset in the West" have to do with what happens in the movie? There’s never so much as an attempt at the sort of high-brow philosophical wordplay you find in more venerable Westerns. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then again, we don’t watch Westerns for lessons on Plato and Hegel. We migrate to them instinctively, because real life is full of bad days, treacherous days, and it’s nice to have a friendly face on the TV, a warm singing voice to let us know that light really does triumph over darkness. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Roy Rogers has not one but &lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;four&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt; different stars on the Hollywood Walk of Fame. Well deserved, I say. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Sunset in the West" features Roy Rogers and his beautiful horse, Trigger, as well as the country Western band Riders of the Purple Sage. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the time, a review in the theater owners trade magazine BoxOffice noted:&lt;a href="http://www2.boxoffice.com/the_vault/issue_page?issue_id=1950-9-30&amp;amp;page_no=115#page_start" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Patrons may have occasion to wonder just what relation the title has to the subject matter — the answer is, none at all — but otherwise the picture ranks with the best Rogers has made in recent months.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The best picture he’s made in recent months. Not years. Not decades. &lt;em&gt;Months&lt;/em&gt;. That’s how many Westerns Roy Rogers was starring in — that year alone, 1950, he was in six. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A tidy little film. It’s deeply formulaic. But I happen to be a fan of the formula. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Westerns evince disorder. Social violence, widespread and extreme. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I mean the slapstick barroom brawl scene, which goes on way too long and features at least one beanbag prop of a human performing impractical tricks. The best part is the total lack of concern from the producers and cinematographers and special effects experts. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They did not care. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But, plenty of positives, also. The chase scene is great cinema. Lots of action. Pure action, really. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Directed by William Whitney — I’m sure that’s important. Or it isn’t. Which is nice, because not every Western has to be a masterpiece in order to be a treasure. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of my favorite things about Westerns is the blend of garish stage sets and intoxicating wilderness. But the switch between them is often sloppy. Oh, man, I love it when it is. The jolt in perspective actually draws me closer to the characters. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Sunset in the West" is not "Stagecoach" or "The Searchers." This is a film, a Western, designed to satisfy people who just want a good story, pinned to a familiar face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oh man, and that fight scene. Watch “Sunset in the West” simply for that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The response of the townsfolk to the sheriff is oddly civilized compared to many Westerns. Or, at least it starts that way. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those scene-fade transitions are lovely. In general, the whole thing feels rushed, but somehow that makes it more enjoyable — the cut corners give this film a feisty charm. Sometimes, it’s nice to see a bit of bad slapstick, dogs that steal sausages from food carts run by sleepy Mexicans. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some psychopath hurts the dog. But don't worry — this isn't "Hondo." He lives to pilfer sausages another day. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The B Westerns have so many lovely characteristics. Their charm, for one. The accents. Either they’re perfect or they’re awful. Either the actors are real-deal country folk, with a few good actors in there; or bad actors stuck in the B-circuit, desperate enough to alienate everyone. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, though, you watch this movie for one reason: Roy Rogers. Like John Wayne or Randolph Scott or Robert Mitchum or Jimmy Stewart or Barbara Stanwyck, I‘ll watch any movie with Roy Rogers in it. And, whether or not it’s good, I’ll probably keep it on repeat. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There’s something deeply relaxing about Roy Rogers. His presence. Wholesome, calming. A good ol' boy who lives to protect the innocent and chase down the bad guys.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then, there’s the unlikely cure for hiccups, a scene that exemplifies everything I’m touting here: somewhat bad acting, overly staged, a little rushed, but incredibly valuable in its laziness and imperfections. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To tell you the truth, the first time I watched "Sunset in the West," I stopped paying attention about halfway through. Still, it was lovely to have on in the background.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since then, I’ve probably put it on several more times. It's that kind of movie. And sometimes, that's just the kind of movie you need. &lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 13:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pelosi calls on Netanyahu to resign, condemns him as 'obstacle' to peace</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/pelosi-calls-netanyahu-resign-condemns-him-obstacle-peace</link><description>Rep. Nancy Pelosi laid into Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu this week, condemning his campaign in Gaza and calling on him to resign.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 11:56:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ex-Cop Accused of Child Rape Goes on Murderous Rampage Before Kidnapping Child, Then Shooting Himself in the Head [VIDEO]</title><link>https://rumble.com/v4r9bj9-ex-cop-accused-of-child-rape-goes-on-rampage-before-shooting-himself-in-the.html</link><description>The post Ex-Cop Accused of Child Rape Goes on Murderous Rampage Before Kidnapping Child, Then Shooting Himself in the Head [VIDEO] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 11:42:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Rot In U.S. Academia Extends To Most of Every Faculty</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/24/the_rot_in_us_academia_extends_to_most_of_every_faculty_622398.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 12:37:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Will the true America stand up for the semiquincentennial?</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/will-the-true-america-stand-up-for-the-semiquincentennial-2667866810.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/will-the-true-america-stand-up-for-the-semiquincentennial.jpg?id=52076831&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C354</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/will-the-true-america-stand-up-for-the-semiquincentennial.jpg?id=52076831&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C354" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/will-the-true-america-stand-up-for-the-semiquincentennial.jpg?id=52076831&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;coordinates=0,0,0,0 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/will-the-true-america-stand-up-for-the-semiquincentennial.jpg%3Fid%3D52076831%26width%3D1200%26height%3D800%26coordinates%3D0%2C0%2C0%2C0%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recently, I came across an interesting online exchange. A Facebook poster expressed puzzlement over the apparent lack of interest in America’s coming semiquincentennial in 2026. In response, a commenter wrote simply, “Waiting to see if we make it that far…”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;img class="rm-shortcode" id="668d6" src="https://www.conservativereview.com/media-library/eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpbWFnZSI6Imh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnRoZWJsYXplLmNvbS9tZWRpYS1saWJyYXJ5L2ltYWdlLmpwZz9pZD01MjA3Mzk0OCZhbXA7d2lkdGg9OTgwIiwiZXhwaXJlc19hdCI6MTc1NDU1MTg3MX0.ryY-9VfkXfA8WdD9vlebF-LTZBFoUo2vjBAV24VEbAY/image.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The silence is odd, the poster argued, because the lead-up to &lt;a href="https://www.fordlibrarymuseum.gov/library/exhibits/bicentennial/bicentennial.asp" target="_blank"&gt;America’s Bicentennial in 1976&lt;/a&gt; generated endless hype and public interest, and not just for history buffs. The hoopla surrounding both the 1976 Bicentennial and the 1987 &lt;a href="https://chroniclesmagazine.org/web/what-the-founders-didnt-count-on/" target="_blank"&gt;Bicentennial of the U.S. Constitution&lt;/a&gt; was so intense that both events inspired in me an intense interest and curiosity about American history.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet it hadn’t even occurred to me until seeing that post that America’s 250th birthday is just around the corner. Naturally, my first question was, “Why am I and, apparently, most Americans feeling this lack of enthusiasm?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maybe the commenter is right. Americans may be uninterested in celebrating this coming milestone because they are on edge about whether “we make it that far.” Or perhaps, Americans are uninterested because they don’t want to take part in the hypocrisy of celebrating the “birthday” of an already dead regime.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By calling America “an already dead regime,” of course, I don’t mean that the country called the United States of America no longer exists. I mean that its soul has been drained out, even as the body politic lives on. Celebrating America as it is now and pretending that it is, in any real or meaningful sense, the heir to the work of the founders is more than a stretch. In what sense may we say that the United States of America, in its current form, is connected to the regime born out of the American Revolution?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Celebrating the occasion of America’s birth as if it had not already slipped away and become something else is to take part in a lie.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;America may still wear the parchment-colored vestments of our founding, but it doesn’t adhere to the same political creed or even worship at the same altar as its founders. Some forms of the old Constitution may still apply — we still recognize only three branches of government, for example. But the truth is that our real government is composed of thousands of nameless, faceless, unelected career bureaucrats advancing an ever-leftward press for more control of the citizens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yes, we still have a bicameral legislature composed of members of the House of Representatives and the Senate, but we have given up on expecting it to be held accountable for the legislation it passes. Instead, lawmakers pass the buck to a vast administrative state that requires not only our money but our ongoing servitude. That governing apparatus does the bidding of the expert and donor classes, and we are supposed to be grateful to them for their wisdom and for “keeping up with the times.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We still elect (or, perhaps, we think we elect) a president who is said to oversee this bureaucracy — this so-called executive branch of government. But today it is unclear whether the bureaucracy answers to the president or if he must answer to them. And, of course, we still have what people are pleased to call an independent judiciary. But this “independence” &lt;a href="https://chroniclesmagazine.org/web/angels-to-govern-us/" target="_blank"&gt;now appears to be independence from the Constitution itself&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The forms of the original Constitution, therefore, no longer hold much power over the moral imaginations of citizens or our elected politicians. And we think nothing of changing our understanding of those forms if the “times” or the power of a political faction demand it. In short, the Constitution is not, in any way, sacred to us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In government schools, our children are taught that our founding was the work of racist, sexist, slaveholding bigots who only wanted to protect their economic interests, kill Indians, and probably didn’t even ask people what their preferred pronouns were. Are we surprised, then, that young people don’t want to celebrate that?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The gloss on the pious left’s narrative is that America is to be celebrated because of what it is becoming — the evolving utopia where history’s injustices will finally be avenged and the people will be ruled in accordance with the left’s own expertise and wisdom. This dreamy potential is the American story for them — and those who cannot be excited by it are the kind of retrograde deplorables Joe Biden decried in his recent State of the Union address. In other words, the kind of people the left think have it coming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So if Americans are hesitant to celebrate the coming 250th anniversary of our Declaration of Independence and founding as a nation, it would be hard to blame them. What, exactly, would they be celebrating: a previous regime they have been taught to believe was evil or a coming regime that they can readily see is evil?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For those like me who look back upon America’s founding and see in it principles that were worthy of defending because they were worthy of free and self-governing men, there is little to do but mourn its passing. We can and should remember that regime. We may even be hopeful of a potential resurrection. But we cannot rightly call this doppelganger going by the name “United States of America” the same regime as the regime of our founders. Celebrating the occasion of America’s birth as if it had not already slipped away and become something else is to take part in a lie.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Editor’s note:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt; A version of this article appeared originally at &lt;a href="https://chroniclesmagazine.org/editorials/an-america-worth-celebrating" target="_blank"&gt;Chronicles&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 13:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SCOTUS to hear arguments in Biden’s lawsuit 'subverting states' rights' on abortion</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/scotus-hear-arguments-bidens-lawsuit-subverting-states-rights-abortion</link><description>The Supreme Court will consider another abortion case dealing with claims by a Republican-led state that the Biden administration is attempting to use a federal law as an "abortion mandate."</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 11:00:15 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>