<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 07:52:22 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Trump May Seek Sanctions, to Dismiss Charges After Jack Smith Admits to Lying</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/trump-may-seek-sanctions-dismiss-charges-after-jack/</link><description>(The Epoch Times)—Attorneys for former President Donald Trump are seeking to push deadlines and file additional motions, including a possible request for sanctions, in the classified documents case prosecuted by special counsel Jack Smith after revelations that the order of files in the physical boxes of documents do not match the digital scans. U.S. District […]
The post Trump May Seek Sanctions, to Dismiss Charges After Jack Smith Admits to Lying appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 07:48:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>&amp;lsquo;Knuckleheads, Ego-Trippers and Extremists'</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2024/05/07/knuckleheads_ego-trippers_and_extremists_150900.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 12:50:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NPR sent an ACORN alum to write a hit piece on us</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/npr-sent-an-acorn-alum-to-write-a-hit-piece-on-us-2668184851.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/npr-sent-an-acorn-alum-to-write-a-hit-piece-on-us.jpg?id=52181540&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C272%2C0%2C82</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/npr-sent-an-acorn-alum-to-write-a-hit-piece-on-us.jpg?id=52181540&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C272%2C0%2C82" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img class="rm-shortcode" id="2c063" src="https://www.conservativereview.com/media-library/eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpbWFnZSI6Imh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnRoZWJsYXplLmNvbS9tZWRpYS1saWJyYXJ5L25wci1zZW50LWFuLWFjb3JuLWFsdW0tdG8td3JpdGUtYS1oaXQtcGllY2Utb24tdXMuanBnP2lkPTUyMTgxNTQwJmFtcDt3aWR0aD05ODAiLCJleHBpcmVzX2F0IjoxNzY2Nzc1NDExfQ.5CtjiIJvBIRdNMh7H7sGcWsV0oTkMWwHUcEbGB2LTpE/image.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;We sat down for an interview on May 2 with one of NPR’s most recent hires, Jude Joffe-Block. The purpose of the conversation was to discuss our &lt;a href="https://x.com/OversightPR/status/1780054306454167954" target="_blank"&gt;bombshell story&lt;/a&gt;, which exposed flyers encouraging illegal aliens to vote for Joe Biden at an invasion staging camp in Mexico. The meeting was only conducted after a written agreement that it would be recorded. NPR now refuses to share the interview recording. Here’s why. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Joffe-Block attempted to question the authenticity of the flyer using the same extreme talking points already employed by the &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2024/04/30/us/politics/immigration-disinformation-campaign-biden-trump.html" target="_blank"&gt;New York Times&lt;/a&gt;, pushing the regime media agenda and gaslighting the public by acting like the invasion at the U.S.-Mexico border is not a threat. We easily debunked these points by pointing to &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/OversightPR/status/1783556912035852653" target="_blank"&gt;additional evidence&lt;/a&gt; we had on the matter, including a sworn statement under the penalty of perjury.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How could someone who worked for an organization rife with corruption remain so skeptical about the possibility of voter fraud elsewhere?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We asked Joffe-Block whether she was concerned about illegal aliens voting in elections. That should have been a softball, but she refused to answer the question. Throughout the interview, Joffe-Block maintained the position that she could not understand the link between mass illegal immigration and the potential for widespread voter fraud, even after we laid out the feverish efforts of some left-wing activists to maintain vulnerabilities to our election systems so that illegal aliens can more easily vote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most shocking part of the interview was when we questioned Joffe-Block about her past affiliation with the defunct left-wing organization known as &lt;a href="https://acorninternational.org/" target="_blank"&gt;ACORN&lt;/a&gt;. When asked whether she used to work for ACORN and whether she helped register illegal aliens to vote, Joffe-Block admitted that she had worked with ACORN to register voters but then went silent and abruptly ended the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We had obviously touched a nerve. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ACORN was a corrupt left-wing organization that championed causes such as affordable housing and voter registration. It was shut down after it was caught on tape giving advice on how to commit &lt;a href="https://theweek.com/articles/496396/fall-acorn-timeline" target="_blank"&gt;tax fraud&lt;/a&gt; and even helped set up &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2009/POLITICS/09/10/acorn.prostitution/" target="_blank"&gt;underage prostitution rings&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ACORN was accused of engaging in &lt;a href="https://www.politico.com/story/2008/11/falsified-registrations-become-votes-015189" target="_blank"&gt;voter registration fraud&lt;/a&gt; during the lead-up to the 2008 presidential election. The organization faced allegations including submitting duplicate registrations and falsifying information, such as &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/id/wbna27270696" target="_blank"&gt;registering fictional characters like Mickey Mouse&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/id/wbna27270696" target="_blank"&gt;Dallas Cowboys&lt;/a&gt; players. The group’s endorsement of Barack Obama raised concerns about potential conflicts of interest and favoritism, especially since Obama had a &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2008/10/11/us/politics/11acorn.html" target="_blank"&gt;prior legal connection with the group&lt;/a&gt;. Finally, multiple ACORN workers across multiple states were &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2008/POLITICS/10/22/voter.fraud/" target="_blank"&gt;convicted of voter fraud&lt;/a&gt;. This further fueled suspicion about the credibility of individuals associated with the organization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How could someone who worked for an organization rife with corruption remain so skeptical about the possibility of voter fraud elsewhere? How could she be assigned to cover a story about voter fraud? Moreover, if Joffe-Block doesn’t actually support illegal aliens voting, why did she refuse to say so?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s impossible not to suspect she knows perfectly well that illegal aliens are being guided to the polls by ACORN’s successors on both sides of the border and is happy to stay silent about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, given the recent accusations of bias at NPR, demonstrated by &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/2024/04/17/1245283076/npr-editor-uri-berliner-resigns-ceo-katherine-maher#:~:text=NPR%20senior%20business%20editor%20Uri,email%20to%20CEO%20Katherine%20Maher." target="_blank"&gt;Uri Berliner’s resignation&lt;/a&gt; attesting to the outlet's prolific left-liberal slant, Joffe-Block’s suspicious behavior should not come as a surprise. The allegations are so serious that NPR CEO Katherine Maher has been requested to appear before the Energy and Commerce Subcommittee on Oversight and Investigations for a hearing on Wednesday to explain her organization’s policies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But we don’t need to wait. We already have all the information we need. Because if NPR was unbiased, it would release the full recording of our interview. Of course, it can’t do that because the video recording would show exactly how radical its reporters are.&lt;/p&gt;Worse still, NPR is a publicly funded organization. So, Jude Joffe-Block and her superiors aren’t simply being bad journalists, they're betraying their duty as public servants while pocketing your tax dollars.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden warns Netanyahu against Rafah invasion as Israel prepares for action</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/biden-warns-netanyahu-rafah-invasion-israel-prepares-action</link><description>President Biden called Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu over the phone on Monday, warning the prime minister against continuing with plans for an invasion of the Gaza city of Rafah.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 12:09:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Massive Rally in Dublin Against Unvetted Illegal Aliens</title><link>https://www.independentsentinel.com/massive-rally-in-dublin-against-unvetted-illegal-immigration/</link><description>The post Massive Rally in Dublin Against Unvetted Illegal Aliens appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 07:47:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sex Selection w/IVF Is Banned In Much of World - Except Here</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/07/sex_selection_wivf_is_banned_in_much_of_world_-_except_here_623149.html</link><description>Little girls are better than little boys-according to these people.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 12:44:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Antonin Scalia: Judge who seasoned opinions with wit</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/antonin-scalia-judge-who-seasoned-opinions-with-wit-2668184848.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/antonin-scalia-judge-who-seasoned-opinions-with-wit.jpg?id=52180147&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C98%2C0%2C73</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/antonin-scalia-judge-who-seasoned-opinions-with-wit.jpg?id=52180147&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C98%2C0%2C73" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img class="rm-shortcode" id="cde40" src="https://www.conservativereview.com/media-library/eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpbWFnZSI6Imh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnRoZWJsYXplLmNvbS9tZWRpYS1saWJyYXJ5L2FudG9uaW4tc2NhbGlhLWp1ZGdlLXdoby1zZWFzb25lZC1vcGluaW9ucy13aXRoLXdpdC5qcGc_aWQ9NTIxODAxNDcmYW1wO3dpZHRoPTk4MCIsImV4cGlyZXNfYXQiOjE3NzMwOTUzNjV9.TLOMVcNViR0WEnRypT6SjIaW7zyFwKnvKiWa2zWV23w/image.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;When it comes down to it, a job is a job, no matter how well-paid or prestigious, and you're bound to find yourself watching the clock at some point. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is why colleagues with a sense of humor are so important — nothing makes the work day fly by like sharing a laugh. For almost 30 years, the judges of the Supreme Court had the privilege of laughing with one of the best: &lt;a href="https://judicature.duke.edu/articles/why-we-read-the-scalia-opinion-first/" target="_blank"&gt;Justice Antonin Scalia&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those of us who didn't work with him can still enjoy the wit and verve on display in his oral arguments and written opinions. For example, &lt;a href="https://www.edweek.org/education/justice-scalias-dissent/1992/08" target="_blank"&gt;this 1992 dissent&lt;/a&gt; on the constitutionality of school prayer:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;I find it a sufficient embarrassment that our Establishment Clause jurisprudence regarding holiday displays, has come to "requir[e] scrutiny more commonly associated with interior decorators than with the judiciary." But interior decorating is a rock hard science compared to psychology practiced by amateurs. A few citations of "[r]esearch in psychology" that have no particular bearing upon the precise issue here cannot disguise the fact that the Court has gone beyond the realm where judges know what they are doing. The Court's argument that state officials have "coerced" students to take part in the invocation and benediction at graduation ceremonies is, not to put too fine a point on it, incoherent.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Or &lt;a href="https://www.law.cornell.edu/supct/html/00-24.ZD.html#:~:text=Justice%20Scalia%2C%20with%20whom%20Justice,I%20respectfully%20dissent." target="_blank"&gt;this 2001 dissent&lt;/a&gt;, from PGA Tour Inc. v. Martin:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;If one assumes, however, that the PGA TOUR has some legal obligation to play classic, Platonic golf — and if one assumes the correctness of all the other wrong turns the Court has made to get to this point — then we Justices must confront what is indeed an awesome responsibility. It has been rendered the solemn duty of the Supreme Court of the United States, laid upon it by Congress in pursuance of the Federal Government’s power "[t]o regulate Commerce with foreign Nations, and among the several States," to decide What Is Golf. I am sure that the Framers of the Constitution, aware of the 1457 edict of King James II of Scotland prohibiting golf because it interfered with the practice of archery, fully expected that sooner or later the paths of golf and government, the law and the links, would once again cross, and that the judges of this august Court would some day have to wrestle with that age-old jurisprudential question, for which their years of study in the law have so well prepared them: Is someone riding around a golf course from shot to shot &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; a golfer? The answer, we learn, is yes. The Court ultimately concludes, and it will henceforth be the Law of the Land, that walking is not a “fundamental” aspect of golf.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I attack ideas,” Scalia once said. “I don’t attack people. And some very good people have some very bad ideas. And if you can’t separate the two, you gotta get another day job.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scalia's close, long-lasting friendship with the far more liberal Ruth Bader Ginsberg bore this out. The lightness, humor, and humility with which Scalia carried out even his most serious duties should be a lesson for us all.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 12:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Group of conservative judges vows to not hire Columbia University law students due to anti-Israel protests</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/group-conservative-judges-vow-not-hire-columbia-university-law-students-due-anti-israel-protests</link><description>A group of conservative federal judges sent a letter to Columbia President Minouche Shafik, vowing to not hire graduates because of the school's response to anti-Israel protests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 09:00:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Traitor Joe Calls Illegal Aliens “Model Citizens” in Cinco De Mayo Speech</title><link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2024/05/joe-biden-calls-illegal-aliens-model-citizens-cinco/</link><description>The post Traitor Joe Calls Illegal Aliens “Model Citizens” in Cinco De Mayo Speech appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 07:46:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Menendez &amp; Cuellar Cases Sound Alarm on Foreign Influence</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/07/menendez_amp_cuellar_cases_sound_alarm_on_foreign_influence_623142.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 12:36:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Red-state governor talks tough on immigration, saves cheap labor</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/red-state-governor-talks-tough-on-immigration-saves-cheap-labor-2668184609.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/red-state-governor-talks-tough-on-immigration-saves-cheap-labor.jpg?id=52180214&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C171</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/red-state-governor-talks-tough-on-immigration-saves-cheap-labor.jpg?id=52180214&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C171" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/red-state-governor-talks-tough-on-immigration-saves-cheap-labor.jpg?id=52180214&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;coordinates=0,0,0,1 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/red-state-governor-talks-tough-on-immigration-saves-cheap-labor.jpg%3Fid%3D52180214%26width%3D1200%26height%3D800%26coordinates%3D0%2C0%2C0%2C1%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite an unrelenting invasion for over three years, red states have been slow to strengthen laws against illegal immigration. Some of it might be due to fear of judicial interference. Much of it, however, is the result of a complicated relationship between most Republican special interests and cheap labor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So it was a pleasant surprise when the Oklahoma legislature swiftly passed the toughest anti-illegal-immigration law in the nation — one that fully criminalizes illegal presence within the state and gives the invaders 72 hours to leave. Unfortunately, Governor Kevin Stitt’s plans for the law show why it faced so little opposition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HB 4156 requires &lt;em&gt;every&lt;/em&gt; illegal alien to leave. Stitt made a mockery of the law the minute he signed it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stitt last week signed &lt;a href="http://www.oklegislature.gov/BillInfo.aspx?Bill=HB4156" target="_blank"&gt;House Bill 4156&lt;/a&gt;, making the Sooner State the first in the nation to outlaw residency without first obtaining legal admission to the country. The first offense, if caught in the state illegally, is a misdemeanor, punishable by up to a year in jail and a $500 fine. Subsequent offenses are considered felonies punishable by up to two years in prison and a $1,000 fine. In both cases, the offender must leave the state within 72 hours of release from jail or prison and is not allowed to return.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The law passed without a single Republican dissent in either chamber. Republicans control the House 81-20 and the Senate 40-8.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If enforced, the law would compel offenders to leave the state whether or not the individual was arrested for committing another crime. It’s model legislation for other red states. The trouble is with the &lt;em&gt;expectation&lt;/em&gt; of enforcement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kevin Stitt has long been a proponent of illegal aliens, even as he criticizes Biden for his open-border policies. As recently as last legislative session, Stitt and his allies &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/columns/opinion/horowitz-why-is-oklahoma-gov-kevin-stitt-pushing-drivers-licenses-for-illegal-aliens" target="_self"&gt;were pushing for driver’s licenses for illegal aliens&lt;/a&gt;. So it came as something of a shock when Stitt signed HB 4156.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Or maybe not. At the very moment he signed the law, Stitt announced a task force to “explore opportunities for those here contributing to our communities and economy.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;div&gt;I just signed HB 4156 in response to Biden\u2019s failure to secure the southern border\u2014 we must be a law and order state.\n\nI\u2019m also announcing the launch of a Task Force to explore opportunities for those here contributing to our communities and economy.\n\nhttps://t.co/OvQlCRsgWd&lt;/div&gt; —  (@)        &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/GovStitt/status/1785442834947985868"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.sos.ok.gov/documents/executive/2104.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;executive order&lt;/a&gt; establishing the task force stipulates, “House Bill 4156 is not aimed at the honest, hardworking Hispanic or other international migrant populations here chasing the American dream, enhancing our communities, economies, and way of life, and otherwise significantly contributing to Oklahoma’s tapestry.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You might suppose Stitt is referring only to legal immigrants because he artfully avoids the adjective “illegal” throughout the order. But on closer inspection, the order calls for the task force to recommend ways “for immigrants here … to secure work permits, work visas, or similar documentation permitting them to remain for established timeframes without separation from their families or livelihood.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Suffice to say, legal immigrants don’t need visas and work permits because they already have them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stitt’s executive order would have the task force find ways to provide essentially every major industry in Oklahoma with cheap labor from the illegal alien population.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It would be one thing if HB 4156 tacked on the crime of illegal residency only for people arrested for other crimes. Stitt could harmonize enforcement of that law with a parallel effort to promote non-criminal aliens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But that isn’t what the law says. HB 4156 requires &lt;em&gt;every&lt;/em&gt; illegal alien to leave. Stitt made a mockery of the law the minute he signed it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stitt is a perfect example of the lawlessness of certain Republican politicians who speak one way about the border invasion to inveigh against Biden while they act another way to protect cheap labor. They want an endless supply of illegal workers from the Third World and are willing to ignore laws while promoting every straw-man Democrat talking point about their “honest” contributions to our way of life (even though every one of them breaks the law and usually steals identities).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; From now until Election Day, you will hear every Republican governor condemn Biden’s immigration policies. But just know that many of them privately root for the success of those policies while denouncing them as a cynical campaign ploy.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NY v Trump to resume after former president threatened with jail, told trial to last at least 2 more weeks</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/ny-v-trump-to-resume-after-former-president-threatened-with-jail-told-trial-will-last-at-least-2-more-weeks</link><description>The unprecedented criminal trial of former President Trump resumes Tuesday morning after the 2024 presumptive Republican presidential nominee was again held in contempt of court.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 09:00:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘Only One Solution, Intifada Revolution’: Boston High School Students Join MIT Anti-Israel Encampment</title><link>https://legalinsurrection.com/2024/05/only-one-solution-intifada-revolution-boston-high-school-students-join-mit-anti-israel-encampment/</link><description>The post ‘Only One Solution, Intifada Revolution’: Boston High School Students Join MIT Anti-Israel Encampment appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 07:44:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>America's China Strategy Has a Credibility Problem</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/07/americas_china_strategy_has_a_credibility_problem_623159.html</link><description>A muddled approach to economic sanctions won't deter Beijing.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 12:35:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>UNC Under Fire After Professors Threaten To Hold Grades Hostage In Solidarity With Hamas</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/unc-under-fire-after-professors-threaten-to-hold-grades-hostage-in-solidarity-with-hamas-2668184927.html</link><image_url>https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/9432559054_4f96172f0b_k-e1715031502117.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/9432559054_4f96172f0b_k-e1715031502117.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img class="rm-shortcode" id="d3341" src="https://www.conservativereview.com/media-library/eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpbWFnZSI6Imh0dHBzOi8vdGhlZmVkZXJhbGlzdC5jb20vd3AtY29udGVudC91cGxvYWRzLzIwMjQvMDUvOTQzMjU1OTA1NF80Zjk2MTcyZjBiX2stZTE3MTUwMzE1MDIxMTctMTIwMHg2NzUuanBnIiwiZXhwaXJlc19hdCI6MTc3NzM2NTM1M30.WxMMXBsregwhxSE9Scja28kRY1hHcCw-cB4F0GAR6GU/image.jpg" /&gt;The University of North Carolina-Chapel Hill confirmed reports of professors punishing students by refusing to submit grades.&lt;/span&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 11:54:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GOP committee chair demands answers from DC officials on controversial noncitizen voting law</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/gop-committee-chair-demands-answers-dc-officials-controversial-noncitizen-voting-law</link><description>The head of the House Administration Committee is expressing concern about what he sees as D.C. officials encouraging non-citizen voting in upcoming elections.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 09:00:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>No, ‘Millions’ of People Did Not Watch X Stream of Angel Reese’s Debut</title><link>https://www.outkick.com/sports/no-millions-of-people-did-not-watch-x-stream-of-angel-reeses-debut</link><description>The post No, ‘Millions’ of People Did Not Watch X Stream of Angel Reese’s Debut appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 07:44:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>No Easter Truce in Ukraine</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/07/no_easter_truce_in_ukraine_623151.html</link><description>If the two sides can't agree on a ceasefire for the holiest day in the Orthodox calendar, negotiations aren't coming soon.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 12:34:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>For Israel, ‘Never Again’ Isn’t Just A Hashtag</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/for-israel-never-again-isnt-just-a-hashtag-2668184478.html</link><image_url>https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Pomnik_Ofiar_Obozu_Zaglady_w_Treblince_2017c.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Pomnik_Ofiar_Obozu_Zaglady_w_Treblince_2017c.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img class="rm-shortcode" id="0064e" src="https://www.conservativereview.com/media-library/eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpbWFnZSI6Imh0dHBzOi8vdGhlZmVkZXJhbGlzdC5jb20vd3AtY29udGVudC91cGxvYWRzLzIwMjQvMDUvUG9tbmlrX09maWFyX09ib3p1X1phZ2xhZHlfd19UcmVibGluY2VfMjAxN2MtMTIwMHg2NzUuanBnIiwiZXhwaXJlc19hdCI6MTc1OTIxMjg2M30.It140HOq4RAFzL_oXlcioGQBKpYOAk-vdNTJHOuBA5Q/image.jpg" /&gt;The Nazis are dead. Hamas is alive.&lt;/span&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 11:45:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Squad' member caught at fundraiser hosted by Islamic leader who praised Hamas attack on Israel</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/squad-member-caught-fundraiser-hosted-islamic-leader-praised-attack-israel</link><description>New York Rep. Jamaal Bowman, a member of the far-left "Squad," was caught attending a fundraiser co-hosted by an Islamic leader who said he was "happy" about the Oct. 7 Hamas attack.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 09:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>