<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 23:49:10 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Wake Up America: Campus Chaos and Blue State Exodus With Dean Cain [Full Show]</title><link>https://frankspeech.com/Video/wake-up-america-campus-chaos-and-blue-state-exodus-1</link><description>The post Wake Up America: Campus Chaos and Blue State Exodus With Dean Cain [Full Show] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 02:01:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Transportation Department's New Path</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/25/the_transportation_departments_new_path_622455.html</link><description>In a busy week for regulatory action, Pete Buttigieg's emergence in fighting corporate power should not be overlooked.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 20:04:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Those children were hunted down and killed': Oklahoma police stunned by family massacre where 10-year-old boy was unharmed</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/those-children-were-hunted-down-and-killed-oklahoma-police-stunned-by-family-massacre-where-10-year-old-boy-was-unharmed-2667907789.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52117242&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C22%2C0%2C57</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52117242&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C22%2C0%2C57" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52117242&amp;amp;width=1245&amp;amp;height=700&amp;amp;coordinates=82,0,0,0 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg%3Fid%3D52117242%26width%3D1245%26height%3D700%26coordinates%3D82%2C0%2C0%2C0%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oklahoma neighbors of a family are shocked and saddened by the &lt;a href="https://lawandcrime.com/crime/those-children-were-hunted-down-and-killed-father-leaves-youngest-child-unharmed-after-killing-wife-3-sons-in-massacre-cops-say/" target="_blank"&gt;gruesome murder-suicide&lt;/a&gt; being reported by police on Monday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 10-year-old boy awoke to find his parents and three siblings shot to death and called police from their Oklahoma City home at about 9:35 a.m., police said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After an investigation, police said that 42-year-old Jonathon Candy got into an argument with his 39-year-old wife, Lindsay Candy, in the middle of the night and then shot her several times, killing her. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“At that point, he systematically went through the home, shooting and killing their children,”  Master Sgt. Gary Knight said to reporters at a media briefing on Tuesday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; “It’s unclear what made him want to go through the home, killing the children," he continued. "But make no mistake about it, what happened in that residence was nothing short of a massacre. Those children were hunted down and killed.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investigators said Jonathon Candy shot 18-year-old Dylan Candy, 14-year-old Ethan Candy, and 11-year-old Lucas Candy, then turned the gun on himself. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knight said they were trying to figure out why the father killed three of his sons but allowed one son to survive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I know that’s a question everybody has,” he said. “That’s a question we have, too. In the end, nobody ever is going to have an answer for that.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investigators have also been so far unable to discover a motive for the massacre, and they may not ever be able to piece it together.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We have no calls to that residence regarding any type of domestic abuse," said Knight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neighbors and friends of the Candy family are equally stunned and horrified.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“All day, we just couldn’t imagine,” Michael Burcham told the Oklahoman newspaper. “He must have really been having a hard time.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Burcham said that Jonathon Candy had previously confided in him that he had suffered from depression. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before the horrifying massacre, Jonathon and Lindsay Candy had been interviewed by a news station and spoke glowingly about a local bakery and deli shop. With Lindsay at his side, Jonathon recommended the breakfast burritos and carrot cake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Oklahoma City Thunder basketball team confirmed that Jonathan Candy had worked for them as a part-time game-night engineer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The surviving child was placed with his relatives. They have set up a &lt;a href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/help-lindseys-surviving-son-and-family?attribution_id=sl:ff7c7c11-f117-4d6d-9c66-26643a89562f&amp;amp;utm_campaign=p_cp+fundraiser-sidebar&amp;amp;utm_medium=copy_link_all&amp;amp;utm_source=customer" target="_blank"&gt;GoFundMe&lt;/a&gt; charity page to help with funeral costs and to help with caring for the boy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Here's a news video about the massacre: &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;! &lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 03:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Columbia University’s policy-making senate votes for resolution calling to investigate school’s leadership</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/columbia-universitys-policy-making-senate-votes-for-resolution-calling-to-investigate-schools-leadership</link><description>The Columbia University Senate voted on a resolution to investigate the school's leadership amid anti-Israel protests that have been going on for more than a week.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 03:12:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mainstream Media Misrepresenting Crime Statistics in Order to Protect Traitor Joe</title><link>https://amgreatness.com/2024/04/26/mainstream-media-misrepresenting-crime-statistics-in-order-to-protect-biden/</link><description>The post Mainstream Media Misrepresenting Crime Statistics in Order to Protect Traitor Joe appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 00:50:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anti-Semitism and the DEI Agenda</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/26/anti-semitism_and_the_dei_agenda_622520.html</link><description>The anti-Israel camps taking over elite universities are a physical manifestation of the DEI agenda.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 20:04:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Mexico grandmom says home intruder didn't listen to her warning, so she shot him to protect her 4-year-old granddaughter</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/new-mexico-grandmom-says-home-intruder-didn-t-listen-to-her-warning-so-she-shot-him-to-protect-her-4-year-old-granddaughter-2667904376.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52117180&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C64%2C0%2C133</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52117180&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C64%2C0%2C133" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52117180&amp;amp;width=600&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0,0,804,0 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg%3Fid%3D52117180%26width%3D600%26height%3D600%26coordinates%3D0%2C0%2C804%2C0%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;A grandmother in New Mexico recalls the terror of the night she shot a home intruder in order to protect her 4-year-old granddaughter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blaze News previously reported the &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/grandmother-protecting-herself-and-her-4-year-old-grandson-shoots-auto-theft-suspect-who-broke-into-her-home-cops-say" target="_blank"&gt;incident from March 21&lt;/a&gt;, but new details have been revealed through the release of the harrowing 911 recording from the night and the victim's interview with KRQE-TV.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anissa Tinnin said that she was happily dancing to the Taylor Swift movie with her granddaughter when her serene evening was obliterated by an uninvited criminal invading her home in Albuquerque.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Joseph Rivera, 32, had reportedly crashed a stolen vehicle after the Albuquerque Police Department had flattened its tires with stop sticks and he continued to drive on the rims. He fled on foot and allegedly ran into Tinnin's home at about 9:30 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I jumped over this couch, and we met there by the front door," the grandmom told KRQE-TV. "That’s when he grabbed me and was upset and said to give him my keys. He said he didn’t want to go to jail. He did threaten to hurt my granddaughter and me."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tinnin gave him her key fob and tried to calm him down. She said that she called 911 and kept the line open while the rest of the events transpired.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"As we were walking, ... I put my hands on him ... to try to be calming," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Tell me what your name is, ... tell me where you are from."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Get back! I will f****** shoot you!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The man took the key fob and left but returned to ask for more keys. She took her granddaughter to a bedroom and grabbed her gun.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I told him to not hurt us, that I would do whatever he wanted. I would give him keys, money, whatever it took,” she continued.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tinnin said she comforted her granddaughter and then returned outside of the bedroom to find that Rivera had not left. That's when she threatened to shoot him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Get back. Get back! I have a gun. Get back! Get back. I will f****** shoot you!" she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At that point, one gunshot can be heard on the recording.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Why did you shoot me?” the suspect can be heard asking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Because you’re in my f****** house!” she responds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite the threat, Tinnin put pressure on the man's wound to stop the bleeding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At that point, video surveillance captures scores of police officers swarming the home and dragging the suspect out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tinnin says she wants Rivera to be prosecuted to the fullest extent of the law and called on the district attorney to refuse a plea deal. The man has had five previous felony convictions and faces numerous charges stemming from the home invasion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Megan Tinnin Austin says that her daughter is traumatized from the events of that night and is afraid of the dark.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tinnin says that she believes God was looking over her and her granddaughter that evening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I do believe we had a guardian angel here with us, and I do firmly believe that God was watching over us,” she concluded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Here's the stunning video report:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 02:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>St. Louis' toxic sites need faster cleanup, lawmakers and residents say</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/st-louis-toxic-sites-need-faster-cleanup-lawmakers-residents-say</link><description>Missouri residents and lawmakers are holding the Environmental Protection Agency and Army Corps of Engineers accountable to carrying out faster cleanups at toxic sites.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 01:35:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>18-Year-Old Former Hostage Reveals Hamas Terrorist Demanded She Marry Him and Stay in Gaza to Raise Their Children</title><link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-hamas-war/article-798830</link><description>The post 18-Year-Old Former Hostage Reveals Hamas Terrorist Demanded She Marry Him and Stay in Gaza to Raise Their Children appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 00:50:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is Biden Slipping in PA?</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/26/is_biden_slipping_in_pa_622572.html</link><description>President Joe Biden's highly unusual three-day swing through the state in the week leading up to primary day.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 20:00:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>UCLA Med School Launches Review Of ‘Health Equity’ Course But Warns That Whistleblowers Could Be Disciplined</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/ucla-med-school-launches-review-of-health-equity-course-but-warns-that-whistleblowers-could-be-disciplined-2667901520.html</link><image_url>https://freebeacon.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/GettyImages-1206664281.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://freebeacon.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/GettyImages-1206664281.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The University of California, Los Angeles medical school is launching a probe of its controversial "health equity" class—and warning whistleblowers they could be punished if any more information leaks about it. The dean of the medical school, Steven Dubinett, announced Friday that his office had formed a task force to review all first-year courses, including […]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://freebeacon.com/campus/ucla-med-school-launches-review-of-health-equity-course-but-warns-that-whistleblowers-could-be-disciplined/"&gt;UCLA Med School Launches Review Of ‘Health Equity’ Course But Warns That Whistleblowers Could Be Disciplined&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://freebeacon.com"&gt;Washington Free Beacon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 02:00:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kansas won't have legal medical pot or expand Medicaid for at least another year</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/kansas-wont-legal-medical-pot-expand-medicaid-least-another-year</link><description>Before the Kansas Legislature's scheduled adjournment for the year, Republican state senators blocked efforts to force debates on expanding Medicaid programs and the medical use of marijuana.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 01:04:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Police Aren’t Impressed by Protesting Professing Professing Her Professorship [VIDEO]</title><link>https://rumble.com/v4rpocl-police-arent-impressed-by-protesting-professing-professing-her-professorshi.html</link><description>The post Police Aren’t Impressed by Protesting Professing Professing Her Professorship [VIDEO] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 00:50:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>It Just Might Be That Dems Know How To Win Michigan</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/23/it_just_might_be_that_dems_know_how_to_win_michigan_622318.html</link><description>A pair of special-election landslides proves that the party is doing something right.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 20:00:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>As many as 59 women were exposed to HIV infection over 'vampire facials' and Botox injections, health officials say</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/as-many-as-59-women-were-exposed-to-hiv-infection-over-vampire-facials-and-botox-injections-health-officials-say-2667902978.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52117133&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C104%2C0%2C0</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52117133&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C104%2C0%2C0" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52117133&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;coordinates=344,0,0,0 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg%3Fid%3D52117133%26width%3D1200%26height%3D800%26coordinates%3D344%2C0%2C0%2C0%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;A report warned that Botox injections and "vampire facials" have led to some women &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/vampire-facial-hiv-new-mexico-infection-cdc/" target="_blank"&gt;being infected&lt;/a&gt; with HIV because of unsanitary conditions at a spa in New Mexico.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This investigation is the first to associate HIV transmission with nonsterile cosmetic injection services," read a statement from the report from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three women tested positive for HIV after receiving the novel cosmetic operations. The report found that they were infected despite not having any other HIV risk factors and determined that the operations were to blame. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vampire facials involve blood being drawn from the client's arm and platelets being removed from the blood and injected into the patients with microneedles. The process is intended to rejuvenate the skin and clear away acne and wrinkles. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The CDC report said as many as 59 clients could have been exposed to HIV through the facials and Botox injections at a business in Albuquerque that was unlicensed and didn't use appropriate safety measures. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the report did not name the clinic, KRQE-TV reported that VIP Spa owner Maria Ramos de Ruiz pleaded guilty to several felony counts of practicing without a license in 2022 and was sentenced to serve three and a half years in prison. The New Mexico Department of Health also shut down her spa in 2018 after finding unlabeled blood tubes on a kitchen counter and injectables stored in a kitchen refrigerator next to food. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;De Ruiz is currently incarcerated at Springer Correctional Center. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to the three HIV positive cases, two other infections were linked to the clinic through "direct or indirect connection with services provided at the VIP Spa," said a department spokesperson. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new case of HIV infection linked to the clinic &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/hiv-cases-linked-new-mexico-salon-vampire-facials-rcna93054" target="_blank"&gt;prompted&lt;/a&gt; the department to tell past clients to be tested for HIV, hepatitis B, and hepatitis C, even if they had previously tested negative. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It’s very important that we spread the word and remind people who received any kind of injection related to services provided at the VIP Spa to come in for free and confidential testing," said Dr. Laura Parajon, the deputy secretary of the health department. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The CDC warns people against seeking treatments and operations at unlicensed spa facilities. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Here's a news report about the report: &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;! &lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 01:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maine governor signs off on new gun laws, mental health supports in wake of Lewiston shootings</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/maine-governor-signs-new-gun-laws-mental-health-supports-wake-lewiston-shootings</link><description>Maine's Democratic Gov. Janet Mills has signed a suite of gun safety legislation into law, after the deadliest mass shooting in the state's history left 18 people dead and 13 people injured.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 00:51:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tranny Sexual Predators Are Being Enabled by the “LGBTQ+” Agenda</title><link>https://www.lifesitenews.com/blogs/transgender-sexual-predators-are-being-enabled-by-the-lgbt-agenda/</link><description>The post Tranny Sexual Predators Are Being Enabled by the “LGBTQ+” Agenda appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 00:50:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Continuing a Tradition of Civics Excellence</title><link>https://www.realcleareducation.com/articles/2024/04/25/continuing_a_tradition_of_civics_excellence_1027548.html</link><description>With new institutes emerging at colleges and universities in Florida, Ohio, Utah, Tennessee, North Carolina, Texas, and elsewhere, civics education may be seeing a rebirth.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 19:53:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ROOKE: Red State Bill Could See Residents Jailed For Online Speech</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/rooke-red-state-bill-could-see-residents-jailed-for-online-speech-2667901498.html</link><image_url>https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/Shutterstock_777890371-scaled-e1714176081164.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/Shutterstock_777890371-scaled-e1714176081164.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;'maximum $100,000 fine or ten years imprisonment'</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 01:29:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tennessee Gov. Lee signs bill allowing concealed carry for public schoolteachers</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/tennessee-gov-lee-signs-bill-allowing-concealed-carry-public-schoolteachers</link><description>Republican Tennessee Gov. Bill Lee signed into law a bill allowing teachers and staff to carry concealed handguns on school grounds.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 00:06:49 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>