<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 06:48:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Conservative Momma Parody: USSS Director Kimberly Cheatle [VIDEO]</title><link>https://rumble.com/v57b765-conservative-momma-parody-usss-director-kimberly-cheatle.html</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>The post Conservative Momma Parody: USSS Director Kimberly Cheatle [VIDEO] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 11:39:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump to formally accept Republican presidential nomination in speech altered after assassination attempt</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-formally-accept-republican-presidential-nomination-speech-altered-after-assassination-attempt</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>Five days after surviving an assassination attempt, former President Trump will formally accept the GOP presidential nomination during the culminating moment of the 2024 Republican National Convention</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 09:00:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wife of Washington Post Columnist Who Spent Almost a Decade Calling Trump a Foreign Agent Gets Indicted for Being an Unregistered Foreign Agent</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/wife-washington-post-columnist-who-spent-almost-decade/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>Federal authorities have indicted the wife of Max Boot, a deranged leftist who works for the Washington Post, for operating as an unregistered foreign agent for South Korea. Which is honestly kind of hilarious given how Boot is one of those TDS morons who accused Trump of being a foreign agent without any evidence. Federal […] The post Wife of Washington Post Columnist Who Spent Almost a Decade Calling Trump a Foreign Agent Gets Indicted for Being an Unregistered Foreign Agent appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 11:37:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Flashback: A look at Donald Trump's remarks at the 2016, 2020 Republican conventions</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/flashback-trumps-2016-2020-rnc-speeches</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>This is Trump's third Republican National Convention being named the GOP's presidential nominee. His remarks are expected to be aimed at bringing the country together after the assassination attempt against him.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 09:00:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Get Your Trump “YOU MISSED!” T-Shirt at The Liberty Daily Store — For a Limited Time Only</title><link>https://shop.thelibertydaily.com/products/you-missed-t-shirt</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>The post Get Your Trump “YOU MISSED!” T-Shirt at The Liberty Daily Store — For a Limited Time Only appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 11:37:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump VP pick JD Vance pledges to ‘commit to the working man’ as populism takes center stage at RNC</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-vp-pick-jd-vance-pledges-commit-working-man-populism-takes-center-stage-rnc</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>Sen. JD Vance, Trump's running mate in the 2024 White House race, said he will be a vice president who “never forgets" where he came from while striking a populist tone at the RNC.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 09:00:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Will it Last? Three Reasons Gold Prices Shot Up After Assassination Attempt Against Trump</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/will-it-last-three-reasons-gold-prices-shot/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>Editor’s Note: This article and any related communications are for informational purposes only and should not be considered as financial advice. We do not provide personalized investment, financial, or legal advice. This outlet benefits from purchases made through our sponsors. The attempted assassination against Donald Trump on Saturday prompted a sharp spike in precious metals […] The post Will it Last? Three Reasons Gold Prices Shot Up After Assassination Attempt Against Trump appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 11:37:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘Ruined by negligence’: Dave Portnoy blasts Nantucket wind farm after broken blade shuts down beaches</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/ruined-negligence-dave-portnoy-blasts-nantucket-wind-farm-after-broken-blade-shuts-down-beaches</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>Barstool Sports' Dave Portnoy is speaking out after an offshore windmill blade snapped and sent fiberglass shards onto the Nantucket shoreline.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 09:00:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dementia Joe Tests Positive for Covid, Cancels Event</title><link>https://www.infowars.com/posts/breaking-biden-tests-positive-for-covid-19-cancels-event/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>The post Dementia Joe Tests Positive for Covid, Cancels Event appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 11:37:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Senators confront Secret Service chief at Republican convention: ‘You owe President Trump answers’</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/senators-confront-secret-service-chief-rnc-you-owe-president-trump-answers</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>Multiple Republican senators confronted Secret Service Director Kimberly Cheatle about the attempted assassination of former President Trump on Wednesday.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 04:31:48 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>