<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 07:17:44 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>5 Things to Know About JD Vance</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/5-things-know-about-jd-vance/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>(Daily Signal)—Donald Trump selected Sen. JD Vance from Ohio on Monday as his running mate in the Nov. 5 election, which the former president hopes will return him to the White House. Vance accepted and Vice President Kamala Harris said she’s ready to debate him. So, who is JD Vance? Here are five things to know […] The post 5 Things to Know About JD Vance appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 12:12:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Democrats spotlight Biden alter-ego 'Dark Brandon' as they launch billboards near GOP convention</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/democrats-spotlight-dark-brandon-launch-billboards-near-gop-convention</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>As GOP delegates, officials, activists and supporters head to day 2 of the Republican National Convention in Milwaukee, Democrats launch billboards spotlighting President Biden's alter-ego: Dark Brandon.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 11:00:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jack Smith Will Appeal Ruling That Upended His Classified Documents Case Against Trump</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/jack-smith-will-appeal-ruling-that-upended-his/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>(DCNF)—Special counsel Jack Smith will appeal a Monday ruling by Judge Aileen Cannon that dismissed the government’s classified documents case against former President Donald Trump. Cannon ruled Monday morning to throw out Smith’s case on the basis that Smith was unlawfully appointed as special counsel. The ruling was a massive victory for Trump, but Smith […] The post Jack Smith Will Appeal Ruling That Upended His Classified Documents Case Against Trump appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 11:44:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Former Trump primary rival Haley in Republican convention spotlight on day after JD Vance named running mate</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/former-trump-primary-rival-haley-republican-convention-spotlight-day-after-jd-vance-named-running-mate</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>One day after Donald Trump was formally nominated as the GOP's 2024 presidential nominee and named Sen. JD Vance as running mate, Nikki Haley takes center stage at the Republican National Convention</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 09:00:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Taco Jill Orchestrated Kimberly Cheatle Heading the Secret Service, Now Everyone Is Doubling Down</title><link>https://redstate.com/bonchie/2024/07/15/jill-biden-pushed-for-kimberly-cheatle-to-head-the-secret-service-disaster-followed-n2176924</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>The post Taco Jill Orchestrated Kimberly Cheatle Heading the Secret Service, Now Everyone Is Doubling Down appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 11:43:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JD Vance brings a wealth of experience from Silicon Valley to the campaign, White House</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/jd-vance-brings-wealth-experience-from-silicon-valley-campaign-white-house</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>The GOP vice presidential nominee is only a freshman senator, but has years of experience outside the political arena that is likely to boost the Republican ticket in November.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 09:00:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pinocchio Joe Is a Terrible Liar About His Dangerous Rhetoric</title><link>https://pjmedia.com/matt-margolis/2024/07/15/joe-biden-is-a-terrible-liar-about-his-dangerous-rhetoric-n4930720</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>The post Pinocchio Joe Is a Terrible Liar About His Dangerous Rhetoric appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 11:42:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kamala Harris congratulates JD Vance, hopes 'that the two can meet' at VP debate</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/kamala-harris-congratulates-jd-vance-hopes-that-two-can-meet-vp-debate</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>Kamala Harris called JD Vance to congratulate him on being selected as former President Trump's running mate, and also to express hope they can meet face to face for a debate.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 09:00:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gruesome Newsom Rescinds Offer to Send Attorneys to Help Bay Area D.A. Fight Crime After She Ignored His Offer</title><link>https://legalinsurrection.com/2024/07/ca-gov-newsom-rescinds-offer-attorneys-to-help-bay-area-d-a-fight-crime-after-she-ignored-his-offer/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>The post Gruesome Newsom Rescinds Offer to Send Attorneys to Help Bay Area D.A. Fight Crime After She Ignored His Offer appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 11:41:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JD Vance, once a Never Trumper, is the VP pick to shape MAGA’s future</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/j-d-vance-once-never-trumper-vp-pick-shape-magas-future</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>Iraq veteran and Sen. JD Vance was selected to be Donald Trump's VP pick on Monday afternoon. Will the senator from Ohio bolster the ticket in the 2024 election?</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 08:00:35 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>