<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 16:32:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>All the Turmoil We’re Seeing Today Is a Stress Test for Real Chaos Around Election Time [VIDEO]</title><link>https://rumble.com/v4sanw6-all-the-turmoil-were-seeing-today-is-a-stress-test-for-real-chaos-around-el.html</link><description>The post All the Turmoil We’re Seeing Today Is a Stress Test for Real Chaos Around Election Time [VIDEO] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 21:23:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Failed Promise of Egg Freezing</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/29/the_failed_promise_of_egg_freezing_622699.html</link><description>The costly procedure was supposed to give women a new kind of freedom. Is that what it really offers?</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 19:44:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘Ominous Trends’: Policy Strategist Says It’s ‘Almost Too Late’ For Biden To ‘Regain’ Support From Key Voter Bloc</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/ominous-trends-policy-strategist-says-its-almost-too-late-for-biden-to-regain-support-from-key-voter-bloc-2668090175.html</link><image_url>https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/Screen-Shot-2024-04-29-at-3.07.14-PM-e1714418635382.png</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/Screen-Shot-2024-04-29-at-3.07.14-PM-e1714418635382.png" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;'No way he can win'</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 21:14:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Johnson urges Biden to intervene in ICC's reported plan for Netanyahu arrest warrant</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/johnson-biden-intervene-icc-reported-plan-netanyahu-arrest-warrant</link><description>House Speaker Mike Johnson is urging the Biden administration to help block the International Criminal Court from issuing arrest warrants against top Israeli officials.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 21:01:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>18-Year-Old Men Can Share Cabin With Preteen Girls at Oregon Outdoor School if Doing so Makes Them “Feel Safer”</title><link>https://www.theblaze.com/news/18-year-old-men-can-share-cabin-with-preteen-girls-at-oregon-outdoor-school-if-doing-so-makes-them-feel-safer</link><description>The post 18-Year-Old Men Can Share Cabin With Preteen Girls at Oregon Outdoor School if Doing so Makes Them “Feel Safer” appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 21:23:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tensions Grow Between Trump &amp; Lake in AZ Senate Race</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/29/tensions_grow_between_trump_amp_lake_in_az_senate_race_622696.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 19:43:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nearly all states take foster kids' federal benefits and use them to offset cost of foster care: Report</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/nearly-all-states-take-foster-kids-federal-benefits-and-use-them-to-offset-cost-of-foster-care-report-2668089797.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/nearly-all-states-take-foster-kids-federal-benefits-and-use-them-to-offset-cost-of-foster-care-report.jpg?id=52133561&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C177%2C0%2C177</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/nearly-all-states-take-foster-kids-federal-benefits-and-use-them-to-offset-cost-of-foster-care-report.jpg?id=52133561&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C177%2C0%2C177" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/nearly-all-states-take-foster-kids-federal-benefits-and-use-them-to-offset-cost-of-foster-care-report.jpg?id=52133561&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;coordinates=0,0,0,0 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/nearly-all-states-take-foster-kids-federal-benefits-and-use-them-to-offset-cost-of-foster-care-report.jpg%3Fid%3D52133561%26width%3D1200%26height%3D800%26coordinates%3D0%2C0%2C0%2C0%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;A disturbing &lt;a href="https://catcher.sandiego.edu/items/usdlaw/Foster_Care_or_Foster_Con_Report_FINAL.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;report&lt;/a&gt; from the Children’s Advocacy Institute at the University of San Diego School of Law indicates that nearly all states routinely take federal benefits from children in the foster system and use those benefits to offset the cost of foster care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like their counterparts who are not in the foster care system, some foster kids are entitled to receive federal money, including disability benefits associated with Social Security as well as survivor benefits associated with the Veterans' Administration and the Old-Age, Survivors, and Disability Insurance program, which are issued upon the death of a parent, the Children's Advocacy Institute study noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, of all 50 states and the District of Columbia, only seven received a passing grade in the study: Arizona, D.C., New Mexico, Oregon, Maryland, Illinois, and Washington state. The rest received an F because they otherwise abscond with the foster kids' federal money in the name of "revenue maximization," oftentimes without even bothering to tell the children first.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"For this subset of foster youth, who face tremendous obstacles when they transition out of care, these assets can serve as a lifeline, contributing to economic stability, self-sufficiency, and successful outcomes," the study said. "Most foster youth eligible for these federal benefits will never see a dollar of their money, or even know that someone has applied for and received benefits on their behalf."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.freep.com/story/news/local/michigan/2024/04/22/michigan-foster-care-federal-benefit-money-child-welfare-costs/73355844007/?s=01" target="_blank"&gt;Detroit Free Press&lt;/a&gt; investigated the issue in Michigan, one of the 44 states to receive a failing grade in the study. According to the outlet, in fiscal year 2022-23, Michigan collected $3.2 million in federal benefits designated for foster children, all of which went toward reimbursing "the state for the cost of caring for kids in the child welfare system."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The only way a Michigan foster child may begin receiving some of his or her federal benefits or have those benefits saved on the child's behalf is when "the child’s total income exceeds the cost of care," the &lt;a href="https://dhhs.michigan.gov/OLMWEB/EX/FO/Public/FOM/902-12.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;Michigan Department of Health and Human Services&lt;/a&gt; indicated. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet, the state has apparently failed to deliver in some of those cases as well. The Free Press noted that one former foster youth whose father died did not receive federal benefits for the first six months after he was returned to the care of his birth mother, meaning the state collected nearly $5,400 to which the young man was entitled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I don’t understand how they can do that to kids when they’re trying to move forward with their life," said the boy's mother, Jenny Bowden.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It makes you feel like they really don’t care about it, or they’re trying to have a good image without having to do the work," Bowden's son added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When asked for comment, the Michigan DHHS made no attempt to deny denying foster kids their federal benefits. "This is common practice among many states," the agency said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"When a child is placed in an out-of-home situation with MDHHS, income or funds available to the child are secured and used to reimburse the public taxpayer dollars that provide payment for the child's care. If the child's total income exceeds the cost of care, the excess is saved for the child," the agency helpfully explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jill Bauer, a staff attorney at Legal Services in Washtenaw County in Michigan, took a decidedly different view. "Why should kids with Social Security have to pay for their own foster care?" she asked rhetorically.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elisa Weichel, administrative director of the Child Advocacy Institute, even suggested that the state practice of taking federal money that belongs to foster children just reinforces to such children that they are viewed as possible revenue sources rather than as human beings. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We believe that the state is choosing to put its own financial interests above the best interests of the children in its care," Weichel told the Free Press, "which unfortunately is a message these children probably also get in other ways."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 20:38:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Last surviving Medal of Honor recipient from the Korean War lies in honor at US Capitol</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/last-surviving-medal-honor-recipient-korean-war-lies-honor-us-capitol</link><description>Col. Ralph Puckett, Jr., the last surviving Medal of Honor recipient from the Korean War, was honored with a ceremony in the Rotunda of the U.S. Capitol surrounded by family members.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 20:36:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>$7 Billion in Taxpayer Funds Went to Ivy League Universities With Anti-Israel Protests</title><link>https://redstate.com/wardclark/2024/04/29/waste-7-billion-in-taxpayer-funds-to-ivy-league-universities-with-anti-isreal-protests-n2173486</link><description>The post $7 Billion in Taxpayer Funds Went to Ivy League Universities With Anti-Israel Protests appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 21:22:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>72 Minutes Until the End of the World?</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/29/72_minutes_until_the_end_of_the_world_622698.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 19:39:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adeel Mangi Downplayed His Involvement With Anti-Israel Think Tank, Emails Show</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/adeel-mangi-downplayed-his-involvement-with-anti-israel-think-tank-emails-show-2668089402.html</link><image_url>https://freebeacon.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/Adeel_Abdullah_Mangi_cropped_736x514.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://freebeacon.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/Adeel_Abdullah_Mangi_cropped_736x514.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;During his confirmation hearing, embattled Biden judicial nominee Adeel Mangi told senators that he left the board of an anti-Israel think tank because it was not sufficiently "productive."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://freebeacon.com/biden-administration/adeel-mangi-downplayed-his-involvement-with-anti-israel-think-tank-emails-show/"&gt;Adeel Mangi Downplayed His Involvement With Anti-Israel Think Tank, Emails Show&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://freebeacon.com"&gt;Washington Free Beacon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 20:30:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>High-profile Dems victimized by string of crimes still deny blue state in crisis</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/high-profile-dems-victimized-string-crimes-still-deny-blue-state-crisis</link><description>Democrats remain divided on solutions to deter crime as a string of high-profile thefts and robbery attempts occurred in the last week of April.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 20:25:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Shares Video Claiming “Old Guard” Globalists Being Politically Destroyed</title><link>https://www.infowars.com/posts/trump-shares-video-claiming-old-guard-globalists-being-politically-destroyed/</link><description>The post Trump Shares Video Claiming “Old Guard” Globalists Being Politically Destroyed appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 21:22:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Plot to Wreck the Democratic Convention</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/29/the_plot_to_wreck_the_democratic_convention_622697.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 19:38:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2 illegal aliens arrested in largest fentanyl bust in Florida county's history: 'Didn't come here to better themselves'</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/2-illegal-aliens-arrested-in-largest-fentanyl-bust-in-florida-county-s-history-didn-t-come-here-to-better-themselves-2668089444.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52133205&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C40%2C0%2C40</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52133205&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C40%2C0%2C40" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52133202&amp;amp;width=600&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=344,0,216,0 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg%3Fid%3D52133202%26width%3D600%26height%3D600%26coordinates%3D344%2C0%2C216%2C0%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Polk County Sheriff's Office in Florida recently announced the "single-largest" fentanyl bust in the county's history, the department revealed in a Friday press conference, &lt;a href="https://www.fox13news.com/news/grady-judd-multiple-people-arrested-as-deputies-make-largest-fentanyl-seizure-in-polk-county-history" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;WTVT&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; reported.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sheriff's office launched the investigation into the illicit operation in August after it learned about an organized drug trafficking operation based out of Mexico. The department arrested four individuals in connection with the scheme and seized 14 kilograms of fentanyl, two vehicles, and $5,261 in cash. Two of the suspected criminals, Pedro Rodriguez Correa and Maria Machuca-Alderete, were in the country illegally, according to Polk County Sheriff Grady Judd. The other two individuals, Maria Guadalupe-Garcia and Sergio Garcia, were from California.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It seems like every time I come up here to talk about fentanyl with my colleagues I'm always saying, 'It's the largest fentanyl seizure in the state of Florida' and, once again, that's what I'm saying today with a seizure of 14 kilos of fentanyl," Judd stated Friday morning. "This is the single-largest seizure in the history of Polk County and that's nothing to be proud of."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the detained suspects, Guadalupe-Garcia, told deputies that she did not know anything about the narcotics and claimed to be delivering a box of diapers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"When was the last time you picked up a box of Huggies that weighed 27 pounds? Maria, we don't have any Huggies in the county jail, but we will have you there," Judd said, according to WTVT.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"They didn't come here to better themselves and their family," he continued, referring to the two illegal migrants. "They came here to kill people in America with a deadly drug through a porous border that we need to seal off."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Judd, the amount of drugs seized in the bust is enough to kill one-third of Florida's population. He stated that the traffickers expected to be paid $42,500 for the delivery from Mexico to Florida. In total, the 14 kilogram shipment was worth $3.5 million, the office reported.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the sheriff's office, Rodriguez-Correa, the driver for the criminal organization, brought a six-year-old boy along for the fentanyl delivery. The Florida Department of Children and Families seized custody of the child.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Immigration and Customs Enforcement has placed a detainer on Machuca-Alderete and Rodriguez-Correa for being in the country illegally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Machuca-Alderete was charged with trafficking fentanyl, maintaining a vehicle to traffic illegal drugs, resisting arrest with violence, battery on an officer, unlawful use of a two-way communication device, and possession of drug paraphernalia, WTVT reported. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rodriguez-Correa was charged with trafficking fentanyl, unlawful use of a two-way communication device, and possession of drug paraphernalia, according to the outlet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Guadalupe-Garcia and Sergio Garcia were both charged with trafficking fentanyl, maintaining a vehicle to traffic illegal drugs, and possession of drug paraphernalia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A fifth suspect, whose identity has not been released to the public, is still at large and wanted for similar charges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Florida Attorney General Ashley Moody said during the Friday news conference, "I would submit to you that an appropriate response would not just be, 'We are going to address the cartels with hugs, not violence.' But how about how I have demanded and suggested in that we declare the cartels terrorist organizations and we designate fentanyl as a weapon of mass destruction."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Over the past year, the PCSO seized 30 additional kilograms of fentanyl - about enough to kill all the people in the state of Florida," according to the sheriff's office.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sign up here&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 20:20:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New poll reveals which party is more enthusiastic about Biden-Trump rematch</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/republicans-much-more-enthusiastic-trump-biden-rematch-democrats-independents</link><description>A new poll says Republicans are significantly more enthusiastic about the 2024 election rematch between President Biden and former President Donald Trump than either Democrats or independent voters</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 19:20:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>“Bigger Than the Holocaust”: British MP Says 10-20 Million People Were Killed by Covid “Vaccines”</title><link>https://www.infowars.com/posts/bigger-than-the-holocaust-british-mp-says-10-20-million-people-were-killed-by-covid-vaccines/</link><description>The post “Bigger Than the Holocaust”: British MP Says 10-20 Million People Were Killed by Covid “Vaccines” appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 20:39:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dr. Patesky: Is Bird Flu the Next Global Pandemic?</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2024/04/29/the_unknowns_bird_flu_the_next_global_pandemic.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 19:33:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FACT CHECK: Did Harvard University Replace The US Flag With Palestinian Flag?</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/fact-check-did-harvard-university-replace-the-us-flag-with-palestinian-flag-2668088970.html</link><image_url>https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Harvard-4-e1541001851903.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Harvard-4-e1541001851903.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The flag was raised by protesters at the campus and was not sanctioned by the school administration</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 20:06:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden admin accuses Israeli military of human rights violations in stunning condemnation</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/biden-admin-accuses-israeli-military-human-rights-violations-stunning-condemnation</link><description>State Department says five IDF units committed human rights violations and while four "effectively remediated," the discussion still continue over the fifth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 18:47:51 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>