<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 22:03:39 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Dementia Joe Is Going to Throw a Fit When He Hears How the Teamsters Responded to Trump Invite</title><link>https://redstate.com/nick-arama/2024/06/21/biden-is-going-to-throw-a-fit-when-he-hears-about-teamsters-boss-response-to-trump-n2175787</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>The post Dementia Joe Is Going to Throw a Fit When He Hears How the Teamsters Responded to Trump Invite appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 03:03:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ted Cruz calls for death penalty if 2 illegal immigrants accused of killing 12-year-old girl are convicted</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/ted-cruz-calls-death-penalty-2-illegal-immigrants-accused-killing-12-year-old-girl-convicted</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>Sen. Ted Cruz said two illegal immigrants accused of killing a Houston girl this week should get the death penalty if they are convicted.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 23:50:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Terrorists Are Coming Through the Southern Border — and We Are Not Nearly Concerned Enough</title><link>https://harbingersdaily.com/terrorists-are-coming-through-the-southern-border-and-we-are-not-nearly-concerned-enough/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>The post Terrorists Are Coming Through the Southern Border — and We Are Not Nearly Concerned Enough appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 03:02:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Texas Lt. Gov. Dan Patrick pledges to pass Ten Commandments bill after Louisiana passes similar law</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/texas-lt-gov-dan-patrick-pledges-pass-ten-commandments-bill-louisiana-passes-similar-law</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>Texas Lt. Gov. Dan Patrick on Friday blamed a fellow Republican for not passing a law requiring public school classrooms to display the Ten Commandments.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 23:16:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Before FedEx Driver Makes it Back to Van, TWO Thugs Race Each Other to Steal Package [VIDEO]</title><link>https://rumble.com/v52zntw-before-fedex-driver-makes-it-back-to-van-two-thugs-race-each-other-to-steal.html</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>The post Before FedEx Driver Makes it Back to Van, TWO Thugs Race Each Other to Steal Package [VIDEO] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 03:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>US v Trump: First day of Florida hearing wraps in classified docs case</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/us-v-trump-first-day-florida-hearing-wraps-classified-docs-case</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>President Trump's legal team was in court Friday arguing that Special Counsel Jack Smith was appointed illegally, meaning that the classified documents case should be tossed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 21:23:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eco-Activist Wimp Who Vandalized Stonehenge Recounts Avoiding Eye Contact With Young American Dudes Who Were Making Fun of Him</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/eco-activist-wimp-who-vandalized-stonehenge-recounts-avoiding/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>(DCNF)—One of the Just Stop Oil protesters who vandalized Stonehenge on Wednesday said that American males taunted him at the site of the demonstration. The disruptive climate protest outfit — which indirectly receives funding from wealthy American liberals via a U.S.-based nonprofit — hosted a Friday Zoom call for Rajan Naidu, a 73-year-old activist for […] The post Eco-Activist Wimp Who Vandalized Stonehenge Recounts Avoiding Eye Contact With Young American Dudes Who Were Making Fun of Him appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 01:00:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fox News Politics: No Guns for Abusers</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/fox-news-politics-no-guns-abusers</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>The latest updates from the 2024 campaign trail, exclusive interviews and more Fox News politics content</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 21:21:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Judge Judy Unloads on Alvin Bragg for Trying Trump Over “Nonsense” Instead of Keeping Criminals “Off the Street”</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/judge-judy-unloads-alvin-bragg-trying-trump-nonsense/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>(DCNF)—Television star Judge Judy Sheindlin on Friday harshly criticized Manhattan District Attorney Alvin Bragg for prosecuting former President Donald Trump over what she considers “nonsense.” The Manhattan jury in Bragg’s case convicted Trump in late May of 34 felony counts of falsifying business documents to conceal a payment to porn star Stormy Daniels ahead of […] The post Judge Judy Unloads on Alvin Bragg for Trying Trump Over “Nonsense” Instead of Keeping Criminals “Off the Street” appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 01:00:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SCOTUS rejects woman's claim she has constitutional right to visa for husband with MS-13 ties</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/scotus-rejects-womans-claim-she-has-constitutional-right-visa-husband-ms-13-ties</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>An American citizen who sued to get her noncitizen MS-13-member husband a visa has no constitutional liberty interest to such a lawsuit, the Supreme Court ruled Friday.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 20:59:32 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>