<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:39:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Study Finds “Significant Increase” in Cancer Mortality After 3rd Covid “Vaccine” Dose</title><link>https://ktrh.iheart.com/featured/houston-texas-news/content/2024-05-02-study-finds-significant-increase-in-cancer-mortality-after-3rd-covid-dose/</link><description>The post Study Finds “Significant Increase” in Cancer Mortality After 3rd Covid “Vaccine” Dose appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Joe Exotic tells ALL from PRISON: Netflix EXPLOITED feud with Carole Baskin; the two never even met</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/joe-exotic-tells-all-from-prison-netflix-exploited-feud-with-carole-baskin-the-two-never-even-met-2668189768.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52191065&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C120</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52191065&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C120" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52191062&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;coordinates=300,0,0,0 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg%3Fid%3D52191062%26width%3D1200%26height%3D800%26coordinates%3D300%2C0%2C0%2C0%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alex Stein was lucky enough to score an interview with the wild Joe Exotic from jail — and it did not disappoint.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But this isn’t his first interview, as Exotic has been seriously making the rounds. Through doing so, he has learned a bit about his old arch nemesis Carole Baskin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I did one with the news station out of Tampa, and they interviewed Carole right before they interviewed me, and she is now even saying on television that Netflix exploited the feud that we had going on,” Exotic tells Stein.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Exotic, Baskin told the news station that the two “had never met” and the “feud wasn’t as bad as Netflix portrayed it to be.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Exotic went on to tell Stein that there was a double agent named Ashley working at his park who had gone undercover for Carole.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“She was the one that was testifying on Carole for Carole at my trial, but they wouldn’t let her because they caught her lying, so she never got to testify. But yeah, she’s Carole’s informant,” Exotic says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Stein was setting up the interview, he had an exchange with Howard Baskin. Baskin told Stein “there are no hard feelings” between him an Exotic, but he still thinks “he’s a liar.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It would be really nice if just one person in the interview media profession actually challenged Joe on all his lies instead of just letting him blather on with nodding heads,” Howard wrote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I don’t know what Howard wants me to admit to. I’ve admitted to shooting the Tigers; I don’t know what else to admit to. But I didn’t pay Allen to go kill Carole,” Exotic says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Well, and I appreciate that,” Stein says. “That’s why I have your back.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Exotic has a message for his old friends.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“What I need them to realize though, is in order to move on, they got to remember that I’m a human being, and my parents died, and I’m no longer going to own animals, and it needs to be over. But it doesn’t need to be over that they can move on with their free life, and Joseph finishes a 21-year prison sentence for something he didn’t do,” he tells Stein.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I think that’s fair,” Stein says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Want more from Alex Stein?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;To enjoy more of Alex's culture jamming, comedic monologues, skits, and street segments, &lt;a href="https://get.blazetv.com/primetime/?utm_source=theblaze&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_campaign=article_shortcode_alexstein" target="_blank"&gt;subscribe to BlazeTV&lt;/a&gt; — the largest multi-platform network of voices who love America, defend the Constitution, and live the American dream.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:18:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GOP rebels back off threat to force Johnson ouster vote this week as they seek deal</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/gop-rebels-back-off-threat-force-johnson-ouster-vote-week-seek-deal</link><description>Reps. Marjorie Taylor Greene and Thomas Massie are in talks with Speaker Johnson as they threaten to force a vote on his ouster.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:10:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Leftists Don’t Quit, They Just Rebrand</title><link>https://patriotpost.us/articles/106583-leftists-dont-quit-they-just-rebrand-2024-05-07</link><description>The post Leftists Don’t Quit, They Just Rebrand appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:36:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PLUMMETING birth rates keep Elon Musk up at night</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/plummeting-birth-rates-keep-elon-musk-up-at-night-2668189695.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52191054&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C120</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52191054&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C120" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52191051&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;coordinates=254,0,46,0 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg%3Fid%3D52191051%26width%3D1200%26height%3D800%26coordinates%3D254%2C0%2C46%2C0%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;How do we solve the crises that are currently burdening America?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While Dave Rubin knows there are “some political ways,” like how “a certain orange man would be better than a certain man with dementia,” there are some more important, more tangible ways that are in your control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s find a mate and have a family. Start the basic building blocks of society, bottom up. The way your parents did it and your grandparents did it,” Rubin explains, adding, “the way civilization has done it for millennia.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If you start building a good family, you might be able to save civilization,” he says, and he’s not alone in his belief.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk recently explained a similar concept to the Milken Institute after being asked what brings him joy and what keeps him up at night.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I probably get the most joy from my kids, and I’m not saying that’s the reason to have kids because we should have them anyway, but certainly kids are the greatest source of joy in my life,” he answered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In terms of what keeps me up at night, I guess it’s anything that’s, like, I think a civilizational risk,” he said, adding, “The birth rates continuing to plummet. I do think about the birth rates plummeting as being a civilizational risk.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Want more from Dave Rubin?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;To enjoy more honest conversations, free speech, and big ideas with Dave Rubin, &lt;a href="https://get.blazetv.com/dave/?utm_source=theblaze&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_campaign=article_shortcode_daverubin" target="_blank"&gt;subscribe to BlazeTV&lt;/a&gt; — the largest multi-platform network of voices who love America, defend the Constitution, and live the American dream.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:15:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NPR CEO Katherine Maher declines House hearing invite amid bias scandal</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/npr-ceo-katherine-maher-declines-house-hearing-invite-bias-scandal</link><description>NPR CEO Katherine Maher won't be testifying before a House committee on Wednesday as requested.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 20:59:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The White House Is Scrambling to Trump-Proof Traitor Joe’s Regulations in Order to Hinder Trump’s Second Term</title><link>https://amgreatness.com/2024/05/07/report-biden-white-house-trying-to-force-new-regulations-to-hinder-second-trump-presidency/</link><description>The post The White House Is Scrambling to Trump-Proof Traitor Joe’s Regulations in Order to Hinder Trump’s Second Term appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:36:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Professional Women's Hockey League has sports fans hoping other leagues will steal its unique opponent-picking rule</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/professional-women-s-hockey-league-has-sports-fans-hoping-other-leagues-will-steal-its-unique-opponent-picking-rule-2668189692.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/professional-women-s-hockey-league-has-sports-fans-hoping-other-leagues-will-steal-its-unique-opponent-picking-rule.jpg?id=52190485&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C171</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/professional-women-s-hockey-league-has-sports-fans-hoping-other-leagues-will-steal-its-unique-opponent-picking-rule.jpg?id=52190485&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C171" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/professional-women-s-hockey-league-has-sports-fans-hoping-other-leagues-will-steal-its-unique-opponent-picking-rule.jpg?id=52190484&amp;amp;width=1024&amp;amp;height=535&amp;amp;coordinates=0,0,0,148 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/professional-women-s-hockey-league-has-sports-fans-hoping-other-leagues-will-steal-its-unique-opponent-picking-rule.jpg%3Fid%3D52190484%26width%3D1024%26height%3D535%26coordinates%3D0%2C0%2C0%2C148%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Professional Women's Hockey League has garnered a respectable amount of fanfare in its first year in existence, but a unique playoff rule is grabbing the attention of fans across the world who want to see it implemented for their preferred league or sport.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The PWHL was hot out of the gates with more than 170,000 views on the &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aKMWI-8Tl_8" target="_blank"&gt;livestream&lt;/a&gt; of its inaugural game in January 2024 and completed its six-team, 24-game season by early May.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Heading into the playoffs, fans are noticing a unique rule that allows the number-one seeded team to choose its opponent out of the last two playoff-qualifying  teams.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the PWHL can only make minimal use of the rule given that just four teams make the playoffs, it isn't hard to imagine this implemented in the NHL, NBA, or NFL, where teams would be seriously looking to avoid top-ranked teams in the first round of the playoffs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inversely, it would create a bit more competition at the top in order to gain the right to choose who to play in the first round. It could be tinkered with to allow a choice of any of the bottom-ranked teams, or perhaps simply any team that doesn't win its division.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;div&gt;PWHL Toronto has clinched the #1 overall seed in the playoffs and will get to choose their opponent!\n\n#PWHL | @PWHL_Toronto&lt;/div&gt; —  (@)        &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/TSN_Sports/status/1785845229863530892"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;It would also be very insulting to a team that was picked, creating an immediate level of animosity between the two opponents.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the PWHL, Toronto won the right to choose its opponent and went with Minnesota.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Oh no, I see this being a very Toronto style outcome," a fan wrote on &lt;a href="https://x.com/kylebechtold3/status/1785848639564181654" target="_blank"&gt;X&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The lore here is, of course, that Toronto sports teams have a way of failing in spectacular fashion, a prime example of that was showcased two days after the fan's comment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; The NHL's Toronto Maple Leafs found themselves down 3-1 in the best-of-seven series against rival Boston Bruins. After winning two games to force a game seven, the Leafs went ahead in the third period for a little over a minute, only to be scored on and then &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=01j2xnnSmuM" target="_blank"&gt;quickly lose in overtime&lt;/a&gt; after a wild bounce of the puck.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moments like this would be even more spectacular with the help of the playoff seeding rule.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;Oh no, I see this being a very Toronto style outcome.....&lt;br /&gt;— Kyle Bechtold (@kylebechtold3) &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/kylebechtold3/status/1785848639564181654?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;May 2, 2024&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One NHL fan &lt;a href="https://x.com/philfparkinson/status/1769744151057252529" target="_blank"&gt;suggested&lt;/a&gt; the new rule to long-time analyst Dave Hodge after the reporter was playing around with a few ideas of his own.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"To add more late-season NHL interest: Award 5 home games to division winners in the 1st playoff round, and 5 home games in every playoff round to the Presidents’ Trophy winners. Currently, the race for 1st overall finds 8 teams separated by 5 pts. Fun, no?" Hodge wrote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Allow seeding to order them to choose opponents in the playoffs," the fan &lt;a href="https://x.com/philfparkinson/status/1769744151057252529" target="_blank"&gt;replied&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;div&gt;@davehodge20 Like PWHL, allow seeding to order them to choose opponent in playoffs.&lt;/div&gt; —  (@)        &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/philfparkinson/status/1769744151057252529"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;ESPN's Greg Wyshynski disagreed with the rule and said that, through testing, it has usually resulted in the expected seeding. "I love 90% of the PWHL rule changes. Can't win 'em all," he &lt;a href="https://x.com/wyshynski/status/1762970998809223668" target="_blank"&gt;wrote&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;Picking your opponent is exciting in theory but whenever it's been tested, it usually results in the expected seeding.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Gold Plan is just dumb but maybe works for a league with so few teams. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I love 90% of the PWhL rule changes. Can't win'em all.&lt;br /&gt;— Greg Wyshynski (@wyshynski) &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/wyshynski/status/1762970998809223668?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;February 28, 2024&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the very least, the rule has done what the league has hoped and created intrigue and discussion around its style of play. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As of late, much of the internet was focused on the league's "&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/theshift_sports/status/1753118230313410881" target="_blank"&gt;diversity, equity, and inclusion&lt;/a&gt;." The league was pushing it so hard that a fan reported attendees at a game in Ottawa were directed to &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/MichelleAlleva/status/1783490673309622646" target="_blank"&gt;recite a diversity statement&lt;/a&gt; before the game as it was displayed on the video arena's video screen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;.&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden plan to extend ObamaCare eligibility to illegal immigrants gets pushback in Congress: 'Madness'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/biden-plan-extend-obamacare-eligibility-illegal-immigrants-pushback-congress-madness</link><description>Rep. Nancy Mace is introducing a resolution of disapproval to oppose a Biden administration rule to grant ObamaCare to some illegal immigrants protected by a 2012 order.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 20:48:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bribery Biden’s “Model Citizens” and Ultra Rich Donors</title><link>https://www.independentsentinel.com/joe-bidens-model-citizens-and-ultra-rich-donors/</link><description>The post Bribery Biden’s “Model Citizens” and Ultra Rich Donors appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:36:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Police release new details about the death of Mica Miller after sister alleges ominous warning made before death</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/police-release-new-details-about-the-death-of-mica-miller-after-sister-alleges-ominous-warning-made-before-death-2668189610.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52190739&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C6%2C0%2C42</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52190739&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C6%2C0%2C42" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52190735&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0,0,0,48 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg%3Fid%3D52190735%26width%3D1200%26height%3D600%26coordinates%3D0%2C0%2C0%2C48%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Authorities have released new information about the death of Mica Miller.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miller's death &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/police-investigate-death-mica-miller" target="_blank"&gt;gained national attention last week&lt;/a&gt; after her husband — John-Paul Miller, a pastor in Myrtle Beach, South Carolina — announced Miller's sudden death at his church after giving a routine sermon. John-Paul claimed that his 30-year-old wife committed suicide the day before.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Mica's family and friends brought scrutiny to Pastor Miller's story. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to them, Mica had suffered abuse and was in the process of divorcing John-Paul. Public records confirmed that Mica had initiated divorce proceedings last year. The Horry County Police Department later &lt;a href="https://mynbc15.com/news/nation-world/mica-miller-john-paul-jp-pastors-wife-tracking-device-stalking-solid-rock-church-death-investigation-suicide-police-report-tire-gps-east-coast-honda-dealership-myrtle-beach-south-carolina" target="_blank"&gt;confirmed&lt;/a&gt; that Mica had filed two police reports in March alleging her tires had been slashed, a tracking device had been placed on her car, and she had been the victim of "strange activity," such as people following and watching her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those police reports redact the suspect's name but confirm that Mica told officers she "was afraid for her life."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But on Monday, Robeson County Medical Examiner Dr. Richard Johnson ruled that Mica had died of a suicide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Based on the nature of the wound, that it is consistent with a self-inflicted gunshot wound. And it was not in the back of the head, as it has been speculated," Johnson &lt;a href="https://wpde.com/news/local/mica-miller-cause-of-death-suicide-self-inflicted-gunshot-wound-nc-robeson-county-medical-examiner-pastor-john-paul-jp-wife-solid-rock-church-myrtle-beach-dr-richard-johnson-harassment-reports-south-carolina" target="_blank"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Tuesday, the Robeson County Sheriff's Office &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/rcso3100/posts/pfbid021Mmt56BtGgbnymh5tM9nbBbR6HNxeXceSrvJWWoSdHsBpwEVqv4WW76xVCs9fD9Tl?__cft__%5B0%5D=AZUM6upAC2aG5gZV-V4gLp7t4GJktnsmLlRUPwPXOoXsttS1FBxOizHwFZBKfQ3apYP5gDR4oIEAfOWAxEkt92-JSEMSkMGzDkn-28Mj7Udp2eTTxONK7ab2GwSrZY6acqRYJBJ2niD0aZYiHIIUi29prEHAk_LSjtnMGSPJuERTjQvb0Hgoycx0nw6Z_ukDKUBRK1T1ClMQwHvkdrolWJY5&amp;amp;__tn__=%2CO%2CP-R" target="_blank"&gt;released additional details&lt;/a&gt; about the events leading up to Mica's death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investigators said that Mica purchased a handgun at a pawn shop in Myrtle Beach on Saturday, April 27, and then drove to Lumber River State Park in North Carolina. They said she then called 911 and informed a dispatcher of plans to kill herself. After she hung up, dispatchers found Mica's location and dispatched officers to respond. Officers later discovered Mica's body and the handgun she purchased earlier in the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Importantly, investigators confirmed the whereabouts of John-Paul "and a female that he is allegedly romantically involved with."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The RCSO explained:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;Investigators were able to confirm that both individuals were not in North Carolina on the night before and the day of the Miller’s death. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Investigators learned through interviews that John Paul Miller was at an athletic event in Charleston on the day of Mica Miller’s death. John Miller’s vehicle was observed traveling on Hwy 17 Bypass, in Horry County at 2:22 pm on April 27, 2024. The investigation confirmed that John Miller was accompanied while traveling to and from the event in Charleston, SC.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, questions remain after Mica's sister submitted a sworn affidavit to the probate court last Thursday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sierra Francis told the court that Mica had suffered "abuse and violence" at the hands of John-Paul while detailing the alleged actions John-Paul took against Mica in the months leading up to her death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"My sister was hopeful for her future after filing for divorce from John-Paul," Francis wrote. "My sister also expressed to me that she was fearful that she would not make it to the divorce and that her life would be taken from her. It is my belief, based on conversations with my sister, that she told multiple people, including other family members."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Mica stated to me on many occasions, 'if I end up with a bullet in my head, it was not by me, it was JP,'" Francis said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;         —  (@)        &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/Protestia/status/1787319801825673723"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Despite the suspicious circumstances, Robeson County Sheriff Burnis Wilkins said Tuesday the evidence of a suicide is "quite clear and compelling."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There are many factors that we have reviewed that occurred over an extended period of time that are probably related to the reason for this investigation, but in the end, sadly, a tragic decision was made by Mica that ended her life," he &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/rcso3100/posts/pfbid021Mmt56BtGgbnymh5tM9nbBbR6HNxeXceSrvJWWoSdHsBpwEVqv4WW76xVCs9fD9Tl?__cft__%5B0%5D=AZUM6upAC2aG5gZV-V4gLp7t4GJktnsmLlRUPwPXOoXsttS1FBxOizHwFZBKfQ3apYP5gDR4oIEAfOWAxEkt92-JSEMSkMGzDkn-28Mj7Udp2eTTxONK7ab2GwSrZY6acqRYJBJ2niD0aZYiHIIUi29prEHAk_LSjtnMGSPJuERTjQvb0Hgoycx0nw6Z_ukDKUBRK1T1ClMQwHvkdrolWJY5&amp;amp;__tn__=%2CO%2CP-R" target="_blank"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New poll reveals what voters think will happen in NY vs Trump</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/nearly-two-thirds-voters-believe-trump-convicted-some-charges-criminal-trial</link><description>Nearly two-thirds of voters say former President Trump will be found guilty on some charges in his unprecedented criminal trial in New York City, according to a new national poll</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 20:17:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>“We Get Paid to Vaccinate Your Children”: Pediatrician Reveals Details of Big Pharma Payola Scheme</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/we-get-paid-vaccinate-your-children-pediatrician-reveals/</link><description>(The Defender)—Can pediatricians afford to run their medical practices without the generous kickbacks they receive for vaccinating every child? Dr. Paul Thomas, a Dartmouth-trained pediatrician, discussed this dilemma during an April 16 interview with Polly Tommey on Children’s Health Defense’s “Vax-Unvax: The People’s Study” bus tour. “You cannot stay in business if you’re not giving […]
The post “We Get Paid to Vaccinate Your Children”: Pediatrician Reveals Details of Big Pharma Payola Scheme appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Democrat Party’s Antisemitism Went Mainstream With Barack Obama</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/the-democrat-partys-antisemitism-went-mainstream-with-barack-obama-2668189527.html</link><image_url>https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/7811066966_e1aa6d0cb2_k.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/7811066966_e1aa6d0cb2_k.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img class="rm-shortcode" id="c2a66" src="https://www.conservativereview.com/media-library/eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpbWFnZSI6Imh0dHBzOi8vdGhlZmVkZXJhbGlzdC5jb20vd3AtY29udGVudC91cGxvYWRzLzIwMjQvMDUvNzgxMTA2Njk2Nl9lMWFhNmQwY2IyX2stMTIwMHg2NzUuanBnIiwiZXhwaXJlc19hdCI6MTc3MjUwNjUyM30.Vfa2NXGWozUq0qa1PZ382JU3-toIbe7LYVsFSrt_g7M/image.jpg" /&gt;Obama's embrace of antisemites is responsible for the anti-Israel radicalism rampant among Democrats today.&lt;/span&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 20:45:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anti-Israel encampments share common traits with Marxist revolutionaries, BLM and the KKK</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/anti-israel-encampments-share-common-traits-marxist-revolutionaries-blm-kkk</link><description>The anti-Israel demonstrations sweeping American college campuses share similar traits to Mao's Cultural Revolution and the Black Lives Matter movement.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 19:51:36 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>