<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:50:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Russia Warns That American Nuclear Weapons in Poland Would Be Priority Military Target</title><link>https://www.infowars.com/posts/us-nuclear-weapons-in-poland-would-be-priority-military-target-moscow/</link><description>The post Russia Warns That American Nuclear Weapons in Poland Would Be Priority Military Target appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:35:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Tricky Judgments on When To Loosen</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/25/the_tricky_judgments_on_when_to_loosen_622382.html</link><description>An ECB interest rate cut soon would make sense but the Fed faces a more difficult call in the US</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 15:19:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>US Economy Sees Low Growth, High Inflation in Q1</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/us-economy-sees-low-growth-high-inflation-in-q1-2667879075.html</link><image_url>https://freebeacon.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/biden-illegal.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://freebeacon.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/biden-illegal.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. economic growth in the first quarter fell below the Federal Reserve's estimates of the economy's long-run potential for the first time in nearly two years, but the signs of slowing were accompanied with fast inflation that, if sustained, would pose a particular dilemma for the central bank.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://freebeacon.com/latest-news/us-economy-sees-low-growth-high-inflation-in-q1/"&gt;US Economy Sees Low Growth, High Inflation in Q1&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://freebeacon.com"&gt;Washington Free Beacon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:05:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NYPD responds to AOC, says officers 'have to teach' anti-Israel mobs the 'consequences of their actions'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/nypd-responds-aoc-says-officers-have-teach-anti-israel-mobs-consequences-their-actions</link><description>The New York Police Department responded to Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez after she criticized Columbia University for allowing law enforcement personnel on campus.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:39:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>At “Women for Sherrod Brown” Event, Progressive Hosts Slam Trump and “Heteronormal Men”</title><link>https://freebeacon.com/democrats/at-women-for-sherrod-brown-event-progressive-hosts-slam-trump-and-heteronormal-men/</link><description>The post At “Women for Sherrod Brown” Event, Progressive Hosts Slam Trump and “Heteronormal Men” appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:30:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Secret Service Scuffle Prompts DEI, Vetting Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2024/04/25/secret_service_scuffle_prompts_dei_vetting_scrutiny__150846.html</link><description>An incident involving a physical attack by a female Secret Service agent tasked with protecting Vice President Kamala Harris is raising questions about whether the agency had thoroughly vetted her during her hiring and whether an ongoing push to increase the numbers of women in the service and boost overall workforce staff played a role in her selection.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 15:11:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jerry Seinfeld's Pop-Tarts movie will feature a January 6 parody, but he's convinced the movie industry is dead anyway</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/jerry-seinfeld-s-pop-tarts-movie-will-feature-a-january-6-parody-but-he-s-convinced-the-movie-industry-is-dead-anyway-2667879061.html</link><image_url>https://img.youtube.com/vi/2lqRPUhPfho/maxresdefault.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/jerry-seinfeld-s-pop-tarts-movie-will-feature-a-january-6-parody-but-he-s-convinced-the-movie-industry-is-dead-anyway.png?id=52102908&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;coordinates=0,0,149,0 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/jerry-seinfeld-s-pop-tarts-movie-will-feature-a-january-6-parody-but-he-s-convinced-the-movie-industry-is-dead-anyway.png%3Fid%3D52102908%26width%3D1200%26height%3D800%26coordinates%3D0%2C0%2C149%2C0%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jerry Seinfeld's movie about breakfast treat Pop-Tarts was revealed to feature a scene reminiscent of January 6, 2021.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The scene in the breakfast-food-centric movie "Unfrosted" was revealed in an interview with Seinfeld in &lt;a href="https://www.gq.com/story/jerry-seinfeld-gq-hype" target="_blank"&gt;GQ&lt;/a&gt;, where he was briefly asked about politics and the film.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The outlet's Brett Martin described the scene as a very funny &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/search/?q=january+6" target="_blank"&gt;January 6&lt;/a&gt; parody, which was a little surprising given Seinfeld's history of being completely devoid of public political opinions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He also asked the comedian about a recent trip to Israel, which reportedly took place a few weeks before Hamas' October 7, 2023, attack on Israelis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seinfeld skipped over the January 6 question, responding to the latter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Well, I'm Jewish."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seinfeld responded to pro-Palestine activists who &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/jerry-seinfeld-hassled-by-anti-israel-protesters-outside-jewish-community-center-in-nyc-you-support-genocide" target="_blank"&gt;harassed him&lt;/a&gt; and called him a "genocide supporter" outside a New York City event.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It never crossed my mind that people would look at me as anything other than, 'I like this comedian. I don't like this comedian.' I think most Jews of my generation never thought about anti-Semitism. It was from history books. And then it was something different. It was something different."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When asked if he regretted his trip, Seinfeld responded by saying "not at all."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I don’t preach about it. I have my personal feelings about it that I discuss privately. It's not part of what I can do comedically, but my feelings are very strong."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The longtime stand-up comic also revealed his belief that the movie industry is on its last legs. When describing how the people he worked with on "Unfrosted" were "so dead serious," he added that they didn't have "any idea that the movie business is over. They have no idea."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Film doesn't occupy the pinnacle in the social, cultural hierarchy that it did for most of our lives. When a movie came out, if it was good, we all went to see it. We all discussed it. We quoted lines and scenes we liked," he continued.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seinfeld compared seeing a movie now to "walking through a fire hose of water."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When asked what is replacing the movie industry, he couldn't help but provide emotional descriptions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Depression? Malaise? I would say confusion. Disorientation replaced the movie business. Everyone I know in show business, every day, is going, 'What's going on? How do you do this? What are we supposed to do now?'"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Pop-Tart movie was born out of boredom, the "Seinfeld" star recalled, stating in an interview with "&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ttKHIBkZNN4" target="_blank"&gt;Good Morning America&lt;/a&gt;" that he was pushed into the idea during COVID-19. He and fellow writer Spike Feresten decided to write a script to steady their idle hands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seinfeld decided he would also direct the movie when he realized it would be an easier process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I can just tell the guys what to do instead of telling the guy to tell the guy what to do. That was the idea. It's still a lot of work," he joked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cutting room floor for "Unfrosted" apparently included a story arc with "Seinfeld" costar Michael Richards, who would have played the father of the main character in the Pop-Tart movie.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I actually had a great thing for him in the movie," Seinfeld explained. "He was going to play my father. We wanted to come up with a tragic childhood story that made me want to invent the Pop-Tart, and it was going to be the death of my father trying to make bacon and eggs. But it didn't survive."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 15:57:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tennessee House tables bill that would have banned consideration of reparations</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/tennessee-house-tables-bill-banned-consideration-reparations</link><description>The TN House tabled until next year legislation that would have banned local governments from paying to study or distribute money for reparations for slavery.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:15:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cashless Society: WEF Boasts That 98% of Central Banks Are Adopting CBDCs</title><link>https://www.zerohedge.com/economics/cashless-society-wef-boasts-98-central-banks-are-adopting-cbdcs</link><description>The post Cashless Society: WEF Boasts That 98% of Central Banks Are Adopting CBDCs appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:25:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Katherine Maher's Color Revolution</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/25/katherine_mahers_color_revolution_622438.html</link><description>The NPR boss is a symbol of regime change-foreign and domestic.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 15:07:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FACT CHECK: Was John Mellencamp Booed Off Stage For Supporting Joe Biden?</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/fact-check-was-john-mellencamp-booed-off-stage-for-supporting-joe-biden-2667878916.html</link><image_url>https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/GettyImages-2149871375-scaled-e1713911275104.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/GettyImages-2149871375-scaled-e1713911275104.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mellencamp left the stage after a heckler interrupted a story about his grandmother</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 15:51:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dems attack Johnson over impassioned Columbia speech condemning anti-Israel student activists</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/dems-attack-johnson-impassioned-columbia-speech-condemning-anti-israel-student-activists</link><description>National Democrats are up in arms over House Speaker Mike Johnson's appearance at Columbia University on Thursday.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 15:32:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Drives the Wedge Where Traitor Joe Is Weak: “Biden Hates Israel, Hates Palestinians More!”</title><link>https://thenationalpulse.com/2024/04/25/trump-drives-the-wedge-biden-hates-israel-hates-palestinians-more/</link><description>The post Trump Drives the Wedge Where Traitor Joe Is Weak: “Biden Hates Israel, Hates Palestinians More!” appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:20:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kennedy Now Threatens Biden and Trump</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/25/kennedy_now_threatens_biden_and_trump_622452.html</link><description>For a while there, the independent ticket of ex-Democrats Robert F. Kennedy Jr. and Nicole Shanahan seemed to be taking crucial votes away from Democrat Joe Biden, at least as indicated by comparing three-way and five-way (with Cornel West and Jill Stein) polls to head-to-head matchups of the incumbent and Donald Trump.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 14:56:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WATCH: Gavin Newsom's new pro-abortion ad is so bad, it’s funny</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/watch-gavin-newsom-s-new-pro-abortion-ad-is-so-bad-its-funny-2667878907.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52103432&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C120</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52103432&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C120" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52103430&amp;amp;width=1245&amp;amp;height=700&amp;amp;coordinates=0,0,0,0 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg%3Fid%3D52103430%26width%3D1245%26height%3D700%26coordinates%3D0%2C0%2C0%2C0%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;While abortion is no laughing matter, Gavin Newsom’s latest pro-abortion – or in his words “reproductive care” – ad has Sara Gonzales in stitches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The commercial comes in unison with Newsom’s latest proposal that aims to pave the way for women in Arizona to seek abortions in California because the “mean red states … are making it harder for them to kill their babies,” mocks Sara.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Newsom’s ad, despite what you might think, “isn’t a parody … [or] SNL.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This is an actual ad released unironically from Gavin Newsom on abortion,” Sara prefaces.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While we don’t want to give away too many spoilers, know that the commercial features a pair of young girls being literally hunted down by a cop with a thick Southern accent, armed with both handcuffs &lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt; a pregnancy test?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It also includes the following statement: “Trump Republicans want to criminalize young Alabama women who travel for reproductive care.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blaze contributor Matthew Marsden is flabbergasted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“What are you thinking, you colossal bunch of morons?” he asks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To see Newsom’s commercial, watch the clip below.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Want more from Sara Gonzales?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;To enjoy more of Sara's no-holds-barred take to news and culture, &lt;a href="https://get.blazetv.com/?utm_source=theblaze&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_campaign=article_shortcode_saragonzalesunfiltered" target="_blank"&gt;subscribe to BlazeTV&lt;/a&gt; — the largest multi-platform network of voices who love America, defend the Constitution, and live the American dream.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 15:50:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump slams 'Bidenomics' ahead of court, claims to have a 'good chance' of winning liberal state</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-slams-bidenomics-ahead-court-claims-good-chance-winning-liberal-state</link><description>Former President Donald Trump slammed "Bidenomics," while touting he could win New York come November in comments Thursday morning ahead of entering the Manhattan courtroom.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 15:20:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Some Very Strange Things Are Happening With Voter Registration in Texas [VIDEO]</title><link>https://rumble.com/v4rhspr-some-very-strange-things-are-happening-with-voter-registration-in-texas.html</link><description>The post Some Very Strange Things Are Happening With Voter Registration in Texas [VIDEO] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 15:55:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Judge Points Out Biden DOJ's Hypocrisy, Double Standard</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/25/judge_points_out_biden_dojs_hypocrisy_double_standard_622464.html</link><description>Peter Navarro, a former Trump trade adviser, is sitting in jail for defying a subpoena from Nancy Pelosi's star chamber, the January 6 Committee.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 14:54:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jonathan Turley Says Alvin Bragg Is Making Trump’s Immunity Case ‘For Him’</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/jonathan-turley-says-alvin-bragg-is-making-trumps-immunity-case-for-him-2667878822.html</link><image_url>https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/DCNF-Turley-Bragg-SCOTUS-Immunity-Featured.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/DCNF-Turley-Bragg-SCOTUS-Immunity-Featured.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;'A highly political, in my view, legally absurd case'</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 15:40:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jewish Democrat calls out Bernie Sanders over opposition to Israel aid: 'Now do antisemitism'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/jewish-democrat-calls-out-bernie-sanders-opposition-israel-aid-now-antisemitism</link><description>Bernie Sanders faced criticism from a Jewish House Democrat, who asked him why he was "so quiet" about antisemitism as he opposed aid for Israel and cited his concern for the Palestinian people.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 15:19:08 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>