<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 13:15:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Prosecutors Claim Trump Violated Gag Order Again, Defense Says “This Is a Political Persecution”</title><link>https://www.theblaze.com/news/prosecutors-claim-trump-violated-gag-order-again-this-is-a-political-persecution-defense-says</link><description>The post Prosecutors Claim Trump Violated Gag Order Again, Defense Says “This Is a Political Persecution” appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 18:03:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Index Funds Need to Be Passive, Not Political</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/02/index_funds_need_to_be_passive_not_political_622876.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 18:13:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tampa Bay coach apologizes for 'an inappropriate analogy' after cries of sexism — says complaints hurt more than playoff loss</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/tampa-bay-coach-apologizes-for-an-inappropriate-analogy-after-cries-of-sexism-says-complaints-hurt-more-than-playoff-loss-2668133153.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/tampa-bay-coach-apologizes-for-an-inappropriate-analogy-after-cries-of-sexism-says-complaints-hurt-more-than-playoff-loss.jpg?id=52160746&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C171</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/tampa-bay-coach-apologizes-for-an-inappropriate-analogy-after-cries-of-sexism-says-complaints-hurt-more-than-playoff-loss.jpg?id=52160746&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C171" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/tampa-bay-coach-apologizes-for-an-inappropriate-analogy-after-cries-of-sexism-says-complaints-hurt-more-than-playoff-loss.jpg?id=52160737&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;coordinates=0,0,0,1 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/tampa-bay-coach-apologizes-for-an-inappropriate-analogy-after-cries-of-sexism-says-complaints-hurt-more-than-playoff-loss.jpg%3Fid%3D52160737%26width%3D1200%26height%3D800%26coordinates%3D0%2C0%2C0%2C1%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Coach Jon Cooper apologized for offending anyone who didn't like his analogy about treating NHL goaltenders softly, as if they were wearing "skirts."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bench boss for the NHL's Tampa Bay Lightning said he was sorry for making relatively harmless remarks when he spoke about goals being called back in his team's playoff series against the Florida Panthers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Multiple goals were disallowed due to goalie interference, and Cooper commented on the goals following the team's &lt;a href="https://www.nhl.com/schedule/playoff-series/2024/series-a/lightning-vs-panthers" target="_blank"&gt;6-1 loss&lt;/a&gt; that eliminated them from the playoffs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If anyone's going to talk about this game they're going to talk about the goals that were taken away," Cooper &lt;a href="https://x.com/BallyLightning/status/1785138353869816244" target="_blank"&gt;began&lt;/a&gt;. "In this league where goals are a premium and how all we've done is make the rules for more goal scoring, that's what we've done."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Every year there seems to be something we tweak so more goals can be scored, and that's great. But, there's mandates and the words were to pull a goal off the board it has be unbelievably egregious. That's the standard to pull a goal off the board ... I couldn't find anything remotely egregious," the coach explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Net front battles aren't allowed anymore? The boxing out rules there are like prison rules in the playoffs, but it's not prison rules for the goalies? We might as well put skirts on them then if that's how it's going to be. I mean they have to battle through stuff too."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;div&gt;"We might has well put skirts on them then... I think we're letting the goalies off the hook."\n\nLightning coach Jon Cooper weighs in with his perspective on the two disallowed goals tonight and the impact those decisions had on the game.&lt;/div&gt; —  (@)        &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/BallyLightning/status/1785138353869816244"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;The throw-away comment did not fall on deaf ears, however, as vapid claims of sexism soon followed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Put skirts on them? Wow, that's some kind of misogyny. Coach, you should be better. Gross," one fan &lt;a href="https://x.com/jessmfla/status/1785144024573108726" target="_blank"&gt;responded&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ian Kennedy, writer for the Hockey News, called Cooper's comments "&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/IanKennedyCK/status/1785157897875300445" target="_blank"&gt;open sexism&lt;/a&gt;" that "just can’t be part of a head coach’s vernacular."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just a couple days later, Cooper opened a &lt;a href="https://x.com/Diandra_loux/status/1785701332470366713" target="_blank"&gt;press conference&lt;/a&gt; by apologizing for the remarks, and shockingly said the negative responses he received felt even worse than the playoff loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a "massive supporter" of women's hockey, Cooper said, "Quite frankly, it was wrong, and I've got to go explain myself to my [daughters]."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Anyway, I sincerely apologize to all I offended, it's pained me more than the actual series loss itself," he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;div&gt;Jon Cooper opens his presser addressing the \u201cgirls in skirts\u201d comment from Monday night. \n\nHe says this has been harder than the loss. #GoBolts&lt;/div&gt; —  (@)        &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/Diandra_loux/status/1785701332470366713"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;"Respect that Jon Cooper opened by addressing this. He’s always been great to deal with, so his comment surprised me. Addressing it head on, with sincerity, is the right approach," wrote betting podcaster &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/racheldoerrie/status/1785714674958303628" target="_blank"&gt;Rachel Doerrie&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A former professional football player in the CFL, &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/TroyWestwood/status/1785734897140666686" target="_blank"&gt;Troy Westwood&lt;/a&gt;, gave advice that men should try to be better "dudes."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Dear cavemen. Jon Cooper is by all accounts a good guy. He made a mistake. He apologized. He, like what all of us should be doing, strives to be a better dude. It’s easy. Try to be a better dude."&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 17:40:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden pressured to sanction China for role in US fentanyl crisis</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/biden-pressured-sanction-china-role-us-fentanyl-crisis</link><description>Rep. Jim Banks is unveiling new legislation to force the Biden administration to severely hike penalties against China and its allied actors over the U.S. fentanyl crisis.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 18:00:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Is the Way: School Superintendent Tells Satanists They Can “Go to Hell”</title><link>https://redstate.com/brandon_morse/2024/05/02/this-is-the-way-oklahoma-school-superintendent-tells-satanists-they-can-go-to-hell-n2173647</link><description>The post This Is the Way: School Superintendent Tells Satanists They Can “Go to Hell” appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 18:02:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Will Crony Capitalism Get Better or Worse If Trump Wins?</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/02/will_crony_capitalism_get_better_or_worse_if_trump_wins_622884.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 14:56:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Progressive Florida Dems Push To Cancel Fetterman Speech Over Support for Israel</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/progressive-florida-dems-push-to-cancel-fetterman-speech-over-support-for-israel-2668133053.html</link><image_url>https://freebeacon.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/congress-returns-to-capitol-hill-including-senators-mcconnell-and-fett.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://freebeacon.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/congress-returns-to-capitol-hill-including-senators-mcconnell-and-fett.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Florida's progressive Democratic caucus this week called on the Florida Democratic Party to cancel Sen. John Fetterman’s (D., Pa.) keynote speech at its 2024 Leadership Blue gala over his support for Israel since Hamas’s Oct. 7 terrorist attack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://freebeacon.com/latest-news/progressive-florida-dems-push-to-cancel-fetterman-speech-over-support-for-israel/"&gt;Progressive Florida Dems Push To Cancel Fetterman Speech Over Support for Israel&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://freebeacon.com"&gt;Washington Free Beacon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 17:35:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden calls Japan 'xenophobic' for not accepting many immigrants, compares to China, Russia</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/biden-calls-japan-xenophobic-not-accepting-many-immigrants-compares-china-russia</link><description>President Biden called the allied nation of Japan "xenophobic" during a speech on Wednesday, comparing the island country to rival powers China and Russia.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 17:20:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Man at George Washington University Protest Calls Byron Donalds a “Race Traitor” And “Uncle Tom”</title><link>https://legalinsurrection.com/2024/05/man-at-george-washington-u-protest-calls-rep-byron-donalds-race-traitor-and-uncle-tom/</link><description>The post Man at George Washington University Protest Calls Byron Donalds a “Race Traitor” And “Uncle Tom” appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 18:02:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>High Costs, Low ROI Take the Sheen Off College Education</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/02/high_costs_low_roi_take_the_sheen_off_college_education_622885.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 14:56:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Election Integrity Group Sues Minnesota, Wisconsin To End NVRA Transparency Exemption</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/election-integrity-group-sues-minnesota-wisconsin-to-end-nvra-transparency-exemption-2668133041.html</link><image_url>https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Screenshot-2024-05-01-at-10.07.04-PM-e1714659428638-1024x576.png</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Screenshot-2024-05-01-at-10.07.04-PM-e1714659428638-1024x576.png" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img class="rm-shortcode" id="62347" src="https://www.conservativereview.com/media-library/eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpbWFnZSI6Imh0dHBzOi8vdGhlZmVkZXJhbGlzdC5jb20vd3AtY29udGVudC91cGxvYWRzLzIwMjQvMDUvU2NyZWVuc2hvdC0yMDI0LTA1LTAxLWF0LTEwLjA3LjA0LVBNLWUxNzE0NjU5NDI4NjM4LTEyMDB4Njc1LnBuZyIsImV4cGlyZXNfYXQiOjE3Mjk5NTY5NDh9.0hceMexzPLa2XMlpYqZOiD46rkEw4S6ZCIrQ_QEgahE/image.png" /&gt;The lawsuits allege the carveouts for Minnesota and Wisconsin violate the principle of equal state sovereignty and should be declared invalid.&lt;/span&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 17:34:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>President Biden condemns violent anti-Israel protests, won't call up National Guard</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/president-biden-condemns-violent-anti-israel-protests-wont-call-national-guard</link><description>President Biden has broken his silence Thursday regarding the anti-Israel demonstrations that are roiling colleges and universities around the nation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:16:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Russian Space Nuclear Weapon Could Devastate Satellites in Low Earth Orbit</title><link>https://www.theepochtimes.com/us/russian-space-nuclear-weapon-could-devastate-satellites-in-low-earth-orbit-pentagon-official-5642113?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=TheLibertyDaily</link><description>The post Russian Space Nuclear Weapon Could Devastate Satellites in Low Earth Orbit appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 18:01:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cost of a Cashless Society: The Most Vulnerable Will Pay</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/02/cost_of_a_cashless_society_the_most_vulnerable_will_pay_622886.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 14:56:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Says States Shouldn’t Deploy National Guard Against Anti-Israel Protests</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/biden-says-states-shouldnt-deploy-national-guard-against-anti-israel-protests-2668132911.html</link><image_url>https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Screen-Shot-2024-05-02-at-11.36.25-AM-e1714664257174.png</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Screen-Shot-2024-05-02-at-11.36.25-AM-e1714664257174.png" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;'The protests have not changed his views on the conflict'</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 17:28:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump slams 'radical left lunatics' creating chaos on college campuses nationwide</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-slams-radical-left-lunatics-creating-chaos-college-campuses-nationwide</link><description>Former President Trump slammed the "radical left lunatics" on college campuses nationwide for creating chaos amid their protests against Israel.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 15:05:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chaos Ensues as Police Breached the “Gaza Solidarity Encampment” on UCLA’s Campus Making Arrests [VIDEO]</title><link>https://rumble.com/v4sulo5-chaos-insues-as-police-breached-the-gaza-solidarity-encampment-on-uclas-cam.html</link><description>The post Chaos Ensues as Police Breached the “Gaza Solidarity Encampment” on UCLA’s Campus Making Arrests [VIDEO] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 17:34:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Stock Market Could Be Calmer</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/02/the_stock_market_could_be_calmer_622852.html</link><description>The Fed's interference creates volatility and raises capital costs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 14:34:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>50 Cent will open a film studio in the Deep South, not Hollywood, to create 'stories that need to be told'</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/50-cent-will-open-a-film-studio-in-the-deep-south-not-hollywood-to-create-stories-that-need-to-be-told-2668133052.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/50-cent-will-open-a-film-studio-in-the-deep-south-not-hollywood-to-create-stories-that-need-to-be-told.jpg?id=52159758&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C16%2C0%2C171</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/50-cent-will-open-a-film-studio-in-the-deep-south-not-hollywood-to-create-stories-that-need-to-be-told.jpg?id=52159758&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C16%2C0%2C171" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/50-cent-will-open-a-film-studio-in-the-deep-south-not-hollywood-to-create-stories-that-need-to-be-told.jpg?id=52159746&amp;amp;width=1024&amp;amp;height=521&amp;amp;coordinates=0,15,0,163 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/50-cent-will-open-a-film-studio-in-the-deep-south-not-hollywood-to-create-stories-that-need-to-be-told.jpg%3Fid%3D52159746%26width%3D1024%26height%3D521%26coordinates%3D0%2C15%2C0%2C163%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rapper and entrepreneur Curtis "50 Cent" Jackson announced his production studio will be located in the South, marking yet another big name to move operations out of California.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jackson, who has produced movies and the successful television series "&lt;a href="https://www.imdb.com/title/tt3281796/" target="_blank"&gt;Power&lt;/a&gt;," will cut the ribbon of a new film studio in Shreveport, Louisiana.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"As someone who has always believed in the transformative power of music, film, and television, I'm beyond excited to introduce the expansion of my G-Unit Film &amp; Television through the launch of G-Unit Studios right here in Shreveport," Jackson said in comments to &lt;a href="https://www.foxbusiness.com/entertainment/50-cent-joins-mark-wahlberg-taking-movie-production-out-hollywood-to-heartland" target="_blank"&gt;Fox News&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;50 Cent has been acting, producing, and creating music videos for nearly two decades now, acting as executive producer for the first time in 2010 for film "&lt;a href="https://www.imdb.com/title/tt1449379/" target="_blank"&gt;Caught in the Crossfire&lt;/a&gt;." He then produced another movie that same year called "&lt;a href="https://www.imdb.com/title/tt1560954/" target="_blank"&gt;Gun&lt;/a&gt;," starring himself and Val Kilmer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;G-Unit Film &amp; Television is already credited with a documentary called "50 Cent: The New Breed" and the production of the aforementioned "Power."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"From the gritty narratives of the streets to the compelling stories that define our era, G-Unit has always been more than just entertainment; it's a platform for voices that need to be heard, stories that need to be told," he said, referring his rap group G-Unit, which is now his production house name.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jackson also explained that the idea of bringing the film studio to Shreveport wasn't simply a business decision, but a targeted commitment to "fostering talent, creating opportunities, and building a community that thrives through creativity and innovation."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We see Shreveport as a beacon of inspiration and creativity," he said about the city. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shreveport has a population of just under 200,000 and is about a three-hour drive from Dallas, Texas, and four hours from Baton Rouge, Louisiana.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;div&gt;You know the vibes Shreveport is gonna be booming \ud83d\udca5this summer \u2022 https://t.co/IH2wzn8Xov&lt;/div&gt; —  (@)        &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/50cent/status/1785281519122026758"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Shreveport Mayor Tom Arceneaux said that he and the city are excited to have the new studio in their back yard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This city's rich culture and talent provides the perfect backdrop for this endeavor. We are eager to collaborate with Mr. Jackson and G-Unit Film &amp; Television to bring captivating movies and entertainment to Shreveport and Caddo Parish."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;50 Cent's footprint has become wider and wider, especially with his charity work with the &lt;a href="https://gunityfoundation.org/g-story/" target="_blank"&gt;G-Unity Foundation&lt;/a&gt;. Charity work has seen Jackson travel to places like Houston, Texas; Somalia; and his hometown of Queens, New York, where he hands out Thanksgiving turkeys.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Team building and entrepreneurship are skills I learned along the way, but they are so important to develop early. I look forward to G-Unity supporting programs that are doing the crucial work of teaching kids to excel at life," Jackson said on the website.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 17:25:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anti-McCarthy GOP rebels distance themselves from push to oust Speaker Johnson</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/anti-mccarthy-gop-rebels-distance-themselves-push-oust-speaker-johnson</link><description>Seven of the eight House Republicans who ousted ex House Speaker Kevin McCarthy are still serving in Congress, and nearly all of them are outright opposed to ousting House Speaker Mike Johnson right now.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 15:03:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>