<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:50:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Donald Trump Litigator Alina Habba Brilliantly Trolls Ron Filipkowski – Avocado&gt;Celery [VIDEO]</title><link>https://rumble.com/v4rbwel-donald-trump-litigator-alina-habba-brilliantly-trolls-ron-filipkowski-avoca.html</link><description>The post Donald Trump Litigator Alina Habba Brilliantly Trolls Ron Filipkowski – Avocado&gt;Celery [VIDEO] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:46:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Young People Are Enraged, Opting Out of America</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2024/04/24/nyus_scott_galloway_for_the_first_time_in_american_history_30-year-olds_arent_doing_as_well_as_their_parents.html</link><description>NYU business school professor Scott Galloway talks to MSNBC's "Morning Joe" about why young people are struggling economically:</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:59:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AOC condemns calling cops over 'nonviolent demonstrations of young students.' Observers hit back with the facts.</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/aoc-condemns-calling-cops-over-nonviolent-demonstrations-of-young-students-observers-hit-back-with-the-facts-2667871495.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/aoc-condemns-calling-cops-over-nonviolent-demonstrations-of-young-students-observers-hit-back-with-the-facts.jpg?id=52093835&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C25%2C0%2C109</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/aoc-condemns-calling-cops-over-nonviolent-demonstrations-of-young-students-observers-hit-back-with-the-facts.jpg?id=52093835&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C25%2C0%2C109" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img class="rm-shortcode" id="54732" src="https://www.conservativereview.com/media-library/eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpbWFnZSI6Imh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnRoZWJsYXplLmNvbS9tZWRpYS1saWJyYXJ5L2FvYy1jb25kZW1ucy1jYWxsaW5nLWNvcHMtb3Zlci1ub252aW9sZW50LWRlbW9uc3RyYXRpb25zLW9mLXlvdW5nLXN0dWRlbnRzLW9ic2VydmVycy1oaXQtYmFjay13aXRoLXRoZS1mYWN0cy5qcGc_aWQ9NTIwOTM4MzQmYW1wO3dpZHRoPTk4MCIsImV4cGlyZXNfYXQiOjE3Mzk2MjI4Mzd9.lTJ3p_qQTRUFh8Ku_TYNLLdbNyHfX-6bqa7csd3lN_M/image.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Far-left U.S. Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.) not surprisingly appears to be fully backing the Hamas-loving, Israel-hating demonstrations that have been springing up with greater frequency on college campuses in the last couple of weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In an X post Tuesday night, Ocasio-Cortez condemned calling police on what she deemed "nonviolent demonstrations of young students."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;         —  (@)        &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/AOC/status/1782943713053790629"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;"Calling in police enforcement on nonviolent demonstrations of young students on campus is an escalatory, reckless, and dangerous act," she &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/AOC/status/1782943713053790629" target="_blank"&gt;wrote&lt;/a&gt;. "It represents a heinous failure of leadership that puts people’s lives at risk. I condemn it in the strongest possible terms."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Surely, AOC realizes not all the protesters are "nonviolent," right? To wit:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Students &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/cal-poly-university-closes-after-apparently-violent-pro-hamas-activists-barricade-themselves-inside-campus-hall" target="_blank"&gt;took over a building&lt;/a&gt; at California State Polytechnic University in Humboldt, forcing the school to &lt;a href="https://krcrtv.com/north-coast-news/eureka-local-news/protestors-barricade-inside-cal-poly-humboldts-siemens-hall-arrests-made" target="_blank"&gt;close temporarily&lt;/a&gt; as a safety precaution. Andy Ngo reported that the occupiers turned to "beat[ing] and assault[ing]" cops who were trying to remove them.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/StopAntisemites/status/1782056834922078558" target="_blank"&gt;male pro-Palestinian protester&lt;/a&gt; stabbed a female Jewish student in the eye amid Yale University &lt;a href="https://www.thefp.com/p/i-was-stabbed-in-the-eye-at-yale" target="_blank"&gt;demonstrations&lt;/a&gt; over the weekend.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://columbiabarnardhillel.org/staff/elie-buechler/" target="_blank"&gt;Rabbi Elie Buechler&lt;/a&gt; of the Columbia University/Barnard College Hillel on Sunday &lt;a href="https://www.newsweek.com/columbia-jewish-students-warned-rabbi-over-their-safety-1892613" target="_blank"&gt;told Jewish students&lt;/a&gt; that police "cannot guarantee [their] safety in the face of extreme antisemitism and anarchy." Buechler also advised Jewish students to "return home as soon as possible and remain home until the reality in and around campus has dramatically improved. It is not our job as Jews to ensure our own safety on campus.” The school soon switched to remote-option learning for safety reasons for the rest of the semester.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Some Columbia protesters reportedly were cited for resisting arrest and assaulting a police officer. Not that it matters — as AOC would be glad to know — since none of the 228 Columbia and NYU demonstrators &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/pro-hamas-protesters-arrested-for-taking-over-new-york-universities-won-t-face-criminal-records-report" target="_blank"&gt;reportedly&lt;/a&gt; received charges that will go on their records.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many of those responding to Ocasio-Cortez saw right through her rhetoric, too. Some prominent examples:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Conservative commentator Jason Rantz &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/jasonrantz/status/1783011937070305634" target="_blank"&gt;told&lt;/a&gt; AOC, "Something tells me if people illegally camped on your property — while supporting terrorists (whomever you think are terrorists since you don’t feel that way about Hamas) — you’d call the cops. Sorry that your fellow Jew-haters don’t get to break the law."&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;International human rights lawyer Arsen Ostrovsky &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/Ostrov_A/status/1782975746719289360" target="_blank"&gt;added&lt;/a&gt; to the congresswoman, "They are explicitly inciting violence, engaging in racial hatred and impeding students and faculty for learning and teaching. The only ‘heinous failure in leadership’ is your justification of this behavior."&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Journalist Kyle Becker &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/kylenabecker/status/1783113171625984276" target="_blank"&gt;noted&lt;/a&gt; to AOC that "radical Marxists don't have a right to disrupt entire communities to throw their temper tantrums."&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:40:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Death to America' pamphlets circulated at college anti-Israel encampment, eyewitness says</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/death-to-america-pamphlets-circulated-college-anti-israel-encampment-eyewitness-says</link><description>Multiple student groups at the University of Michigan shared anti-Israel pamphlets this week, including one labeled "Death to America," at a pro-Palestinian encampment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:35:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Traitor Joe Isn’t Just Refusing to Address the Border Crisis, He’s Siphoning Border Wall Funds for “Environmental Planning”</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/traitor-joe-isnt-just-refusing-address-border-crisis/</link><description>(DCNF)—The Biden administration spent taxpayer dollars meant to fund a border wall to pay for “environmental planning,” according to a new report by the Government Accountability Office (GAO). At the request of Republican Reps. Jack Bergman of Michigan and Jodey Arrington of Texas, the GAO investigated whether the Department of Homeland Security (DHS) broke the […]
The post Traitor Joe Isn’t Just Refusing to Address the Border Crisis, He’s Siphoning Border Wall Funds for “Environmental Planning” appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:43:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In 2024, Americans Will Be Voting Like It's 1892</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/24/in_2024_americans_will_be_voting_like_its_1892_622433.html</link><description>Both candidates have a record, and we know which president saw success and which one has only produced one crisis after another.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:58:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>El Paso judge dismisses riot charges against 140 likely illegal aliens — Republican DA indicts them anyway</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/el-paso-judge-dismisses-riot-charges-against-140-likely-illegal-aliens-republican-da-indicts-them-anyway-2667871427.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/el-paso-judge-dismisses-riot-charges-against-140-likely-illegal-aliens-republican-da-indicts-them-anyway.jpg?id=52094096&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C111%2C0%2C137</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/el-paso-judge-dismisses-riot-charges-against-140-likely-illegal-aliens-republican-da-indicts-them-anyway.jpg?id=52094096&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C111%2C0%2C137" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/el-paso-judge-dismisses-riot-charges-against-140-likely-illegal-aliens-republican-da-indicts-them-anyway.jpg?id=52094096&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=400&amp;amp;coordinates=0,211,0,237 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/el-paso-judge-dismisses-riot-charges-against-140-likely-illegal-aliens-republican-da-indicts-them-anyway.jpg%3Fid%3D52094096%26width%3D1200%26height%3D400%26coordinates%3D0%2C211%2C0%2C237%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;A district attorney in Texas has indicted 141 allegedly illegal aliens for riot participation just one day after a judge claimed there was no probable cause for doing so.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On April 12, a group of 300 or so individuals reportedly crossed the U.S. border illegally near Riverside High School in El Paso, Texas. Of those 300, 142 allegedly cut through a temporary fence constructed of concertina wire, an act that "constitutes an illegal entry into the U.S.," according to a &lt;a href="https://kfoxtv.com/news/local/el-paso-texas-tx-judge-drops-state-charges-for-140-migrants-accused-of-rioting-concertina-wire-public-defender-kelli-childress-diaz-jennifer-vandenbosch" target="_blank"&gt;statement&lt;/a&gt; from Border Patrol. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They then allegedly engaged in some kind of "encounter" with law enforcement agents with Gov. Greg Abbott's Operation Lone Star, the &lt;a href="https://www.elpasotimes.com/story/news/immigration/2024/04/22/el-paso-county-judge-no-probable-cause-of-border-riot-arrests-judge-ruben-morales/73418221007/" target="_blank"&gt;El Paso Times&lt;/a&gt; reported, though the nature of that "encounter" is unclear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All 142 individuals, most of whom are &lt;a href="https://elpasomatters.org/2024/04/23/el-paso-da-bill-hicks-migrant-riot-indictments-border-wall/" target="_blank"&gt;believed to be&lt;/a&gt; Venezuelan nationals, currently face federal charges of illegal entry into the U.S. However, when local prosecutors also wanted to charge them with riot participation for the alleged confrontation with law enforcement, El Paso County Judge Ruben Morales expressed doubt about the underlying predicate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"After reviewing the affidavit, I don't believe that [probable cause] exists," Morales said at a hearing on Monday. "I don't believe there is probable cause for these individuals to continue to be detained for the offense of riot participation."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Morales ultimately dismissed 140 of the riot-related cases. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Morales' ruling was not legally binding, however, and on Tuesday, just one day after Morales' dismissal, El Paso District Attorney Bill Hicks proceeded with the indictments anyway, having first impaneled a grand jury that supported the indictments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"When we took the broader case to the grand jury, we presented the case as a whole, we presented videotape evidence of what happened. The grand jurors believed that there was, in fact, probable cause," Hicks said at a &lt;a href="https://elpasomatters.org/2024/04/23/el-paso-da-bill-hicks-migrant-riot-indictments-border-wall/" target="_blank"&gt;press conference&lt;/a&gt; on Tuesday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In all, Hicks has charged 141 people with riot participation. They include all 140 cases dismissed by Judge Morales as well as an individual with an additional charge of criminal mischief. None of their names have been released. All have reportedly been transferred from the county jail into ICE's custody as part of their immigration detainer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Texas, riot participation is a Class B misdemeanor that carries a maximum penalty of 180 days in jail or a $2,000 fine, so impaneling a grand jury for such a case was unusual. But Hicks, a Republican, believes that adjudicating these cases is important for public safety.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"People believe they can come to our country knocking down barriers, endangering lives, causing our national guardsmen to fear for their lives," &lt;a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/da-bill-hicks-indicts-migrants-for-rioting-after-judge-ruled-there-was-no-probable-cause/ar-AA1nxRYe" target="_blank"&gt;he said&lt;/a&gt;. "... They cannot do that."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;El Paso County Public Defender Kelli Childress, who represents the defendants, views these cases very differently. She called the indictments "horrific" and indicated they were largely baseless. "They have no witnesses. They have no evidence," she said. Prosecutors are simply charging them as "part of [a] group," she claimed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hicks countered that individuals should be held accountable for participating in a group that then collectively commits a crime: "If you’re a part of the group that is committing a criminal act, you know that you’re part of that group, you know that the group has committed a criminal act, then you are guilty of the offense of riot."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hicks noted that he intends to offer the defendants a plea deal that will include time served. Thus far, none have reportedly accepted it. Following their hearings for the state charges, Hicks said, "They’d be released to Border Patrol, and either some people will be deported, or some people are going to get released."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:25:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fox News Politics: Agent of chaos</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/fox-news-politics-agent-of-chaos</link><description>The latest updates from the 2024 campaign trail, exclusive interviews and more Fox News politics content</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:27:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Argentina President Javier Milei Announces First Quarterly Budget Surplus in 16 Years [VIDEO]</title><link>https://rumble.com/v4rakzz-argentina-president-javier-milei-announces-first-quarterly-budget-surplus-i.html</link><description>The post Argentina President Javier Milei Announces First Quarterly Budget Surplus in 16 Years [VIDEO] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:43:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>On Trial, Trump Isn't the Superhero MAGA Craves</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/24/on_trial_trump_isnt_the_superhero_maga_craves_622400.html</link><description>He wants his devotees to see the court case as trial by combat, with him as warrior. But the truth is more pathetic</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:55:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stephen A. Smith now APOLOGIZING for Trump comments after backlash ensues</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/stephen-a-smith-now-apologizing-for-trump-comments-after-backlash-ensues-2667871327.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52096901&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C120</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52096901&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C120" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52096872&amp;amp;width=2000&amp;amp;height=1500&amp;amp;coordinates=0,0,480,0 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg%3Fid%3D52096872%26width%3D2000%26height%3D1500%26coordinates%3D0%2C0%2C480%2C0%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stephen A. Smith committed the ultimate crime in the media’s eyes — defending Donald Trump — and instead of standing his ground, he’s backing down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/shows/fearless-with-jason-whitlock/stephen-a-smith-2667868950" target="_blank"&gt;The sports commentator had told Sean Hannity on Fox News just days ago that the persecution of Trump by the justice system has been “relatable” to the black community.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And the “blacklash” that ensued inspired him to apologize.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“A lot of folks in black America seem pretty pissed at me right now,” Smith told his audience, adding that his “words were interpreted as associating support for Trump from the black community with all the legal issues he’s facing.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Smith went on to apologize and say that the black community will “never forget how Trump claimed Obama, the nation's first black president, wasn’t even qualified to hold office because he was born in Kenya.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Jason Whitlock isn’t surprised, calling him “Stephen A. No Backbone.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I have a question though,” Steve Kim adds. “Do black pundits not have a right to have their own feelings? I don’t see this pressure on anyone white.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whitlock didn’t see a problem with his original comments, only the black community’s supposed reaction and the lack of strength behind his own convictions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“His comments are innocuous, and just not very harmful or impactful. That ‘Hey black people find Trump relatable because of you know, the criminal justice problems,’” Whitlock says. “That’s not a controversial statement.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This is why I just said, and have been saying for months now, this guy’s installed. He’s got puppet strings on him,” he adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Want more from Jason Whitlock?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;To enjoy more fearless conversations at the crossroads of culture, faith, sports, and comedy with Jason Whitlock, &lt;a href="https://get.blazetv.com/fearless/?utm_source=theblaze&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_campaign=article_shortcode_jasonwhitlock" target="_blank"&gt;subscribe to BlazeTV&lt;/a&gt; — the largest multi-platform network of voices who love America, defend the Constitution, and live the American dream.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:08:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Foreign students could face harsher penalties than suspension for anti-Israel rioting: DHS</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/dhs-official-reveals-what-could-happen-foreign-students-suspended-anti-israel-protests-rage</link><description>DHS Homeland Security Investigations confirmed to Fox that there is a path for foreign students to be deported if they are suspended from university.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:27:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Cost-Benefit Analysis of Having a Baby</title><link>https://thefederalist.com/2024/04/24/is-there-a-cost-benefit-analysis-for-having-a-baby-this-economist-thinks-so/</link><description>The post The Cost-Benefit Analysis of Having a Baby appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:43:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chicago's Criminal Complex Denies Our Right to Safety</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/24/chicagos_criminal_complex_denies_our_right_to_safety_622422.html</link><description>By Paul Vallas April 24, 2024 You want to know why violent crime is surging in the nation's urban centers? Look no further than the radical left's efforts to reform the criminal justice system by pretending that criminals are just a new class of victims whose violence is a product of our systemically racist society. According to them it's not ... Read More</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:50:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Joe Biden Just Promised America A Massive Tax Hike</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/joe-biden-just-promised-america-a-massive-tax-hike-2667871121.html</link><image_url>https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/Joe-Biden-AOC-1024x664.png</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/Joe-Biden-AOC-1024x664.png" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img class="rm-shortcode" id="84b7a" src="https://www.conservativereview.com/media-library/eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpbWFnZSI6Imh0dHBzOi8vdGhlZmVkZXJhbGlzdC5jb20vd3AtY29udGVudC91cGxvYWRzLzIwMjQvMDQvSm9lLUJpZGVuLUFPQy0xMjAweDY3NS5wbmciLCJleHBpcmVzX2F0IjoxNzYzMTg4MDQ1fQ.qkZB0zHQdy6xiwyPbCyI1wN51MbCjhfr2QKHCOqy270/image.png" /&gt;Joe Biden says he will let Donald Trump's across-the-board $2 trillion tax cut expire. That would mean the biggest tax increase in history.&lt;/span&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:50:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The House is practically functioning as a parliament, with Mike Johnson as its 'prime minister'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/house-practically-functioning-parliament-mike-johnson-became-prime-minister</link><description>While the U.S. doesn't have a parliamentary system, America has been functioning with a coalition government, with Mike Johnson acting as the "prime minister."</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:10:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Experts Expose Dementia Joe’s Stunning Plastic Surgery</title><link>https://trendingpoliticsnews.com/new-joe-bidens-plastic-surgery-exposed-mace/</link><description>The post Experts Expose Dementia Joe’s Stunning Plastic Surgery appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:39:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Student Protesters Are Schooling Their Universities</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/24/student_protesters_are_schooling_their_universities_622429.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:50:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden’s Approval Bump in Swing States Has Vanished, Poll Shows</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/bidens-approval-bump-in-swing-states-has-vanished-poll-shows-2667871079.html</link><image_url>https://freebeacon.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/biden-senior1.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://freebeacon.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/biden-senior1.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;A poll released Wednesday shows President Joe Biden’s approval bump last month in swing states has all but vanished, with Republican nominee Donald Trump again ahead of Biden in six of the seven states most likely to impact the 2024 presidential election.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://freebeacon.com/latest-news/bidens-approval-bump-in-swing-states-has-vanished-poll-shows/"&gt;Biden’s Approval Bump in Swing States Has Vanished, Poll Shows&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://freebeacon.com"&gt;Washington Free Beacon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:40:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden appears to read script instructions out loud in latest teleprompter gaffe: 'Four more years, pause'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/biden-appears-read-script-instructions-loud-latest-teleprompter-gaffe-four-more-years-pause</link><description>President Biden appeared to incorporate script instructions from his teleprompter into his speech on Wednesday, resulting in a memorable gaffe.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:55:50 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>