<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 00:44:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>List of Democrats Calling for Dementia Joe to Step Aside Grows After Disastrous NATO Press Briefing</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/list-democrats-calling-dementia-joe-step-aside-grows/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>(DCNF)—Democratic Rep. Brittany Pettersen of Colorado is one of several Democrats who have called on President Joe Biden to drop out of the election following the president’s press briefing on Thursday. Pettersen released a statement Friday following Biden’s highly criticized NATO press briefing, in which he committed several crucial gaffes that fueled continued speculation that […] The post List of Democrats Calling for Dementia Joe to Step Aside Grows After Disastrous NATO Press Briefing appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 01:00:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Yearslong tensions boil over as ex-Obama staffers gang up on Biden: 'Clooney was exactly right'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/yearslong-tensions-boil-ex-obama-staffers-gang-up-biden-clooney-right</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>The tensions between President Biden and former President Obama go back nearly two decades and are once again in the spotlight as the former faces calls to end his re-election bid.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 23:37:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Donors to the Largest Biden Super PAC Will Freeze Donations if Pinocchio Joe Stays in the Race</title><link>https://twitchy.com/samj/2024/07/12/breaking-massive-donors-freeze-donations-biden-n2398284</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>The post Donors to the Largest Biden Super PAC Will Freeze Donations if Pinocchio Joe Stays in the Race appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 01:00:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Congressional bypass: Many Democrats elusive on Biden issue</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/congressional-bypass-many-democrats-elusive-biden-issue</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>While some Congressional Democrats have called on Biden to step aside, others have shared opaque statements, deflected or avoided responding to questions about the president altogether.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 23:37:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>J.D. Vance Is the Right Choice for Trump’s VP, and There Is No Close Second</title><link>https://www.dossier.today/p/jd-vance-is-the-right-choice-for</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>The post J.D. Vance Is the Right Choice for Trump’s VP, and There Is No Close Second appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 01:00:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>White House doctor pressured to convince Biden to take cognitive exam, publicize results</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/white-house-doctor-pressured-convince-biden-take-cognitive-exam-publicize-results</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>Sen. Lindsey Graham pleaded with the White House doctor to convince Biden he should take a new neurological exam and make the results public.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 23:27:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>White House Seeks to Clarify Its Previous Clarification of Dementia Joe’s Health</title><link>https://mishtalk.com/politics/white-house-seeks-to-clarify-its-clarification-of-bidens-health/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>The post White House Seeks to Clarify Its Previous Clarification of Dementia Joe’s Health appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 01:00:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lawmakers rip Army brass over training slides suggesting pro-life groups could be tied to terrorism</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/lawmakers-rip-army-brass-over-training-slides-suggesting-pro-life-groups-could-terrorism-risks</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>At least 25 Republicans called on Army Secretary Christine Wormuth to explain slides used in training at Fort Bragg/Fort Liberty depicting pro-life groups among potential terror threats.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 23:13:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Democrat Donor Says Her Party Needs to “Grow a Spine” and Express Concerns About Dementia Joe Publicly</title><link>https://dailycallernewsfoundation.org/2024/07/12/democrat-donor-says-her-party-needs-to-grow-a-spine-by-expressing-concerns-about-biden-publicly/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>The post Democrat Donor Says Her Party Needs to “Grow a Spine” and Express Concerns About Dementia Joe Publicly appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 01:00:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden campaign hypes president's foreign policy chops after high-stakes NATO press conference</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/biden-campaign-hypes-presidents-foreign-policy-chops-after-nato-press-conference</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>The Biden campaign is praising the president's performance during Thursday's NATO press conference despite strong pushback from Republicans and the Trump campaign.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 22:40:30 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>