<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 11:55:44 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Judge Merchan Fines Trump . . . Again, Threatens Him With Jail Time . . . Again</title><link>https://pjmedia.com/matt-margolis/2024/05/06/judge-merchan-fines-trump-again-threatens-him-with-jail-time-n4928794</link><description>The post Judge Merchan Fines Trump . . . Again, Threatens Him With Jail Time . . . Again appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:20:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Israel's Citizen-Soldiers</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/06/israels_citizen-soldiers_622849.html</link><description>How do Israelis go from fighting in Gaza to making lunches for their children, knowing that any day now they are likely to be called back into the army? In Ari Kalker's case, with help from Maimonides.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:56:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FACT CHECK: Did The New York Post Report About A Bill That Bans Questioning 9/11?</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/fact-check-did-the-new-york-post-report-about-a-bill-that-bans-questioning-9-11-2668175634.html</link><image_url>https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/07/Twin-Towers-e1468953060591.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/07/Twin-Towers-e1468953060591.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The headline and image are edited</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:32:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Speaker Johnson to discuss issues with Marjorie Taylor Green ahead of her threats to oust him</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/speaker-johnson-marjorie-taylor-greene-meet-monday-threatst-motion-vacate</link><description>Speaker Mike Johnson is expected to meet privately, one-on-one, with Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene on Monday amid speculation that she may trigger her motion to vacate.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:40:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Devotional: The Key to Survival</title><link>https://anotherwell.org/2024/05/06/the-key-to-survival/</link><description>The post Devotional: The Key to Survival appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:20:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Suffering in Gaza Is Different From Other Conflicts</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/06/the_suffering_in_gaza_is_different_from_other_conflicts_623078.html</link><description>A child shrieks in pain in a medical tent at a field clinic in southern Gaza. He's 7, with severe burns on his back that are being cleaned and slathered with balm. It's an excruciating process that would be done under anesthesia, in the sterile setting of a hospital, in ideal circumstances. But after nearly seven months of bombing and shelling in Gaza, conditions of any sort have ceased to be even adequate, let alone ideal.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:53:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DOJ claims Google deleted chat logs as antitrust case comes to a close</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/doj-claims-google-deleted-chat-logs-as-antitrust-case-comes-to-a-close-2668175538.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/doj-claims-google-deleted-chat-logs-as-antitrust-case-comes-to-a-close.jpg?id=52179303&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C85%2C0%2C86</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/doj-claims-google-deleted-chat-logs-as-antitrust-case-comes-to-a-close.jpg?id=52179303&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C85%2C0%2C86" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/doj-claims-google-deleted-chat-logs-as-antitrust-case-comes-to-a-close.jpg?id=52179303&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;coordinates=0,0,0,1 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/doj-claims-google-deleted-chat-logs-as-antitrust-case-comes-to-a-close.jpg%3Fid%3D52179303%26width%3D1200%26height%3D800%26coordinates%3D0%2C0%2C0%2C1%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Department of Justice has alleged that Google implemented a policy that encouraged employees to delete chat logs and other discussions around certain business practices during its investigation, according to &lt;a href="https://www.techspot.com/news/102874-doj-alleges-google-destroyed-hundreds-thousands-chats-antitrust.html" target="_blank"&gt;Tech Spot&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The business practices in question have to do with revenue-sharing agreements and mobile application distribution deals. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Government lawyers noted that these internal conversations could have revealed Google's attempt to illegally leave out rivals and maintain its dominion as the top company in the search market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a href="https://www.livemint.com/news/world/google-takes-questions-over-ads-as-us-trial-comes-to-a-close-11714786048991.html" target="_blank"&gt;Mint&lt;/a&gt;, antitrust enforcers have suggested that Google has kept a monopoly over online search and related advertising.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Obama-appointed Judge Amit Mehta did not hold back when addressing Google's legal team, suggesting that he was taken aback by the major tech company's deliberate effort to destroy records. "Google's document retention policy leaves a lot to be desired," he said on Friday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Google's attorney Colette Connor &lt;a href="https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2024/05/judge-mulls-sanctions-over-googles-shocking-destruction-of-internal-chats/" target="_blank"&gt;told the judge&lt;/a&gt; that DOJ should have known about Google's policy well before the government agency challenged the company's conduct.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Connor also noted that Google's conduct could not be sanctioned because there is no evidence that any of the missing chat logs would have shed new light on the case.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The question still remains as to why Google employees allegedly deleted chat logs while under investigation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In January 2023, the DOJ &lt;a href="https://www.justice.gov/opa/pr/justice-department-sues-google-monopolizing-digital-advertising-technologies" target="_blank"&gt;released a statement&lt;/a&gt;, saying:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;Filed in the U.S. District Court for the Eastern District of Virginia, the complaint alleges that Google monopolizes key digital advertising technologies, collectively referred to as the “ad tech stack,” that website publishers depend on to sell ads and that advertisers rely on to buy ads and reach potential customers. Website publishers use ad tech tools to generate advertising revenue that supports the creation and maintenance of a vibrant open web, providing the public with unprecedented access to ideas, artistic expression, information, goods, and services. Through this monopolization lawsuit, the Justice Department and state Attorneys General seek to restore competition in these important markets and obtain equitable and monetary relief on behalf of the American public.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the time, Attorney General Merrick Garland said: "Today’s complaint alleges that Google has used anticompetitive, exclusionary, and unlawful conduct to eliminate or severely diminish any threat to its dominance over digital advertising technologies."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“No matter the industry and no matter the company, the Justice Department will vigorously enforce our antitrust laws to protect consumers, safeguard competition, and ensure economic fairness and opportunity for all.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:25:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ex-top Biden DOJ official now prosecuting Trump was once paid by DNC for 'political consulting'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/ex-top-biden-doj-official-prosecuting-trump-once-paid-by-dnc-political-consulting</link><description>EXCLUSIVE: The Democratic National Committee paid prosecutor Matthew Colangelo thousands of dollars for “political consulting" in 2018, Fox News Digital has learned.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 15:57:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>China Is Buying up Unprecedented Amounts of Gold</title><link>https://endtimeheadlines.org/2024/05/china-is-buying-up-unprecedented-amounts-of-gold/</link><description>The post China Is Buying up Unprecedented Amounts of Gold appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:20:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Trustees Can Save Their Schools</title><link>https://www.realcleareducation.com/articles/2024/05/03/how_trustees_can_save_columbia_brown_northeastern_penn_indiana_yale_1029360.html</link><description>In an unprecedented display of leadership, the president, flanked by the provost and the chairman of the board of trustees, announced to the chanting and drumming students encamped in the South Quad:</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:52:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hakeem Jeffries Boasts About House Dems ‘Effectively’ Running Congress Despite GOP Majority</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/hakeem-jeffries-boasts-about-house-dems-effectively-running-congress-despite-gop-majority-2668175516.html</link><image_url>https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/DCNF-Jeffries-CBS-House-MTG-Featured.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/DCNF-Jeffries-CBS-House-MTG-Featured.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;'Those are just the facts'</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:17:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NY v Trump: Judge threatens jail time for 'possibly the next president' for future gag order violations</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/ny-v-trump-judge-threatens-jail-time-for-possibly-the-next-president-for-future-gag-order-violations</link><description>Judge Juan Merchan on Monday said he will consider a jail sentence for former President Trump if he continues to violate the gag order imposed upon him in his unprecedented criminal trial.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:53:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>President Trump Calls for Jack Smith to Be Arrested After Special Counsel Admits HE LIED to the COURT About Classified Docs Seized From Mar-a-Lago</title><link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2024/05/president-trump-calls-jack-smith-be-arrested-after/</link><description>The post President Trump Calls for Jack Smith to Be Arrested After Special Counsel Admits HE LIED to the COURT About Classified Docs Seized From Mar-a-Lago appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:20:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Lip Gloss Became the Answer to Gen Z's Problems</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/06/how_lip_gloss_became_the_answer_to_gen_zs_problems_623080.html</link><description>In 2007, it was hard to go anywhere without hearing someone chanting the lyrics to Lil Mama's signature bop "Lip Gloss."</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:51:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Red states show they are better at law and order by the way they clear unlawful college encampments</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/red-states-show-they-are-better-at-law-and-order-by-the-way-they-clear-unlawful-college-encampments-2668175535.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/red-states-show-they-are-better-at-law-and-order-by-the-way-they-clear-unlawful-college-encampments.png?id=52177607&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C334</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/red-states-show-they-are-better-at-law-and-order-by-the-way-they-clear-unlawful-college-encampments.png?id=52177607&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C334" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/red-states-show-they-are-better-at-law-and-order-by-the-way-they-clear-unlawful-college-encampments.png?id=52177607&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;coordinates=0,0,0,16 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/red-states-show-they-are-better-at-law-and-order-by-the-way-they-clear-unlawful-college-encampments.png%3Fid%3D52177607%26width%3D1200%26height%3D800%26coordinates%3D0%2C0%2C0%2C16%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ongoing breakdown of law and order on college campuses across the country highlights just how differently Democrats and Republicans approach the issue since the BLM riots in 2020. Nowhere is this disparity more clear than when one examines what happened at the University of California Los Angeles under Democrat Governor Gavin Newson compared with what happened at the University of Virginia and Virginia Commonwealth University under Republican Governor Glenn Youngkin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At VCU, anti-Israel protesters started an occupation on campus to pressure the school to divest from Israel as the war in Gaza continues. Within a very short amount of time, VCU officials warned the protesters that if they did not stop their encampment, they could be arrested for trespassing. Naturally, the protesters refused.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once night fell, videos showed local and state law enforcement in riot gear moving to clear the camp. But the protesters were ready, having makeshift shields of their own and having objects handy to throw at the officers. It was a brutal clash, with riot shields banging up against banners. But eventually, the campus rebellion was brought to heel. A total of 13 people were arrested that night. While the scene was chaotic, order was eventually restored.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;div&gt;Virginia State Police, Campus Police, and other State as well as Local Law Enforcement Agencies are attempting to Clear the Pro-Hamas Encampment at Virginia Commonwealth University in Richmond, which has taken over some of the Campus alongside at least 1 School Building. Several\u2026&lt;/div&gt; —  (@)        &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/sentdefender/status/1785112621814866290"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;"After repeated warnings and refusal to disperse, law enforcement must protect Virginians. My administration will continue to fully support campus, local and state law enforcement and university leadership to keep our campuses safe,” Virginia Gov. Glenn Youngkin posted on X.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I arrived in Richmond the next day, I expected further resistance from students and protesters. But instead, I found VCU's Students for Justice in Palestine imploring people to stand down for now to avoid another crackdown. At UVA, the planned encampment started a day early. Campus police informed protesters there would be no sweep if they did not set up tents. With what happened at VCU fresh in mind, the protesters complied. They still protested, but there was no entrenched camp.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After almost a week of following what UVA leadership told them, protesters tried setting up an encampment again. After the protesters resisted campus police, the Virginia State Police took the lead in clearing out the camp and holding off angry protesters who started to show up. The affair was over quickly, similar to what happened at VCU.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;         —  (@)        &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/anahitajafary_/status/1786852846589087910"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;This was in stark contrast to what was happening at UCLA, where a camp, complete with barricades, had been set up by anti-Israel protesters. Jewish students had been blocked from entering the area by the occupiers, with some being attacked during a counter-rally. This caused an attack on the encampment by a pro-Israeli crowd, causing a riot that lasted for almost four before police finally intervened. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The only means of protection we had was each other. WE KEEP US SAFE. The university’s hypocrisy [is] all too apparent. The university would rather see us dead than divest. Call on UCLA to disclose, divest, end the silence,” a Los Angeles far-left group &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/PplsCityCouncil/status/1785620846700351510" target="_blank"&gt;posted&lt;/a&gt; on X. The group's official statement went on to complain that police ignore their “screams” for help. That same far-left group, People’s City Council - Los Angeles, is virulently anti-police and is not shy about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It became clear this was no longer a situation that could be allowed to continue. The order was finally given to clear the camp.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The problem for police at that point was that the encampment's defenses had been reinforced after the initial riot. So instead of only having to worry about tents, police had to figure out how to break through the rudimentary yet effective barricades. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In short, it was a slog. I arrived at the encampment around midnight. California Highway Patrolmen in riot gear started to advance on the camp in force around 3:00 a.m. The camp was finally cleared after 6:00 a.m., just as the sun was starting to rise. Over 200 people were arrested. Full details on what happened that night can be found &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/riot-police-successfully-take-control-at-ucla-throwing-away-hamas-endorsed-radicals-palestinian-flag" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The problem California faces is that UCLA was far from the only encampment at a college. The very same day police cleared out UCLA's camp, another one sprang up at California State University Long Beach. Protesters set up a “zona autonoma” outside Brotman Hall in an effort to get the school to bow to their demands to divest from and boycott Israel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;img class="rm-shortcode" id="d029e" src="https://www.conservativereview.com/media-library/eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpbWFnZSI6Imh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnRoZWJsYXplLmNvbS9tZWRpYS1saWJyYXJ5L2ltYWdlLnBuZz9pZD01MjE3NzY5NSZhbXA7d2lkdGg9OTgwIiwiZXhwaXJlc19hdCI6MTcyNTg0MzMwMn0.6ZVk_mUASFHWLwblpl-dj7EQuVcM7cir4hFMy1HQKL8/image.jpg" /&gt;                        Julio Rosas/Blaze Media&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Protesters created barriers for their newly established zone, which initially took students by surprise who were trying to walk through the outdoor area. Eventually, lanes of traffic were created for people who wanted to walk in or leave the zone. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In response, a few Jewish students stood next to the protest zone holding American and Israeli flags. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“God bless America,” one of the students holding the American flag told me was his response to the protest zone. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When asked if there was concern that the protest zone could turn into another UCLA situation, the counter-protesters said they did not think that would happen at CSULB. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This campus is not as unified as [UCLA]; it’s a commuter school, right? A lot of people have jobs. A lot of people at Columbia, UCLA, and USC are from a higher income bracket, so a lot of them don’t have jobs,” said a student who wanted to be identified as Sheryl.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As for UCLA? The organizers who created the camp near Royce Hall have already promised their fight is not over and hinted that another camp will be created. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The country is starting to unravel once again as it did nearly four years ago. In combination with the warmer weather and the election year, it does not appear the unrest will go away any time soon, but it is clear some states will weather the coming storm better than others.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:10:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Noem addresses feeling 'threatened' by Nikki Haley, a controversial dog killing, Trump VP speculation in book</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/noem-addresses-threatened-nikki-haley-dog-killing-trump-vp-book</link><description>Gov. Kristi Noem's new book, titled "No Going Back," details her life in politics and several controversial topics discussed in an interview with Fox News Digital.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 09:13:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Parents Seek Tuition Refund Amidst College Protests</title><link>https://www.libertynation.com/parents-seek-tuition-refund-amidst-college-protests/</link><description>The post Parents Seek Tuition Refund Amidst College Protests appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:13:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The End of Old Left-Wing Mythologies</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/06/the_end_of_old_left-wing_mythologies_623077.html</link><description>The current radical and often violent protests on mostly blue-state, supposedly elite campuses have exposed in toxic fashion what the left has become. And yet, in a paradoxical fashion, the campus insanity has offered the nation some moral clarity.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:49:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Former Columnist Exposes Scientific American’s Sudden Descent Into Left-Wing Ideology</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/former-columnist-exposes-scientific-americans-sudden-descent-into-left-wing-ideology-2668175444.html</link><image_url>https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Screenshot-2024-05-06-10.04.59-AM-e1715007014404.png</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Screenshot-2024-05-06-10.04.59-AM-e1715007014404.png" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;'Nudged away from certain topics'</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:04:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>House Dems seeking re-election seemingly reverse course, call on Biden to 'bring order to the southern border'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/house-dems-seeking-re-election-seemingly-reverse-course-call-biden-bring-order-southern-border</link><description>Five House Democrats who voted against measures to strengthen border security in the past have seemingly changed their tune as they seek re-election.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 09:00:59 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>