<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 17:17:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Based Andrew Tate Goes on Explicit Rant About “Vaccine Injured” Whining About Being Pressured [VIDEO]</title><link>https://rumble.com/v4u3yll-based-andrew-tate-goes-on-explicit-rant-about-vaccine-injured-whining-about.html</link><description>The post Based Andrew Tate Goes on Explicit Rant About “Vaccine Injured” Whining About Being Pressured [VIDEO] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:20:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Student Journalists Are Needed Now More Than Ever</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/09/student_journalists_are_needed_now_more_than_ever_623305.html</link><description>While the mainstream media repeatedly mischaracterizes pro-Palestine protests on campus, police and university administrations are attempting to repress the student press.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 22:09:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Turley Skewers Hillary Clinton For Attacking Trump Over Payments Despite Her Campaign Being Fined For Steele Dossier</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/turley-skewers-hillary-clinton-for-attacking-trump-over-payments-despite-her-campaign-being-fined-for-steele-dossier-2668214335.html</link><image_url>https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/DCNF-Turley-Clinton-Steele-Daniels-Featured-e1715286636938.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/DCNF-Turley-Clinton-Steele-Daniels-Featured-e1715286636938.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;'Her campaign did exactly what she is suggesting here'</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:59:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Former GOP Rep. Fortenberry charged with lying about illegal campaign contribution</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/former-gop-rep-fortenberry-charged-lying-illegal-campaign-contribution</link><description>Republican former Nebraska Rep. Jeff Fortenberry has been charged with lying to federal authorities about an illegal, $30,000 campaign contribution by a Nigerian billionaire.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 22:00:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Did Federal Agencies Plant Classified Documents to Frame Trump?</title><link>https://thefederalist.com/2024/05/09/did-federal-agencies-plant-classified-documents-to-frame-trump/</link><description>The post Did Federal Agencies Plant Classified Documents to Frame Trump? appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:20:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Gantz Megillah</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/09/the_gantz_megillah_623282.html</link><description>How America is using ex-IDF Chief Benny Gantz as its Trojan horse to impose U.S. demands-and ensure Israel's defeat in Gaza</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 22:08:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vulnerable Dem Senator Co-Sponsors Laken Riley Act Weeks After Opposing Provision</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/vulnerable-dem-senator-co-sponsors-laken-riley-act-weeks-after-opposing-provision-2668214320.html</link><image_url>https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/2017-02-01T000000Z_79631318_RC12C3865930_RTRMADP_3_USA-CONGRESS-scaled-e1715285964582.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/2017-02-01T000000Z_79631318_RC12C3865930_RTRMADP_3_USA-CONGRESS-scaled-e1715285964582.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;'Keeping Montana safe is my top priority'</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:58:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Taxpayer-funded ID program for illegal immigrants expected to begin this summer</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/ice-eyes-summer-rollout-for-id-card-program-for-illegal-immigrants</link><description>Immigration and Customs Enforcement is looking to roll out a controversial ID card pilot program for illegal immigrants as early as this summer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:31:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>As American Citizens We Have a Fundamental Right to Preserve Our Culture</title><link>https://clashdaily.com/2024/05/as-u-s-citizens-we-have-a-fundamental-right-to-preserve-our-culture/</link><description>The post As American Citizens We Have a Fundamental Right to Preserve Our Culture appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Left-Wing Voter Turnout Op Targets Vulnerable Patients</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/09/left-wing_voter_turnout_op_targets_vulnerable_patients_623327.html</link><description>A left-wing group called Vot-ER that is linked to the Biden White House is poised to play a key role registering voters ahead of the 2024 election.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 22:07:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Students expelled over bogus 'blackface' claims just taught the school a valuable lesson worth over $1 million</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/students-expelled-over-bogus-blackface-claims-just-taught-the-school-a-valuable-lesson-worth-over-1-million-2668214336.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52211450&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C50%2C0%2C57</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52211450&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C50%2C0%2C57" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52211439&amp;amp;width=1245&amp;amp;height=700&amp;amp;coordinates=16,0,0,0 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg%3Fid%3D52211439%26width%3D1245%26height%3D700%26coordinates%3D16%2C0%2C0%2C0%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;A pair of 14-year-old boys donned acne face masks along with a friend in August 2017. Realizing they looked "silly," they decided to take a selfie — having no idea that a mob of thin-skinned ideologues might jump to conclusions years down the road.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The photo resurfaced in June 2020. It was immediately seized upon as an example of the racism that was supposedly everywhere in the aftermath of the deadly Black Lives Matter riots.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rather than launch a proper investigation, which would have undoubtedly cleared the boys of any wrongdoing, the teens' school  effectively branded them as racists then had them expelled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We would never wish the pain, humiliation, and suffering St. Francis has inflicted on our families on anyone," said the Hughes family&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Saint Francis High School in Mountain View, California, has paid the price for rushing to judgment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With the help of the Dhillon Law Group, which has represented &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/parents-of-boy-suspended-for-wearing-warrior-paint-at-football-game-sue" target="_blank"&gt;other minors similarly traduced&lt;/a&gt; over racially-charged hoaxes, the teens, Holden Hughes and Aaron Harley, sued the high school with their parents for over $20 million. While ultimately unable to exact the full toll for their malignment, the former students walked walked away this week with $1 million plus tuition reimbursement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Los Angeles Times &lt;a href="https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2024-05-08/two-expelled-bay-area-high-school-students-awarded-1-million-in-blackface-lawsuit" target="_blank"&gt;indicated&lt;/a&gt; that a Santa Clara County jury sided with the former students who claimed the school breached an oral contract and failed to give them due process before expelling them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Twenty percent of our boys' lives have been spent seeing this process come to fruition. But the sacrifice is worth it to clear our boys' names, and to try and make sure that St. Francis can never again assume a child is guilty without giving a child the opportunity to show their innocence. To never again sacrifice any child to protect the school's reputation like they did our boys," the Hughes family &lt;a href="https://www.dhillonlaw.com/lawsuits/jurys-groundbreaking-decision-all-california-high-schools-must-give-students-fair-procedure-st-francis-high-school-is-not-above-the-law/" target="_blank"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; in a statement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We would never wish the pain, humiliation, and suffering St. Francis has inflicted on our families on anyone, but we are thankful that the jury has spoken, and vindicated our boys, and forced St. Francis to finally take responsibility for their repeated personal attacks on the boys," added the family.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Background&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The original complaint indicated that on Aug. 17, 2017, Hughes and Hartley, then both 14 years old, put on white acne masks that Hartley's mother purchased to help with his skin condition, &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/20-million-lawsuit-filed-against-catholic-high-school-over-blackface-n1259464" target="_blank"&gt;reported&lt;/a&gt; NBC News.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Believing themselves to look 'silly' in the masks, [Harley] and [a friend from another school identified as Minor III] took a time-stamped photograph of themselves in the masks," said the lawsuit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next day, Hughes, Hartley and Minor III instead tried on a light green acne face mask.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Again, they took a silly photograph in this mask, which had turned dark green by the time it dried on their faces," said the lawsuit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;         —  (@)        &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/CollinRugg/status/1788369045617889737"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;The boys did not share the image online. However, Minor III shared it to a friend, who ultimately "tagged a music playlist on her Spotify account with a copy of the photograph."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Years later, a student at the school reportedly obtained a copy of the photo, named the students, and insinuated that they had engaged in blackface.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alicia Labana, a parent originally named as a defendant in the suit, made matters worse by allegedly posting the photo on Facebook ahead of a planned march to protest "outrageous behavior" and to pressure the school to act.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to lawsuit, the image was  condemned by school staff and parents alike and prompted a parent-led protest against the minors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason Curtis, &lt;a href="https://www.sfhs.com/about-us/leadership" target="_blank"&gt;president of the school&lt;/a&gt;, reportedly rushed to issue a public condemnation. Absent an investigation into the image, a hearing taking up the accusations or the involvement of the school's review board, Hartley and Hughes were told within 24 hours of the scandal breaking they had  to withdraw from the school or face expulsion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The teens left the school in June 2020 and filed suit the following year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hughes reportedly indicated his family had to put up security cameras around their home and pled with the Los Altos Police to execute additional patrols in the area for fear of attacks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hartley said his family had to move away on account of the persistent harassment and that he had to complete high school remotely, reported the Post.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Vindicated&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Palo Alto Post &lt;a href="https://padailypost.com/2024/05/07/jury-sides-with-students-in-blackface-lawsuit/" target="_blank"&gt;reported&lt;/a&gt; that a jury of 12 reached their verdict on Monday following 20 days of testimony and three days of deliberation. The boys will receive $500,000 each from the high school and be reimbursed for their tuition, an estimated $70,000 for their three years at Saint Francis High School.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Saint Francis High School spokesman Jamie Perkins said in a statement obtained by the Post, "We respectfully disagree with the jury's conclusion … regarding the fairness of our disciplinary review process and are exploring legal options, including appeal as there is no legal precedent applying that claim to a high school."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The former students' legal team suggested that this case establishes a new precedent by extending protections set by the California Supreme Court in &lt;em&gt;Boermeester v. Carry&lt;/em&gt;, which requires fair procedure rights for students at private universities. Accordingly, such fair procedure rights will allegedly apply to private high schools.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Krista Baughman, partner at the Dhillon Law Group, &lt;a href="https://www.dhillonlaw.com/lawsuits/jurys-groundbreaking-decision-all-california-high-schools-must-give-students-fair-procedure-st-francis-high-school-is-not-above-the-law/" target="_blank"&gt;stated&lt;/a&gt;, "This case is significant not only for our clients but for its groundbreaking effect on all private high schools in California, which are now legally required to provide fair procedure to students before punishing or expelling them."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The jury's verdict finally cleared our clients' names after four long years of repeated personal attacks from St. Francis High School. Schools are supposed to protect and nurture children, not sacrifice them when it is convenient for public relations purpose," added Karin Sweigart, counsel with the Dhillon Law Group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The former students' parents expressed hope that this result will prompt the school's board of directors to "hold those responsible for these actions and make needed changes to protect students moving forward."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://youtu.be/t-52CwewZhg" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:46:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mike Pence accuses Biden of impeachment hypocrisy amid Israel arms threat</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/mike-pence-accuses-biden-impeachment-hypocrisy-amid-israel-arms-threat</link><description>Former Vice President Mike Pence called out President Biden for threatening to withhold arms aid to Israel during a CNN interview, warning the Israelis not to go farther into Rafah.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:04:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Billionaire Tech CEO Calls Wokeness the “Central Risk” to America</title><link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/media/billionaire-tech-ceo-calls-wokeness-central-risk-america</link><description>The post Billionaire Tech CEO Calls Wokeness the “Central Risk” to America appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:19:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is the Corporate DEI Panic Finally Over?</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/09/is_the_corporate_dei_panic_finally_over_623319.html</link><description>Since the Supreme Court overturned the use of affirmative action in college admissions last summer, it seems like corporate America has been consumed by panic over diversity and inclusion.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 22:06:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CNN reporter sends blunt warning to Biden for claiming economy is doing great: 'Voters don't like being told they're wrong'</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/cnn-reporter-sends-blunt-warning-to-biden-for-claiming-economy-is-doing-great-voters-don-t-like-being-told-they-re-wrong-2668214239.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52211413&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C5%2C0%2C100</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52211413&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C5%2C0%2C100" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52211406&amp;amp;width=2000&amp;amp;height=1500&amp;amp;coordinates=217,0,264,0 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg%3Fid%3D52211406%26width%3D2000%26height%3D1500%26coordinates%3D217%2C0%2C264%2C0%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;CNN correspondent John King believes President Joe Biden should think twice before boasting about the economy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4P1E9iKf__Q" target="_blank"&gt;an interview with CNN anchor Erin Burnett&lt;/a&gt;, the president used rose-colored glasses to preach about the economy, claiming his economic policies have "already turned it around." Biden repeated his misleading claim about creating jobs and falsely said inflation was 9% when he came into office to claim that his policies have turned around inflation. The real problem, Biden claimed, is "corporate greed."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Voters don't like being told they're wrong."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those arguments and claims, King said, put Biden on "very dangerous ground" because, in his experience from the campaign trail, a lot of voters disagree with Biden.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"He is on very dangerous ground," King reacted. "I would say he risks offending — forgive my language — I would say he risks pissing off some of the voters I've talked to in my travels over the last six or seven months because they don't feel it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;King said he recently spoke with voters in Wisconsin and Michigan who are sour on the economy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those voters said they're facing a loss of jobs, the crushing weight of inflation, an unmanageable cost of living, and the inability to improve their lives — hardly anything good.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Voters don't like being told they're wrong," King observed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What is most interesting about King's observations is that polls and other interviews have corroborated them: Americans are generally sour on the economy because of inflation, high interest rates, and a rising cost of living that isn't slowing down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And yet, King claimed: "The statistics back up the president's argument that the economy is much better and is growing and is the strongest in the world."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But do they?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;First, inflation was not 9% when Biden entered office. The inflation rate when Biden entered office was 1.4%, &lt;a href="https://www.bls.gov/news.release/archives/cpi_02102021.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;according to the Bureau of Labor Statistics&lt;/a&gt;. It skyrocketed to 9.1% by June 2022 and remains above the Federal Reserve's targeted rate of 2%. In fact, inflation has increased every month of 2024 so far. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rate aside, inflation has a &lt;em&gt;compounding effect&lt;/em&gt;. So, despite inflation coming down from its highs two years ago, the purchasing power of each dollar in your pocket continues to diminish at an alarming rate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Second, the GDP &lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2024/04/25/gdp-q1-2024-increased-at-a-1point6percent-rate.html" target="_blank"&gt;grew at just 1.6%&lt;/a&gt; in the first quarter, much lower than expectations. It's not exactly the signal of a booming economy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Third, Biden has not created more than 10 million jobs, as he often likes to claim. Instead, the majority of jobs added to the economy under his presidency were people re-entering the workforce after the COVID pandemic lockdowns. And, while monthly jobs reports have looked good, those numbers are later revised, often &lt;a href="https://recruitonomics.com/revisions-to-the-job-numbers-may-trouble-the-fed/" target="_blank"&gt;to reflect that&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.barrons.com/livecoverage/february-jobs-report-today/card/labor-department-cuts-167-000-jobs-from-december-and-january-payrolls-FrRetAnGWH85TGfCeJ8n" target="_blank"&gt;fewer jobs were&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.foxbusiness.com/economy/initial-us-employment-reports-overstated-jobs" target="_blank"&gt;added than first claimed&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, the number of Americans filing for unemployment reached the highest point in eight months last week, Reuters &lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/us-weekly-jobless-claims-increase-more-than-expected-2024-05-09/" target="_blank"&gt;reported&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:16:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anti-Israel occupiers could lose federal student loans under new GOP Senate bill</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/anti-israel-occupiers-lose-federal-student-loans-new-gop-senate-bill</link><description>Sen. Thom Tillis, R-N.C., introduced a bill to strip financial aid from protesters who break the law at universities.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 20:41:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tranny Runner Dominates High School Girls Race in Latest Mocking of Women’s Sports</title><link>https://www.outkick.com/sports/transgender-runner-aayden-gallagher-dominates-high-school-girls-race-oregon-video</link><description>The post Tranny Runner Dominates High School Girls Race in Latest Mocking of Women’s Sports appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:19:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden's Economic Elitism Devastating Americans</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/09/bidens_economic_elitism_devastating_americans_623240.html</link><description>Despite administration and establishment media drumbeats, Americans aren't buying Biden's economic elitism.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:04:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>EXCLUSIVE: One Of Trump-World’s Favorite Lawyers Hatched Playbook With House GOP On Ending Biden Lawfare Against Trump</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/exclusive-one-of-trump-worlds-favorite-lawyers-hatched-playbook-with-house-gop-on-ending-biden-lawfare-against-trump-2668214028.html</link><image_url>https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/TrumpMikeDavis-copy-1-scaled.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/TrumpMikeDavis-copy-1-scaled.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;EXCLUSIVE: One Of Trump-World's Favorite Lawyers Hatched Playbook With House GOP On Ending Biden Lawfare Against Trump</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:10:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>House GOP drafting Biden impeachment articles over Israel aid cutoff threat</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/house-gop-drafting-biden-impeachment-articles-israel-aid-cutoff-threat</link><description>House Republicans are coming out with calls for President Biden to be impeached after he threatened to halt offensive weapons aid to Israel if it invaded Rafah.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 20:22:05 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>