<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 08:27:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The Deception of ‘One Health’: What Will World Leaders Be Willing to Give Up?</title><link>https://harbingersdaily.com/the-deception-of-one-health-what-will-world-leaders-be-willing-to-give-up/</link><description>The post The Deception of ‘One Health’: What Will World Leaders Be Willing to Give Up? appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:17:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>On CNN, Biden Tells Tales About Economy</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2024/05/09/realclearpolitics_bidens_cnn_interview_speaker_johnson_and_the_democrats_barron_trump_steps_into_politics_freedomworks_shuts_down.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:10:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Presbyterian Church In America Invites Professional Polarizer David French To Lecture Christians On Getting Along</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/presbyterian-church-in-america-invites-professional-polarizer-david-french-to-lecture-christians-on-getting-along-2668221483.html</link><image_url>https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Screenshot-2024-05-09-at-4.05.01%E2%80%AFPM.png</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Screenshot-2024-05-09-at-4.05.01%E2%80%AFPM.png" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Screenshot-2024-05-09-at-4.05.01 PM-1200x675.png crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Screenshot-2024-05-09-at-4.05.01%5Cu202fPM-1200x675.png%22%7D" expand=1]If the PCA wants to have David French talk about polarization, it should be as a poster child, not a panelist.&lt;/span&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:53:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alabama legislative session adjourned without final vote on gambling bill: 'Frustrated'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/alabama-legislative-session-adjourned-without-final-vote-gambling-bill-frustrated</link><description>Alabamians won't have a chance to vote on gambling within the state this year after lawmakers failed to come to an agreement during the latest legislative session before it adjourned.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:02:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Thanks a Lot, Speaker Johnson: FBI Brass Just Urged Agents to Use Warrantless Wiretaps on US Citizens</title><link>https://revolver.news/2024/05/thanks-mike-johnson-wiretaps/</link><description>The post Thanks a Lot, Speaker Johnson: FBI Brass Just Urged Agents to Use Warrantless Wiretaps on US Citizens appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:16:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Bill Ackman's Anti-Woke Crusade Paid Off</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/09/how_bill_ackmans_anti-woke_crusade_paid_off_623349.html</link><description>Shares of his fund, Pershing Square Holdings, have soared since he's taken to X to criticize corporate diversity efforts, support Israel, and bash student protests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:59:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is the GOP still pushing the left’s decarceration agenda?</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/why-is-the-gop-still-pushing-the-lefts-decarceration-agenda-2668221284.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/why-is-the-gop-still-pushing-the-lefts-decarceration-agenda.jpg?id=52214583&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C197%2C0%2C197</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/why-is-the-gop-still-pushing-the-lefts-decarceration-agenda.jpg?id=52214583&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C197%2C0%2C197" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/why-is-the-gop-still-pushing-the-lefts-decarceration-agenda.jpg?id=52214583&amp;amp;width=1245&amp;amp;height=700&amp;amp;coordinates=0,132,0,132 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/why-is-the-gop-still-pushing-the-lefts-decarceration-agenda.jpg%3Fid%3D52214583%26width%3D1245%26height%3D700%26coordinates%3D0%2C132%2C0%2C132%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reducing sentences for our already under-incarcerated criminal population is a great goal of George Soros. Yet for the past 15 years, this dystopian objective has been supported by the Kochs and other libertarian front groups that convinced Republicans — and, eventually, Donald Trump — to join the jailbreak bandwagon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, despite the ubiquitous recognition that we have a violent crime problem because of weak deterrent power against criminals, particularly juveniles, the Koch-funded groups continue to wield influence among Republicans to further weaken the criminal deterrent rather than strengthening it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is a reason we enjoyed a drop in crime under tougher drug laws, and there is a reason we are seeing a resurgence in crime now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These same organizations are dead silent when it comes to the January 6 trials, which should be their Super Bowl — the one example where their “over-criminalization” and “over-incarceration” talking points are on point.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watch any Republican campaign ad, and you will see universal condemnation of the “Biden crime wave,” with the portrayal of violent, decaying blue cities. You’d think this would indicate Republicans have finally learned their lesson and come to regret joining Soros and the left to release criminals &lt;em&gt;en masse&lt;/em&gt; in red states and pass the federal First Step Act.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet when it comes to actual legislation, not only are Republicans failing to push for tougher sentencing, but they continue, at the behest of Koch-funded groups such as Right on Crime, to push lighter sentencing for drug traffickers, gangbangers, repeat felons, parole violators, and violent juvenile criminals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just last month, Republican-aligned advocacy groups allied with &lt;a href="https://www.fwd.us/news/long-sentences-dont-make-mississippi-safer-lawmakers-must-reject-mandatory-minimum-bills/" target="_blank"&gt;Mark Zuckerberg-funded Fwd.us&lt;/a&gt; to hollow out Mississippi Senate Bill 2174, which originally proposed mandatory minimums for car theft, despite originally passing the Senate with every Republican and three-quarters of Democrats. The bill &lt;a href="https://magnoliatribune.com/2024/04/03/house-removes-mandatory-minimum-sentences-from-senates-auto-theft-legislation/" target="_blank"&gt;was gutted&lt;/a&gt; before heading to the governor for his signature.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SB 2175, which would have established mandatory minimums for possession of stolen property, died in conference committee. Instead, the legislature wound up passing yet another bill expanding parole, which was championed by Right on Crime.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For some reason, despite the supposed awareness of the crime wave, every legislative effort from Republicans and their think tanks seems to be aimed at coddling the criminal, not victims of crime. And no, none of these bills targets the overzealous prosecution of political opponents.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Given the ubiquitous nature of juvenile crime, and carjackings in particular, it’s shocking how we still can’t get tougher sentencing even in red states.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And in the GOP-controlled House, where lawmakers are constantly blaming Joe Biden for crime and drugs, the Judiciary Committee has failed to pass a single tough-on-crime bill — beefing up sentencing, limiting supervised release, or getting tough on drug traffickers and gun felons that the Justice Department refuses to prosecute. Instead, GOP members have sponsored and marked up bills that seem to focus on the well-being of criminals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Armstrong’s bill highlights why we have so many repeat violent offenders who barely serve time in prison despite robust rap sheets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last November, the House Judiciary Committee considered a bill by Representative Kelly Armstrong (R-N.D.) to make it more difficult to impose longer sentences for career criminals. Armstrong aspires to be the next governor of North Dakota. Without much thought, the committee members unanimously passed &lt;a href="https://www.congress.gov/bill/118th-congress/house-bill/5430/text?s=6&amp;amp;r=5" target="_blank"&gt;H.R. 5430&lt;/a&gt;, which would prohibit judges from considering “acquitted conduct” when sentencing someone for later convictions. Acquitted conduct is defined either as a charge for which the defendant was found not guilty or any conduct underlying any charge that was dismissed after a motion for acquittal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Armstrong’s bill highlights why we have so many repeat violent offenders who barely serve time in prison despite robust rap sheets. We are not discussing first-time offenders here. These are people who have just been convicted of a crime.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is prudent for a judge to consider the totality of circumstances. Often, it’s clear that these criminals have committed many other crimes but got off on technicalities. You can’t convict someone for that, but if the facts are proven by a preponderance of evidence (but not beyond a reasonable doubt) that a defendant was involved in other crimes, it makes sense for the judge to lean toward the higher end of sentencing guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Keep in mind, these are people in the federal system who generally have long rap sheets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Isn’t it ironic that these same organizations and politicians who hate mandatory minimums because they supposedly hamper a judge’s ability to look at the totality of circumstances to rule more leniently are suddenly offended by the discretion of a judge to sentence more strictly?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;None of this is about reform but about one-sided leniency to take an already shrinking prison population (down 28% over the past decade while crime increases) and diminish it as quickly as possible. None of these people are pushing legislation to rein in abusive January 6 prosecutions. By definition, a bill like H.R. 5430 is aimed at habitual degenerates who are constantly in court, not for first-time misdemeanor offenders like the January 6 defendants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;H.R. 5430 passed 23-0, but some prominent anti-jailbreakers, such as Chip Roy (R-Texas), Andy Biggs (R-Ariz.), Ben Cline (R-Va.), and Ken Buck (R-Colo.) were not present. While it’s unclear how they would have voted, it’s interesting that the bill was timed for consideration when the other side of the debate would not be aired.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s also peculiar that Republicans unanimously decry the drug crisis, but they have declined to pass a single bill toughening sentencing on even the most hardened traffickers of the most dangerous drugs, like fentanyl. Instead, they have proposed several bills promoting even more leniency for drug peddlers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Armstrong, a criminal defense attorney by trade, has also introduced &lt;a href="https://www.congress.gov/bill/118th-congress/house-bill/1062?s=3&amp;amp;r=16" target="_blank"&gt;H.R. 1062&lt;/a&gt;, which would eliminate the sentencing disparity between crack and powder cocaine. Under current law, the criminal penalty for possessing 18 grams of crack cocaine is the same as possessing one gram of powdered cocaine, meaning the bill would give possessing equal amounts of either drug the same penalties. It is now roundly condemned by mindless race-panderers in both parties.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bottom line is crack cocaine traffickers are &lt;a href="https://www.ussc.gov/sites/default/files/pdf/research-and-publications/quick-facts/Crack_Cocaine_FY21.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;more than twice as likely&lt;/a&gt; as &lt;a href="https://www.ussc.gov/sites/default/files/pdf/research-and-publications/quick-facts/Powder_Cocaine_FY21.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;powdered cocaine traffickers&lt;/a&gt; to involve weapons in their crimes. Crack cocaine traffickers are also the most likely to be rearrested — nearly &lt;a href="https://www.ussc.gov/sites/default/files/pdf/research-and-publications/research-publications/2017/20170221_Recidivism-Drugs.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;60%&lt;/a&gt; are rearrested within a few years of release, often for violent offenses.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is a reason we enjoyed a drop in crime under tougher drug laws (which affect many other crimes), and there is a reason we are seeing a resurgence in crime now. Armstrong and other members of the Judiciary Committee have introduced other bills perpetuating the myth that people are in federal prison for low-level drug offenses, even after we’ve already released anyone who could possibly fit that description. Yet bizarrely, Republicans have yet to introduce a bill to toughen &lt;em&gt;any&lt;/em&gt; area of criminal law.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Evidently, the crime wave has not gotten bad enough. I shudder to think what needs to happen before Republican special interests realize where “criminal justice reform” is coming from and where it is headed. It’s just a shame that January 6 defendants and all those targeted for political beliefs don’t seem to benefit from these “reforms” for “low level, first-time” offenders. No, that sentiment is reserved for Black Lives Matter rioters in the streets.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IRS urged to probe tax-exempt groups supporting anti-Israel protests</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/irs-urged-probe-tax-exempt-groups-supporting-anti-israel-protests</link><description>Several Republicans signed onto a letter calling for a number of groups to have their tax-exempt statuses investigated over their support for anti-Israel protests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 09:00:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Woman Lived in a Grocery Store Sign in Michigan With a Computer and Keurig for a Year</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/woman-lived-grocery-store-sign-michigan-computer-keurig/</link><description>Contractors in Midland, Michigan, recently discovered a 34-year-old woman living inside a Family Fare grocery store sign. The woman, whose name was not disclosed, had been residing in the sign for approximately a year and had access to amenities such as a computer, printer, and coffee maker, according to Officer Brennon Warren of the Midland […]
The post Woman Lived in a Grocery Store Sign in Michigan With a Computer and Keurig for a Year appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:57:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Faces New Democratic Divisions After Israel Shift</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/10/biden_faces_new_democratic_divisions_after_israel_shift_623390.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:58:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>North Carolina’s Early Voting Locations Illegally Favor Democrats</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/north-carolinas-early-voting-locations-illegally-favor-democrats-2668221251.html</link><image_url>https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/8623348962_6c0ae4103b_k-e1715277926862.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/8623348962_6c0ae4103b_k-e1715277926862.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img class="rm-shortcode" id="e409b" src="https://www.conservativereview.com/media-library/eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpbWFnZSI6Imh0dHBzOi8vdGhlZmVkZXJhbGlzdC5jb20vd3AtY29udGVudC91cGxvYWRzLzIwMjQvMDUvODYyMzM0ODk2Ml82YzBhZTQxMDNiX2stMTIwMHg2NzUuanBnIiwiZXhwaXJlc19hdCI6MTcyNDMxMDQ1M30._OOjCIbux4_w-PcG6QBd79kmCpKQkXiElDQnS54aS2M/image.jpg" /&gt;Data reveals noncompliance with a North Carolina statutory requirement for neutrality in early voting venues.&lt;/span&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:43:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GOP Rep calls on Biden to denounce, reject cash from progressive groups fueling anti-Israel protests</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/biden-should-denounce-progressive-groups-fueling-anti-israel-protests-reject-cash-from-shared-donors-gop-rep</link><description>GOP Rep. Darrell Issa told Fox News Digital it would 'very helpful' if Biden denounced progressive donors who are fueling anti-Israel protests but acknowledged its unlikely.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 09:00:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Working Moms Shouldn’t Have to Choose Between Girlboss and Tradwife</title><link>https://thefederalist.com/2024/05/10/working-moms-shouldnt-have-to-choose-between-girl-boss-or-tradwife/</link><description>The post Working Moms Shouldn’t Have to Choose Between Girlboss and Tradwife appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:13:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Tries to Have It Both Ways With New Asylum Rules</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/10/biden_tries_to_have_it_both_ways_with_new_asylum_rules_623391.html</link><description>The president is under pressure from Republicans and progressives as humanitarian crisis builds and immigration remains a key voter issue</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:51:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meta Relies On ‘Human Rights Norms’ To Censor Protected Speech, Board Member Admits</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/meta-relies-on-human-rights-norms-to-censor-protected-speech-board-member-admits-2668221013.html</link><image_url>https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/52320866096_1b8a2e1240_o.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/52320866096_1b8a2e1240_o.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img class="rm-shortcode" id="3f53d" src="https://www.conservativereview.com/media-library/eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpbWFnZSI6Imh0dHBzOi8vdGhlZmVkZXJhbGlzdC5jb20vd3AtY29udGVudC91cGxvYWRzLzIwMjQvMDUvNTIzMjA4NjYwOTZfMWI4YTJlMTI0MF9vLTEyMDB4Njc1LmpwZyIsImV4cGlyZXNfYXQiOjE3NzgxNzk3MjV9.AGdrZRE58-MjidAW0DqJ0m_5exlkS3UZzVxotm1cqf0/image.jpg" /&gt;A Meta Oversight Board member dismisses 'First Amendment jurisprudence,' even as the FBI restarts its social media censorship machine.&lt;/span&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:33:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'We are so innocent': Top 5 moments of Trump trial, from mistrial denials to Stormy Daniels' testimony</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/we-are-so-innocent-top-5-moments-trump-trial-mistrial-denials-stormy-daniels-testimony</link><description>Former President Trump will attend court Friday after a week of salacious testimony from Stormy Danials and the denial of multiple mistrial motions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 09:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oops: First Neuralink Brain Implant in Human Malfunctions</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/oops-first-neuralink-brain-implant-human-malfunctions/</link><description>(Discern Media)—The first human to receive a Neuralink implant experienced a malfunction when several threads designed to record neural activity retracted from the brain, as revealed by the Elon Musk-owned startup. The incident occurred in the weeks following the surgery in late January that implanted the Neuralink hardware in 29-year-old Noland Arbaugh, a quadriplegic. As […]
The post Oops: First Neuralink Brain Implant in Human Malfunctions appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:11:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>You Cannot Defend Yourself</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/10/you_cannot_defend_yourself_623389.html</link><description>The group quota regime has largely succeeded in stripping its opponents, the American people, of the power to fight back.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:47:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekend Watch: Watching the watchers in 'Cinemania'</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/weekend-watch-watching-the-watchers-in-cinemania-2668221277.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52211408&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C62%2C0%2C67</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52211408&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C62%2C0%2C67" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52211408&amp;amp;width=1245&amp;amp;height=700&amp;amp;coordinates=0,39,0,44 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg%3Fid%3D52211408%26width%3D1245%26height%3D700%26coordinates%3D0%2C39%2C0%2C44%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today, it is possible to watch more than half of the movies ever made with the touch of a button. The 2002 documentary &lt;a href="https://www.justwatch.com/us/movie/cinemania" target="_blank"&gt;"Cinemania"&lt;/a&gt; takes us back to a time when being a dedicated cineaste required significantly more effort. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;None of the five New Yorkers profiled here are married or work (four are on disability and one is independently wealthy), which means they can spend their days in one small repertory theater after another, meticulously cross-referencing screening times and public transit routes to cram in as many films as possible. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These movies aren't always easy to appreciate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This obsessive moviegoing seems like a kind of mental hoarding; indeed, each of the subjects has a cluttered home to match. Roberta, the sole female of the bunch, lives in an apartment crammed with memorabilia of dubious value, including promotional plastic cups, and was banned from one theater for accosting an employee who ripped her ticket stub. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And yet they're all charmingly knowledgeable and intelligent. “A commitment to cinema means one must have a technically deviant lifestyle,” says 30-something trust-funder Jack in a particularly self-aware moment. Their company is fascinating for 80 minutes or so. Longer than that, and you might start pondering your own compulsive enthusiasms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;img class="rm-shortcode" id="2531a" src="https://www.conservativereview.com/media-library/eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpbWFnZSI6Imh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnRoZWJsYXplLmNvbS9tZWRpYS1saWJyYXJ5L2ltYWdlLmpwZz9pZD01MjIxMTQyNCZhbXA7d2lkdGg9OTgwIiwiZXhwaXJlc19hdCI6MTc3NTI0NTEwNX0.baQ3el-NQUuAAWwKyGIOjoVYqLDQ9qCjUIxl3pLU-zg/image.jpg" /&gt;                        MGM&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The characters of the 1952 masterpiece &lt;a href="https://www.justwatch.com/us/search?q=singin%20in%20the%20rain" target="_blank"&gt;"Singin' in the Rain"&lt;/a&gt; have an especially urgent "commitment to cinema" — it's how they put food on the table. The movie may look so ancient to us, it's easy to forget it was itself a period piece. Set in 1927, it stars Gene Kelly as a silent film star struggling to make the transition to "talkies."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The midcentury studio musical is one of the pinnacles of American moviemaking. The first thing a viewer weaned on CGI spectacle will notice is the sheer physical talent on display: Vaudeville veterans like Kelly and Judy Garland did not require camera trickery or audio enhancement to wow audiences with their singing and dancing. Elaborate and beautifully executed set pieces become all the more impressive when you consider that they had to be pulled off entirely with practical effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These movies aren't always easy to appreciate; their rigid conventions and stylized emotion can seem corny and shallow to the uninitiated. And yet, they convey depths of feeling to rival any of the "grittier" films that supplanted them by the end of the ‘60s. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Singin' in the Rain," for example, is at once a sophisticated romantic comedy, a sharp showbiz satire, and a crowd-pleasing display of song and dance. Nuanced meditation on the relationship between mass entertainment and art. It also provides a dazzling showcase for the charms of Kelly, Debbie Reynolds, and Donald O'Connor, which in itself is worth the price of admission. &lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden admin's National Guard 'power grab' slammed by former general as governors put up rare united front</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/biden-admins-national-guard-power-grab-slammed-former-general-governors-put-rare-united-front</link><description>A plan that could let the Air Force transfer Air National Guard troops to the Space Force has been met with fierce opposition from governors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>