<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 03:52:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Church Committee Flashback: CIA Has Weapon That Makes Murder Look Like a Natural Heart Attack [VIDEO]</title><link>https://rumble.com/v54erw6-church-committee-flashback-cia-has-weapon-that-makes-murder-look-like-a-nat.html</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>The post Church Committee Flashback: CIA Has Weapon That Makes Murder Look Like a Natural Heart Attack [VIDEO] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 06:56:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Texas Supreme Court upholds state ban on gender transition treatment for minors</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/texas-supreme-court-upholds-state-ban-gender-transition-treatment-minors</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>The Texas Supreme Court upheld the state's ban on gender transition treatment for children in an 8-1 decision after a lawsuit that argued the law harms transgender teenagers.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 06:57:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Buzz Around Precious Metals “Prepper Bars” Is Ramping Up</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/buzz-around-precious-metals-prepper-bars-is-ramping/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>Editor’s Note: This article and any related communications are for informational purposes only and should not be considered as financial advice. We do not provide personalized investment, financial, or legal advice. This outlet benefits from purchases made through our sponsors. Americans who want to easily store and carry gold or silver are increasingly turning to […] The post Buzz Around Precious Metals “Prepper Bars” Is Ramping Up appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 06:49:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump says 'biggest problem' not Biden's age, 'decline,' but his policies in first appearance since debate</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-says-biggest-problem-not-bidens-age-decline-his-policies-first-appearance-debate</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>In his first rally following the debate, former President Trump told Virginia voters the "biggest problem" for the U.S. is not Biden's "decline" but his policies.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 02:23:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chip Roy Files Resolution Calling on Chlamydia Harris to Invoke the 25th Amendment</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/chip-roy-files-resolution-calling-chlamydia-harris-invoke/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>(The Daily Signal)—A leading House Republican filed a resolution in Congress urging Vice President Kamala Harris to invoke the 25th Amendment in the wake of President Joe Biden’s performance Thursday night in the first debate with former President Donald Trump. Even Democrats and Biden supporters described the president’s performance as poor, though few have suggested […] The post Chip Roy Files Resolution Calling on Chlamydia Harris to Invoke the 25th Amendment appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 06:00:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Speaker’s Lobby: A Universal Interest</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/speakers-lobby-universal-interest</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>President Joe Biden and Former President Donald Trump faced off in the first Presidential Debate, showcasing the weight of live television in politics today.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 01:17:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>“Here’s the Issue”: MSNBC Data Guru Lays Out the Obstacles to Democrats Replacing Dementia Joe</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/heres-issue-msnbc-data-guru-lays-obstacles-democrats/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>(DCNF)—MSNBC data guru Steve Kornacki said that Democrats had multiple obstacles to overcome when it came to replacing President Joe Biden on the ballot Friday. Democrats are considering how to replace Biden after the president’s gaffe-filled performance during the 90-minute debate moderated by CNN hosts Jake Tapper and Dana Bash Thursday night. Kornacki noted that […] The post “Here’s the Issue”: MSNBC Data Guru Lays Out the Obstacles to Democrats Replacing Dementia Joe appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 06:00:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cornell Law professor calls to invoke 25th Amendment after Biden's debate performance</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/cornell-law-professor-calls-invoke-25th-amendment-biden-debate-performance</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>After President Biden's weak debate performance Thursday night, Cornell Law Professor William Jacobson called for the 25th Amendment to be invoked.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 01:15:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Skyrocketing Food Prices Are Prompting Many Americans to Stock Up on Long-Term Storage Beef</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/skyrocketing-food-prices-are-prompting-many-americans-stock/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>If one watches corporate media or listens to the narrative coming out of Washington DC, inflation is going down and everyone should be happy with the economy. If one looks at the prices at the grocery store, they realize that the narrative doesn’t match reality. With some foods skyrocketing in price over the last year, […] The post Skyrocketing Food Prices Are Prompting Many Americans to Stock Up on Long-Term Storage Beef appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 06:00:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WATCH: Dem. Rep. snatches phone in testy airport exchange over Biden's mental clarity: 'Who owns you?'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/watch-dem-rep-snatches-phone-in-testy-airport-exchange-over-bidens-mental-clarity-who-owns-you</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>Democratic Rep. Marcy Kaptur got into a contentious exchange with a man at a Detroit airport who asked her about President Biden's cognitive abilities after Thursday's debate.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 00:21:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>