<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 06:59:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Taylor Lorenz Goes After Libs of TikTok Again</title><link>https://twitchy.com/brettt/2024/04/29/taylor-lorenz-goes-after-libs-of-tiktok-again-n2395703</link><description>The post Taylor Lorenz Goes After Libs of TikTok Again appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 11:39:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Growing RFK Jr Coalition</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/29/the_growing_rfk_jr_coalition_622701.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 03:47:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dem Fundraising Platform ActBlue Takes a Cut of Donations to Michigan State University’s Anti-Israel Tent Encampment</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/dem-fundraising-platform-actblue-takes-a-cut-of-donations-to-michigan-state-universitys-anti-israel-tent-encampment-2668094360.html</link><image_url>https://freebeacon.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/MixCollage-29-Apr-2024-03-27-PM-1990-e1714418890834.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://freebeacon.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/MixCollage-29-Apr-2024-03-27-PM-1990-e1714418890834.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Democratic Party’s primary fundraising platform helped facilitate donations to the anti-Israel encampment at Michigan State University. ActBlue is set to receive a 3.95 percent cut of those donations, according to its stated policies. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://freebeacon.com/campus/dem-fundraising-platform-actblue-takes-a-cut-of-donations-to-michigan-state-universitys-anti-israel-tent-encampment/"&gt;Dem Fundraising Platform ActBlue Takes a Cut of Donations to Michigan State University’s Anti-Israel Tent Encampment&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://freebeacon.com"&gt;Washington Free Beacon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 10:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Senate gridlock could worsen with Romney, Sinema, Manchin retirements: experts</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/senate-gridlock-worsen-romney-sinema-manchin-retirements-experts</link><description>The Senate is losing three of the more moderate lawmakers in the body, and some experts predict it could lead to more gridlock in the already narrowly divided upper chamber.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 09:00:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Columbia Begins Suspending Students Who Refuse to Leave Encampment [VIDEO]</title><link>https://rumble.com/v4sfbr3-columbia-begins-suspending-students-who-refuse-to-leave-encampment.html</link><description>The post Columbia Begins Suspending Students Who Refuse to Leave Encampment [VIDEO] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 10:38:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The State of the American Teenager</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/29/thenbspstatenbspofnbspthenbspamericannbspteenager_622657.html</link><description>From the dislocating effects of the pandemic that impacted teens' academic and social development to the effects of widespread smartphone use, there are plenty of reasons to be concerned.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 03:37:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Noem defends decision to kill dog, saying she 'was being a responsible parent, dog owner, and neighbor'</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/noem-defends-decision-to-kill-dog-saying-she-was-being-a-responsible-parent-dog-owner-and-neighbor-2668092807.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52134938&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C171</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52134938&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C171" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52134938&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;coordinates=0,0,0,1 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg%3Fid%3D52134938%26width%3D1200%26height%3D800%26coordinates%3D0%2C0%2C0%2C1%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;South Dakota Gov. Kristi Noem has defended her decision to kill a young dog many years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/books/2024/apr/26/trump-kristi-noem-shot-dog-and-goat-book" target="_blank"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/a&gt; reported that in her forthcoming book, "No Going Back: The Truth on What's Wrong with Politics and How We Move America Forward," Noem recounted the story about the dog, Cricket, that had been around 14 months old. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the outlet, Noem recalled that she had taken the dog on a pheasant hunt with older canines, desiring to calm Cricket down and start to teach her how to act. But she was "out of her mind with excitement, chasing all those birds and having the time of her life."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Noem stopped to speak to a family after that hunt, the dog escaped from her truck and killed the family's chickens, "grabb[ing] one chicken at a time, crunching it to death with one bite, then dropping it to attack another," Noem recounted, according to the outlet. When she grabbed the canine, Cricket "whipped around to bite me," she noted. Noem cut a check "for the price they asked, and helped them dispose of the carcasses littering the scene of the crime," she reportedly indicated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I hated that dog," Noem noted, according to the Guardian, which reported that she described the dog as "untrainable," "dangerous to anyone she came in contact with," and "less than worthless … as a hunting dog."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I realised I had to put her down," Noem recalled, according to the outlet. "It was not a pleasant job," she noted, "but it had to be done."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Noem's story about killing the young dog sparked significant criticism, but she has defended her decision.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I can understand why some people are upset about a 20 year old story of Cricket, one of the working dogs at our ranch, in my upcoming book — No Going Back," she &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/KristiNoem/status/1784631108207849781" target="_blank"&gt;tweeted&lt;/a&gt;. "The fact is, South Dakota law states that dogs who attack and kill livestock can be put down. Given that Cricket had shown aggressive behavior toward people by biting them, I decided what I did," she noted. "I followed the law and was being a responsible parent, dog owner, and neighbor."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;         —  (@)        &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/KristiNoem/status/1784631108207849781"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 05:06:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NY v Trump criminal trial begins its 3rd week as former president accused of gag order violations</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/ny-v-trump-criminal-trial-begins-3rd-week-former-president-accused-gag-order-violations</link><description>The historic and unprecedented criminal trial of former President Trump is set to resume for its third week Tuesday.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 09:00:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Viktor Orban “Ran George Soros and His Operations” Out of Hungary – Americans Can Learn From That</title><link>https://humanevents.com/2024/04/29/exclusive-viktor-orban-ran-george-soros-and-his-operations-out-of-hungary-americans-can-learn-from-that</link><description>The post Viktor Orban “Ran George Soros and His Operations” Out of Hungary – Americans Can Learn From That appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 10:24:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Great Week for American Workers</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/29/a_great_week_for_american_workers_622667.html</link><description>Thanks to autoworkers, baristas, and some Biden administration agencies</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 03:37:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tulsi Gabbard on whether she'd accept a Trump VP offer: 'I would say yes'</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/tulsi-gabbard-on-whether-she-d-accept-a-trump-vp-offer-i-would-say-yes-2668092546.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.png?id=52134707&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C118%2C0%2C0</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.png?id=52134707&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C118%2C0%2C0" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.png?id=52134705&amp;amp;width=2000&amp;amp;height=1500&amp;amp;coordinates=798,0,4,0 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.png%3Fid%3D52134705%26width%3D2000%26height%3D1500%26coordinates%3D798%2C0%2C4%2C0%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former U.S. Rep. Tulsi Gabbard indicated to BlazeTV host Dave Rubin that if former President Donald Trump asked her to serve as his 2024 running mate, she would accept the offer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gabbard told Rubin, "If that call came I would say yes." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She indicated that getting the U.S. "back on track" would involve having courageous government figures "who care more about the country than they do about the political elite in Washington, and actually rooting out the deep rot that exists within our bureaucracies, the administrative state, the deep state in Washington."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;BlazeTV host Steve Deace &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/SteveDeaceShow/status/1785030973316366595" target="_blank"&gt;noted&lt;/a&gt; in a tweet that Gabbard is his "prediction for Trump's running mate."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gabbard, who &lt;a href="https://bioguide.congress.gov/search/bio/G000571" target="_blank"&gt;served&lt;/a&gt; in Congress as a Hawaii Democrat from early 2013 through early 2021, backed Joe Biden in 2020 when she &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/TulsiGabbard/status/1240650484546859008" target="_blank"&gt;dropped&lt;/a&gt; her bid for the Democratic presidential nomination. But she &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/tulsi-gabbard-leaves-democratic-party" target="_self"&gt;announced&lt;/a&gt; in 2022 that she was "leaving the Democratic Party." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Love-Country-left-Democratic-Party/dp/1684514851/ref=sr_1_1?crid=2P31H33J1MYJY&amp;amp;dib=eyJ2IjoiMSJ9.J-CYwfL5AH2zY7Ta4zAf-i5PW32eAT0U7G4J7kMUsglMuYIjDT_UldoG9dqneoj4a3J9Ia4sni-W5uR_vAKWgQ7UlGqmLR6i4TIVyh0J6VCfxypPEpJUs--K_jipak27OPYMZFfAZxOLDoZzsNcVZW-qAuPU3a6pg_qu4I58rCi-tc1o_96Z5eyhkeR7OxyMZDilrsEedpqepZRZDV4LDQqiW8nF1qOfqz4d2nDhQow.K18wzJ5UOpRn57u5Rpb4XP9z0GFGWL7Mq6YeOmTtjx8&amp;amp;dib_tag=se&amp;amp;keywords=tulsi+gabbard&amp;amp;qid=1714439457&amp;amp;sprefix=tulsi+gabbard%2Caps%2C130&amp;amp;sr=8-1" target="_blank"&gt;book&lt;/a&gt;, "For Love of Country: Leave the Democrat Party Behind," is slated for release on April 30.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/tulsi-gabbard-turned-rfk-jrs-offer-running-mate/story?id=108723568#:~:text=Tulsi%20Gabbard%2C%20who%20left%20the,would%20be%20his%20running%20mate." target="_blank"&gt;ABC News&lt;/a&gt; reported that Gabbard, referring to independent presidential candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr., said in a statement, "I met with Kennedy several times, and we have become good friends." Gabbard reportedly said in the statement, "He asked if I would be his running mate. After careful consideration, I respectfully declined."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kennedy &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/kennedy-announces-shanahan-running-mate" target="_blank"&gt;picked&lt;/a&gt; Nicole Shanahan as his running mate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Former Vice President Mike Pence, who served with Trump from early 2017 through early 2021, has &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/pence-wont-endorse-trump-2024" target="_blank"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; that he will not endorse Trump in 2024. Pence mounted a Republican presidential primary bid last year but then dropped it months later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 03:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dem mayor's spox defends meeting with controversial Chinese diplomat who praised CCP</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/dem-mayors-spox-defends-meeting-controversial-diplomat-praised-ccp</link><description>A controversial Chinese diplomat who has met with a variety of U.S. lawmakers and officials recently appeared alongside Democrat Philadelphia Mayor Cherelle Parker.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 09:00:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Title IX Definitions Rewritten to Include Controversial Sexual Orientation and Gender Ideology Theories</title><link>https://www.independentsentinel.com/title-ix-definitions-rewritten-to-include-controversial-sexual-orientation-and-gender-ideology-theories/</link><description>The post Title IX Definitions Rewritten to Include Controversial Sexual Orientation and Gender Ideology Theories appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 10:24:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GOP Establishment's Days Are Numbered</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/28/gop_establishments_days_are_numbered_622647.html</link><description>The recent House vote on foreign aid while the southern border remains wide open reveals a divide within the GOP.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 03:37:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Northwestern University agreement with anti-Israel protesters includes Palestinian student scholarships and visiting faculty</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/northwestern-university-agreement-with-anti-israel-protesters-includes-palestinian-student-scholarships-and-visiting-faculty-2668092512.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52134699&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C45%2C0%2C46</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52134699&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C45%2C0%2C46" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52134699&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;coordinates=181,0,182,0 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg%3Fid%3D52134699%26width%3D1200%26height%3D800%26coordinates%3D181%2C0%2C182%2C0%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Northwestern University officials &lt;a href="https://www.chicagotribune.com/2024/04/29/northwestern-university-reaches-agreement-with-protesters/" target="_blank"&gt;announced&lt;/a&gt; Monday that it had reached an agreement with anti-Israel protesters that included funding for Palestinian scholarships and for Palestinian visiting faculty members.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The agreement comes five days after the pro-Palestinian demonstrators began building an encampment in the middle of Deering Meadow on the Evanston Campus. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/chicago/news/northwestern-university-deal-pro-palestinian-protesters/" target="_blank"&gt;WBBM-TV reported&lt;/a&gt; soon after the agreement was announced that tents were already being dismantled. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This agreement was forged by the hard work of students and faculty working closely with members of the administration to help ensure that the violence and escalation we have seen elsewhere does not happen here at Northwestern,” said University President Michael Schill in a campus-wide email. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Schill said that university officials agreed to allow peaceful demonstrations to continue until June 1 but that the demonstrators must agree to observe their security regulations. The university will provide funding for two visiting at-risk Palestinian faculty members for two years and for five visiting at-risk Palestinian students for four years. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the protesters were angry that the deal was struck with a small group of demonstrators that they claimed were not representative of the entire group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Schill also said that the demonstrations could only include students, faculty, and staff in order to exclude outside participants. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Acts of antisemitism, anti-Muslim/Arab racism, and hate will not be tolerated, and community members who can be identified participating in such acts will face disciplinary action,” he wrote in the email. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Junior Abhi Nimmagadda told WBBM that the agreement was a tremendous achievement for the anti-Israel movement. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"No other university, to my knowledge, has been able to secure wins this great," said Nimmagadda. "I don't believe my heart has been fuller. I'm very, very proud of everything we have been able to achieve." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But other students were reportedly angry that the university did not agree to concrete steps to end any investments that might be tied to the state of Israel. WBBM reported that they felt "blind-sided" and accused those who made the agreement of being "sellouts." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The university did agree to relaunch an advisory council to review the organization's investments and answer protesters' questions within 30 days. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The private research university serves more than 23,400 students and is located in Evanston, Illinois. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Here's more about the protests:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;! &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 03:15:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Columbia protestors occupy building as Trump blames Biden for antisemitic demonstrations</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/columbia-caves-trump-blames-biden-antisemitic-protests</link><description>The White House stated President Biden has denounced campus antisemitism, but former President Trump is calling out his opponent as anti-Israel protests across the nation rage on.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 08:00:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Satanic Temple Seeks to Introduce Ministers in Oklahoma Public Schools if “Chaplain Bill” Becomes Law</title><link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2024/04/satanic-temple-seeks-introduce-ministers-oklahoma-schools-if/</link><description>The post Satanic Temple Seeks to Introduce Ministers in Oklahoma Public Schools if “Chaplain Bill” Becomes Law appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 10:24:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Academic Freedom Under Fire</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/29/academic_freedom_under_fire_622663.html</link><description>Politicians despise it. Administrators aren't defending it. But it made our universities great-and we'll miss it when it's gone.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 03:37:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Man allegedly vandalized cars at New Hampshire GOP convention, police say they found guns and 'suicide manifesto' at his home</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/man-allegedly-vandalized-cars-at-new-hampshire-gop-convention-police-say-they-found-guns-and-suicide-manifesto-at-his-home-2668092455.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52134663&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C64%2C0%2C27</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52134663&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C64%2C0%2C27" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52134663&amp;amp;width=1245&amp;amp;height=700&amp;amp;coordinates=0,0,60,0 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg%3Fid%3D52134663%26width%3D1245%26height%3D700%26coordinates%3D0%2C0%2C60%2C0%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;A man who was arrested for &lt;a href="https://patch.com/new-hampshire/concord-nh/new-hampshire-republicans-threatened-cars-keyed-party-convention-concord" target="_blank"&gt;allegedly vandalizing&lt;/a&gt; almost a dozen cars outside of a New Hampshire Republican convention was denied bail after police found weapons and a manifesto at his home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Police said 37-year-old Lawrence Anthony Dunlap keyed the cars on April 13 as Republicans were at a biennual event at the Christa McAuliffe Auditorium at Concord High School. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It seems as if someone knew there was a Republican event going on at the high school, and this was their chance to tell Republicans they hate us,” said GOP delegate Di Lothrop at the time. “Divisiveness at its worst!”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Others reported threats made around the same time. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Concord Police Det. Sgt. Benjamin Mitchell said that they were able to obtain surveillance video of a suspect with a beard, long hair, and riding a long skateboard near the cars. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They identified the man as Dunlap and arrested him on Friday. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Police said a search warrant at his home “yielded firearms, a manifesto, suicide notes, and a bag containing zip ties, masks, and gloves." A weapon described as a "medieval mace" was also found in the man's belongings. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deputy Chief John Thomas &lt;a href="https://www.concordmonitor.com/Lawrence-Dunlap-plea-Concord-NH-GOP-vandalism-facebook-54928248" target="_blank"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; that they found eight guns, including one AR-15. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He &lt;a href="https://nhjournal.com/trump-hating-realtor-with-guns-manifesto-arrested-in-gop-vandalism-incident/" target="_blank"&gt;reportedly&lt;/a&gt; made political postings online, including one in which he referred to the rioting at the U.S. Capitol on Jan. 6 as “domestic terrorism." He also accused former President Donald Trump of being a dictator. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;WMUR-TV &lt;a href="https://www.wmur.com/article/vandalism-cars-concord-lawrence-dunlap-42924/60640490" target="_blank"&gt;reported&lt;/a&gt; part of the manifesto obtained through the search warrant. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I can't continue to exist for everyone else. I truly despite humanity and all the filth we have accepted as acceptable," the manifesto read. "I'm sorry for the pain I know I will cause with this decision." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dunlap's defense attorney, Jim Rosenberg, argued that the items obtained through the search warrant were unrelated to the incidents of vandalism. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This is a person with no significant prior criminal record, who has struggled with regard to his professional relationships work-wise recently," said Rosenberg in court. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The judge denied bail out of concern for the safety of the community as well as for the safety of the suspect. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dunlap was charged with 11 felony counts of criminal mischief.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Here's more about the arrest: &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;! &lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 02:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Democratic mayor joins Kentucky GOP lawmakers to celebrate state funding for Louisville</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/democratic-mayor-joins-kentucky-gop-lawmakers-celebrate-state-funding-louisville</link><description>More than $1 billion in state funding will head to Louisville, the largest city in Kentucky, to support education, health care, downtown renewal and other priorities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 01:44:48 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>