<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 08:41:10 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Missouri AG Demands Traitor Joe’s DOJ Turn Over Communications Related to Prosecutions of President Trump</title><link>https://thepostmillennial.com/new-missouri-ag-demands-biden-doj-turn-over-communications</link><description>The post Missouri AG Demands Traitor Joe’s DOJ Turn Over Communications Related to Prosecutions of President Trump appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:37:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>On CNN, Biden Tells Tales About Economy</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2024/05/09/realclearpolitics_bidens_cnn_interview_speaker_johnson_and_the_democrats_barron_trump_steps_into_politics_freedomworks_shuts_down.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:10:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blue state Dems turn on governor as homeless council can't account for $20B in spending</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/blue-state-dems-turn-governor-homeless-council-cant-account-20b-spending</link><description>Democrats and Republicans alike are taking issue with California Gov. Newsom as his homelessness council has failed to track its billions spent on the state's homelessness crisis.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:30:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Deception of ‘One Health’: What Will World Leaders Be Willing to Give Up?</title><link>https://harbingersdaily.com/the-deception-of-one-health-what-will-world-leaders-be-willing-to-give-up/</link><description>The post The Deception of ‘One Health’: What Will World Leaders Be Willing to Give Up? appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:17:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Bill Ackman's Anti-Woke Crusade Paid Off</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/09/how_bill_ackmans_anti-woke_crusade_paid_off_623349.html</link><description>Shares of his fund, Pershing Square Holdings, have soared since he's taken to X to criticize corporate diversity efforts, support Israel, and bash student protests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:59:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alabama legislative session adjourned without final vote on gambling bill: 'Frustrated'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/alabama-legislative-session-adjourned-without-final-vote-gambling-bill-frustrated</link><description>Alabamians won't have a chance to vote on gambling within the state this year after lawmakers failed to come to an agreement during the latest legislative session before it adjourned.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:02:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Thanks a Lot, Speaker Johnson: FBI Brass Just Urged Agents to Use Warrantless Wiretaps on US Citizens</title><link>https://revolver.news/2024/05/thanks-mike-johnson-wiretaps/</link><description>The post Thanks a Lot, Speaker Johnson: FBI Brass Just Urged Agents to Use Warrantless Wiretaps on US Citizens appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:16:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Faces New Democratic Divisions After Israel Shift</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/10/biden_faces_new_democratic_divisions_after_israel_shift_623390.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:58:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IRS urged to probe tax-exempt groups supporting anti-Israel protests</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/irs-urged-probe-tax-exempt-groups-supporting-anti-israel-protests</link><description>Several Republicans signed onto a letter calling for a number of groups to have their tax-exempt statuses investigated over their support for anti-Israel protests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 09:00:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Woman Lived in a Grocery Store Sign in Michigan With a Computer and Keurig for a Year</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/woman-lived-grocery-store-sign-michigan-computer-keurig/</link><description>Contractors in Midland, Michigan, recently discovered a 34-year-old woman living inside a Family Fare grocery store sign. The woman, whose name was not disclosed, had been residing in the sign for approximately a year and had access to amenities such as a computer, printer, and coffee maker, according to Officer Brennon Warren of the Midland […] The post Woman Lived in a Grocery Store Sign in Michigan With a Computer and Keurig for a Year appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:57:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Tries to Have It Both Ways With New Asylum Rules</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/10/biden_tries_to_have_it_both_ways_with_new_asylum_rules_623391.html</link><description>The president is under pressure from Republicans and progressives as humanitarian crisis builds and immigration remains a key voter issue</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:51:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GOP Rep calls on Biden to denounce, reject cash from progressive groups fueling anti-Israel protests</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/biden-should-denounce-progressive-groups-fueling-anti-israel-protests-reject-cash-from-shared-donors-gop-rep</link><description>GOP Rep. Darrell Issa told Fox News Digital it would 'very helpful' if Biden denounced progressive donors who are fueling anti-Israel protests but acknowledged its unlikely.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 09:00:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Working Moms Shouldn’t Have to Choose Between Girlboss and Tradwife</title><link>https://thefederalist.com/2024/05/10/working-moms-shouldnt-have-to-choose-between-girl-boss-or-tradwife/</link><description>The post Working Moms Shouldn’t Have to Choose Between Girlboss and Tradwife appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:13:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>You Cannot Defend Yourself</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/10/you_cannot_defend_yourself_623389.html</link><description>The group quota regime has largely succeeded in stripping its opponents, the American people, of the power to fight back.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:47:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'We are so innocent': Top 5 moments of Trump trial, from mistrial denials to Stormy Daniels' testimony</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/we-are-so-innocent-top-5-moments-trump-trial-mistrial-denials-stormy-daniels-testimony</link><description>Former President Trump will attend court Friday after a week of salacious testimony from Stormy Danials and the denial of multiple mistrial motions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 09:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>