<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 00:43:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Meet the Tech Moguls Flocking to Trump’s Banner</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/meet-tech-moguls-flocking-trumps-banner/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>(DCNF)—Big names in the cryptocurrency and venture capital worlds, some of whom are former Democratic donors, are throwing their support behind former President Donald Trump. Venture capitalists David Sacks and Chamath Palihapitiya organized a high-dollar fundraiser for the former president Thursday night in San Francisco, raising $12 million for the Trump 47 Joint Fundraising Committee […] The post Meet the Tech Moguls Flocking to Trump’s Banner appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 01:00:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>God Gave Me Someone To Fight For</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/06/07/god_gave_me_someone_to_fight_for_625171.html</link><description>I thought losing my brother in a tragic accident would be the hardest thing I ever had to endure. Then doctors diagnosed me with a rare and aggressive esophageal cancer, typically only seen in men 70</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 19:09:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Jersey businessman testifies he promised up to $250,000 in bribes in exchange for Sen. Bob Menendez's help</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/new-jersey-businessman-testifies-promised-250000-bribes-exchange-sen-bob-menendezs-help</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>In the bribery case against New Jersey Sen. Bob Menendez, a businessman took his turn on the witness stand and said he believed he had a $200,000-to-$250,000 deal in 2018 for Menendez's help.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 02:12:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Here Are 12 Stories of Good Guys With Guns (From Just Last Month) That Leftists Don’t Want You to See</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/here-are-12-stories-good-guys-guns-just/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>(The Daily Signal)—It seems that many gun control activists want to take your guns so badly that they’re willing to take your voice, too. And increasingly, the war for the Second Amendment involves battles waged on a First Amendment front. Just ask the National Rifle Association, which last week needed the Supreme Court to vindicate […] The post Here Are 12 Stories of Good Guys With Guns (From Just Last Month) That Leftists Don’t Want You to See appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 01:00:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Does Biden Reject Israel's Right to Self-Defense?</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2024/06/06/does_biden_reject_israels_right_to_self-defense_151066.html</link><description>The administration's effort to stymie military action, coupled with its continued criticism as to how Israel is conducting a just war against a terror group, puts the Jewish state at risk in the region and the world.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 19:09:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Landmark bill targets hidden foreign funds in schools as officials warn of CCP influence</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/landmark-bill-targets-hidden-foreign-funds-schools-officials-warn-ccp-influence</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>A House bill will provide parents with more oversight of any foreign sources or funding of their children's curriculum, its sponsor said.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 22:56:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Here’s Why American-Born Workers Are Getting Killed in Traitor Joe’s Economy</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/heres-why-american-born-workers-are-getting-killed/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>(DCNF)—Native-born American workers are taking a beating in the job market from gains by foreign-born workers, according to the data released by the Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS) on Friday. The number of foreign-born workers employed in the U.S. rose by 637,000 in the last year to nearly 30.9 million, while the number of employed […] The post Here’s Why American-Born Workers Are Getting Killed in Traitor Joe’s Economy appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 01:00:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>There Are Risks Lurking in the World of Private Capital</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/06/07/there_are_risks_lurking_in_the_world_of_private_capital_625173.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 19:09:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NY v. Trump: Judge reveals Facebook post implying juror discussed guilty verdict before trial concluded</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/ny-v-trump-judge-reveals-juror-allegedly-spoke-about-case-family-member-before-guilty-verdict</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>The judge presiding over former President Trump’s New York criminal trial notified his defense team on Friday of a comment on the court's public Facebook page that implies one of the jurors discussed the guilty verdict ahead of time.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 22:31:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>“People Are Being Coddled”: Trigger Warnings Increasingly Embraced by Hollywood Even as They Spoil Plotlines</title><link>https://www.theblaze.com/news/trigger-warnings-spoilers-streaming-services</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>The post “People Are Being Coddled”: Trigger Warnings Increasingly Embraced by Hollywood Even as They Spoil Plotlines appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 01:00:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Defaming of Brandon Straka and #Walkaway</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/06/07/the_defaming_of_brandon_straka_and_walkaway_625176.html</link><description>Smeared as a Russian proxy after founding a movement to</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 19:09:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Illegal immigrants are offered an array of taxpayer funded benefits, enticing more to come: 'Pull factor'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/explained-what-can-illegal-immigrants-get-free-united-states</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>Illegal immigrants are eligible for a number of benefits and services provided by both local governments and taxpayer-funded non-governmental organizations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 22:27:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>“Not Going to Be Silenced”: Surgeon Indicted by Traitor Joe’s DOJ for Blowing the Whistle on Child Genital Mutilation Speaks Out</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/not-going-be-silenced-surgeon-indicted-traitor-joes/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>(DCNF)—The Department of Justice (DOJ) recently indicted Texas surgeon Dr. Eithan Haim, who blew the whistle on a children’s hospital performing sex change procedures on minors. Haim told the Daily Caller News Foundation he will not be intimidated or silenced, vowing to fight the allegations in court. In 2023, Haim discovered Texas Children’s Hospital was […] The post “Not Going to Be Silenced”: Surgeon Indicted by Traitor Joe’s DOJ for Blowing the Whistle on Child Genital Mutilation Speaks Out appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 01:00:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pro-Israel Community Fights Extremism in Both Parties</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/06/07/pro-israel_community_fights_extremism_in_both_parties_625182.html</link><description>At a time of extreme polarization and partisanship, one super PAC is pouring resources into pivotal primary campaigns-with the tangential benefit of promoting moderation and tamping down extremes within both parties. The American Israel Public Affairs Committee</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 19:09:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fox News Politics: 'Low IQ individual'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/fox-news-politics-low-iq-individual</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>The latest updates from the 2024 campaign trail, exclusive interviews and more Fox News politics content</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 21:38:28 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>