<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 17:28:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>J6 Defendant David Homol Commits Suicide in Florida While Awaiting Trial, the 5th Defendant to Do So</title><link>https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-j6-defendant-david-homol-commits-suicide-in-florida-while-awaiting-trial</link><description>The post J6 Defendant David Homol Commits Suicide in Florida While Awaiting Trial, the 5th Defendant to Do So appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 22:18:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>East Asia's Coming Population Collapse</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/08/east_asias_coming_population_collapse_623222.html</link><description>And how it will reshape world politics.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 20:44:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Texas AG Paxton accuses NGO of 'criminal conduct,' including 'facilitating the unlawful entry of illegal aliens': Report</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/texas-ag-paxton-accuses-ngo-of-criminal-conduct-including-facilitating-the-unlawful-entry-of-illegal-aliens-report-2668202983.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/texas-ag-paxton-accuses-ngo-of-criminal-conduct-including-facilitating-the-unlawful-entry-of-illegal-aliens-report.jpg?id=52202261&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C42%2C0%2C129</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/texas-ag-paxton-accuses-ngo-of-criminal-conduct-including-facilitating-the-unlawful-entry-of-illegal-aliens-report.jpg?id=52202261&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C42%2C0%2C129" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/texas-ag-paxton-accuses-ngo-of-criminal-conduct-including-facilitating-the-unlawful-entry-of-illegal-aliens-report.jpg?id=52202264&amp;amp;width=1245&amp;amp;height=700&amp;amp;coordinates=75,42,0,107 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/texas-ag-paxton-accuses-ngo-of-criminal-conduct-including-facilitating-the-unlawful-entry-of-illegal-aliens-report.jpg%3Fid%3D52202264%26width%3D1245%26height%3D700%26coordinates%3D75%2C42%2C0%2C107%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Texas Attorney General Ken Paxton (R) recently doubled down on his claims that a nongovernmental organization is engaging in "criminal conduct," according to a Wednesday report from the &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2024/05/08/us-news/texas-ag-enhances-legal-pressure-on-annunciation-house/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;New York Post&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In February, &lt;a href="https://elpasomatters.org/2024/02/20/ag-ken-paxton-targets-el-paso-annunciation-house/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Paxton filed a lawsuit&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; against Annunciation House, an El Paso-based Catholic organization that provides aid to "migrants, immigrants, and refugees," according to its &lt;a href="https://annunciationhouse.org/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;website&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Any NGO facilitating the unlawful entry of illegal aliens into Texas is undermining the rule of law," Paxton stated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the time of the filing, Paxton requested documents from the organization, but it failed to comply. &lt;a href="https://www.documentcloud.org/documents/24476263-judge-blocks-texas-attorney-generals-administrative-subpoena" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Court documents&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; obtained by the Post revealed that the organization asked for 30 days to respond to the information request. Paxton stated that Annunciation House would be considered "non-compliant" if it did not produce the documents the following day. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ruben Garcia, the organization's founder and executive director, obtained a temporary restraining order against the request for documents. A judge claimed that the AG's request "did not cite which Texas laws the Attorney General believed were being violated."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The Attorney General's efforts to run roughshod over Annunciation House, without regard to due process or fair play, call into question the true motivation for the Attorney General's attempt to prevent Annunciation House from providing the humanitarian and social services that it provides," the judge wrote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Annunciation House claims it provides services similar to "that of the schools who enroll children of refugees, the clinics and hospitals who care for the needs of refugees, and the churches, synagogues, and mosques who welcome families to join in worship."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Annunciation House has provided hospitality to hundreds of thousands of refugees for over forty-six years. It is a work recognized by the Catholic Church and is listed in the National Catholic Directory," the organization said. "Annunciation House has done this work of accompaniment out of the scriptural and Gospel mandate to welcome the stranger."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paxton claims that the NGO is participating in "human smuggling" and shielding illegal immigrants from law enforcement agencies. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The lawsuit against the organization stated, "According to its own in-Court admission, Annunciation House contracts with a local company once or twice a week to transport migrants in passenger vans in groups of approximately 15."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a statement to the Post, Paxton stated, "Any NGO facilitating the unlawful entry of illegal aliens into Texas is undermining the rule of law and potentially jeopardizing the safety and wellbeing of our citizens."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"All NGOs who are complicit in Joe Biden's illegal immigration catastrophe and think they are above the law should consider themselves on notice," he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Annunciation House has claimed that Paxton's accusations are "unfounded" as well as "illegal, immoral and anti-faith."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sign up here&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Arkansas cannot prevent 2 teachers from discussing critical race theory in classroom, judge rules</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/arkansas-cannot-prevent-2-teachers-discussing-critical-race-theory-classroom-judge-rules</link><description>U.S. District Judge Lee Rudofsky has ruled 2 Arkansas high school teachers cannot be prevented by the state from discussing critical race theory in their classrooms.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:33:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alex Jones Has Epic Rant About Good vs. Evil and Our Enemies at War With God [VIDEO]</title><link>https://rumble.com/v4tvx20-alex-jones-has-epic-rant-about-good-vs-evil-and-our-enemies-at-war-with-god.html</link><description>The post Alex Jones Has Epic Rant About Good vs. Evil and Our Enemies at War With God [VIDEO] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 22:17:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>US's Greatest Strategic Failure? Embracing Communist China</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2024/05/08/embracing_communist_china_was_us_greatest_strategic_failure_150905.html</link><description>From the war in Ukraine to the horrific terror attack on Oct. 7 and the subsequent conflict in the Middle East to the roiling waters of the South China Sea, the world today is in crisis. The causes are not found in Moscow or Tehran alone, but primarily in Washington and Beijing. They are the consequence of two fundamental and interrelated grand strategic mistakes made by the U.S. First, the failure to understand the threat from the People's Republic of China.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 20:43:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>EXCLUSIVE: Leaked Pitch Reveals Plot By Former Vivek Staffer To Use MAGA Influencers Against Trump, For RFK</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/exclusive-leaked-pitch-reveals-plot-by-former-vivek-staffer-to-use-maga-influencers-against-trump-for-rfk-2668202953.html</link><image_url>https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/REUTERSElizabeth-Frantz-3-scaled-e1715188671116.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/REUTERSElizabeth-Frantz-3-scaled-e1715188671116.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Leaked Pitch Reveals Plot By Former Vivek Staffer To Use MAGA Influencers Against Trump, For RFK</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:55:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>House antisemitism hearing: NYC schools leader reveals case that has 'troubled' him the most</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/house-antisemitism-hearing-nyc-schools-leader-reveals-case-troubled-him-most</link><description>New York City Public Schools Chancellor David Banks on Wednesday told lawmakers there have been 281 reported antisemitic and Islamophobic incidents within his school system since Oct. 7.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:28:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The FDA Can’t Get Its Story Straight About Reducing Tobacco-Related Dangers</title><link>https://www.theblaze.com/columns/opinion/the-fda-cant-get-its-story-straight-about-reducing-tobacco-related-dangers</link><description>The post The FDA Can’t Get Its Story Straight About Reducing Tobacco-Related Dangers appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 22:17:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump's Plan To Take Out Cartel Leaders</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/08/trumps_plan_to_take_out_cartel_leaders_623219.html</link><description>Trump has told allies about his plans to covertly send Special Forces to Mexico to assassinate drug kingpins, sources say.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 20:40:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indictment reveals disturbing new accusations against illegal immigrant charged with killing Laken Riley: 'A peeping tom'</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/indictment-reveals-disturbing-new-accusations-against-illegal-immigrant-charged-with-killing-laken-riley-a-peeping-tom-2668202975.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52202134&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C4%2C0%2C62</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52202134&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C4%2C0%2C62" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img class="rm-shortcode" id="cb4bb" src="https://www.conservativereview.com/media-library/eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpbWFnZSI6Imh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnRoZWJsYXplLmNvbS9tZWRpYS1saWJyYXJ5L2ltYWdlLmpwZz9pZD01MjIwMjEyNiZhbXA7d2lkdGg9OTgwIiwiZXhwaXJlc19hdCI6MTczMzY2NTA0Nn0.qn_m010SkSJgb4-dahHrMRGTSMijp0kmRA5z0aigcsw/image.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Georgia grand jury has officially indicted &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/georgia-nursing-murder-suspect-migrant" target="_blank"&gt;the man police say killed&lt;/a&gt; college student Laken Riley in February.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An &lt;a href="https://roar-assets-auto.rbl.ms/files/62527/JoseIbarraIndictment.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;indictment filed&lt;/a&gt; on Tuesday in Clarke County charged 26-year-old illegal immigrant Jose Ibarra with 10 crimes: three counts of felony murder, one count of malice murder, kidnapping with bodily injury, aggravated assault with intent to rape, aggravated battery, obstruction or hindering a person making an emergency telephone call, and tampering with evidence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They described the horrific murder as a "crime of opportunity."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The indictment included another charge for a totally separate, yet disturbing, allegation: Ibarra was charged with one count of being a "peeping tom."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the indictment, Ibarra went to an apartment complex at the University of Georgia on the same day he allegedly killed Riley "for the purpose of becoming a peeping tom in that he did peep through the window and spied upon and invaded the privacy" of the occupant. That victim is a university employee, WAGA-TV &lt;a href="https://www.fox5atlanta.com/news/illegal-immigrant-suspect-in-laken-rileys-murder-indicted-accused-of-peeping-on-uga-staff-member" target="_blank"&gt;reported&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The indictment includes other shocking allegations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prosecutors allege that Ibarra killed Riley "by inflicting blunt-force trauma to her head and by asphyxiating her." The indictment alleges that Ibarra "seriously disfigured" Riley "by striking her head multiple times with a rock."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Police have said that Ibarra did not know Riley. Rather, they described the horrific murder as a "crime of opportunity."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ibarra, an immigrant from Venezuela, has been living in the U.S. since September 2022 when he entered illegally near El Paso, Texas. After entering illegally, Ibarra was taken into custody and then paroled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Immigration officials &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/ice-confirms-jose-ibarra-history" target="_blank"&gt;say&lt;/a&gt; Ibarra later moved to New York City, where he had encounters with police. Last September, Ibarra was charged with a felony for "acting in a manner to injure a child less than 17 and a motor vehicle license violation," but he was released from jail before Immigration and Customs Enforcement could lodge a detainer against him. New York City is a "sanctuary city."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ibarra then moved to Georgia last fall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tragically, ICE was able to lodge a detainer against Ibarra only after Riley's murder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stefanik grills NYC schools chief on pro-Hamas teacher kept on payroll after antisemitic riot</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/stefanik-grills-nyc-schools-chief-pro-hamas-teacher-kept-payroll-antisemitic-riot</link><description>Rep. Elise Stefanik, R-N.Y., blasted New York City Public Schools Chancellor David Banks over the former Hillcrest High School principal's employment status after an antisemitic riot.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:25:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Venezuelan Illegal Alien Jose Ibarra Charged in Murder of Laken Riley in Georgia</title><link>https://thepostmillennial.com/breaking-venezuelan-illegal-immigrant-jose-ibarra-charged-in-murder-of-laken-riley-in-georgia</link><description>The post Venezuelan Illegal Alien Jose Ibarra Charged in Murder of Laken Riley in Georgia appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 22:17:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Argentina Has Already Experienced Results of Socialism</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2024/05/08/president_milei_argentine_history_is_a_testimony_to_what_happens_when_you_replace_liberty_with_socialism.html</link><description>President of Argentina Javier Milei speaks about his economic reform platform and the value of liberty in human flourishing at the Milken Institute Global Conference.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 20:38:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Illegal alien driving Prius allegedly caused car crash that killed Maine woman</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/illegal-alien-driving-prius-allegedly-caused-car-crash-that-killed-maine-woman-2668202901.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52202045&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C59%2C0%2C60</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52202045&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C59%2C0%2C60" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52202045&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;coordinates=14,0,15,0 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg%3Fid%3D52202045%26width%3D1200%26height%3D800%26coordinates%3D14%2C0%2C15%2C0%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;An illegal alien is allegedly responsible for a recent car crash in Maine that left one woman dead and her husband critically injured.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Around 8:40 a.m. on April 26, 23-year-old Oguzhan Cildir, a Mexican national in the U.S. illegally, was allegedly driving a Toyota Prius on I-95 in Wells, Maine, just south of Kennebunkport, when he suddenly crashed into a minivan and a pickup truck. The pickup truck then "rolled over several times," a &lt;a href="https://spectrumlocalnews.com/me/maine/public-safety/2024/04/26/multi-vehicle-fatal-crash-shuts-down-i-95-in-wells-friday" target="_blank"&gt;police report&lt;/a&gt; said, before coming to a stop.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Outlets reporting on the fatal crash described Cildir as a Massachusetts resident, but the Maine Wire reported that the agents who arrested him at the scene immediately contacted a local Customs and Border Protection official because of Cildir's immigration status. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The driver, 53-year-old Gloria Cascio of Albion, Maine, was pronounced dead at the scene. Her husband, 60-year-old Vincent Cascio, who had been sitting in the passenger seat, was soon flown to a hospital via helicopter in critical condition. His current condition remains unclear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cildir was likewise taken to the hospital with injuries described by the &lt;a href="https://www.themainewire.com/2024/05/man-involved-in-four-car-crash-that-left-maine-woman-dead-entered-u-s-illegally-in-january-oguzhan-cildir/#:~:text=The%20man%20who%20caused%20a,the%20Maine%20Wire%20can%20confirm" target="_blank"&gt;Maine Wire&lt;/a&gt; as "non-life-threatening." The driver of the minivan sustained minor injuries. A fourth car was also involved in the crash, but the driver was not injured. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The following short clip shows the crash scene as well as the helicopter that transported Vincent Cascio to the hospital:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Maine Wire reported that at least five witnesses told police that Cildir had been driving "erratically" just before the crash, weaving in and out of traffic. Moreover, Cildir reportedly does not have a driver's license. How he came into possession of the Prius and who it's owner might be are both unclear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Multiple &lt;a href="https://www.masslive.com/news/2024/04/mass-driver-involved-in-four-car-fatal-crash-in-maine-authorities-say.html" target="_blank"&gt;outlets&lt;/a&gt; reporting on the fatal crash described Cildir as a Massachusetts resident, but the Maine Wire reported that the agents who arrested him at the scene immediately contacted a local Customs and Border Protection official because of Cildir's immigration status. He is believed to have crossed from Mexico into the U.S. illegally sometime in January.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cildir has been placed in the custody of Immigration and Customs Enforcement’s Enforcement Removal Operations "for further processing and potential detainment," the Maine Wire reported.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Maine Wire also indicated that York County District Attorney Kathryn Slattery may be hesitating to charge Cildir in connection with the crash because he is an illegal alien who would likely be deported if convicted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Monday, Slattery told the Maine Wire in an email that her office "has not received a final report" on the crash and that it "remains under investigation." She added that she could not comment further on the incident.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WATCH: Dem governor swarmed by anti-Israel agitators while celebrating daughter's college graduation</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/gretchen-whitmer-swarmed-anti-israel-protesters-celebrating-daughter-college-graduation</link><description>Video captured anti-Israel protesters swarming Michigan Gov. Gretchen Whitmer as she celebrated her daughter's college graduation at a local restaurant.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:20:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GOP Announces “The Save Act” Requiring Proof of Citizenship to Register to Vote in Federal Elections [VIDEO]</title><link>https://rumble.com/v4tyw9e-gop-announces-the-save-act-requiring-proof-of-citizenship-to-register-to-vo.html</link><description>The post GOP Announces “The Save Act” Requiring Proof of Citizenship to Register to Vote in Federal Elections [VIDEO] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 22:15:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The WHO's Plan for Public-Health Tyranny</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/08/the_whos_plan_for_public-health_tyranny_623221.html</link><description>Unelected officials want the power to drag us back into lockdown.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 20:37:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Georgia ‘Get Trump’ Lawfare Could Be Tossed If Appeals Court Rules Willis Disqualified Herself</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/georgia-get-trump-lawfare-could-be-tossed-if-appeals-court-rules-willis-disqualified-herself-2668202743.html</link><image_url>https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Fani-Willis.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Fani-Willis.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img class="rm-shortcode" id="57180" src="https://www.conservativereview.com/media-library/eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpbWFnZSI6Imh0dHBzOi8vdGhlZmVkZXJhbGlzdC5jb20vd3AtY29udGVudC91cGxvYWRzLzIwMjQvMDUvRmFuaS1XaWxsaXMtMTIwMHg2NzUuanBnIiwiZXhwaXJlc19hdCI6MTcyOTc0MTc0M30.Zx_EMeuJBNdJR9sKZ9ZpV6Zeio5BuyWnKr2XTq2Tbwg/image.jpg" /&gt;If Trump prevails, the case against him in Georgia could be dropped.&lt;/span&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:16:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fox News Politics: Literal Brain Worms</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/fox-news-politics-literal-brain-worms</link><description>The latest updates from the 2024 campaign trail, exclusive interviews and more Fox News politics content</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:06:36 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>