<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 02:38:08 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Court Ordered to Reconsider Biden-Harris Regime’s Green Investing Rule Following Landmark Supreme Court Ruling</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/court-ordered-reconsider-biden-harris-regimes-green-investing/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>(DCNF)—A federal appeals court ordered a judge on Thursday to reconsider blocking a Biden administration rule that allows environmental, social and governance (ESG) investing in employee retirement plans following a landmark Supreme Court ruling. The Fifth Circuit Court of Appeals ruled that a Texas judge must reconsider a decision upholding a Department of Labor rule, […] The post Court Ordered to Reconsider Biden-Harris Regime’s Green Investing Rule Following Landmark Supreme Court Ruling appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 05:01:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rep. Sheila Jackson Lee has passed away after battle with pancreatic cancer</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/rep-sheila-jackson-lee-has-passed-away-after-battle-pancreatic-cancer</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>Rep. Sheila Jackson Lee, D-Texas, has died at the age of 74 following a battle with pancreatic cancer. She leaves behind her husband and two children.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 04:03:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chop Chop, NATO: Impatient Zelensky Complains He Isn’t Receiving His Handouts Quickly Enough</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/chop-chop-nato-impatient-zelensky-complains-he-isnt/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>(ZeroHedge)—During the big NATO summit earlier this month, everyone from Antony Blinken to Lloyd Austin to President Biden touted the imminent delivery of US-made F-16 jet fighters to Ukraine. “American-made F-16 fighter jets are on their way to Ukraine” and they will be flying “this summer” – Secretary of State Blinken had vowed at the […] The post Chop Chop, NATO: Impatient Zelensky Complains He Isn’t Receiving His Handouts Quickly Enough appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 05:01:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Babydog bobbleheads to hit shelves after 'first dog' stole the show at Republican National Convention</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/babydog-bobbleheads-hit-shelves-after-first-dog-stole-show-republican-national-convention</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>After an appearance at the RNC in her own dog-sized chair, Babydog will get her own bobblehead thanks to the National Bobblehead Hall of Fame and Museum.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 02:35:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>If They’re Willing to Assassinate a Future President, What Would They Be Willing to Do to the Future Economy?</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/2-6/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>Editor’s Note: This article and any related communications are for informational purposes only and should not be considered as financial advice. We do not provide personalized investment, financial, or legal advice. This outlet benefits from purchases made through our sponsors. “They” are coming after us. “They” are willing to assassinate a former and future president. […] The post If They’re Willing to Assassinate a Future President, What Would They Be Willing to Do to the Future Economy? appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 05:01:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JD Vance, others say Biden should resign presidency if he drops out of the race</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/jd-vance-others-say-biden-resign-presidency-drops-out-race</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>Senators JD Vance and Marco Rubio, along with pollster Nate Silver and Democratic Rep. Marie Gluesenkamp Perez, are among those suggesting Biden should resign the presidency.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 01:46:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gen-Z Is Waking Up One Former-Leftist at a Time [VIDEO]</title><link>https://rumble.com/v57lz0k-genz-is-waking-up-one-former-leftist-at-a-time.html</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>The post Gen-Z Is Waking Up One Former-Leftist at a Time [VIDEO] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 05:00:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Hitchhiker's Guide to next week's blockbuster week in Congress</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/hitchhikers-guide-next-weeks-blockbuster-week-congress</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>Five topics will be top-of-mind on Capitol Hill this coming week including the investigation of the Trump assassination attempt and questions about Biden's future.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 00:20:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tucker Carlson’s Haters and Second-Guessers Keep Losing, Especially Rupert Murdoch</title><link>https://revolver.news/2024/07/tucker-haters-and-second-guessers-keep-losing-especially-rupert-murdoch/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>The post Tucker Carlson’s Haters and Second-Guessers Keep Losing, Especially Rupert Murdoch appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 05:00:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ohio Democrat Sen. Sherrod Brown urges Biden to end campaign</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/ohio-democrat-sen-sherrod-brown-urges-biden-end-campaign</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>Sen. Brown called on President Biden to end his campaign on Friday, becoming the 34th Congressional Democrat to do so.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 23:35:47 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>