<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 01:02:07 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Are Religious Leaders in Israel Getting Ready to Sacrifice a Red Heifer?</title><link>https://basedunderground.com/2024/08/09/are-religious-leaders-in-israel-getting-ready-to-sacrifice-a-red-heifer/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>The post Are Religious Leaders in Israel Getting Ready to Sacrifice a Red Heifer? appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 04:59:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Harris supporters sound off on her border blueprint: ‘Her policies will make a difference'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/harris-supporters-sound-off-her-border-blueprint-her-policies-make-difference</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>Attendees at Kamala Harris and Tim Walz' Arizona rally on Friday were asked to define the nominee's border policies, and offered their take on her other proposals and record.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 05:09:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Data Analyst Says Gold Will Be the “New Reserve Asset” — Time to Get the Gold Guide</title><link>https://americafirstreport.com/data-analyst-says-gold-will-be-the-new-reserve-asset-time-to-get-the-gold-guide/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>The post Data Analyst Says Gold Will Be the “New Reserve Asset” — Time to Get the Gold Guide appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 04:18:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Harris addresses anti-Israel protesters at Arizona rally as crowd tries to drown them out with 'USA!' chants</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/harris-addresses-anti-israel-protesters-arizona-rally-crowd-tries-drown-them-out-usa-chants</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>Vice President Kamala Harris told anti-Israel protesters at her rally in Glendale, Arizona, on Friday that she and the president are working toward a Gaza cease-fire.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 03:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>3 Non-Fearmongering Reasons Survival Food Should Be Purchased Immediately</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/3-non-fearmongering-reasons-survival-food-should-be/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>The Liberty Daily supports America First companies and benefits when readers purchase from them. “The sky is falling!” — Every Survival Food Company Ever In reality, the sky isn’t falling yet. Things are getting bad for millions of Americans, but there is still time to turn things around. Whether that means saving the country or […] The post 3 Non-Fearmongering Reasons Survival Food Should Be Purchased Immediately appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 04:18:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Arizona Kamala Harris rally speakers court 'John McCain Republicans' support; man brings border map for VP</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/arizona-kamala-harris-rally-speakers-court-john-mccain-republicans-support-man-brings-border-map-vp</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>A theme among several of the speakers at Vice President Kamala Harris' campaign rally outside Phoenix Friday was courting supporters of the late moderate GOP Sen. John McCain.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 02:41:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Attorney Tells CNN It’s “Virtually Impossible” That Trump Will Face His D.C. Trial Before the Election</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/attorney-tells-cnn-its-virtually-impossible-that-trump/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>(DCNF)—Criminal defense attorney Bill Brennan said Friday that there is almost no chance former President Donald Trump will face a trial in his Washington, D.C. case before the November election. Judge Tanya Chutkan agreed Friday with special counsel Jack Smith’s request for a postponement in Trump’s election interference case by delaying a scheduled hearing from […] The post Attorney Tells CNN It’s “Virtually Impossible” That Trump Will Face His D.C. Trial Before the Election appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 04:17:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tim Walz 'misspoke' about using weapons ‘in war,' Harris campaign says: report</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/tim-walz-misspoke-using-weapons-war-harris-campaign-says-report</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>Minnesota Gov. Tim Walz, Kamala Harris' running mate whose military service has come under heavy scrutiny, "misspoke" in a 2018 video where he is heard talking about his handling of weapons "in war," the Harris campaign says.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 02:29:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Staged Photo Op: Gruesome Newsom Cleans Up a Bum Camp in Commiefornia [VIDEO]</title><link>https://rumble.com/v5a9jk1-staged-photo-op-gruesome-newsom-cleans-up-a-bum-camp-in-commiefornia.html</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>The post Staged Photo Op: Gruesome Newsom Cleans Up a Bum Camp in Commiefornia [VIDEO] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 04:16:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>US officials identify Buffalo Soldier killed in World War II</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/us-officials-identify-buffalo-soldier-killed-world-war-ii</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>The remains U.S. Private First Class Lemuel Dent Jr. were recently identified by the DPAA, which is working to identify dozens of Buffalo Soldiers who were killed in World War II.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 00:19:18 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>