<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 06:57:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Woman Lived in a Grocery Store Sign in Michigan With a Computer and Keurig for a Year</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/woman-lived-grocery-store-sign-michigan-computer-keurig/</link><description>Contractors in Midland, Michigan, recently discovered a 34-year-old woman living inside a Family Fare grocery store sign. The woman, whose name was not disclosed, had been residing in the sign for approximately a year and had access to amenities such as a computer, printer, and coffee maker, according to Officer Brennon Warren of the Midland […]
The post Woman Lived in a Grocery Store Sign in Michigan With a Computer and Keurig for a Year appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:57:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FBI Bungling May Collapse Mar-a-Lago Case Against Trump</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/09/fbi_bungling_may_collapse_mar-a-lago_case_against_trump_623317.html</link><description>The government's evidence about what it found during its raid on Mar-a-Lago may be contaminated and the case seems ready to implode.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 04:04:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Even Babies With ‘No Chance Of Survival’ Deserve A Shot At Life</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/even-babies-with-no-chance-of-survival-deserve-a-shot-at-life-2668217489.html</link><image_url>https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/engin-akyurt-84fhDJI6Nfs-unsplash.jpeg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/engin-akyurt-84fhDJI6Nfs-unsplash.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img class="rm-shortcode" id="230dd" src="https://www.conservativereview.com/media-library/eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpbWFnZSI6Imh0dHBzOi8vdGhlZmVkZXJhbGlzdC5jb20vd3AtY29udGVudC91cGxvYWRzLzIwMjQvMDUvZW5naW4tYWt5dXJ0LTg0ZmhESkk2TmZzLXVuc3BsYXNoLTEyMDB4Njc1LmpwZWciLCJleHBpcmVzX2F0IjoxNzY4ODA3NjUxfQ.XgLE1IXVLgQk1na6K0qrKRLubGU2VAAgh8FgTm_tj-M/image.jpeg" /&gt;Doctors told me I should abort my baby because that’s what 'everyone does' in that situation.&lt;/span&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 08:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alabama legislative session adjourned without final vote on gambling bill: 'Frustrated'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/alabama-legislative-session-adjourned-without-final-vote-gambling-bill-frustrated</link><description>Alabamians won't have a chance to vote on gambling within the state this year after lawmakers failed to come to an agreement during the latest legislative session before it adjourned.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:02:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Working Moms Shouldn’t Have to Choose Between Girlboss and Tradwife</title><link>https://thefederalist.com/2024/05/10/working-moms-shouldnt-have-to-choose-between-girl-boss-or-tradwife/</link><description>The post Working Moms Shouldn’t Have to Choose Between Girlboss and Tradwife appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:13:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Campus Chaos</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/09/campus_chaos_623370.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 03:54:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Working Moms Shouldn’t Have To Choose Between Girlboss And Tradwife</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/working-moms-shouldnt-have-to-choose-between-girlboss-and-tradwife-2668217274.html</link><image_url>https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/pexels-anastasia-shuraeva-4079281.jpeg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/pexels-anastasia-shuraeva-4079281.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img class="rm-shortcode" id="b1acd" src="https://www.conservativereview.com/media-library/eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpbWFnZSI6Imh0dHBzOi8vdGhlZmVkZXJhbGlzdC5jb20vd3AtY29udGVudC91cGxvYWRzLzIwMjQvMDUvcGV4ZWxzLWFuYXN0YXNpYS1zaHVyYWV2YS00MDc5MjgxLTEyMDB4Njc1LmpwZWciLCJleHBpcmVzX2F0IjoxNzQ0NDE2MTE4fQ.OyK88M1SpKOdSK0zgYrnNSYL74s7eFTBInajRoU2rgo/image.jpeg" /&gt;Why must women choose between 40 hours per week outside the home or homeschooling, sourdough, and gingham dresses?&lt;/span&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 08:27:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IRS urged to probe tax-exempt groups supporting anti-Israel protests</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/irs-urged-probe-tax-exempt-groups-supporting-anti-israel-protests</link><description>Several Republicans signed onto a letter calling for a number of groups to have their tax-exempt statuses investigated over their support for anti-Israel protests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 09:00:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oops: First Neuralink Brain Implant in Human Malfunctions</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/oops-first-neuralink-brain-implant-human-malfunctions/</link><description>(Discern Media)—The first human to receive a Neuralink implant experienced a malfunction when several threads designed to record neural activity retracted from the brain, as revealed by the Elon Musk-owned startup. The incident occurred in the weeks following the surgery in late January that implanted the Neuralink hardware in 29-year-old Noland Arbaugh, a quadriplegic. As […]
The post Oops: First Neuralink Brain Implant in Human Malfunctions appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:11:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stormy Daniels Takes the Stand</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/09/stormy_daniels_takes_the_stand_623307.html</link><description>The trial isn't about Trump's bad behavior but committing business crimes to win an election. It's a shame that Daniels's story is being ruled largely irrelevant in the courtroom.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 03:30:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>California college has only one pro-Palestinian protester because city is blue-collar and conservative, political science prof says</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/california-college-has-only-one-pro-palestinian-protester-because-city-is-blue-collar-and-conservative-political-science-prof-says-2668215256.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52212496&amp;width=980</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52212496&amp;amp;width=980" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52212496&amp;amp;width=1245&amp;amp;height=700&amp;amp;coordinates=0,0,0,290 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg%3Fid%3D52212496%26width%3D1245%26height%3D700%26coordinates%3D0%2C0%2C0%2C290%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;While pro-Palestinian protesters disrupted colleges across the country, one institution of higher learning in California could only muster one single protester for the cause.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That's because Cal-State University at Bakersfield is too blue-collar and conservative, says one political science professor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This is largely a blue collar school where students are more concerned with getting their degrees and getting on with their lives than anything else," said CSUB professor Mark Martinez &lt;a href="https://www.kget.com/news/local-news/why-do-gaza-protests-roil-us-universities-everywhere-except-csu-bakersfield/" target="_blank"&gt;to KGET-TV. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Cal-State system was specifically designed to serve students who live in California and can attend classes while still living at home. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s primarily a commuter school, too, and that has an effect on campus culture and therefore the tendency toward activism," he explained. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Bakersfield is a conservative city, and that plays a role," Martinez added. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;KGET spoke to the single, solitary protester who held up a poster with the Palestinian flag on campus. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“My daughter is at UCLA protesting and I thought — I don’t know if Bakersfield was going to join in, but I thought I would just do something," said part-time lecturer Carolyn Lane, "instead of feeling helpless and hopeless, join in.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She said her 10-year-old daughter painted her Palestinian poster for the protest. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I figured a protest of one was better than none," she added. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Freshman Brayan Garcia told KGET that it just wasn't in the nature of the students at the school to protest. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“They don’t really like making that much noise. I mean, we don’t have a football team to begin with, if you get me," said Garcia. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Martinez went on to offer another reason students didn't care to protest against Israel. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I think the relative lack of interest in the Study Abroad program is a factor. Study Abroad is an important program because it fosters an understanding of global events and attitudes. Many students here at CSUB just see it as a luxury they don’t have the time or money for,” he added. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the campus continued to stay relatively peaceful, after this report aired, a larger number of pro-Hamas &lt;a href="https://www.kget.com/news/local-news/campus-protests-over-israel-hamas-war-come-to-bakersfields-cal-state-campus/" target="_blank"&gt;protesters showed&lt;/a&gt; up at the university. Officials said the protesters organized the one-hour rally with them. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The CSU system said in a statement that it did not intend to change its investments in relation to the Israeli-Hamas conflict. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bakersfield is a city of about 400,000 residents in the San Joaquin Valley about 113 miles north of Los Angeles. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Here's more about CSU Bakersfield:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;! &lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 02:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GOP Rep calls on Biden to denounce, reject cash from progressive groups fueling anti-Israel protests</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/biden-should-denounce-progressive-groups-fueling-anti-israel-protests-reject-cash-from-shared-donors-gop-rep</link><description>GOP Rep. Darrell Issa told Fox News Digital it would 'very helpful' if Biden denounced progressive donors who are fueling anti-Israel protests but acknowledged its unlikely.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 09:00:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vulnerable Democrat Senator Co-Sponsors Laken Riley Act Weeks After Opposing Provision</title><link>https://americanactionnews.com/featured/2024/05/09/vulnerable-dem-senator-co-sponsors-laken-riley-act-weeks-after-opposing-provision/</link><description>The post Vulnerable Democrat Senator Co-Sponsors Laken Riley Act Weeks After Opposing Provision appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 09:50:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Doug Burgum Is Having a Moment. Seriously</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/09/doug_burgum_is_having_a_moment_seriously_623303.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 03:30:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elon Musk makes dire prediction about the future of US elections</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/elon-musk-makes-dire-prediction-about-the-future-of-us-elections-2668215223.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52212388&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C75%2C0%2C96</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52212388&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C75%2C0%2C96" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52212388&amp;amp;width=600&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=175,0,167,0 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg%3Fid%3D52212388%26width%3D600%26height%3D600%26coordinates%3D175%2C0%2C167%2C0%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Business magnate Elon Musk has suggested that because the U.S. is being inundated by illegal aliens, the 2024 election will likley be the last in which the results are determined by American citizens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Given the massive influx of illegals from every country on Earth, 2024 will probably be the last election actually decided by US citizens," Musk &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1788431023593697519" target="_blank"&gt;tweeted&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Unanimous Democrat opposition to requiring citizenship for apportionment of House seats and Presidential electoral college votes says it all"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The House of Representatives &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/house-passes-bill-to-add-citizenship-question-to-census-to-stop-illegal-aliens-from-distorting-congressional-representation" target="_blank"&gt;passed&lt;/a&gt; a &lt;a href="https://www.congress.gov/bill/118th-congress/house-bill/7109/text" target="_blank"&gt;measure&lt;/a&gt; that would require the nation's decennial census count to include a component for respondents to indicate whether they and those in their household are U.S. citizens. The measure would require the exclusion of noncitizens from the figures used in determining each state's number of seats in the U.S. House of Representatives. The number of House seats in a state also impacts how much influence that state will have on the outcome of presidential elections. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://clerk.house.gov/Votes/2024193" target="_blank"&gt;vote&lt;/a&gt; was 206-202, strictly along party lines, with Republicans supporting passage and Democrats voting against the measure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Unanimous Democrat opposition to requiring citizenship for apportionment of House seats and Presidential electoral college votes says it all," Musk &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1788429941081555229" target="_blank"&gt;tweeted&lt;/a&gt;. "The Democratic Party goal is to disenfranchise US citizens by importing as many illegal immigrants as possible," he &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1788430266769314028" target="_blank"&gt;added&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;         —  (@)        &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1788429941081555229"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Musk has previously &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/elon-musk-illegal-immigrants-apportionment" target="_blank"&gt;pointed out&lt;/a&gt; that illegal immigrants impact apportionment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Most Americans are still unaware that the census counts ALL people, including illegal immigrants, for deciding how many House seats each state gets!" Musk noted in a March &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1765771338457719262?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1765771338457719262%7Ctwgr%5Eb5d5f5b0703070974daf24de086ebf8e5f550dab%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theblaze.com%2Fnews%2Felon-musk-illegal-immigrants-apportionment" target="_blank"&gt;tweet&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"And House seats determine how many votes each state has in the electoral college. So although illegal aliens don’t vote, they can determine the outcome of Presidential races," GOP Rep. Thomas Massie of Kentucky &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/RepThomasMassie/status/1765808329832476754?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1765808329832476754%7Ctwgr%5E9fc57ac8378f3300ff1286b0280031aeae01058c%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theblaze.com%2Fr%2Fentryeditor%2F2668214825publish" target="_blank"&gt;wrote&lt;/a&gt; when replying to Musk in March.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;         —  (@)        &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/RepThomasMassie/status/1765808329832476754"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;"Apportionment is the process of dividing the 435 memberships, or seats, in the U.S. House of Representatives among the 50 states based on the apportionment population counts from the decennial census," according to the &lt;a href="https://www.census.gov/topics/public-sector/congressional-apportionment/about/faqs.html" target="_blank"&gt;Census Bureau&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The apportionment population count for each of the 50 states includes the state’s total resident population plus a count of the overseas federal employees (and their dependents living with them overseas) who have that state listed as their home state in their employers’ administrative records," the Census Bureau notes. "Yes, all people (citizens and noncitizens) with a usual residence in the United States are included in the resident population for the census."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Musk has also discussed the issue of election fraud. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Widespread voting by mail (not allowed before the scamdemic) makes proving fraud almost impossible," Musk &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1788441056905707613" target="_blank"&gt;wrote&lt;/a&gt;. "Out of ~100M votes, there will be at least a tiny amount of fraud. Anyone who claims there is none is obviously lying," he said in another &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1788442417747648598" target="_blank"&gt;post&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt;         —  (@)        &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1788442417747648598"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 02:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'We are so innocent': Top 5 moments of Trump trial, from mistrial denials to Stormy Daniels' testimony</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/we-are-so-innocent-top-5-moments-trump-trial-mistrial-denials-stormy-daniels-testimony</link><description>Former President Trump will attend court Friday after a week of salacious testimony from Stormy Danials and the denial of multiple mistrial motions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 09:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Malta’s Central Bank Governor Charged With Fraud and Misappropriation of Funds</title><link>https://www.zerohedge.com/economics/maltas-central-bank-governor-charged-fraud-and-misappropriation-funds</link><description>The post Malta’s Central Bank Governor Charged With Fraud and Misappropriation of Funds appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 09:49:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wisconsin Is a Must-Win State for Biden in 2024</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2024/05/08/special_report_panel_wisconsin_is_a_must-win_state_for_president_biden_in_2024.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 03:30:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Memphis mom turns daughter over to police after seeing security video of suspect in shooting death over $60 oral sex deal</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/memphis-mom-turns-daughter-over-to-police-after-seeing-security-video-of-suspect-in-shooting-death-over-60-oral-sex-deal-2668215156.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52212369&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C157%2C0%2C94</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52212369&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C157%2C0%2C94" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52212369&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0,157,0,94 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg%3Fid%3D52212369%26width%3D1200%26height%3D600%26coordinates%3D0%2C157%2C0%2C94%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Tennessee woman marched her daughter to the police station after seeing security video of the aftermath where a man was shot and killed over $60 in Memphis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Memphis Police Department said the body of the deceased man was found near Filmore Avenue in Cherokee Park on Monday just before 8 a.m. Security video showed a woman running way from the park about the time that they believe the man was killed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That evening, Shante Jones was watching the news and was shocked to find that the woman caught on video looked just like her daughter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I don’t condone violence. I don’t. If you do something, you will pay for it,” said Jones&lt;a href="https://www.fox13memphis.com/news/mother-turns-daughter-in-for-murder-after-seeing-her-on-news-police-say/article_36002738-0d44-11ef-975b-7f1078d540c0.html" target="_blank"&gt; to WHBQ-TV.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next day, she brought her daughter to the office of the homicide detectives. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Court records say that 26-year-old Kenyetta Hayes told police that the man had offered to pay her $60 for oral sex when she saw him at the Marathon gas station on Lamar Avenue. She said she intended to rob him and not participate in oral sex. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Police said that when Hayes and the man got to the park, she shot and killed him in order to take his $60. She reportedly told police she was "thirsty for money" and used the money to buy two hot wing combo meals for herself and her boyfriend. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite admitting that the woman on the video was her daughter, she says that she doesn't believe she pulled the trigger. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Police however, charged Hayes with first-degree murder in perpetration of a robbery. Judge Ronald Lucchesi  &lt;a href="https://wreg.com/news/local/woman-accused-of-killing-man-for-60-appears-in-court/" target="_blank"&gt;told Hayes&lt;/a&gt; Thursday in court that she could face the death penalty or life in prison if she's convicted for the crime. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jones had a warning for young people who were at risk of getting in trouble.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Think about what you're doing," she said. "They need to be a leader, not a follower, and watch who they hang around with."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hayes said she had $13 leftover after buying the combos, prompting many on social media to comment on inflation hitting chicken wing prices. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href="https://wreg.com/news/local/shelby-county-memphis-murder-rate-increased-50-in-2023-crime-commission-says/" target="_blank"&gt;recent report&lt;/a&gt; found that the murder rate in Memphis and the surrounding had soared by 50% in 2023 from the previous year, and crime rates across the board had increased from 2022. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Here's a local news report about the incident:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;! &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 01:44:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden admin's National Guard 'power grab' slammed by former general as governors put up rare united front</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/biden-admins-national-guard-power-grab-slammed-former-general-governors-put-rare-united-front</link><description>A plan that could let the Air Force transfer Air National Guard troops to the Space Force has been met with fierce opposition from governors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>