<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 07:26:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Tucker Carlson: The Defining Features of a Pagan Society Are Slavery and Human Sacrifice [VIDEO]</title><link>https://rumble.com/v4slmth-tucker-carlson-the-defining-features-of-a-pagan-society-are-slavery-and-hum.html</link><description>The post Tucker Carlson: The Defining Features of a Pagan Society Are Slavery and Human Sacrifice [VIDEO] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 10:11:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Are U.S. Campuses Facing State Repression?</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/30/why_are_us_campuses_facing_state_repression_622761.html</link><description>The right has painted nonviolent protests against the war on Gaza as hotbeds of 'woke' terrorism. It's a pretext for repression</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 04:53:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anti-borders activists are now running U.S. border security</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/anti-borders-activists-are-now-running-u-s-border-security-2668119002.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/anti-borders-activists-are-now-running-u-s-border-security.jpg?id=52142613&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C32%2C0%2C33</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/anti-borders-activists-are-now-running-u-s-border-security.jpg?id=52142613&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C32%2C0%2C33" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/anti-borders-activists-are-now-running-u-s-border-security.jpg?id=52142613&amp;amp;width=2000&amp;amp;height=1500&amp;amp;coordinates=127,0,127,0 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/anti-borders-activists-are-now-running-u-s-border-security.jpg%3Fid%3D52142613%26width%3D2000%26height%3D1500%26coordinates%3D127%2C0%2C127%2C0%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Michelle Brané is an &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2024/04/22/us-news/bidens-dhs-taps-anti-ice-activist-to-scrutinize-detention-of-illegal-immigrants/" target="_blank"&gt;anti-borders extremist&lt;/a&gt;. Her entire career has been dedicated to undermining America’s immigration laws and interfering with efforts to secure America’s borders. She has characterized U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement as “abusive” and has been a vocal advocate for defunding the agency. The bulk of her employment history consists of jobs with organizations that oppose any reasonable immigration enforcement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you think Brané sounds like an incredibly poor choice to make decisions about who ICE should and should not detain, you would be correct. Nevertheless, the White House has chosen her to be the Department of Homeland Security’s &lt;a href="https://www.dhs.gov/office-immigration-detention-ombudsman" target="_blank"&gt;immigration detention ombudsman&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This administration’s hiring practices, like its policy choices, are nothing less than a deliberate attempt to undermine the DHS from within.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In her new job, Brané will “assist individuals with complaints about the potential violation of immigration detention standards or other misconduct by DHS (or contract) personnel and provides oversight of immigration detention facilities.” Given her publicly and frequently expressed bias against any type of immigration enforcement, how often do you think she’s going to find in favor of ICE?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This recent hire continues the Biden administration's series of controversial job picks. For instance, Tucson, Arizona, police chief &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/2022/11/12/1136321045/customs-and-border-protection-chris-magnus-resigns-migrants" target="_blank"&gt;Chris Magnus&lt;/a&gt; was selected to serve as the commissioner of U.S. Customs and Border Protection, despite (more likely because of ) his advocacy of sanctuary city policies. Magnus instructed his department not to cooperate with ICE or the Border Patrol. He eventually proved so incompetent as his job that even the White House had to acknowledge his shortcomings and accept his resignation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The DHS tapped &lt;a href="https://cis.org/Feere/Bidens-New-ICE-Appointee-Wants-Criminal-Aliens-Kept-Our-Communities" target="_blank"&gt;Kerry Doyle&lt;/a&gt;, a pro-illegal alien, anti-ICE activist with no immigration enforcement experience, as ICE’s chief attorney. Doyle is a vocal critic of ICE’s successful 287(g) program that enlisted local law enforcement agencies’ assistance in apprehending criminal aliens. She has also been an outspoken supporter of foolish and dangerous sanctuary city policies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.texastribune.org/2022/06/27/ed-gonzalez-ice-nomination/" target="_blank"&gt;Ed Gonzalez&lt;/a&gt;, the sheriff of Harris County, Texas, was nominated to run ICE in 2021. A vocal opponent of the Trump administration’s immigration policies, he ended his department’s cooperative agreements with ICE and criticized ICE enforcement actions as unfair to alien lawbreakers. Gonzalez eventually withdrew his name from consideration after he was accused of domestic violence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s not unusual for individuals with &lt;em&gt;both&lt;/em&gt; prosecution and defense experience to be nominated for positions as judges or criminal justice agency heads. In the past, however, those nominees have typically been people who, along with having familiarity with both sides of an issue, have expressed a strong belief in the American system of justice. They have not been ideological extremists who believe that certain groups of people are entitled to break the law. But that is exactly what we’re getting now. The people in charge of immigration enforcement with the DHS are ideological extremists whose primary concern is the well-being of alien lawbreakers, not the American people they are supposed to protect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DHS Secretary &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/politics/biden-claims-done-all-can-secure-border" target="_blank"&gt;Alejandro Mayorkas&lt;/a&gt; regularly appears before Congress and, with a straight face, claims he is doing everything possible to secure America’s border and discourage illegal immigration. But even if Mayorkas were serious about immigration enforcement — he is not remotely interested in enforcing the provisions of the Immigration and Nationality Act or securing the border — how would he do it if every agency that reports to him is being run by people who are stridently opposed to secure borders? This administration’s hiring practices, like its policy choices, are nothing less than a deliberate attempt to undermine the DHS from within.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In fact, the very office that Brané is heading up is a classic inside-the-beltway boondoggle. Congress established the Office of the Immigration Detention Ombudsman in 2019. The office did not exist before because, like everyone else detained in the United States, incarcerated aliens could seek legal review of their detention, both before the U.S. Immigration Court and the federal courts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If that somehow wasn’t enough, immigration detention is also overseen by the DHS Office of the Inspector General, the DHS Office of Civil Rights and Civil Liberties, the ICE Office of Professional Responsibility (aka “internal affairs”), and the ICE Custody Management Division.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dissatisfied guests in an $800-per-night luxury hotel have fewer avenues of recourse when they are dissatisfied with the service they receive. So it’s unclear why foreign nationals who have either worn out their welcome in the United States or were never welcome in the first place, should have so many taxpayer-funded officials ensuring that federal incarceration is to their liking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ICE’s job is tough enough under the best of circumstances. There is no reason for Congress to further complicate it by creating unnecessary watchdog agencies like OIDO. That’s bad enough. But appointing an ICE-hating extremist like Michelle Brané to oversee such an agency is an unforgivable slap in the face to the dedicated, patriotic, and hardworking men and women of ICE. And it serves only to further politicize a basic public safety and national security function that should receive unqualified bipartisan support.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden laments 'extreme' Florida abortion ban, blames Trump</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/biden-laments-extreme-florida-abortion-ban-blames-trump</link><description>President Biden called Florida's new 6-week limit on abortion an "extreme ban" in a Wednesday statement, blaming the restrictions on former President Donald Trump.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 12:16:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jordan Jumps in, House Judiciary Chair Demands Answers on Politically Motivated Prosecutions</title><link>https://warroom.org/jordan-jumps-in-house-judiciary-chair-demands-answers-on-politically-motivated-prosecutions/</link><description>The post Jordan Jumps in, House Judiciary Chair Demands Answers on Politically Motivated Prosecutions appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 10:10:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Progressivism Wrought</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/26/what_progressivism_wrought_622569.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 03:25:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blaze News investigates: Texas prepares to cut costs by using AI to grade students' state-required exams</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/blaze-news-investigates-texas-prepares-to-cut-costs-by-using-ai-to-grade-students-state-required-exams-2668117820.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/blaze-news-investigates-texas-prepares-to-cut-costs-by-using-ai-to-grade-students-state-required-exams.jpg?id=52132040&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C128%2C0%2C128</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/blaze-news-investigates-texas-prepares-to-cut-costs-by-using-ai-to-grade-students-state-required-exams.jpg?id=52132040&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C128%2C0%2C128" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/blaze-news-investigates-texas-prepares-to-cut-costs-by-using-ai-to-grade-students-state-required-exams.jpg?id=52132040&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;coordinates=0,43,0,43 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/blaze-news-investigates-texas-prepares-to-cut-costs-by-using-ai-to-grade-students-state-required-exams.jpg%3Fid%3D52132040%26width%3D1200%26height%3D800%26coordinates%3D0%2C43%2C0%2C43%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Students sitting for the STAAR exam throughout the state of Texas will have their written &lt;a href="https://www.texastribune.org/2024/04/09/staar-artificial-intelligence-computer-grading-texas/#:~:text=This%20spring%2C%20as%20students%20complete,automatically%20reassigned%20to%20a%20human." target="_blank"&gt;answers automatically graded&lt;/a&gt; by artificial intelligence. The development comes as some fear AI could &lt;a href="https://www.holderness.org/story/~board/news/post/how-is-classroom-ai-changing-education#:~:text=Rather%20than%20banning%20AI%2C%20educators,personalized%2C%20and%20effective%20for%20students." target="_blank"&gt;significantly affect education&lt;/a&gt; in the near future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The exam — provided by the Texas Education Agency — will use an "automated scoring engine" to help grade open-ended questions on the State of Texas Assessment of Academic Readiness for writing, reading, science, and social studies. The move is a step beyond using machines to simply grade multiple-choices answers or Scantron sheets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It appears the state is prepared to save $15-$20 million per year by significantly reducing the number of humans who have to grade the tests. The plan in &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/4/10/24126206/texas-staar-exam-graders-ai-automated-scoring-engine" target="_blank"&gt;2024 is to hire just 2,000 graders&lt;/a&gt;, representing a steep cut from the 6,000 human graders who were hired in 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The technology that will be utilized to grade the long-form answers uses natural language processing, which is just one of the building blocks of artificial intelligence that well-known chatbots use, such as &lt;a href="https://openai.com/research/gpt-4" target="_blank"&gt;GPT-4&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blaze News reached out to John Symons — professor of philosophy and director of the Center of Cyber Social Dynamics at the University of Kansas — who appeared to be optimistic about AI's ability to effectively grade STAAR exams without any significant setbacks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We're basically looking for thresholds, how can the kids hit those thresholds? And I think, you know, contemporary LLM [large language models] will be able to catch most of those cases and do just fine."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since the STAAR exam was restructured in 2023, it now features fewer multiple-choice questions and more open-ended questions. These open-ended questions are also known as constructed response items.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jose Rios, the director of student assessment at the Texas Education Agency, said, "We wanted to keep as many constructed open-ended responses as we can, but they take an incredible amount of time to score."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before the AI technology would be capable of accurately grading students' exams, the Texas Education Agency had to develop a scoring system. The scoring system was developed by the agency, which gathered 3,000 responses that underwent two rounds of human grading.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the responses were graded by humans, the automated scoring engine learned the specific characteristics of responses, allowing it to assign the same scores as would have been given by a human.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When he was asked about the potential for AI to make mistakes, Symons noted that the technology being used is sophisticated enough to identify answers in a manner similar to how humans find a specific shade on a color wheel. Between red and blue on a color wheel, there are tens, possibly hundreds, of shades of blue and red.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"So if you think about something like a color wheel, right, and you think about the location of a color in a color wheel, you'd say this particular shade of red has a particular coordinate in this color wheel, right? You could represent that with two numbers," Symons said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Now imagine making that three-dimensional, right? And so you could say okay, not just the color but the shade of the color, or the brightness of the color, and you could add other dimensions like the warmth of the color. And eventually, you'd have a multi-dimensional space of color."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"And what these [AI] systems do is they can do that with concepts."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite the AI's sophisticated nature, there is still the possibility that it will generate a "low confidence" response in the score it assigned. If this happens, the score will be double-checked by humans. The same is true if the AI meets a response to a question that its programming does not recognize, such as an answer that uses slang terms or words that are not in the English language.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chris Rozunick — the division director for assessment development at the Texas Education Agency — said that the agency has "always had very robust quality control processes with humans," and that the same is true for technologies that will replace humans in the grading process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to humans supporting AI's grading efforts, a random sampling of student responses will automatically be pushed to humans to double-check that the technology is on the right track.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Software engineer and technologist Mike Wacker told Blaze News that it is imperative AI not suddenly "replace humans ... without evidence that the AI performs comparably to humans. You can't trust a rating just because it was produced by a fancy AI."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the Texas Education Agency has pushed back against the notion that it is using AI to grade the exams. The agency has conceded that while the automatic graders will use technology similar to GPT-4 and Google's Gemini, humans will still retain significant oversight over the process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rozunick said that "we are way far away from anything that's autonomous or can think on its own."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even though the agency has insisted that the technology is a reliable grading mechanism, educators across the state have expressed their pessimism about the prospect of a machine grading a child's work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kevin Brown, who is the executive director for the Texas Association of School Administrators, said that "there ought to be some consensus about, hey, this is a good thing, or not a good thing, a fair thing or not a fair thing."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Carrie Griffith, a policy specialist for the Texas State Teachers Associations, appeared to echo Brown's sentiment, saying that "there's always this sort of feeling that everything happens to students and to schools and to teachers and not for them or with them."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The STAAR exam results are a pivotal accountability system that the Texas Education Agency uses to determine the proficiency of learning in school districts and individual campuses across the state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each district and individual campus is graded on a A-F scale. If a district or individual campus is discovered to have underperformed on the exam, the Texas education commissioner is obliged to intervene.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The stakes are high for campuses and districts across the state, which is partly why some feel uneasy about leaving the students' exams in the hands of sophisticated technology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It has yet to be seen how sophisticated technology will handle grading the state's required exams and the unforeseen consequences it may present.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sanctuary city police arrest over 1K migrants from this country as residents rage against Dem leaders</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/sanctuary-city-police-arrest-over-1k-migrants-from-this-country-residents-rage-against-dem-leaders</link><description>Chicago police have made more than 1,000 arrests of Venezuelan nationals in the first three months of 2024, according to new data from a local outlet.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 12:16:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Unification of CBDCs? Global Banks Are Telling Us the End of the Dollar System Is Near</title><link>https://ourgoldguy.com/2024/05/01/unification-of-cbdcs-global-banks-are-telling-us-the-end-of-the-dollar-system-is-near/</link><description>The post Unification of CBDCs? Global Banks Are Telling Us the End of the Dollar System Is Near appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 10:10:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GOP Establishment's Days Are Numbered</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/30/gop_establishments_days_are_numbered_622647.html</link><description>The recent House vote on foreign aid while the southern border remains wide open reveals a divide within the GOP.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 03:25:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anti-Israel Group Encouraged Columbia Protesters To Re-Create 'The Summer of 2020' Hours Before Students Stormed a Building</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/anti-israel-group-encouraged-columbia-protesters-to-re-create-the-summer-of-2020-hours-before-students-stormed-a-building-2668115583.html</link><image_url>https://freebeacon.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/GMZCTZWWIAENn-v.jpeg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://freebeacon.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/GMZCTZWWIAENn-v.jpeg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;A New York City charity encouraged anti-Israel activists to recreate the violent protests of  "the summer of 2020," just hours before rioters stormed and occupied a building on Columbia University’s campus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://freebeacon.com/campus/anti-israel-group-encouraged-columbia-protesters-to-recreate-the-summer-of-2020-hours-before-students-stormed-a-building/"&gt;Anti-Israel Group Encouraged Columbia Protesters To Re-Create 'The Summer of 2020' Hours Before Students Stormed a Building&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://freebeacon.com"&gt;Washington Free Beacon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 10:01:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump says violence on college campuses 'has to stop immediately' amid violent anti-Israel protests</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-says-weak-ineffective-leadership-universities-must-replaced-violent-anti-israel-chaos</link><description>Former President Trump condemned violent anti-Israel protests erupting on college campuses, saying “weak and ineffective leadership" must be “replaced."</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 11:51:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Most Americans Now Realize They Were Happier and the Nation Was Stronger Under Donald Trump [VIDEO]</title><link>https://rumble.com/v4slmli-most-americans-now-realize-they-were-happier-and-the-nation-was-stronger-un.html</link><description>The post Most Americans Now Realize They Were Happier and the Nation Was Stronger Under Donald Trump [VIDEO] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 09:56:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When Silicon Valley Stopped Trying To Save the World</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/30/when_silicon_valley_stopped_trying_to_save_the_world_622709.html</link><description>Four years ago, Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong was treated as a heretic when he insisted on leaving politics out of work. Now he looks prophetic.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 03:25:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>David Trone's Financial Disclosures Don't Add Up. Experts Say That Could Land Him in Legal Trouble.</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/david-trone-s-financial-disclosures-don-t-add-up-experts-say-that-could-land-him-in-legal-trouble-2668115577.html</link><image_url>https://freebeacon.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJhxvIFW8AArY3Y_736x514.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://freebeacon.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/GJhxvIFW8AArY3Y_736x514.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s unclear how much Rep. David Trone’s stake in Indiana Fine Wine &amp; Spirits is worth, but it’s enough that the Maryland Democrat pledged it as collateral for a loan worth up to $25 million in August 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://freebeacon.com/democrats/david-trones-financial-disclosures-dont-add-up-experts-say-that-could-land-him-in-legal-trouble/"&gt;David Trone's Financial Disclosures Don't Add Up. Experts Say That Could Land Him in Legal Trouble.&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://freebeacon.com"&gt;Washington Free Beacon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 10:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Newsom, state officials silent on anti-Israel protests at UCLA</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/newsom-state-officials-silent-anti-israel-protests-ucla</link><description>California Gov. Gavin Newsom and other state officials have avoided commenting on the anti-Israel protests at universities in the state amid unrest at UCLA and Cal Berkeley.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 10:03:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>More Evidence Showing Vitamin D Combats Cancer</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/more-evidence-showing-vitamin-d-combats-cancer/</link><description>Evidence continues to accumulate showing that vitamin D is a strong ally to combat cancer Low vitamin D levels are linked to an increased risk of cancers, while vitamin D can attach to the vitamin D receptor (VDR) in your cells, setting off a series of signals that may affect how they grow, develop and […]
The post More Evidence Showing Vitamin D Combats Cancer appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 09:52:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Watch the Trump Veepstakes</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/30/how_to_watch_the_trump_veepstakes_622758.html</link><description>New names are popping up constantly, but don't put too much stock in rumors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 03:25:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Democrat Tim Kennedy wins US House seat in New York special election</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/democrat-tim-kennedy-wins-us-house-seat-in-new-york-special-election-2668112507.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52146519&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C171%2C0%2C0</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52146519&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C171%2C0%2C0" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52146518&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=400&amp;amp;coordinates=0,171,0,171 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg%3Fid%3D52146518%26width%3D1200%26height%3D400%26coordinates%3D0%2C171%2C0%2C171%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Democratic New York state Sen. Tim Kennedy has &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2024/04/30/us/elections/results-new-york-us-house-26.html" target="_blank"&gt;defeated&lt;/a&gt; West Seneca Supervisor Gary Dickson, a Republican, in a special election in the state's 26th Congressional District.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kennedy's espouses pro-choice and pro-gun control policy positions, expressing &lt;a href="https://kennedyforuscongress.com/issues/" target="_blank"&gt;support&lt;/a&gt; for an assault weapons ban and for the codification of &lt;em&gt;Roe v. Wade &lt;/em&gt;into federal law.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We did it. We did it as a COMMUNITY. Because that’s what this was all about since Day One. And that’s what it will always be about. I'm honored. I'm humbled. I'm ready to get to Washington and get to work. Thank you, endlessly. Let's meet this moment together," Kennedy said in a &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/kennedyforny26/status/1785493111180841081" target="_blank"&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; on X.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;         —  (@)        &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/kennedyforny26/status/1785493111180841081"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic Rep. Brian Higgins, who previously occupied the House seat, &lt;a href="https://bioguide.congress.gov/search/bio/H001038" target="_blank"&gt;departed&lt;/a&gt; from office earlier this year before his term concluded. He had been serving in Congress since 2005. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Higgins announced his plan to step down last year. "I've always been a little impatient, and that trait has helped us deliver remarkable progress for this community. But the pace in Washington, D.C. can be slow and frustrating, especially this year," he said in a &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/BHigginsBflo/status/1723767289844023684" target="_blank"&gt;statement&lt;/a&gt; in November. "Therefore, after thoughtful consideration, I have made the difficult decision to leave Congress and explore other ways I can build up and serve Buffalo and Western New York." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The former lawmaker is now the president and CEO of Shea's Performing Arts Center.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;         —  (@)        &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/BHigginsBflo/status/1723767289844023684"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 04:42:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump eyes 2 battleground states as he looks to tear down Dem 'blue wall' again</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-heads-back-to-two-key-battlegrounds-as-he-aims-to-tear-down-blue-wall-again</link><description>Former President Trump to make campaign stops in Wisconsin and Michigan for the second time in a month as the presumptive GOP nominee aims to rip down Democrats' "blue wall" again.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 09:00:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>