<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 12:44:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>CDC Found Evidence That Covid “Vaccines” Caused Multiple Deaths Before Lying and Saying They Didn’t</title><link>https://www.theepochtimes.com/article/exclusive-cdc-found-evidence-covid-19-vaccines-caused-deaths-5632265?utm_source=partner&amp;utm_campaign=TheLibertyDaily</link><description>The post CDC Found Evidence That Covid “Vaccines” Caused Multiple Deaths Before Lying and Saying They Didn’t appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 17:00:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chicago Mayor Told To Stay Away From Slain Officer's Funeral</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/01/chicago_mayor_told_to_stay_away_from_slain_officers_funeral_622798.html</link><description>John Catanzara, police union president, discussed the maneuvering with the Sun-Times. When the mayor's office began</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 14:38:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oklahoma Just Became The Latest State To Take Immigration Enforcement Into Its Own Hands</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/oklahoma-just-became-the-latest-state-to-take-immigration-enforcement-into-its-own-hands-2668123741.html</link><image_url>https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Kevin-Stitt-e1714579602311.png</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Kevin-Stitt-e1714579602311.png" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;'We cannot sit idle'</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 17:20:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Screaming and cursing' anti-Israel agitators descend on senator's home more than a dozen times</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/screaming-cursing-anti-israel-agitators-descend-senators-home-more-dozen-times</link><description>Anti-Israel agitators have protested outside of Sen. Ted Cruz's home 14 times since February over his support of Israel, Fox News Digital has learned.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 17:19:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Violent Clashes Break Out at UCLA With Fireworks, Improvised Weapons, and Bear Spray [VIDEO]</title><link>https://rumble.com/v4sm4v9-violent-clashes-break-out-at-ucla-with-fireworks-improvised-weapons-and-bea.html</link><description>The post Violent Clashes Break Out at UCLA With Fireworks, Improvised Weapons, and Bear Spray [VIDEO] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 17:00:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Enduring Lawlessness in Our Cities</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/01/enduring_lawlessness_in_our_cities_622786.html</link><description>Crime continues to plague the American urban core at much higher levels than before the pandemic.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 14:26:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Russell Brand: Christian or New Ager?</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/russell-brand-christian-or-new-ager-2668123634.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52151153&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C120</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52151153&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C120" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img class="rm-shortcode" id="d29e1" src="https://www.conservativereview.com/media-library/eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpbWFnZSI6Imh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnRoZWJsYXplLmNvbS9tZWRpYS1saWJyYXJ5L2ltYWdlLmpwZz9pZD01MjE1MTE1NCZhbXA7d2lkdGg9OTgwIiwiZXhwaXJlc19hdCI6MTc2NzgzNTYxNn0.SspOfweUQ2lqppp2Z0XWABFJbmGNgxEISDm-XmNL3aM/image.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Russell Brand has been an openly spiritual person, but his recent conversion to Christianity has many asking if he’s truly a Christian or simply a New Ager. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“He’s certainly a critical thinker,” Allie Beth Stuckey says. “Over the past couple of years, we’ve seen him question a lot of progressive propaganda and I would say just mainstream propaganda.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stuckey believes it’s possible that Brand’s skepticism has led him down a path toward Christianity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“These powerful institutions are not worth placing our hope and trust in, and when you start to realize that, when you start to realize that all of these man-made entities are filled with sinful and deceitful people and we still find ourselves longing for someone to be in charge of us, longing for someone to give us order, longing for someone to tell us the truth.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“That can really only be fulfilled not through the government, not through the state, not through health entities, not through scientists, but through the God who created all things, who transcends all earthly power,” Stuckey continues. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While no one can truly be sure what Brand’s true intentions are, it’s not on us to decide. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I am hopeful, I am optimistic in the same way that I was with Kanye West. And as I said last week with Jason Whitlock, I do not regret being hopeful about West,” Stuckey explains. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just as she doesn’t regret being hopeful for Kanye West, who has recently announced his new porn website — she won’t regret being hopeful for Russell Brand. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I will pray for him as I pray for all of us, and I will pray especially though for someone like him, who does have a public platform and will be receiving a lot of push back and a lot of temptation, maybe even more than most, just that he would stay grounded and rooted in Christ.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 17:03:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sen Tim Scott slams 'disgusting' court gag order restricting Trump's 'First Amendment rights'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/sen-tim-scott-slams-disgusting-court-gag-order-restricting-trumps-first-amendment-rights</link><description>Sen. Tim Scott accused the New York court of stripping former President Trump of his First Amendment rights after he was fined thousands of dollars for violating a gag order.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 16:54:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jewish Girl on UCLA Campus Beaten to the Ground, Sent to Hospital</title><link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2024/04/shock-video-jewish-girl-ucla-campus-beaten-bloody/</link><description>The post Jewish Girl on UCLA Campus Beaten to the Ground, Sent to Hospital appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 17:00:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Gavin Newsom's Governance Boosts Trump</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/01/how_gavin_newsomrsquos_governance_boosts_trump_622765.html</link><description>Gavin Newsom is Joe Biden's double-edged sword. California's governor is a telegenic, well-spoken defender of the president and his economic policies, yet his state is a reliable reminder of everything that's wrong with them.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 14:25:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jacky Rosen Pledges To Combat Overpriced Drugs as She Rakes In Cash From Big Pharma</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/jacky-rosen-pledges-to-combat-overpriced-drugs-as-she-rakes-in-cash-from-big-pharma-2668123607.html</link><image_url>https://freebeacon.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/GettyImages-860604662-e1531163605175.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://freebeacon.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/GettyImages-860604662-e1531163605175.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sen. Jacky Rosen boasts that she "took on big drug companies" to stop them from jacking up prices. The Nevada Democrat also took on close to a quarter million dollars in donations from those same companies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://freebeacon.com/democrats/jacky-rosen-pledges-to-combat-overpriced-drugs-as-she-rakes-in-cash-from-big-pharma/"&gt;Jacky Rosen Pledges To Combat Overpriced Drugs as She Rakes In Cash From Big Pharma&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://freebeacon.com"&gt;Washington Free Beacon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 17:00:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mexico's migrant bussing spree a lifeline for Biden on border crisis: expert</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/mexicos-migrant-bussing-spree-lifeline-biden-border-crisis-expert</link><description>A recent lull in attempts to illegally cross the U.S. southern border could have more to do with beefed up enforcement efforts by Mexico in recent months.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 15:56:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>UCLA Security Abandons Posts as Pro-Israeli Group Engages With Anti-Zionist Encampment [VIDEO]</title><link>https://rumble.com/v4sm5g3-ucla-security-abandons-posts-as-pro-israeli-group-engages-with-anti-zionist.html</link><description>The post UCLA Security Abandons Posts as Pro-Israeli Group Engages With Anti-Zionist Encampment [VIDEO] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 17:00:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>President Biden Needs a Real Iran Policy</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2024/05/01/biden_administration_needs_a_real_iran_policy_150867.html</link><description>The world is becoming more unstable of late. Witness the collapse of Afghanistan to the Taliban, the march of Russian troops into Ukraine, the increasing threats China poses to its smaller neighbors, and the potential of an escalating regional war in the Middle East. An alliance formed by China, Russia, and Iran is on the march - with Western power seeming to blanche at the tough choices ahead.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 14:23:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Columbia protester asked for 'humanitarian aid' for Hamilton Hall occupiers so they don't 'die of dehydration and starvation'</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/columbia-protester-asked-for-humanitarian-aid-for-hamilton-hall-occupiers-so-they-don-t-die-of-dehydration-and-starvation-2668123614.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/columbia-protester-asked-for-humanitarian-aid-for-hamilton-hall-occupiers-so-they-don-t-die-of-dehydration-and-starvation.jpg?id=52150393&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C96</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/columbia-protester-asked-for-humanitarian-aid-for-hamilton-hall-occupiers-so-they-don-t-die-of-dehydration-and-starvation.jpg?id=52150393&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C96" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/columbia-protester-asked-for-humanitarian-aid-for-hamilton-hall-occupiers-so-they-don-t-die-of-dehydration-and-starvation.jpg?id=52150391&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0,0,0,96 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/columbia-protester-asked-for-humanitarian-aid-for-hamilton-hall-occupiers-so-they-don-t-die-of-dehydration-and-starvation.jpg%3Fid%3D52150391%26width%3D1200%26height%3D600%26coordinates%3D0%2C0%2C0%2C96%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Columbia University anti-Israel protest leader held a press conference Tuesday during which she expressed her desire that students occupying Hamilton Hall get "humanitarian aid" — you know, so they don't "die of dehydration and starvation."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/nypd-breach-occupied-columbia-university-building-and-arrest-around-100-hamas-endorsed-students" target="_blank"&gt;New York City police entered the building Tuesday night&lt;/a&gt; and made arrests,  getting an earful and eyeful of this protest leader and her wish list for her ultra-privileged, radical peers is still quite informative. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some might even say entertaining:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;         —  (@)        &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/TPostMillennial/status/1785386376755900611"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;A reporter asked her, "Why should the university be obligated to provide food to people who've taken over a building?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She replied, "Well, first of all, we're saying that they're obligated to provide food to students who pay for a meal plan here."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That's right. Meal plan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The reporter continued: "You mentioned that there was a request that food and water be brought in."&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you didn't think the protest leader — garbed in the familiar keffiyeh scarf that's pretty much required clothing for anti-Israel college students — lacked self-awareness before, she lets it all hang out from here on in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"To allow it to be brought in," she said. "I mean, well, I guess it's ultimately a question of what kind of community and obligation Columbia feels it has to its students. Do you want students to die of dehydration and starvation or get severely ill even if they disagree with you? If the answer is no, then you should allow basic — I mean, it's crazy to say because we are on an Ivy League campus, but this is like basic humanitarian aid we're asking for. Like, could people please have a glass of water?"&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The reporter, refreshingly, wasn't buying it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"But they did put themselves ... very deliberately in that situation, in that position, so it seems like you're sort of saying, 'We wanna be revolutionaries, we wanna take over this building — now would you please bring us food and water?'"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The protest leader replied, "Nobody's asking them to bring anything. We're asking them to not violently stop us from bringing in basic humanitarian aid."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another reporter inquired if Columbia was preventing food from getting to the protesters, and the protest leader replied, "We are looking for a commitment from them that they will not stop it. ... I don't know to what extent it has been attempted, but we're looking for a commitment."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Anything else?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In response to the Post Millennial's video of the protest leader, journalist Jordan Schachtel &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/JordanSchachtel/status/1785407783677862093" target="_blank"&gt;added on X&lt;/a&gt; that "I did a quick search and found that this lady, who refused to reveal her name, is named Johannah King-Slutzky. She is a paid instructor &amp; PhD candidate at Columbia studying 'theories of the imagination &amp; poetry as interpreted through a Marxian lens.' No, I'm not making this up."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Post Millennial &lt;a href="https://thepostmillennial.com/columbia-phd-student-accuses-school-administrators-of-wanting-students-to-die-of-dehydration-and-starvation-in-occupied-campus-building" target="_blank"&gt;reported&lt;/a&gt; that King-Slutsky had been listed on Columbia's website as a Ph.D. student on Tuesday morning, but the page was missing by Tuesday evening. The outlet said King-Slutsky's biography read, "My dissertation is on fantasies of limitless energy in the transatlantic Romantic imagination from 1760-1860. My goal is to write a prehistory of metabolic rift, Marx’s term for the disruption of energy circuits caused by industrialization under capitalism. I am particularly interested in theories of the imagination and poetry as interpreted through a Marxian lens in order to update and propose an alternative to historicist ideological critiques of the Romantic imagination. Prior to joining Columbia, I worked as a political strategist for leftist and progressive causes and remain active in the higher education labor movement."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More from the Post Millennial:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;King-Slutsky has a long history of activism. In January, she attended an event where the head of the UAW was speaking. "Johannah King-Slutzky, a Columbia University graduate student and member of the student workers union within the UAW, was one of several attendees who chanted 'ceasefire now' during Fain’s afternoon speech Monday. The union called for a ceasefire in Gaza in December," WHYY reported.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;“Right now he’s done nothing to earn my vote,” WHYY reported King-Slutzky as saying, because “he has not acted with urgency to stop the genocide in Gaza.”&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In 2021, she participated in a campus strike of graduate student workers.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This story has been updated.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 16:23:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hundreds of asylum seekers in encampment at Seattle park after funding for hotel stay runs out</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/hundreds-asylum-seekers-encampment-seattle-park-funding-hotel-stay-runs-out</link><description>Hundreds of asylum seekers set up an encampment at Powell Barnett Park in Seattle's Central District neighborhood after funding for housing ran out.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 15:46:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>“She Lied Under Oath”: Senator Mike Lee Calls for DOJ’s Kristen Clarke to Resign After Her Lies Get Exposed</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/she-lied-under-oath-senator-mike-lee-calls/</link><description>(The Daily Signal)—Republican Utah Sen. Mike Lee is calling for the resignation of Kristen Clarke, the head of the Justice Department’s Civil Rights Division. “Kristen Clarke is in charge of enforcing civil rights laws,” Lee said in a statement posted to X on Tuesday evening. “She enforces those laws aggressively against anyone who sneezes near […]
The post “She Lied Under Oath”: Senator Mike Lee Calls for DOJ’s Kristen Clarke to Resign After Her Lies Get Exposed appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 17:00:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Trying to Guarantee a Forever War in Ukraine</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/01/biden_trying_to_guarantee_a_forever_war_in_ukraine_622790.html</link><description>Washington and Kiev are negotiating a bilateral security agreement that mirrors the 10-year commitments Ukraine has entered into with several European powers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 14:23:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FACT CHECK: Does This Image Show Neo-Nazi Protesters Carrying Israeli Flag?</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/fact-check-does-this-image-show-neo-nazi-protesters-carrying-israeli-flag-2668123177.html</link><image_url>https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/KKK-rally-e1560794552904.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/KKK-rally-e1560794552904.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A post shared on social media purports that Harvard University replaced the American flag with the Palestinian flag. Verdict: False The image is digitally altered. The original image does not include an Israeli flag. Fact Check: Protesters have barricaded Hamilton Hall on the Columbia University campus as arrests near 1,000 nationwide, The Guardian reported.  The university has […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 16:18:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fetterman blasts UN rights chief for 'concern' over anti-Israel agitators while never condemning Hamas</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/senator-blasts-un-rights-chief-concern-anti-israel-agitators-never-condemning-hamas</link><description>The U.N. has consistently urged restraint in dealing with the situation in the Gaza Strip, but critics have blasted officials for not condemning Hamas.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 15:42:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>