<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 23:56:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Colonel Derek Harvey Gives Insights on Unrestricted Warfare and Urgent Call for Action</title><link>https://warroom.org/colonel-derek-harvey-gives-insights-on-unrestricted-warfare-and-urgent-call-for-action/</link><description>The post Colonel Derek Harvey Gives Insights on Unrestricted Warfare and Urgent Call for Action appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 04:52:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Rapid Deterioration of the Sahel</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/02/the_rapid_deterioration_of_the_sahel_622882.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 14:47:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How cartel hitman used a food pic to hunt down Ecuadorian beauty queen and brazenly murder her in broad daylight</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/how-cartel-hitman-used-a-food-pic-to-hunt-down-ecuadorian-beauty-queen-and-brazenly-murder-her-in-broad-daylight-2668165140.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.png?id=52175003&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C6%2C0%2C180</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.png?id=52175003&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C6%2C0%2C180" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.png?id=52175002&amp;amp;width=600&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=138,0,22,0 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.png%3Fid%3D52175002%26width%3D600%26height%3D600%26coordinates%3D138%2C0%2C22%2C0%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cartel hitmen utilized a food photo posted on Instagram to hunt down an Ecuadorian beauty queen and murder her in broad daylight, according to police. Investigators believe that the 23-year-old model was gunned down because of her previous relationship with a married drug lord. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shocking surveillance video shows the moment that a beauty pageant contestant was murdered inside a restaurant in Quevedo, &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/tag/equador" target="_blank"&gt;Ecuador&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CCTV footage shows Landy Párraga Goyburo eating a meal at a restaurant with a man on Sunday afternoon. Suddenly, a masked assailant burst through the front door to shoot and kill the model. A second gunman secures the front door. After the beauty model was shot three times, both men are seen fleeing the &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/tag/crime" target="_blank"&gt;crime scene&lt;/a&gt;. Goyburo is left in a pool of her own blood before dying. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Authorities suspect that the lethal hit job was ordered by the spouse of a drug lord, whom Goyburo was rumored to have a fling with. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In December, Goyburo was reportedly mentioned in a text message conversation between now-deceased drug trafficker Leandro Norero and his accountant – Helive Angulo. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If my wife comes across anything about her, I’m screwed," Norero allegedly &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2024/04/29/world-news/moment-beauty-queen-is-gunned-down-after-being-linked-to-ecuadorian-gang-boss/" target="_blank"&gt;wrote&lt;/a&gt; to his attorney in 2022. "My friend, her name cannot come out anywhere. Otherwise, my world will come crashing down."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Attorney General’s Office was reportedly investigating Goyburo's finances, but she was never charged with any crime. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Norero would later be arrested and then killed in prison just six months into his incarceration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Goyburo has not publicly commented on Norero or his purported criminal organization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ecuadorian investigators believe that a food pic shared on &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/tag/instagram" target="_blank"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt; tipped off the alleged cartel hitmen on Goyburo's location. Goyburo – who has more than 175,000 followers on her &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/landyparraga.ec/" target="_blank"&gt;Instagram page&lt;/a&gt; – posted a photo of octopus ceviche to her social media account. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Goyburo had been in Quevedo to attend a wedding last Saturday, according to &lt;a href="https://www.ecuavisa.com/noticias/seguridad/landy-parraga-excandidata-miss-ecuador-asesinada-quevedo-FD7243025" target="_blank"&gt;Ecuavisa&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Goyburo competed in the 2022 Miss Ecuador beauty contest, where she represented the Los Rios province. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In her final Instagram post made on Wednesday, Párraga wrote: "The world is an echo, what you send into it, you get out of it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;WARNING: Graphic video&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;        Cartel-Linked Beauty Queen SHOT Dead in Ecuador                        &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iBBOm0k-dZE" target="_blank"&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 02:20:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anti-Israel groups accuse Chicago, DNC of trying to ‘protect’ Biden from protests at 2024 Dem convention</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/anti-israel-groups-accuse-chicago-dnc-trying-protect-biden-protests-2024-dem-convention</link><description>A coalition of anti-Israel agitators claim their First Amendment Rights have been violated by Chicago as they seek to protest outside the Democratic National Convention in August.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 20:56:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Long Beach Hotel Housing “Homeless” Sparks Tuberculosis Outbreak as Health Emergency Declared</title><link>https://discernreport.com/long-beach-hotel-housing-homeless-sparks-tuberculosis-outbreak-as-health-emergency-declared/</link><description>The post Long Beach Hotel Housing “Homeless” Sparks Tuberculosis Outbreak as Health Emergency Declared appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 04:50:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How We Know Climate Hysteria Is Not About the Climate</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/04/how_we_know_climate_hysteria_is_not_about_the_climate_622954.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 14:45:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Federal judge warns married teacher of 3 previously charged with sexual abuse of mentally ill student is 'danger to the community'​</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/federal-judge-warns-married-teacher-of-3-previously-charged-with-sexual-abuse-of-mentally-ill-student-is-danger-to-the-community-2668165042.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.png?id=52174970&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C100%2C0%2C13</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.png?id=52174970&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C100%2C0%2C13" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.png?id=52174913&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;coordinates=15,0,7,0 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.png%3Fid%3D52174913%26width%3D1200%26height%3D800%26coordinates%3D15%2C0%2C7%2C0%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;A former teacher allegedly broke the conditions of her home confinement regarding charges of sexually assaulting an underage mentally ill student. A federal judge warned that the married mother of three poses a "danger to the community."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/i-sound-like-a-pervert-high-school-teacher-accused-of-having-sexual-relationship-with-mentally-ill-16-year-old" target="_blank"&gt;Blaze News previously reported&lt;/a&gt;, Sandy Carazas-Pinez was accused last year of engaging in multiple sexual acts in her car with a 16-year-old boy. The New York City public teacher was fired from her job. Carazas-Pinez, 34, had been a biology teacher at the Biondi School in Yonkers, New York.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Biondi is run by the nonprofit organization Rising Ground and assists students with special needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The Biondi Middle and High School provides educational and therapeutic support to both residential and day students who have behavioral and emotional challenges, learning disabilities, or intellectual/developmental disabilities," the Rising Ground &lt;a href="https://www.risingground.org/biondimiddlehigh/" target="_blank"&gt;website&lt;/a&gt; states.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Carazas-Pinez was arrested in July after allegedly sending nude images and sexually explicit text messages to a 16-year-old student. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I do miss your touch and kisses not going to lie. I also miss seeing you masturbate, I sound like a pervert," she purportedly wrote to the boy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The mother of the alleged victim discovered the illicit content and reported the teacher to local authorities. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The mother said, "It’s the rape of a child with a mental illness. As a society, we have to prioritize the safety of children who are mentally ill and boys who are sexually assaulted."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The minor reportedly suffers from schizophrenia and a mood disorder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Carazas-Pinez allegedly committed multiple violations after being arrested. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This week, Carazas-Pinez allegedly violated her bail conditions. She was instructed not to have any unsupervised contact with any child under the age of 18.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The married mother of three reportedly emailed another former student a day after he turned 18 to wish him a happy birthday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2024/05/04/us-news/ny-teacher-charged-with-sex-abuse-of-mentally-ill-student-jailed/" target="_blank"&gt;New York Post&lt;/a&gt; reported that Brooklyn federal judge John Cronan revoked the bail of Carazas-Pinez after she allegedly breached her bail conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cronan noted that the infraction was technically not a violation, but "it seems to fly in the face of the spirit of the conditions."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cronan said Carazas-Pinez poses “a real danger to the community.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even her own lawyer called the ex-teacher's behavior "troubling." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prosecutors said the former teacher’s conduct shows a "pattern of grooming" a student for sex. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The mother of the alleged victim told The Post, "She’s a very disturbed individual, and I’m glad she no longer has access to children — especially mine."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@mattersofaccountability" target="_blank" title="@mattersofaccountability"&gt;@mattersofaccountability&lt;/a&gt; &lt;p&gt;Sandy Carazas-Pinez, 33, a biology teacher and married mother of three, was arrested and charged with sexual abuse of a minor with mental disabilities. The charges involve a sixteen year-old student at The Biondi School in Yonkers, New York. #TikTokJournalism🗣️#FirstThem👉🏾 #SexualAssault😤 #SexualViolence🤕 #ExposeGroomers👀 #fypシ  SOURCE: https://nypost.com/2023/03/25/nyc-teacher-accused-of-sex-with-mentally-ill-student/&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 00:33:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Conservative beer brand plans 'Frat Boy Summer' event celebrating college students who defended American flag</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/conservative-beer-brand-plans-frat-boy-summer-event-celebrating-college-students-defended-american-flag</link><description>Ultra Right Beer Company will host an event at a UNC-Chapel Hill fraternity house to celebrate the actions of the students who defended the American flag from anti-Israel protesters.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 18:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rob Schmitt: DOJ Can Make or Kill Any Case It Wants [VIDEO]</title><link>https://rumble.com/v4t5vuo-rob-schmitt-doj-can-make-or-kill-any-case-it-wants.html</link><description>The post Rob Schmitt: DOJ Can Make or Kill Any Case It Wants [VIDEO] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 04:50:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Not in Our Name--Antisemitism Is No Excuse To Censor</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/03/not_in_our_name--antisemitism_is_no_excuse_to_censor_622978.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 14:45:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bodies of missing American, Australian surfers believed to have been found in Mexico, 3 suspects in custody</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/bodies-of-missing-american-australian-surfers-believed-to-have-been-found-in-mexico-3-suspects-in-custody-2668164730.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.png?id=52174822&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C17%2C0%2C82</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.png?id=52174822&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C17%2C0%2C82" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.png?id=52174727&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;coordinates=187,0,0,0 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.png%3Fid%3D52174727%26width%3D1200%26height%3D800%26coordinates%3D187%2C0%2C0%2C0%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;An American and two Australian surfers have gone missing in Mexico and investigators believe they were killed. Four bodies have been discovered in a well, according to &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/tag/mexico" target="_self"&gt;authorities in Mexico&lt;/a&gt;. Three suspects are in custody in relation to the disappearance of the surfers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Baja California Attorney General’s Office confirmed on Friday that four bodies were found in a well near a surfing spot known as La Bocana, about 130 miles south of San Diego, California. It took rescuers 20 hours to pull the bodies out of the well that was said to be 50 feet deep. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Citing a source within the attorney general's office, &lt;a href="https://fox5sandiego.com/news/local-news/fourth-body-found-in-well-where-three-missing-surfers-located/?ipid=promo-link-block1" target="_blank"&gt;KUSI-TV&lt;/a&gt; reported that three of the bodies were the missing surfers. The news outlet reported that the fourth body was a ranch owner who was reported missing two weeks ago. The rancher purportedly owned the property where the bodies were located. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://zetatijuana.com/2024/05/arrestan-a-tres-por-desaparicion-surfistas-extranjeros-en-ensenada/" target="_blank"&gt;Zeta Tijuana&lt;/a&gt; reported that police officers located the surfers' camping area, where there were "blood and dental parts."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Authorities believe the surfers were killed in a robbery. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“When they tried to get the vehicle, the victims opposed the robbery, the robbers were armed with a firearm and apparently shot the victims,” Baja California State Attorney-General Maria Elena Andrade Ramirez told &lt;a href="https://www.news.com.au/travel/travel-updates/incidents/shot-australian-brothers-killed-in-robbery-according-to-authorities/news-story/7f2ff57d256878afe8ddf3fd236c9272" target="_blank"&gt;7News&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shell casings were reportedly found at the campsite where the trio was last seen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The missing surfers who are presumably dead are a San Diego man named 30-year-old Jack Carter Rhoad and Australian brothers 30-year-old Jake Robinson and 33-year-old Callum Robinson, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/border-baja-california/story/2024-05-02/search-missing-surfers-ensenada-robinson-rhoad" target="_blank"&gt;San Diego Union-Tribune&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.S. and Australian citizens went missing earlier this week during a surfing trip south of Ensenada, Mexico.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Family members last heard from men last Saturday. However, they did not notify authorities until a few days later when the surfers didn't show up at an Airbnb near K38 – a popular Baja surfing spot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Wednesday, a white Chevrolet Colorado pickup truck belonging to the San Diego man was located and had been set on fire. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three suspects were arrested on Wednesday in two different police operations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2024/05/04/us-news/three-suspects-arrested-in-disappearance-of-three-surfers-in-mexico/" target="_blank"&gt;New York Post&lt;/a&gt; reported that police arrested Jesús Gerardo Garica Cota, alias El Kekas, and his partner Ari Gisel García Cota. Also taken into custody was Cristian Alejandro García – the brother of Kekas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cota – a 23-year-old Mexican woman – allegedly had a surfer's cell phone in her possession at the time of the arrest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All three of the suspects were in possession of an assortment of methamphetamines and other illegal drugs at the time of their arrest, according to Baja California's chief public prosecutor Maria Elena Andrade Ramirez.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Baja California Attorney's Office &lt;a href="https://www.fgebc.gob.mx/boletines/10929-fge-en-coordinacion-con-fbi-trabajan-para-localizar-a-ciudadanos-extranjeros-desaparecidos" target="_blank"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; Mexican authorities were in close communication with the Federal Bureau of Investigation, the United States Consulate, and the Australian Consulate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Baja California is known as one of Mexico's most violent, cartel-controlled states.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Callum Robinson shared photos from the trio's surfing vacation on his &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/stories/highlights/17990422016637680/?hl=en" target="_blank"&gt;Instagram account&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Robinson was an accomplished lacrosse player known as "The Big Koala."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stevenson University paid tribute to the former student-athlete and alumni.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our prayers and thoughts are now for Callum's parents, Martin and Debra Robinson, who lost their two sons; the family of their friend Jack Carter Rhoad; and the many loved ones and friends all of these young men had," the university said in a &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/baltimore/news/stevenson-mourns-loss-of-alumni-callum-robinson/" target="_blank"&gt;statement&lt;/a&gt; on Saturday morning. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"He was a stellar student, a stellar athlete, and an even better friend. We will look forward to a time when we can all join together as a community to honor and celebrate his life," said Brett Adams – director of athletics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;        Mexican authorities find the bodies of missing surfers near Ensenada                        &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9edwmbnzEYc&amp;amp;list=RDNS9edwmbnzEYc" target="_blank"&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 22:01:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Stop the invasion': Migrant flights in battleground state ignite bipartisan backlash from lawmakers</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/stop-invasion-migrant-flights-battleground-state-ignite-bipartisan-backlash-lawmakers</link><description>Montana representatives are sounding the alarm on the southern border crisis, after a group of migrants flew into state late Wednesday night.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 15:31:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Karl Marx Weekend Special: Fight Against Rising Marxism With Personal Preparedness</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/karl-marx-weekend-special-fight-against-rising-marxism/</link><description>The Liberty Daily benefits when you buy from their sponsors. This weekend marks 206 years since the birth of one of the most destructive leaders in world history. Karl Marx, born May 5, 1818, was 30-years-old when he created a broken philosophy that was used to brainwash tens of millions of people. As he and […]
The post Karl Marx Weekend Special: Fight Against Rising Marxism With Personal Preparedness appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 04:50:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Applying to College Shouldn't Be So Complicated</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/04/applying_to_college_shouldnt_be_so_complicated_623032.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 14:45:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>15-year-old New York City girl charged with murder for fatal stabbing of teen over social media feud: 'A beautiful child'</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/15-year-old-new-york-city-girl-charged-with-murder-for-fatal-stabbing-of-teen-over-social-media-feud-a-beautiful-child-2668164445.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.png?id=52174217&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C65%2C0%2C66</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.png?id=52174217&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C65%2C0%2C66" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.png?id=52174217&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;coordinates=22,0,23,0 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.png%3Fid%3D52174217%26width%3D1200%26height%3D800%26coordinates%3D22%2C0%2C23%2C0%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 15-year-old girl was arrested and &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/tag/murder" target="_blank"&gt;charged with murder&lt;/a&gt; in connection with the fatal stabbing of a fellow teen in &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/tag/new-york-city" target="_blank"&gt;New York City&lt;/a&gt;. The deadly stabbing stemmed from a social media feud, according to reports. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 15-year-old suspect – whose name is being withheld by police due to her age – was charged with murder, manslaughter, and criminal possession of a weapon on Thursday. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Around 2:16 p.m. on Thursday, 17-year-old Emery Mizell was found critically injured in the courtyard of a Bronx building. She had been stabbed in the chest. Mizell was rushed to the nearby Jacobi Medical Center, but she succumbed to her injuries soon after. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The superintendent of the building where Emery was found outside bleeding to death identified the suspect as a resident of the building.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"[The attacker] came out of the building, and the other girl came from outside," superintendent Armando De La Cruz told the &lt;a href="https://www.nydailynews.com/2024/05/03/teen-girl-15-charged-in-fatal-stabbing-of-17-year-old-emery-mizell-in-the-bronx/" target="_blank"&gt;New York Daily News&lt;/a&gt;. "They started fighting, and one of them pulled a knife and stabbed the other."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was reportedly a group of about 10 minors around when the fatal stabbing happened. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A neighbor told the news outlet, "I thought they were playing. They were just kids. Then people were running back and forth getting tissues to stop the bleeding."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to her grieving father, Mizell attended James Monroe High School and was set to graduate in June. Emery was looking forward to attending her senior prom. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The suspect reportedly attended the same high school as Mizell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tony Mizell told the &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2024/05/03/us-news/girl-charged-with-murder-in-fatal-nyc-stabbing-of-emery-mizell-over-social-media-feud-sources/" target="_blank"&gt;New York Post&lt;/a&gt;, "She was a beautiful child, just a beautiful child."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to police, Emery and her alleged killer were involved in an ongoing feud on social media. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to a police insider who spoke to the New York Post, the victim had faced relentless harassment on social media prior to the tragic slaying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Latanya Mizell, Emery’s second cousin, said, "They shouldn’t be fighting because somebody said this about that person. It’s stupid stuff. It’s not worth taking somebody’s life."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She added, "These are kids, both of them. They both lost their lives. That right there is hurtful enough as a whole because we got to be better with our kids."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We’ve got some difficulty in our schools. But we have seen a very significant uptick in violence right outside the school, around the corner and up the block," David C. Banks – the New York City schools chancellor – &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2024/05/03/nyregion/teenager-stabbing-murder-bronx.html" target="_blank"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; during a town hall meeting in Manhattan on Thursday night.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mizell's 13-year-old sister Gianna told the New York Post, "She was there for me when no one was there all the time. She gave me advice all the time when I needed it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I don’t know how I feel right now. I have mixed emotions right now. At one point, I’m crying. The next minute I’m like, I don’t know. Every time I go through my camera I see her," the heartbroken Gianna said of her slain sister. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Emery has two other siblings. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"She was good. Strong. I miss her so much. I want to tell her that, 'I love you, please be safe, and I love you so much,'" said 6-year-old Josiah.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"She was a good girl. I love her. I want her to come back," said 9-year-old Josiah. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;        17-year-old girl stabbed to death in the Bronx: NYPD                        &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DPh9aFu-Xd8" target="_blank"&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Former Trump official announces major 'Deport Them All' border initiative amid bid to flip crucial Senate seat</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/former-trump-official-deport-them-all-border-plan-bid-flip-battleground-senate-seat</link><description>Dr. Jeff Gunter, Republican Nevada Senate candidate and former U.S. ambassador to Iceland, announced a new initiative to help end the border crisis.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 14:00:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pastor Waits Until Very End of Sermon to Casually Reveal His Wife Committed Suicide the Night Before</title><link>https://revolver.news/2024/05/watch-pastor-waits-until-end-of-sermon-casually-reveals-wife-committed-suicide-night-before/</link><description>The post Pastor Waits Until Very End of Sermon to Casually Reveal His Wife Committed Suicide the Night Before appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 04:50:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A New Source of Protest: Parents Requesting Tuition Refunds</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/04/a_new_source_of_protest_parents_requesting_tuition_refunds_623026.html</link><description>Frustrated parents are pushing back against university responses to the Gaza protests</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 14:39:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kevin Spacey breaks his silence over sexual assault allegations amid UK documentary release</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/kevin-spacey-breaks-his-silence-over-sexual-assault-allegations-amid-uk-documentary-release-2668164141.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52174094&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C171</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52174094&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C171" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52174094&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;coordinates=0,0,0,1 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg%3Fid%3D52174094%26width%3D1200%26height%3D800%26coordinates%3D0%2C0%2C0%2C1%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Actor Kevin Spacey — who was previously cleared of sexual assault charges after trials the U.S. and U.K. — has finally decided to speak out about allegations of illegal behavior ahead of a documentary about him set to air next week, according to &lt;a href="https://deadline.com/2024/05/kevin-spacey-inappropriate-behaviour-never-illegal-ahead-documentary-1235904335/" target="_blank"&gt;Deadline Hollywood&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spacey recently appeared for an interview with former GB News presenter Dan Wootton on his Outspoken channel on YouTube, saying that while he may have, at times, behaved inappropriately, there was never a time when he committed an illegal act. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“I take full responsibility for my past behaviour and my actions. But I cannot and will not take responsibility or apologise to anyone who’s made up stuff about me or exaggerated stories about me."&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I’ve never told someone that if they give me sexual favours, then I will help them out with their career, ever."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I’ve clearly hooked up with, you know, some men who thought they might get ahead in their careers by having a relationship with me. But there was no conversation with me, it was all part of their plan, one that was always destined to fail, because I wasn’t in on the deal.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And he said: “Were there times when I would flirt with some of the people who were involved in those programmes who were in their 20s? Yes. Did I ever hook up with another actor? Yes. Did I make a clumsy pass at someone who wasn’t interested as it turned out? Yes.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“That may not have been the best decision and it’s not one that I would do today. But it happened. It wasn’t illegal, and nor has it ever been alleged to have been illegal," he continued.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spacey &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/KevinSpacey/status/1786080999526322465" target="_blank"&gt;took to X&lt;/a&gt;, writing: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;Over the last week, I have repeatedly requested that @Channel4 afford me more than 7 days to respond to allegations made against me dating back 48 years and provide me with sufficient details to investigate these matters.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;Channel 4 has refused on the basis that they feel that asking for a response in 7 days to new, anonymized and non-specific allegations is a “fair opportunity” for me to refute any allegations made against me. I will not sit back and be attacked by a dying network's one-sided “documentary” about me in their desperate attempt for ratings. There's a proper channel to handle allegations against me and it’s not Channel 4. Each time I have been given the time and a proper forum to defend myself, the allegations have failed under scrutiny and I have been exonerated.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blaze News &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/actor-kevin-spacey-acquitted-of-all-charges-in-sexual-assault-trial-i-ve-lost-everything" target="_blank"&gt;previously reported&lt;/a&gt; on Spacey's case in 2023. Four individuals came forward, claiming that Spacey had sexually assaulted them. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The report read:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;All four alleged victims testified during the trial, and three of them alleged that Spacey had either grabbed their genitals without consent or forced them to touch his. However, the &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2023/07/26/uk/kevin-spacey-trial-jury-verdict-intl/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;fourth&lt;/a&gt; accuser made an even more serious allegation. He claimed that he had once sought Spacey's advice regarding his burgeoning acting career. Two weeks later, Spacey invited the man over to his apartment, where Spacey then drugged the man and sexually assaulted him, he testified. After falling asleep or losing consciousness, the man said he woke up to find Spacey performing a sex act on him.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite winning the case, Spacey says that he has nothing left. He went on to mention that he still has legal bills to pay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Georgia senators find little oversight over how Fani Willis spends taxpayer dollars: 'Like the Wild West'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/georgia-senators-find-little-oversight-fani-willis-spends-taxpayer-dollars-like-wild-west</link><description>Georgia lawmakers heard testimony from Fulton County officials Friday that suggested there is little oversight over how District Attorney Fani Willis manages her $36.6 million budget.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 13:08:15 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>