<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 13:41:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Marco Rubio Pretends He Doesn’t Know Who Alex Jones Is [VIDEO]</title><link>https://rumble.com/v4trg15-marco-rubio-pretends-he-doesnt-know-who-alex-jones-is.html</link><description>The post Marco Rubio Pretends He Doesn’t Know Who Alex Jones Is [VIDEO] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:39:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sex Selection w/IVF Is Banned in Much of World - Except Here</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/07/sex_selection_wivf_is_banned_in_much_of_world_-_except_here_623149.html</link><description>Little girls are better than little boys-according to these people.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 15:54:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>John Kirby Says Israel Can’t Eliminate An Ideology With Force. History Disagrees</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/john-kirby-says-israel-cant-eliminate-an-ideology-with-force-history-disagrees-2668188220.html</link><image_url>https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Defendants_in_the_dock_at_the_Nuremberg_Trials.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Defendants_in_the_dock_at_the_Nuremberg_Trials.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img class="rm-shortcode" id="04040" src="https://www.conservativereview.com/media-library/eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpbWFnZSI6Imh0dHBzOi8vdGhlZmVkZXJhbGlzdC5jb20vd3AtY29udGVudC91cGxvYWRzLzIwMjQvMDUvRGVmZW5kYW50c19pbl90aGVfZG9ja19hdF90aGVfTnVyZW1iZXJnX1RyaWFscy0xMjAweDY3NS5qcGciLCJleHBpcmVzX2F0IjoxNzY5MDA3Mzc2fQ.guT9CZZikQjuRE5AE1uoc53hPakJlCV9oOhNi_K9wLM/image.jpg" /&gt;No, Israel can't bore into the souls of Gazans and transform them into right-thinking people. It can render Hamas' ideology largely useless.&lt;/span&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:23:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Johnson warned against making 'side deals' with GOP rebels: Don't 'grease a squeaky wheel'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/johnson-warned-making-side-deals-gop-rebels-dont-grease-squeaky-wheel</link><description>House Republican lawmakers are calling on Speaker Mike Johnson to resist acquiescing to the demands of GOP rebels who are threatening to oust him.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:21:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ex-CNN Reporter Says She’s “Haunted” by Dinner She Had With “Closeted Trump Supporters”</title><link>https://conservativefiringline.com/ex-cnn-reporter-says-shes-haunted-by-dinner-she-had-with-closeted-trump-supporters/</link><description>The post Ex-CNN Reporter Says She’s “Haunted” by Dinner She Had With “Closeted Trump Supporters” appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:38:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Karen Party Has No Place for Men</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/07/the_karen_party_has_no_place_for_men_623114.html</link><description>The Democratic Party does not want or need men.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 15:54:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Politico ‘Surprised’ Biden Donors Are Funding Pro-Hamas Revolutionaries</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/politico-surprised-biden-donors-are-funding-pro-hamas-revolutionaries-2668188162.html</link><image_url>https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/53696390543_f3b9604abe_k-e1715101164377.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/53696390543_f3b9604abe_k-e1715101164377.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img class="rm-shortcode" id="21a0d" src="https://www.conservativereview.com/media-library/eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpbWFnZSI6Imh0dHBzOi8vdGhlZmVkZXJhbGlzdC5jb20vd3AtY29udGVudC91cGxvYWRzLzIwMjQvMDUvNTM2OTYzOTA1NDNfZjNiOTYwNGFiZV9rLWUxNzE1MTAxMTY0Mzc3LTEyMDB4Njc1LmpwZyIsImV4cGlyZXNfYXQiOjE3Mjc4NjA3ODl9.5RaS4ZFVBaWcDhgK7n7cSd2cXxKNjYi39k7b89xo10c/image.jpg" /&gt;'Pro-Palestinian protesters are backed by a surprising source: Biden's biggest donors,' headlined an article by Politico.&lt;/span&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:17:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hamas sympathizers could be added to list that includes terrorist suspects if GOP bill becomes law</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/hamas-sympathizers-could-be-added-list-includes-terrorist-suspects-if-gop-bill-becomes-law</link><description>Legislation by a Republican senator would put terrorist supporters on the no-fly list, including if they had been disciplined for such conduct, in response to college protests.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:09:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Disney Lost Over $600 Million From Just 4 Movies in 2023 After Year of Epic Woke Flops</title><link>https://www.theblaze.com/news/disney-600million-four-movies-23</link><description>The post Disney Lost Over $600 Million From Just 4 Movies in 2023 After Year of Epic Woke Flops appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:38:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Menendez &amp; Cuellar Cases Sound Alarm on Foreign Influence</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/07/menendez_amp_cuellar_cases_sound_alarm_on_foreign_influence_623142.html</link><description>Last week, Rep. Henry Cuellar of Texas and his wife were charged with accepting bribes from two foreign entities. Cuellar said he and his wife are innocent.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 15:52:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tom Brady’s 9/11 joke 'threw political correctness out the window' at WILD Netflix roast</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/tom-bradys-9-11-joke-threw-political-correctness-out-the-window-at-wild-netflix-roast-2668188244.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52187964&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C4%2C0%2C116</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52187964&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C4%2C0%2C116" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52187960&amp;amp;width=2000&amp;amp;height=1500&amp;amp;coordinates=0,0,480,0 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg%3Fid%3D52187960%26width%3D2000%26height%3D1500%26coordinates%3D0%2C0%2C480%2C0%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the woke crowd comes out of the woodwork to yell about a show, you know it’s probably a good one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was the case in the roast of Tom Brady, where absolutely nothing was off limits — not even Aaron Hernandez.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I knew it must have been funny when the people on a certain side of Twitter and sports media, you know who I’m talking about, started whining about how it wasn’t funny,” Steve Kim tells Jason Whitlock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I said, ‘You know what, hold on, this makes it a must-see,’” he adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During the roast, Brady even made a joke about 9/11 — which has the woke crowd completely up in arms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Like the rest of America, I’ll always remember where I was that fateful day in September of 2001, when, tragically, those two Jets … slammed into Drew Bledsoe,” Brady said to roaring laughter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whitlock believes it’s a “good sign that people were offended.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There wasn’t one ounce of PC in this entire deal. Nothing about this was politically correct, and for that to be transpiring on Netflix,” he says, adding that “this is another one of those moments where I’m like the dam is breaking.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Jews weren’t off-limits, black people weren’t off-limits, gays, transgenders, white people, nobody was off-limits,” he continues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“They just threw political correctness out the window and just went for it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Want more from Jason Whitlock?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;To enjoy more fearless conversations at the crossroads of culture, faith, sports, and comedy with Jason Whitlock, &lt;a href="https://get.blazetv.com/fearless/?utm_source=theblaze&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_campaign=article_shortcode_jasonwhitlock" target="_blank"&gt;subscribe to BlazeTV&lt;/a&gt; — the largest multi-platform network of voices who love America, defend the Constitution, and live the American dream.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:06:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chip Roy demands sanctions on ICC officials going after US, Israel</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/chip-roy-demands-sanctions-on-icc-officials-going-after-us-israel</link><description>House GOP lawmakers are pushing for a new bill to force President Biden to sanction ICC officials who go after Americans or U.S. allies.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:00:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gen-Z Is Watching Their Debt Climb Amid Soaring Food and Rent Prices</title><link>https://www.dailywire.com/news/gen-z-watching-their-debt-climb-amid-soaring-rent-food-prices</link><description>The post Gen-Z Is Watching Their Debt Climb Amid Soaring Food and Rent Prices appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:37:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>America's Hypocrisy on Civilian Deaths Is Infuriating</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/07/americas_hypocrisy_on_civilian_deaths_is_infuriating_623146.html</link><description>To preach to Israel about civilian deaths is hypocritical - the US should know better, given its track record.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 15:51:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Report: Disney lost over $600 million from just 4 movies in 2023 after year of epic flops</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/report-disney-lost-over-600-million-from-just-4-movies-in-2023-after-year-of-epic-flops-2668188243.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/report-disney-lost-over-600-million-from-just-4-movies-in-2023-after-year-of-epic-flops.png?id=52187105&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C59</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/report-disney-lost-over-600-million-from-just-4-movies-in-2023-after-year-of-epic-flops.png?id=52187105&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C59" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/report-disney-lost-over-600-million-from-just-4-movies-in-2023-after-year-of-epic-flops.png?id=52187095&amp;amp;width=2000&amp;amp;height=1500&amp;amp;coordinates=146,0,93,0 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/report-disney-lost-over-600-million-from-just-4-movies-in-2023-after-year-of-epic-flops.png%3Fid%3D52187095%26width%3D2000%26height%3D1500%26coordinates%3D146%2C0%2C93%2C0%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;A stunning report detailed the expenses on Disney films and found that the totals of just four of its big-budget projects lost the company more than half a billion in 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disney films showed up repeatedly on a list of the biggest bombs of the year, and the amount of money the mouse brand is willing to shell out only for the movies to end up deeply in the red is truly mesmerizing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The report by &lt;a href="https://deadline.com/2024/05/biggest-box-office-bombs-2023-lowest-grossing-movies-1235902825/" target="_blank"&gt;Deadline&lt;/a&gt; is a real eye opener in terms of the volume of cash that can be evaporated by a studio — even outside of the actual production budget — when a film doesn't live up to expectations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The outlet reported that typically Disney pumps out the majority of the top 10 most-profitable films in a year due to its Marvel movies, but those figures have largely unraveled due to the losses of Disney+. However, it should be noted that Disney and Marvel movies have suffered from insufferable wokeness and diversity-driven casting, which of course CEO Bob Iger &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/disney-not-woke-bob-iger" target="_blank"&gt;denies&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Topping the list of flops was "The Marvels," a project that checked a lot of boxes for the film studio as a diverse, female-led and directed superhero movie. Unfortunately, the movie's $218 million in revenues was overshadowed by a $270 million production budget along with over $100 million in advertising. It crossed the finish line with an estimated &lt;strong&gt;$237 million loss&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disney was rated the worst movie studio of 2023 by &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/disney-worst-major-studio-2023" target="_blank"&gt;Variety&lt;/a&gt;, and it's no wonder given that for the entire year moviegoers were perplexed that the studio seemed unwilling to change its ideological path.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Indiana Jones and the Dial of Destiny" was yet another heartache for both the studio and fans of the franchise. With reports of rewrites and reshoots after &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/indiana-jones-female-lead" target="_blank"&gt;leaked storylines&lt;/a&gt; angered fans, it was hard to imagine the film could turn around the negative hype.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Add on a reported &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/indiana-jones-dialofdestiny-loses-130m" target="_blank"&gt;$80 million&lt;/a&gt; in post-production costs to de-age Harrison Ford, and it's no surprise the film made the list. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The expenses totaled $300 million in production, $120 million in ads, and another $96 million in residuals, distribution, and overhead. The film &lt;strong&gt;lost about $143 million&lt;/strong&gt; according to Deadline, meaning even showing Indiana Jones with his true face for the film's entirety couldn't have saved it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disney's "Wish" suffered terrible &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/align/review-wish-is-the-latest-failure-from-no-luck-disney" target="_blank"&gt;reviews&lt;/a&gt; and went relatively unnoticed even to Disney's most critical observers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;$300 million in production and advertising easily dwarfed its box office and streaming numbers, leaving the studio with &lt;strong&gt;-$131 million&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The animated film about the production company's own legacy wasn't the biggest hit with young girls who likely expected a better storyline for a Disney princess. The report described the movie as reeking of corporate product with nothing magical about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Keeping in line with strange movie ideas, Disney's "Haunted Mansion" is the studio's second foray into making a movie based around its theme-park attraction of the same name. While the Eddie Murphy-led &lt;a href="https://www.boxofficemojo.com/release/rl2690024961/" target="_blank"&gt;2003 iteration&lt;/a&gt; seemingly performed very poorly, it still outshined the 2023 film. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 2003 flick saw a global box office of $182 million, but 20 years later, the new version could only make $117 million. Against a $150 million production budget, the totals were again not on Disney's side with &lt;strong&gt;$117 million in losses&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In total, that left Disney with an estimated $628 million in losses from just four movies. How the company fairs in 2024 is anyone's guess, but it's hard to imagine Mickey can lose that much money without some big-name budgets suffering severe flops in theaters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Flights for illegal immigrants without IDs targeted in FAA bill as deadline looms</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/flights-illegal-immigrants-ids-targeted-faa-bill-deadline-looms</link><description>GOP senators are looking to include a measure in the FAA reauthorization bill to stop illegal immigrants from flying without proper identification.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:00:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Republican Don Bacon Is Moving to Censure Ilhan Omar Today</title><link>https://therightscoop.com/breaking-republican-moving-to-censure-of-ilhan-omar-today/</link><description>The post Republican Don Bacon Is Moving to Censure Ilhan Omar Today appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:22:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>America's China Strategy Has a Credibility Problem</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/07/americas_china_strategy_has_a_credibility_problem_623159.html</link><description>A muddled approach to economic sanctions won't deter Beijing.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 15:50:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Education Secretary Refuses To Say If He Would Let Boys Fight His Daughter And Undress In Front Of Her</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/biden-education-secretary-refuses-to-say-if-he-would-let-boys-fight-his-daughter-and-undress-in-front-of-her-2668188026.html</link><image_url>https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Screenshot-2024-05-07-12.42.36-PM-e1715100299851.png</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Screenshot-2024-05-07-12.42.36-PM-e1715100299851.png" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;'I am not going to be commenting'</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:03:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eric Trump slams Stormy's testimony from front row court seat: 'Garbage'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/eric-trump-slams-stormys-testimony-front-row-court-seat-garbage</link><description>Eric Trump, former President Donald Trump's son, slammed the Manhattan trial's testimony from former pornographic actress Stormy Daniels as "garbage."</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:50:45 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>