<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 07:54:39 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Poll Finds Massive Majority of College Students Not Interested in Anti-Israel Protests – Want Protesters Held Accountable</title><link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2024/05/poll-finds-massive-majority-college-students-not-interested/</link><description>The post Poll Finds Massive Majority of College Students Not Interested in Anti-Israel Protests – Want Protesters Held Accountable appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:34:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>4 Issues for an Article V Convention</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2024/05/08/an_article_v_convention_150906.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:38:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Celebrities’ ‘Misery Chic’ Aesthetic Flows From Their Spiritually Poverty</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/celebrities-misery-chic-aesthetic-flows-from-their-spiritually-poverty-2668198084.html</link><image_url>https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/48590442896_616da11419_k-e1715021375592.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/48590442896_616da11419_k-e1715021375592.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img class="rm-shortcode" id="d01be" src="https://www.conservativereview.com/media-library/eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpbWFnZSI6Imh0dHBzOi8vdGhlZmVkZXJhbGlzdC5jb20vd3AtY29udGVudC91cGxvYWRzLzIwMjQvMDUvNDg1OTA0NDI4OTZfNjE2ZGExMTQxOV9rLTEyMDB4Njc1LmpwZyIsImV4cGlyZXNfYXQiOjE3MjU1NTU4Njl9.YZBvnsTKAKirOkPM2sv6IVpDb5UCZbutJKpYn0nkYvg/image.jpg" /&gt;The cultural and spiritual wreckage around us makes clear that finding our true selves will not make us happy.&lt;/span&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:39:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RFK Jr re-ups Trump debate challenge, suggesting venue in 'perfect neutral territory'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/rfk-jr-re-ups-trump-debate-challenge-suggesting-venue-perfect-neutral-territory</link><description>Robert F. Kennedy Jr. challenged former President Trump to a debate at the Libertarian Convention in Washington, D.C., where both are scheduled to appear.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GA Election Board Confirms Over 300K Ballot Images From 2020 Election Are MISSING From Fulton County [VIDEO]</title><link>https://rumble.com/v4tvn4q-ga-election-board-confirms-over-300k-ballot-images-from-2020-election-are-m.html</link><description>The post GA Election Board Confirms Over 300K Ballot Images From 2020 Election Are MISSING From Fulton County [VIDEO] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:33:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Can $1.6 Trillion in Government Spending Save Biden's Job?</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/08/can_16_trillion_in_government_spending_save_bidens_job_623233.html</link><description>President Joe Biden is racing to spend money to green the economy, outcompete China and fix crumbling roadways in hopes voters reward him in November.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:17:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Democrats, Media Allies Pressure Georgia Election Officials To Blindly Certify Elections</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/democrats-media-allies-pressure-georgia-election-officials-to-blindly-certify-elections-2668198050.html</link><image_url>https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/47421890312_dbfe90b516_o.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/47421890312_dbfe90b516_o.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img class="rm-shortcode" id="da6af" src="https://www.conservativereview.com/media-library/eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpbWFnZSI6Imh0dHBzOi8vdGhlZmVkZXJhbGlzdC5jb20vd3AtY29udGVudC91cGxvYWRzLzIwMjQvMDUvNDc0MjE4OTAzMTJfZGJmZTkwYjUxNl9vLTEyMDB4Njc1LmpwZyIsImV4cGlyZXNfYXQiOjE3Mjc3MDM1MzB9.-JrCcu5glu0gOZyg_1iWKD_SkycPIpb8qrLmZuVUN9o/image.jpg" /&gt;A new rule could stop leftists from bullying election officials into certifying results without completing their duties.&lt;/span&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:33:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump says keeping FBI in DC will be 'centerpiece of my plan' rebuilding capital city</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-keeping-fbi-dc-centerpiece-plan-rebuilding-capital-city</link><description>Former President Donald Trump wrote on Tuesday via his social media platform Truth Social that if elected to a second term, he would ensure the FBI headquarters stays in Washington, D.C.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:14:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trojan Tomato: A New GMO Is Designed to Infiltrate America’s Gardens</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/trojan-tomato-new-gmo-is-designed-infiltrate-americas/</link><description>(The Epoch Times)—As spring gardening approaches, a new contender has entered the fray—the genetically modified (GM) Purple Tomato. Unlike its GM predecessors, the GM Purple Tomato is not destined solely for the fields of commercial agriculture—it has made its debut in the backyards of home gardeners across the United States. With claims of heightened antioxidant […]
The post Trojan Tomato: A New GMO Is Designed to Infiltrate America’s Gardens appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:30:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Hochul's Dim Slur on Black Kids Says About Dems</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/08/what_hochuls_dim_slur_on_black_kids_says_about_dems_623228.html</link><description>Bronx Politicians ripped Gov. Kathy Hochul after she said that some black children in the borough don't know what the word computer means.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:11:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are you really better off? Get ready for the Biden reckoning</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/are-you-really-better-off-get-ready-for-the-biden-reckoning-2668198139.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/are-you-really-better-off-get-ready-for-the-biden-reckoning.jpg?id=52191060&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C171</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/are-you-really-better-off-get-ready-for-the-biden-reckoning.jpg?id=52191060&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C171" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/are-you-really-better-off-get-ready-for-the-biden-reckoning.jpg?id=52191060&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;coordinates=0,0,0,1 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/are-you-really-better-off-get-ready-for-the-biden-reckoning.jpg%3Fid%3D52191060%26width%3D1200%26height%3D800%26coordinates%3D0%2C0%2C0%2C1%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Are you better off now than you were, say, five years ago? Is &lt;em&gt;our country&lt;/em&gt; better than it was five years ago? These are the questions that really matter heading into the November election. If we judged the state of the nation solely by what Joe Biden says, we would think we are living in the greatest years of American history. The economy is booming. Jobs are up. Diversity is on the rise. We can’t let Donald Trump come back and ruin all the incredible things Biden has accomplished. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Has that been &lt;em&gt;your &lt;/em&gt;experience? These politicians govern at your consent, and we are the ones who must live downstream from Washington, D.C.’s effects while the political elites shield themselves from their own policies. What kind of a report card would you give our leaders for the past five years? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Do you want another four years of our current path? If so, there's a reckoning coming. Don’t say you weren’t warned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Are we more stable than we were five years ago? Is the world closer to world peace or closer to world war — or even nuclear war? Are we more respected in the world today than we were five years ago? Do our foreign adversaries fear us more or less? Is our military more or less prepared for a major war? These foreign policy questions should concern you. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our problems don’t stop with our international reputation, however. What about the challenges in our own backyard? Are our streets safer than they were five years ago? Are police more respected? If someone commits a crime, are they more or less likely to go to jail? Do you have more trust or less trust in our justice system?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you don’t trust the justice system, the police, or the government, where or to whom will you go when you have a problem? It used to be that you could go to the media. The media would expose the bad guys, and the government would intervene and take care of it. If the bad guys were the government, then the people would take care of business. Do you have more faith in the government or the media to have your back than you did five years ago?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;High inflation forever&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then there is our fiscal policy — or lack thereof. Do you have trust that our Treasury and our Federal Reserve have your best interest at heart? Is inflation better or worse than it was five years ago? Do you know our new target for inflation is now 3%? That means the target is 3% of &lt;em&gt;additional&lt;/em&gt; inflation every single year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Inflation doesn’t reverse. A drop in inflation doesn't mean prices have gone down. It means that the growth of price increases has slowed. That means the Federal Reserve’s goal is to have inflation increase 3% per year. Are you on board with that? How about its track record so far? Over the last three years, official inflation was around 12%. It’s probably closer to 20% in reality. If all goes according to plans, inflation will be at least 15% higher by the time the next president’s term ends. Is that in the right direction? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Are gas prices better or worse than they were five years ago? How about the cost of insurance? Is it easier or harder for you to find a house? From your mortgage rate to your grocery bill, I think the answer is clear. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let’s consider the future we are building for our children. Do you feel our children are more or less safe in their schools than they were five years ago? It was about three years ago when we started finding critical race theory and diversity, equity, and inclusion indoctrination in our kids’ classrooms. Has that given you more or less confidence in your kids' school? Are our children better educated now than they were five years ago? Are our children more stable mentally than they were before this woke agenda erupted into the open? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Change course or fail&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;I can't think of a category that has gotten better. Can you? Every category doesn’t point to health, growth, or flourishing in any way, shape, or form.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A reckoning is coming. When our country goes this far off from securing your freedom and the fundamentals of our Bill of Rights, a reckoning is inevitable. It’s like telling your kids that they’re getting bad grades in school and warning them that they are going to flunk if they don't change course. You can offer to help. You can get them a tutor. But if your kid does not change, the time will come when it’s too late. They’re going to fail. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That's a reckoning, and it’s a natural response to harmful ideas being implemented constantly and without any regard to consequences or any thought of changing course. Until we change our ways, the reckoning will come, and it will be devastating. Right now, we're just moving the chairs on the deck of the Titanic. We can discuss symptomatic issues all the while heading straight for the iceberg. If we don't change, we will crash. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;November is the opportunity for us to change the leadership that has been leading us down our current course. Do you want another four years of our current path? If so, there's a reckoning coming. Don’t say you weren’t warned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Want more from Glenn Beck? Get Glenn's &lt;a href="https://links.glennbeck.com/join/51r/signup-theblaze" target="_blank"&gt;FREE email newsletter&lt;/a&gt; with his latest insights, top stories, show prep, and more delivered to your inbox.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>California Gov Gavin Newsom roasted over video promoting state's ‘record’ tourism: ‘Smoke and mirrors’</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/california-gov-gavin-newsom-roasted-over-video-promoting-states-record-tourism-smoke-and-mirrors</link><description>Governor Gavin Newsom took to social media over the weekend to announce that California’s tourism is at “an all-time high," while on top of the Golden Gate Bridge.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 11:00:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>“Climate Friendly Beef” Is Here and It’s Terrifying</title><link>https://wholecowstld.com/2024/05/08/climate-friendly-beef-is-here-and-its-terrifying/</link><description>The post “Climate Friendly Beef” Is Here and It’s Terrifying appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Of Course the Death Penalty Is Racist. It'd Be Wrong Even If It Weren't</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/08/of_course_the_death_penalty_is_racist_itd_be_wrong_even_if_it_werent_623213.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 11:56:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Judge Halts Trump’s Classified Docs Trial After DOJ Admits To Evidence Tampering</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/judge-halts-trumps-classified-docs-trial-after-doj-admits-to-evidence-tampering-2668197902.html</link><image_url>https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/52250930382_21ecad3a78_k-e1715139995738.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://thefederalist.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/52250930382_21ecad3a78_k-e1715139995738.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img class="rm-shortcode" id="e2f36" src="https://www.conservativereview.com/media-library/eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpbWFnZSI6Imh0dHBzOi8vdGhlZmVkZXJhbGlzdC5jb20vd3AtY29udGVudC91cGxvYWRzLzIwMjQvMDUvNTIyNTA5MzAzODJfMjFlY2FkM2E3OF9rLWUxNzE1MTM5OTk1NzM4LTEyMDB4Njc1LmpwZyIsImV4cGlyZXNfYXQiOjE3MjA5ODA5MTR9.zJnqqhTSiiBovsosxNLLySu5jz6jmLV77-m8HO0fh2k/image.jpg" /&gt;Judge Cannon halted Jack Smith's classified docs case against Trump indefinitely, days after the DOJ admitted it tampered with evidence.&lt;/span&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:19:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Republicans keep pressure on NPR and controversial CEO amid political bias scandal</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/republicans-pressure-npr-controversial-ceo-political-bias-scandal</link><description>Republicans are keeping the pressure on NPR and CPB after a senior editor at the former alleged a partisan bias in the newsroom that affected coverage.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 09:00:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Only Thing That Would Have Been Better is if the Painter Would Have Went Up the Masks [VIDEO]</title><link>https://rumble.com/v4tvlpb-the-only-thing-that-would-have-been-better-is-if-the-painter-would-have-wen.html</link><description>The post The Only Thing That Would Have Been Better is if the Painter Would Have Went Up the Masks [VIDEO] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 10:59:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Was Judge Cannon Right About a Special Master All Along?</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/05/08/was_judge_cannon_right_about_a_special_master_all_along_623203.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 11:56:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hate binds a bizarre coalition of contradictory leftist forces</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/hate-binds-a-bizarre-coalition-of-contradictory-leftist-forces-2668197821.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/hate-binds-a-bizarre-coalition-of-contradictory-leftist-forces.jpg?id=52190568&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C30%2C0%2C90</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/hate-binds-a-bizarre-coalition-of-contradictory-leftist-forces.jpg?id=52190568&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C30%2C0%2C90" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/hate-binds-a-bizarre-coalition-of-contradictory-leftist-forces.jpg?id=52190568&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;coordinates=0,0,300,0 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/hate-binds-a-bizarre-coalition-of-contradictory-leftist-forces.jpg%3Fid%3D52190568%26width%3D1200%26height%3D800%26coordinates%3D0%2C0%2C300%2C0%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before you enter a battle, it is best to understand the kind of monster you are fighting. With its use of mob violence, censorship, propaganda, and even criminal prosecution, it can be easy to conceive of the left as a unified tyrannical colossus. Not so. While a thin veneer of vindictive Marxist rhetoric is smeared across the coalition to create the appearance of a solid front, progressives in reality are a snarling mass of contradictory interests unified by their hate for America.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This distinction is critical, as it radically shifts the tactics one can consider when engaging in combat, and make no mistake, we are in a fight for the future of our country. The progressive coalition is powerful but contains many critical fault lines, and a proper understanding of this foe can help to strike decisive blows at critical moments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The left truly believes conservatives are an existential threat and that progressives have a moral duty to rule over and punish red America.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is easy to become demoralized and paralyzed by inaction when you see your opponent as an omnipotent and omniscient leviathan capable of crushing all opposition. Conservatives and right-wingers need to realize the totality of the forces arrayed against them, but only with the goal of increasing urgency and gathering courage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With the rising awareness of the deep state and the fact that the American ruling class is largely organized in opposition to the interests of those they govern, there is a tendency to view the left as a highly coordinated and monolithic force. It is a critical mistake to attribute unified intention and strategy to mass coalitions. It gives the illusion of playing chess against a single grand champion, when in reality, you are dealing with a loose but powerful oligarchy that is herding increasingly rabid cattle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The deep contradictions at the heart of the progressive coalition often baffle conservatives. Trans activists work alongside African-American and Muslim communities that find their lifestyles repulsive. Marxist radicals agitate for economic revolution but end up supporting woke multinational corporations. Liberal pro-Israel Jewish donors fund the same political movement that contains Palestinian activists who chant “from the river to the sea” across college campuses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These groups would be fighting to the death in any other context, but somehow, they find a way to work together and dominate the pollical landscape.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many on the right have attempted to explain this curious phenomenon by attributing it to the prevalence of postmodern neo-Marxist thought on the left. This is tempting, as many on the left explicitly embrace Marxist language or apply the “oppressed and oppressor” frame to their evaluation of every social ill. I think it fair to say that, to some degree, Marxist thought has become the superstructure that grants a level of coherence to the leftist coalition, but ultimately this is not the deciding factor that causes “Queers for Palestine” to cheer for a group of people who would kill them in a heartbeat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Naked desire for power&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;At its core the left is a movement unified by hatred of the average red-state American. The rural, white, small-business-owning evangelical Christian male with a wife and kids is the evilest thing progressives can imagine. Every faction inside the leftist coalition has its own interests and grievances, but they are united by the fact that they hold red America in the deepest contempt and blame them for everything wrong in the country. This is why the left seems fine with discarding and adopting contradictory narratives at a moment’s notice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, the left is held together by a naked desire for power and vengeance, and that power comes from dismantling the civilization built by previous generations of Americans and distributing the spoils to the various client classes that serve the progressive movement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Under any other circumstances, the different factions inside the left would tear each other apart, but that animosity is held at bay by a general fear and loathing of conservative America.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is a reason that universities, corporations, and even the United States military have identified “whiteness” as an evil that must be suppressed or expelled from public life. Many in the progressive coalition are of course white, but they see themselves as “one of the good ones” — allies against the deplorables and bitter clingers who wear MAGA hats and attend church on Sunday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As wild as it may seem due to the meek resistance offered by the Republican Party, the left truly believes conservatives are an existential threat and that progressives have a moral duty to rule over and punish red America.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hatred and fear are powerful motivators, but they cannot paper over the critical fault lines in the progressive coalition forever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The leftist civil war over Israel and Palestine that has erupted on college campuses during an election year shows how quickly rival factions can turn on each other without a shared enemy to fight. The right should keep these hostile divisions in mind and look to exacerbate them at every opportunity.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conservatives should also know when to get out of the way and let warring factions fight each other, rather than riding to the rescue by providing a shared symbol around which the left can rally. While it’s highly unlikely that any of these groups will suddenly flip and begin voting Republican, sowing chaos among the ranks of the enemy in a critical election year is always a good tactic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Conservatives’ task now&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The hatred shared by the different factions in the progressive coalition can galvanize them into an intimidating force, but the right should never be blind to the fact that these groups have very different interests and goals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conservatives should also avoid the temptation to over-intellectualize the motives of a movement that is driven entirely by resentment and the lust for power. The left is only capable of acting as a force of hatred and deconstruction, which means it has nothing to offer but the gutted ruins of a civilization progressives are intent on destroying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Progressives are clear about what they hate and seek to dismantle, so conservatives should be clear about what they love and what they intend to build, while taking every opportunity to expose and exacerbate the rift between factions in the leftist coalition.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Top 5 moments of Trump trial after 'salacious' Stormy Daniels testimony</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/top-5-moments-of-trump-trial-after-salacious-stormy-daniels-testimony</link><description>Former President Trump's criminal trial reached a fever pitch Tuesday amid salacious testimony from Stormy Daniels that prompted a motion for a mistrial and a scolding from the judge.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 09:00:51 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>