<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 06:47:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Conservative Momma Reminds Us About ‘Day 1’ of a Heels Up Harris Regime [VIDEO]</title><link>https://rumble.com/v5an50l-conservative-momma-reminds-us-about-day-1-of-a-heels-up-harris-regime.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>The post Conservative Momma Reminds Us About ‘Day 1’ of a Heels Up Harris Regime [VIDEO] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 09:04:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump legal cases in limbo after SCOTUS immunity ruling, freeing up schedule to campaign</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-legal-cases-limbo-after-scotus-immunity-ruling-freeing-up-schedule-campaign</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Former President Trump has had a number of legal victories in recent weeks, putting a pause on a majority of cases and delaying others that could have complicated his campaigning during the general election season.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 09:00:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trigger a Libtard! We Double-Dog Dare Ya! Own Our New Kamala Shirt at The Liberty Daily Store Now — For a Limited Time Only</title><link>https://shop.thelibertydaily.com/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>The post Trigger a Libtard! We Double-Dog Dare Ya! Own Our New Kamala Shirt at The Liberty Daily Store Now — For a Limited Time Only appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 09:04:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Here's where the vice presidential candidates stand on top issues</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/heres-vice-presidential-candidates-stand-top-issues</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Republican Sen. JD Vance and Democratic Gov. Tim Walz have differing views on most key issues as they campaign against one another as the 2024 vice presidential nominees.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 09:00:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meena Harris: Kamala’s Niece Cashing In on Political Ties, Echoing Hunter</title><link>https://headlineusa.com/meena-harris-kamalas-niece-cashing-in-on-political-ties-echoing-hunter/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>The post Meena Harris: Kamala’s Niece Cashing In on Political Ties, Echoing Hunter appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 09:04:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Harris hauls in $12 million at San Francisco fundraiser as Pelosi welcomes vice president home</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/harris-hauls-12-million-san-francisco-fundraiser-pelosi-welcomes-vice-president-home</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Vice President Kamala Harris hauls in over $12 million in her race against Donald Trump, at a fundraiser in San Francisco where she was introduced by former House Speaker Nancy Pelosi</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 04:33:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Detransitioners Are Starting to Fight Back Against Planned Butcherhood [VIDEO]</title><link>https://rumble.com/v5an4tx-detransitioners-are-starting-to-fight-back-against-planned-butcherhood.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>The post Detransitioners Are Starting to Fight Back Against Planned Butcherhood [VIDEO] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 09:03:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden to hit campaign trail for Harris in Pennsylvania</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/biden-hit-campaign-trail-harris-pennsylvania</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>President Biden said in a CBS interview that he will be hitting the campaign trail in Pennsylvania in support of Vice President Harris' presidential run.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 00:50:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Russian Military Ship Spotted 30 Miles Off Alaska by Coast Guard</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/russian-military-ship-spotted-30-miles-alaska-coast/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>(Zero Hedge)—A U.S. Coast Guard cutter on routine patrol around Alaska’s Aleutian Islands came across a Russian military ship in international waters but within the U.S. exclusive economic zone, the AP reported citing US military officials The crew on the U.S. Coast Guard Cutter Alex Haley on Monday detected the vessel about 30 miles (48 […] The post Russian Military Ship Spotted 30 Miles Off Alaska by Coast Guard appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 09:02:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Secret Service hints it wasn’t behind salon break-in during Kamala Harris campaign event</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/secret-service-hints-wasnt-behind-salon-break-in-during-kamala-harris-campaign-event</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>The U.S. Secret Service on Sunday hinted it wasn't involved in a break-in of a hair salon during a Kamala Harris campaign event in Massachusetts late last month.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 22:12:33 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>