<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 02:22:37 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>MLB Ump With Stellar Accuracy Ratings Busted Gambling</title><link>https://wgntv.com/sports/reports-mlb-disciplines-umpire-for-gambling/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>The post MLB Ump With Stellar Accuracy Ratings Busted Gambling appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 06:25:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump vows to build Israel-style 'Great Iron Dome' over US if re-elected: 'Made in America'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-vows-build-israel-style-great-iron-dome-over-us-re-elected-made-america</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>Former President Trump promised supporters at a Florida rally that he would make a "beautiful" American made Iron Dome.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 05:01:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DOJ Refuses to Pursue Criminal Contempt Changes Against Merrick Garland</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/doj-refuses-pursue-criminal-contempt-changes-against-merrick/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>(The Epoch Times)—An official from the Department of Justice (DOJ) told House Speaker Mike Johnson (R-La.) in a letter that Attorney General Merrick Garland will not be prosecuted for contempt of Congress because his refusal to hand over audio recordings of President Joe Biden’s interview with a prosecutor did not amount to a crime. In […] The post DOJ Refuses to Pursue Criminal Contempt Changes Against Merrick Garland appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 05:59:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Under the dome and on the diamond</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/under-dome-diamond</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>Similarly to daily life on Capitol Hill, Republicans and Democrats recently faced off in the Congressional Baseball Game, an annual charity event that started more than 100 years ago.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 01:09:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I Hope Commiefornia Is Ready for a Recession Because One May Be Coming Whether It’s Ready or Not</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/i-hope-commiefornia-is-ready-recession-because-one/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>(The Epoch Times)—Several economic indicators are flashing warning lights for a recession in California. Unlike the 2020 recession, which ended as quickly as the COVID-19 restrictions were lifted, this one would be more structural. Some indicators: 1. Allen Buchanan, a principal with Lee &amp; Associates Commercial Real Estate Services in Orange, is warning of price […] The post I Hope Commiefornia Is Ready for a Recession Because One May Be Coming Whether It’s Ready or Not appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 05:59:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Military officials' worries about 'optics' are to blame for National Guard delay Jan. 6, top Republican says</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/military-officials-national-guard-delay-top-republican</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>Rep. Barry Loudermilk, R-Ga., discussed the findings from his subcommittee's investigation into the Jan. 6 Capitol riot with Fox News Digital.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:42:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Los Angeles Removes “No U-Turn” Signs in a Sodomite Neighborhood Because They Were “Homophobic” or Something [VIDEO]</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/los-angeles-removes-no-u-turn-signs-sodomite/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>The Commiefornia s**thole known as Los Angeles may be riddled with crime, drugs, gangs, illegal aliens, and vagrants, but at least it’s not homophobic. The heroes at the Los Angeles City Council made sure of that this morning when they removed all the “No U-Turn” signs, which everyone knows are virulently homophobic, from a sodomite […] The post Los Angeles Removes “No U-Turn” Signs in a Sodomite Neighborhood Because They Were “Homophobic” or Something [VIDEO] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 05:59:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>4 Connecticut Democratic operatives charged in absentee ballot misuse investigation</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/connecticut-democratic-operatives-charged-absentee-ballot-misuse-investigation</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>Four individuals tied to Democratic politics in Connecticut's largest city were arrested in connection with an absentee ballot mishandling investigation, according to Constitution State officials.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 23:00:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Insights from a radical Muslim who converted to Judaism</title><link>https://www.wnd.com/2024/06/insights-radical-muslim-converted-judaism/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>The post Insights from a radical Muslim who converted to Judaism appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 05:58:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ICE sounds alarm on what migrants are failing to bring to border as fears mount after ISIS arrests</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/ice-sounds-alarm-migrants-failing-bring-border-fears-mount-isis-arrests</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>Acting ICE Director Patrick Lechleitner was asked for his response to reports of eight Tajikistan nationals with ties to ISIS being apprehended at the southern border.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 23:00:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>