<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 17:18:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Thanos vs. the World Economic Forum [VIDEO]</title><link>https://rumble.com/v4r4s9c-thanos-vs-the-world-economic-forum.html</link><description>The post Thanos vs. the World Economic Forum [VIDEO] appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 22:15:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Speaker Johnson Got 'Swamped' Over Ukraine</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/23/speaker_johnson_got_swamped_over_ukraine_622380.html</link><description>The return of GOP's minority-party mindset is very likely to be a self-fulfilling prophecy come November.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 20:57:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>As Crime Worsens in California, Soros-Backed Group Mobilizes Against Referendum To Restore Tougher Criminal Penalties</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/as-crime-worsens-in-california-soros-backed-group-mobilizes-against-referendum-to-restore-tougher-criminal-penalties-2667861503.html</link><image_url>https://freebeacon.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/George-Soros-1.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://freebeacon.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/George-Soros-1.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;A George Soros-backed progressive group behind many of California's soft-on-crime reforms has launched a fundraising effort against a potential November voter referendum to restore tougher criminal penalties for theft and drug offenses—even as Golden State voters increasingly disapprove of their state's lax approach to criminal justice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://freebeacon.com/california/as-crime-worsens-in-california-soros-backed-group-mobilizes-against-referendum-to-restore-tougher-criminal-penalties/"&gt;As Crime Worsens in California, Soros-Backed Group Mobilizes Against Referendum To Restore Tougher Criminal Penalties&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://freebeacon.com"&gt;Washington Free Beacon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 22:10:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Watchdog CEO confronts anti-Israel protesters at Columbia: 'Which is your favorite terrorist group?'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/watchdog-ceo-confronts-anti-israel-protesters-columbia-favorite-terrorist-group</link><description>Adam Guillette, the CEO of the Accuracy In Media watchdog group, was met with hostility while speaking to anti-Israel protesters at Columbia University.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 22:10:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mike Rowe Unloads on Anti-Semitic Protests: “The Ivy League Has Truly Lost Its Mind”</title><link>https://www.dailywire.com/news/mike-rowe-unloads-on-anti-semitic-protests-the-ivy-league-has-truly-lost-its-mind</link><description>The post Mike Rowe Unloads on Anti-Semitic Protests: “The Ivy League Has Truly Lost Its Mind” appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 22:14:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Ukraine Wins</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/23/how_ukraine_wins_622387.html</link><description>It took far too long, but House Speaker Mike Johnson showed true leadership in bringing Ukraine aid to a vote.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 20:56:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WATCH: History According to Joe Biden (Vol. 2)</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/watch-history-according-to-joe-biden-vol-2-2667861468.html</link><image_url>https://freebeacon.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/biden-revolution.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://freebeacon.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/biden-revolution.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Joe Biden's lies are out of control. The president sparked an international incident last week by implying his uncle was eaten by "cannibals" in New Guinea during World War II.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://freebeacon.com/satire/watch-history-according-to-joe-biden-vol-2/"&gt;WATCH: History According to Joe Biden (Vol. 2)&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://freebeacon.com"&gt;Washington Free Beacon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 22:00:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fox News Politics: Trump's other crime, revealed</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/fox-news-politics-trumps-other-crime-revealed</link><description>The latest updates from the 2024 campaign trail, exclusive interviews and more Fox News politics content</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 22:07:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>China Is Desperately Lobbying Congress Amid TikTok Ban Efforts</title><link>https://amgreatness.com/2024/04/18/china-lobbying-congress-amid-tiktok-ban-efforts/</link><description>The post China Is Desperately Lobbying Congress Amid TikTok Ban Efforts appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 22:14:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Leadership Lied, Said Border Funding Before Ukraine Aid</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2024/04/22/gop_rep_byron_donalds_house_republican_leadership_lied_when_they_said_no_more_ukraine_aid_without_border_funding.html</link><description>Florida Republican Rep. Byron Donalds told CNBC on Monday that the MAGA supporters who attempted to tie border security funding to military aid for Ukraine were lied to.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 20:53:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientific American pushes claims that science-based critiques of gender ideology are 'misinformation,' 'violence'</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/scientific-american-pushes-claims-that-science-based-critiques-of-gender-ideology-are-misinformation-violence-2667861469.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/scientific-american-pushes-claims-that-science-based-critiques-of-gender-ideology-are-misinformation-violence.webp?id=52079906&amp;width=980</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/scientific-american-pushes-claims-that-science-based-critiques-of-gender-ideology-are-misinformation-violence.webp?id=52079906&amp;amp;width=980" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img class="rm-shortcode" id="468e9" src="https://www.conservativereview.com/media-library/eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpbWFnZSI6Imh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LnRoZWJsYXplLmNvbS9tZWRpYS1saWJyYXJ5L3NjaWVudGlmaWMtYW1lcmljYW4tcHVzaGVzLWNsYWltcy10aGF0LXNjaWVuY2UtYmFzZWQtY3JpdGlxdWVzLW9mLWdlbmRlci1pZGVvbG9neS1hcmUtbWlzaW5mb3JtYXRpb24tdmlvbGVuY2Uud2VicD9pZD01MjA3OTkwNiZhbXA7d2lkdGg9OTgwIiwiZXhwaXJlc19hdCI6MTcxNTk3MTAwN30.jA3un4C4UE_O-hv1k-vhnfN7vUlJ3KRkenqSvNfM4SQ/image.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gender ideologues have &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/bidens-final-title-ix-regulations-will-require-accommodation-of-gender-ideologues-delusions-nationwide" target="_blank"&gt;the Biden administration&lt;/a&gt; and multitudes of Democratic lawmakers across the country dutifully advancing their agenda and victimizing &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/detransitioner-warns-shareholders-disney-will-pay-a-price-for-stealing-the-voices-of-thousands-of-little-ariels" target="_blank"&gt;multitudes&lt;/a&gt; of Americans, but apparently that's not enough. They also appear keen to have the broader public buy into their narrative around sex, genital mutilations, and transgenderism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In an effort to overcome or at the very least sidestep the common citizen's common sense, social constructivists have in recent decades attempted to mask their reality-defying philosophy in the language of science.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The trouble with this effort is that when exposed to actual scientific scrutiny, their &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/scientists-confirm-men-and-womens-brains-work-differently" target="_blank"&gt;claims&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/core-claim-in-lgbt-narrative-around-gender-affirming-care-busted-in-new-finnish-study" target="_blank"&gt;have&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/leaked-wpath-files-shed-light-on-the-horror-show-that-is-gender-affirming-care" target="_blank"&gt;altogether&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/finnish-child-psychiatrist-gender-id" target="_blank"&gt;failed&lt;/a&gt; to hold water. That has become especially clear in recent months where even Britain's National Health Service has &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/britains-nhs-to-reevaluate-all-transgender-treatments-in-wake-of-investigation-revealing-theyre-based-on-pseudoscience" target="_blank"&gt;pumped the brakes&lt;/a&gt; on so-called "gender-affirming care."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Faced with the collapse of their narrative, ideologues have worked to villainize critics and to reframe the debate about gender. On Friday, &lt;a href="https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/anti-trans-efforts-use-misinformation-epistemological-violence-and-gender/?utm_campaign=socialflow&amp;amp;utm_medium=social&amp;amp;utm_source=twitter" target="_blank"&gt;one such attempt&lt;/a&gt; was made in the pages of Scientific American, a 178-year-old science magazine published by the German-British  Springer Nature Group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientific American published an interview that originally appeared in OpenMind Magazine — former Discover magazine editor in chief Corey Powell's outlet that supposedly tackles "disinformation" in science.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The interview, originally made possible by a grant from the Pulitzer Center's aptly titled "Truth Decay" initiative, comprises an engagement between Powell and two transvestites, both of whom are self-identified activists: a French-Canadian man who calls himself &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/ButNotTheCity" target="_blank"&gt;Florence Ashley&lt;/a&gt; and describes himself as a "transfeminine activist, academic, and slut"; and &lt;a href="https://www.calacademy.org/new-science/sim%C3%B3ne-sun" target="_blank"&gt;Simon Dow-Kuang Sun&lt;/a&gt;, a senior fellow at the Center for Applied Transgender Studies in Chicago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blaze News &lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/news/transvestite-who-wants-puberty-blockers-as-default-option-for-kids-joins-other-radicals-on-who-task-force" target="_blank"&gt;previously reported&lt;/a&gt; that Ashley, &lt;a href="https://apps.ualberta.ca/directory/person/fashley" target="_blank"&gt;an assistant professor&lt;/a&gt; at the University of Alberta Faculty of Law in Canada, wrote that where confused kids are concerned, "Unbounded social transition and ready access to puberty blockers ought to be treated as the default option, and support should be offered to parents who may have difficulty accepting their youth."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He &lt;a href="https://truthout.org/articles/the-anti-trans-panic-is-rooted-in-white-supremacist-ideology/" target="_blank"&gt;claimed&lt;/a&gt; in an article for the leftist blog Truthout that efforts to protect children from irreversible puberty blockers, genital mutilations, and LGBT propaganda are "rooted in racism and white supremacy."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ashley has also &lt;a href="https://www.florenceashley.com/uploads/1/2/4/4/124439164/ashley_genderfucking_non-disclosure_-_sexual_fraud_transgender_bodies_and_messy_identities.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;called&lt;/a&gt; for the decriminalization of rape by fraud, particularly in cases in which a transvestite has sex with a victim without indicating he isn't actually a woman as advertised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/simonedsun" target="_blank"&gt;Sun&lt;/a&gt;, unlike Ashley, actually has credentials as a scientist and has studied neuroplasticity. However, the credibility of his scientific declarations concerning gender ideology may not altogether be scientific.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In an &lt;a href="https://www.openmindmag.org/articles/anti-trans-myths" target="_blank"&gt;article&lt;/a&gt; he co-authored last year with Ashley, Sun declared there is "no such thing as a male or female brain." Just months later, a &lt;a href="https://www.pnas.org/doi/abs/10.1073/pnas.2310012121" target="_blank"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; published in the Proceedings of the National Academy of Science revealed that a group of Stanford Medicine researchers identified "highly replicable, generalizable, and behaviorally relevant sex differences in human functional brain organization localized to the default mode network, striatum, and limbic network."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The framing of the interview in Scientific American made clear that science would be taking a back seat and that the aim was political.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Powell's interview is prefaced with the following statement: "In 2023 alone, more than 500 anti-trans bills were proposed or adopted in nearly every state in the United States, targeting everything from drag performances to gender-affirming medical care to school inclusion policies for trans people. Support for these measures has been enabled and propelled by scientific misinformation, which has proven to be a distressingly effective tool in outraging a public that might otherwise be broadly empathetic, or at least uncertain about where to stand."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After recycling the suggestion that the science informing legislation against sex change mutilations is "disinformation," Scientific American recirculated the suggestion by Sun that the notion there are "just two sexes" — characterized in the piece as "sex essentialism" — is "completely wrong about the biology of how sex characteristics arise."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The error is simply that the gametes are a determining factor of sex — that once you know what gametes a person produces, that's their sex and nothing about it can change," claimed Sun. "But biology is a dynamic system where an organism starts in a particular state and grows through life and through development with multiple systems interacting. That is, more precisely, how sex works. Sex essentialism boils all that down to one, immutable characteristic to preclude transness as a biological phenomenon."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ashley chimed in, saying, "The people who use ideas about biological sex against trans people are first appealing to the idea of biology as a description of difference, but then they do a jump and use that conception of biology as a form of meaning. The thing is, we organize society around meaning, not difference. Biology at its core can't tell you what matters to human organizations."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We should really be asking what we care about, and then look to see if biology has anything to say about it. If you go through that exercise, then you realize that biology really has very little, if not virtually nothing, to say about things like trans rights," added Ashley.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Canadian activist went on to intimate that when a scientist interprets empirical results in a way that hurts the transgender narrative, he or she is committing "epistemological violence."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Epistemological violence occurs when a researcher or somebody else interprets empirical results in a way that devalues, pathologizes, or harms a marginalized group, even though there are equally good or better explanations for the same data," said Ashley.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ashley then noted in the interview, "We should try to interpret the data in a way that's compatible with their inclusion and well-being, if that's an equally good interpretation."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The interview concluded with a call for shutting down undesirable speech.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Shut down misinformation and hate when you see it crop up around you," Ashley told Powell. "Oftentimes we don't like confrontation, so we just let misinformation go. We need people to start speaking up whenever it comes up. And be loud. We’re in an ecosystem where the anti-trans voices are trying to portray themselves as speaking for a silent majority. We need people to be loud enough to counter any impression of a silent majority.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While Scientific American &lt;a href="https://www.scientificamerican.com/page/about-scientific-american/" target="_blank"&gt;claims&lt;/a&gt; it is "committed to sharing trustworthy knowledge" and "enhancing our understanding," it has also indicated it is committed to "advancing social justice." It appears these commitments are not equally weighted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like Blaze News? Bypass the censors, sign up for our newsletters, and get stories like this direct to your inbox. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theblaze.com/newsletters/theblaze-articlelink" target="_self"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>State Department contradicts claim of 'same standard' for Israeli, Hamas conduct</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/state-dept-claims-different-standard-israeli-hamas-conduct</link><description>The U.S. State Department contradicted its previous statements on Tuesday, asserting that Israel is being held to a "different standard" for its conduct amid the ongoing war with Hamas.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 21:57:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Republican Senators Demand Biden-Harris Regime Crack Down on Campus Anti-Semitism</title><link>https://www.dailywire.com/news/gop-senators-demand-biden-admin-crack-down-on-campus-anti-semitism</link><description>The post Republican Senators Demand Biden-Harris Regime Crack Down on Campus Anti-Semitism appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 22:13:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I Was Stabbed in the Eye at Yale</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/23/i_was_stabbed_in_the_eye_at_yale_622334.html</link><description>The school has allowed anti-Israel students to run roughshod over their most basic policies. Yesterday, I paid the price for their inaction.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 20:52:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden’s Former ‘Disinformation’ Czar Teams Up With Liberal Operatives For New Gig</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/bidens-former-disinformation-czar-teams-up-with-liberal-operatives-for-new-gig-2667861383.html</link><image_url>https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/GettyImages-1252127150-scaled-e1683760667798.jpg</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://cdn01.dailycaller.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/GettyImages-1252127150-scaled-e1683760667798.jpg" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;'We will obviously share more publicly as things develop'</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 21:57:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Conservative group builds ‘America First’ coalition to fight 'radical left's extreme positions and agenda'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/conservative-group-builds-america-first-coalition-fight-radical-lefts-extreme-positions-agenda</link><description>America First Works has united a coalition of conservative groups dedicated to spreading a winning message and fighting together ahead of the 2024 presidential election.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 21:47:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Media Has Been so Successful on the Stock Market That Trump Is Getting an Extra 36 Million Shares Valued at $1.25 Billion</title><link>https://thepostmillennial.com/trump-set-to-gain-36-million-shares-of-trump-media-valued-at-1-25-billion</link><description>The post Trump Media Has Been so Successful on the Stock Market That Trump Is Getting an Extra 36 Million Shares Valued at $1.25 Billion appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 22:11:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Coming Arab Backlash</title><link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/2024/04/23/the_coming_arab_backlash_622338.html</link><description>Middle Eastern regimes-and America-ignore public anger at their peril</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 20:51:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Glenn Beck / RFK Jr. interview going viral — especially the part when Kennedy says how Fauci avoided jail time ...</title><link>https://www.conservativereview.com/glenn-beck-rfk-jr-interview-going-viral-especially-the-part-when-kennedy-says-how-fauci-avoided-jail-time-2667861417.html</link><image_url>https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52080062&amp;width=1200&amp;height=600&amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C120</image_url><description>&lt;img src="https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52080062&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=600&amp;amp;coordinates=0%2C0%2C0%2C120" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[rebelmouse-proxy-image https://www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg?id=52080052&amp;amp;width=1200&amp;amp;height=800&amp;amp;coordinates=0,0,300,0 crop_info="%7B%22image%22%3A%20%22https%3A//www.theblaze.com/media-library/image.jpg%3Fid%3D52080052%26width%3D1200%26height%3D800%26coordinates%3D0%2C0%2C300%2C0%22%7D" expand=1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last week, Glenn Beck sat down with independent candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr. for an extensive interview. The duo broached a wide range of subjects, including the World Economic Forum, NATO, the conflicts in Russia/Ukraine and Israel/Gaza, climate change, and of course, Big Pharma — which Kennedy has been incredibly outspoken about.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On that subject, Kennedy was quick to bring up the absurdity of how COVID-19 was handled, starting with Donald Trump.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“During COVID ... President Trump got rolled by his bureaucrats, and he came in saying, ‘I’m a businessman, I’m gonna run this place like a business,' [so] he gave the keys to all of our shops and stores and businesses to Tony Fauci and shut down 3.3 million businesses,” he told Glenn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Glenn agreed wholeheartedly and followed with a question we all want answered: “What do you do to restore the trust [in the medical industry]?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“What we now know because of the Wuhan lab ... [is] they’re messing with Ebola and they’re messing with Chikungunya and all of these really horrific diseases ... with 50%, 20%, 10% [mortality rates],” he told Glenn, adding that “of course some of them escape every year.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Who’s behind this atrocity?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you guessed Anthony Fauci, you’re correct.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kennedy explained that when the Patriot Act was passed, it mandated “that any federal officer or employee who violates [the Geneva Convention or the 1973 Bioweapons Convention] cannot be prosecuted.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“That relaunched the bioweapons arms race,” he said. The Pentagon “started redirecting all that money to Anthony Fauci to do bioweapons research.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“So, why isn’t he in jail?” Glenn asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“He’s not in jail because Joe Biden is president,” was Kennedy’s frank answer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That honesty perked up the ears of news outlets such as the &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2024/04/23/us-news/rfk-jr-anthony-fauci-not-in-jail-because-joe-biden-is-president/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;New York Post&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-13340583/rfk-jr-dr-fauci-jail-covid-pandemic-response.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Daily Mail&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, which published articles covering Glenn and Kennedy’s candid conversation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To see the full interview, watch the video below.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="rm-shortcode" style="display: block; padding-top: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Want more from Glenn Beck?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;To enjoy more of Glenn’s masterful storytelling, thought-provoking analysis, and uncanny ability to make sense of the chaos, &lt;a href="https://get.blazetv.com/glenn/?utm_source=theblaze&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_campaign=article_shortcode_glennbeck" target="_blank"&gt;subscribe to BlazeTV&lt;/a&gt; — the largest multi-platform network of voices who love America, defend the Constitution, and live the American dream.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 21:41:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump slams 'unconstitutional' gag order as trial wraps for the day: 'All Biden'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-slams-unconstitutional-gag-order-trial-wraps-day-trial-all-biden</link><description>Former President Donald Trump slammed the gag order imposed on him during his trial in Manhattan court as "unconstitutional" in public comment Tuesday afternoon.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 20:25:40 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>