<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 12:07:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>MSNBC Host Calls for Biden Aides to Be Allowed on Stage With Him at Next Debate</title><link>https://modernity.news/2024/07/08/msnbc-host-calls-for-biden-aides-to-be-allowed-on-stage-with-him-at-next-debate/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>The post MSNBC Host Calls for Biden Aides to Be Allowed on Stage With Him at Next Debate appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:00:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden tells congressional Democrats that calling for him to drop out 'only helps Trump and hurts us'</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/biden-tells-congressional-democrats-calls-him-drop-out-only-helps-trump-hurts-us</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>President Biden is urging congressional Democrats to stop questioning whether he should end his re-election bid and “move forward as a unified party" in order to defeat Trump in their 2024 rematch.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 16:22:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Here’s the Tweet That Perfectly Sums Up Why Conservatives Were Way Ahead of Liberals on Dementia Joe</title><link>https://townhall.com/tipsheet/mattvespa/2024/07/08/is-this-why-liberal-america-got-blindsided-by-joe-bidens-mental-collapse-n2641482</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>The post Here’s the Tweet That Perfectly Sums Up Why Conservatives Were Way Ahead of Liberals on Dementia Joe appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:00:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hollywood elites, megadonors turn on Biden amid growing calls for new Democratic nominee</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/hollywood-elites-megadonors-calls-democrat-nominee-step-aside</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>Hollywood Democrat megadonors are calling for President Biden to step down as the party's nominee amid backlash over his debate performance.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 16:09:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>X Is Censoring a Conservative News Site Over a Thumbnail and the Excuse Is Disturbing</title><link>https://www.louderwithcrowder.com/x-censoring-the-publica</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>The post X Is Censoring a Conservative News Site Over a Thumbnail and the Excuse Is Disturbing appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:00:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dems' 'deeply self-destructive' attacks on Biden to blame for weakening his candidacy, lawmaker says</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/dems-deeply-self-destructive-attacks-biden-blame-weakening-his-candidacy-lawmaker-says</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>A House Democrat who supports President Biden's reelection campaign is slamming members of his own party for "weakening" Biden's chances with public criticism of his debate performance.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:54:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Radio Station Cuts Ties With Host Who Admitted Being Fed Questions by Biden-Harris Regime</title><link>https://www.zerohedge.com/political/biden-campaign-gives-list-approved-questions-two-radio-interviews</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>The post Radio Station Cuts Ties With Host Who Admitted Being Fed Questions by Biden-Harris Regime appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:00:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden staff prepped him on how to enter, exit fundraiser room: report</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/biden-staff-prepped-him-how-enter-exit-fundraiser-room-report</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>A document President Biden's staffer used to prepare him for a recent fundraiser includes detailed instructions for where to walk, enter and exit places.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 14:21:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dementia Joe Claims “Dark Brandon Is Coming Back” as Desperation Spews From Flailing Campaign</title><link>https://thelibertydaily.com/dementia-joe-claims-dark-brandon-is-coming-back/</link><image_url>https://thelibertydaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/The-Liberty-Daily-Liberty-Bell-Logo-300x169.jpg</image_url><description>(NOQ Report)—Joe Biden stirred up voters during a series of campaign stops in Pennsylvania on Sunday, attempting to quell growing concerns among some Democrats about his suitability for a second term. “Dark Brandon is coming back,” he quipped to a supporter in Harrisburg who mentioned the meme, initially used to counter worries about Biden’s age […] The post Dementia Joe Claims “Dark Brandon Is Coming Back” as Desperation Spews From Flailing Campaign appeared first on 🔔 The Liberty Daily .</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 16:40:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump approval rating tops 50% as he leads Biden on voters' top two issues: poll</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-approval-rating-tops-50-he-leads-biden-voters-top-two-issues-poll</link><image_url>https://global.fncstatic.com/static/orion/styles/img/fox-news/logos/fox-news-desktop.png</image_url><description>A poll found former President Trump's approval rating is above 50%, leading President Biden on economy and immigration, two top issues of the 2024 race.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 12:35:29 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>