<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 06:59:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Whoa, Did You See the Market Today? 📉</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/whoa-did-you-see-the-market-today-%f0%9f%93%89/</link><image_url>https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXfLqkKf1L5t3pYrb1o9ftXBq8m_ieOTWaQ3C18E29QgPUdSYAZ_FHzRJ0V9OZ4IS5E1AH4V08OKYcapzmBdbohzs3SoBXoLDSvlBbM-UDolOOzbky4en0Yaqi01OCkuhSdexU49cTi0cZUzbl19zTD9jkOm?key=j9OsXDoZ3BMs6oOXNl5I7Q</image_url><description>Quick Reminder: JW’s Market Navigator Special Trial is over this evening — so take advantage today and trade the SPY with him and his gang! Just this morning, I said the QQQ had to hold above $475, or else we were headed for a big drop. If you haven’t looked at your portfolio today, I’d […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 15:20:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hedge-fund giant Man says assets reach record levels</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/hedge-fund-giant-man-says-assets-reach-record-levels-7c938d7f?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-59226811</image_url><description>Man Group, the world’s largest publicly traded hedge fund manager, on Friday said investment gains helped its assets under management grow by 17.5% in the first half to record highs of $178.2 billion.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 11:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Venezuela’s Maduro bids for a third term in power — as U.S., Brazil warn over need for free election</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/26/venezuela-presidential-election-maduro-bids-for-a-third-term-in-power.html</link><description>Venezuela's Nicolas Maduro will seek his third term in office on Sunday in a vote that's regarded as the country's most open contest in more than a decade.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 08:13:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dow futures pop more than 100 points as investors prepare for Fed’s preferred inflation gauge: Live updates</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/25/stock-market-today-live-updates.html</link><description>The major averages are poised to end the week with losses as investors dump megacap tech and AI-related names.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 11:31:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Big earnings beats have these stocks moving</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/insider/big-earnings-beats-have-these-stocks-moving/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/1022e75f-9694-451c-95ba-14ec0069c5e9/image__1_.png</image_url><description>*sponsored by Sica Media Good morning, 360! Don’t forget to join us today for LIVE trading in the Market Master’s Room. Be the best prepared trader on the Street! FOCUS LIST🔎 TUSK – Up over 34% in the pre-market after settlement agreement with PREPA for $188.4 million FEIM – Up over 30% in pre […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 16:22:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Market bubbles expand longer than many expect. But this metric shows valuations will matter.</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/market-bubbles-expand-longer-than-many-expect-but-this-metric-shows-valuations-will-matter-0896b66d?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-54388546</image_url><description>Valuation may not matter in the short term but it eventually does, says this fund manager</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 11:53:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elon Musk’s transgender daughter, in first interview, says he berated her for being queer as a child</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/25/elon-musks-transgender-daughter-in-first-interview-says-he-berated-her-for-being-queer-as-a-child.html</link><description>In an exclusive interview, Vivian Jenna Wilson said her father’s recent statements including that she is “not a girl” inspired her to speak out: “I’m not just gonna let that slide.”</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 04:47:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>France's high-speed rail network hit by arson attacks, canceling trains ahead of Olympics</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/26/french-rail-network-hit-by-arson-canceling-trains-on-eve-of-olympics.html</link><description>SNCF said in a statement its network had experienced several concurrent attacks on Thursday night, with fire damaging its facilies.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 11:12:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Plan your trade and trade your plan!</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/insider/plan-your-trade-and-trade-your-plan/</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f4a5.png</image_url><description>Try SPY💥 I Market Masters I Drops Monday🎯 Good evening, Folks! This is Jeff Bishop and work closely with Jeff Williams in the Market Masters Room. Tomorrow I’d like you to join me LIVE at 11AM EST MONDAY for a special market rundown as well as my thoughts behind my Bullseye Pick of the Week. […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 14:12:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Liquidation of crowded trades so far is healthy — but these levels must hold, says Bank of America</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/liquidation-of-crowded-trades-so-far-is-healthy-but-these-levels-must-hold-says-bank-of-america-6202c00a?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-12216420</image_url><description>Expectations over Fed rate cuts and a presidential victory by former President Donald Trump are what’s behind a liquidation of the most crowded trades that so far is healthy, says a Bank of America strategist.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 11:38:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kamala Harris debuts official TikTok account as presidential campaign picks up</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/25/kamala-harris-debuts-official-tiktok-account-as-presidential-campaign-picks-up.html</link><description>Kamala Harris debuted an official TikTok account on Thursday, underscoring the social broadcasting app's importance to the 2024 presidential campaign.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 00:49:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Novo Nordisk's Wegovy wins EU backing for reducing heart risks</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/26/novo-nordisks-wegovy-wins-eu-backing-for-reducing-heart-risks.html</link><description>Novo Nordisk's Wegovy has received backing from the EU's medical regulator to expand the weight loss drug's use to reducing the rise of serious heart events.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 11:07:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eyes on This Momentum Stock! 🔥</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/insider/eyes-on-this-momentum-stock-%f0%9f%94%a5/</link><image_url>https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXfsHn019VnwmfJCZj87xuzaeWBaT__ckWJsu-MFD3ObMxQo_5GC89k9x8bjKBwYBNc9nt2Kxx_VK2eRGKFdyJ8EZaUtmnVPMWKKHt6Aid0WmGOVEjjwRnVkkgIaG5YxzdXZwdneeRbByL-Oy8z8K0tBRcsU?key=jlWHzQzXht1Yq8KsV_XuYA</image_url><description>📈 Join us for LIVE TRADING action all day long in the 📈 Market Master’s trading room Now, at absolutely no cost to our readers ✅Just one click, and you’re in! GM, Jeff here! It looks like the market is trying to stage a comeback on the final day of this week after several rough […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 14:20:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘I am an only child’: My father left his $50 million estate to my stepmother in an irrevocable trust. I inherited $1 million. Is this reasonable?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/i-am-an-only-child-my-father-left-his-50-million-estate-to-my-stepmother-in-an-irrevocable-trust-i-inherited-1-million-is-this-reasonable-b1639174?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-62155849</image_url><description>“Is it common for entire estates to be left to the second spouse instead of being divided among the children?”</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 10:57:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GM reveals new Chevy Corvette with 1,000-plus horsepower and record top speed</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/25/gm-chevy-corvette-zr1-performance.html</link><description>The ZR1 joins what GM is calling the "Corvette family," leveraging the reputation of the quintessential American sports car to boost revenue and sales.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 00:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>European stocks rise as global selloff eases; NatWest up 6%</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/26/europe-markets-26-july-2024.html</link><description>European markets were higher on Friday as the global selloff seen this week eases.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 10:48:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Did you miss boot camp and need a doctor’s note? We got you covered 🎥</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/pennypro/did-you-miss-boot-camp-and-need-a-doctors-note-we-got-you-covered-%f0%9f%8e%a5/</link><image_url>https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXfwINhuJ2-nkiSNdOSokY1XPgUdqNR4_8FfLOtXe9M4gRPVbSbAb2k5MWUz7TT0h42Ra76g6aGykdoJABfPOLXfByIOdBn4UWwOTyL6NR_2gqvrjLYkf0Ucn6jkfstpZ1aZRo4k2EiDYswr3VdKZ-xKRx4x?key=QudxO7LTgvPEtQ4Q__v_qA</image_url><description>💥MARKET NAVIGATOR &amp; ATOMIC TRADES💥 DEAL ENDS @ MIDNIGHT BUNDLE &amp; SAVE BIG HERE! Howdy gang! Jeff Williams (JW) here, did you miss my boot camp earlier this week? I took some time to go over how I try to simplify my options trading in the morning and how I hunt down the best penny […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 19:53:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘I’m having panic attacks’: My ex-husband emptied our joint bank accounts, hacked into my email and stole my life savings. Do I have any recourse?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/im-having-panic-attacks-my-ex-husband-emptied-our-joint-bank-accounts-hacked-into-my-email-and-stole-my-life-savings-do-i-have-any-recourse-3e27babd?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-62694006</image_url><description>“I’m working with the fund manager, as I found some emails where he pretended to be me on some forged documents.”</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 10:57:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OpenAI announces a search engine called SearchGPT; Alphabet shares dip</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/25/openai-announces-a-search-engine-called-searchgpt.html</link><description>OpenAI announced a prototype of its SearchGPT search engine on Thursday.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 23:05:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nvidia supplier SK Hynix to build $6.8 billion chip plant in South Korea</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/26/nvidia-supplier-sk-hynix-to-build-6point8-billion-chip-plan-in-south-korea.html</link><description>SK Hynix's plant will be in the Yongin Semiconductor Cluster where the South Korean government is looking to build a massive complex of chip operations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 10:12:23 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>