<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 12:43:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Big partnerships and earnings have these stocks moving</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/big-partnerships-and-earnings-have-these-stocks-moving/</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f525.png</image_url><description>Good day, 360! Here are our top investing ideas today. And don’t forget to join us in Market Masters – the hottest trading room around 🔥. Be the best prepared trader on the Street! FOCUS LIST🔎 CXAI – Up over 50% in the pre-market after announcing Q2 earnings and largest “expansion” deal and strategic multi-year […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 16:14:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Traders see big drop in interest rates into 2025, at risk of underestimating inflation</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/traders-see-big-drop-in-interest-rates-into-2025-at-risk-of-underestimating-inflation-32dcffaa?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-23024300</image_url><description>Cutting interest rates as many times as fed -funds traders currently expect would imply that policymakers are confident they could do so without reigniting inflation all over again.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:38:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>UAW hits Musk, Trump with federal labor charges over union-busting comments</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/13/musk-trump-uaw-labor-union-x-interview.html</link><description>During Donald Trump and Elon Musk's two-hour conversation on X, the former president complimented the Tesla CEO on firing workers who wanted to strike.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:31:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Starbucks replaces CEO Laxman Narasimhan with Chipotle CEO Brian Niccol</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/13/starbucks-replaces-ceo-laxman-narasimhan-with-chipotle-ceo-brian-niccol.html</link><description>After several quarters of weak sales, Starbucks has tapped Chipotle CEO Brian Niccol as Laxman Narasimhan's replacement.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:30:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This tiny cap is soaring after winning its appeal 💪</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/this-tiny-cap-is-soaring-after-winning-its-appeal-%f0%9f%92%aa/</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f50e.png</image_url><description>Good day, 360! Here are our top movers today. And don’t forget to join us in Market Masters all day today. Jeff Bishop will be LIVE in there at 11AM with Bullseye Trades so get in there and… be the best prepared trader on the Street! FOCUS LIST🔎 TRNR – Up over 50% in the […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:24:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stage set for mild increase in consumer prices as Fed readies rate cuts</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/dont-expect-inflation-to-take-a-turn-for-the-worse-in-ppi-and-cpi-reports-f79ba180?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-37333250</image_url><description>Wholesale inflation was fairly tame in July, and most economists think consumer prices will show a similarly mild increase. If so, that would keep the Federal Reserve on track to cut interest rates next month.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Wall Street thinks Brian Niccol is the person to revive Starbucks — and end the Howard Schultz era</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/13/starbucks-ceo-wall-st-cheers-brian-niccol-appointment.html</link><description>Starbucks tapped Brian Niccol as its latest CEO, effective Sept. 9, after sales slumped under Laxman Narasimhan.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:31:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Europe stocks close higher; Sterling gains after UK wage growth falls to two-year low</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/13/european-markets-live-updates-stocks-news-data-and-earnings.html</link><description>European stocks closed higher on Tuesday, as market participants monitored a fresh batch of economic data following last week's volatility.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:15:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Great earnings have these stocks firing</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/great-earnings-have-these-stocks-firing/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/1022e75f-9694-451c-95ba-14ec0069c5e9/image__1_.png</image_url><description>*sponsored by The Market Master’s Trading Room is open today but will be a little quiet, as we mourn the loss of JW’s stock market faithful companion, Bentley. Although Bentley could not “legally” tell someone to buy or sell a stock, a bark or two from him when JW was digging in it gave you […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 16:32:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Harley-Davidson dealers say the company is sending them too many motorcycles</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/harley-davidson-dealers-say-the-company-is-sending-them-too-many-motorcycles-2d0e6c8e?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-32847533</image_url><description>Some of the famed motorcycle maker’s dealers reportedly complained about being sent too many bikes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:21:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This startup will sell methane-eating microbes to Whole Foods</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/13/this-startup-will-sell-methane-eating-microbes-to-whole-foods.html</link><description>Windfall uses "mems" — methane-eating microbes. These naturally occurring microscopic organisms live in the soil and eat methane as food for survival.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:13:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HelloFresh shares pop 19% as meal kit giant beats profit estimates</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/13/hellofresh-shares-pop-11percent-as-meal-kit-giant-beats-profit-estimates.html</link><description>HelloFresh said it got a boost from healthy growth in its ready-to-eat meal delivery business.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:00:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Major players are buying puts. Why?</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/major-players-are-buying-puts-why/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/f6b0f870-08e8-4670-8536-5c31a102981f/image__14_.png?t=1723125974</image_url><description>*sponsored by We haven’t seen this since the-pandemic-that-shall-not-be-named. My trading partner Taiku pointed something out to me Tuesday that really opened my eyes to what’s going on in the markets. Yeah, we had a big sell-off earlier this week and the VIX spiked. But that’s not the real story… the VIX gradually went back down […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 18:33:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Starbucks’ stock rallies on speculation of a turnaround under its new CEO — the head of Chipotle Mexican Grill</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/starbucks-names-new-ceo-the-head-of-chipotle-mexican-grill-80e547f8?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-08324977</image_url><description>Brian Niccol will lead the 39,000-store coffee-shop giant after six years at Chipotle.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is Netflix recession resistant? JPMorgan thinks so</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/13/is-netflix-recession-resistant-jpmorgan-thinks-so.html</link><description>Netflix provides "compelling value" even in an economic slowdown scenario, says Netflix.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 16:40:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ukraine wants more negotiating power as forces advance into Russia, humiliating Moscow</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/13/what-does-ukraine-want-from-its-incursion-into-russia.html</link><description>More light is being shed on Ukraine's incursion into Russian territory and Kyiv hopes it could recalibrate the war, and any future peace.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 16:42:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AstraZeneca partners with tiny Biotech</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/astrazeneca-partners-with-tiny-biotech/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/429efb2a-1efa-4c3e-a6fb-b3e7aa96593b/Screenshot_2024-07-08_at_10.10.56_AM.png?t=1723119686</image_url><description>*together with Brooks Enterprises Good day, 360! Here are our TOP movers today. And don’t forget to join us in Market Masters Trading Room. Even freeloaders are welcome… FOCUS LIST🔎 CDT – up over 100% in the pre-market after entering into exclusive license agreement with AstraZeneca for multiple assets to advance potential first-in-class treatments WENA […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 14:39:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Will Social Security be your only lifeline in retirement? Some people say yes.</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/will-social-security-be-your-only-lifeline-in-retirement-some-people-say-yes-473af550?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-28117351</image_url><description>Almost a third of Americans will rely solely on Social Security and not on any retirement savings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 16:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Crypto magnate buys SpaceX mission for private polar spaceflight expedition</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/13/crypto-magnate-chun-wang-buys-spacex-polar-spaceflight-fram2.html</link><description>Cryptocurrency speculator Chun Wang bought a SpaceX multi-day flight for an undisclosed amount, the company announced on Monday.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 16:04:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wholesale inflation measure rose 0.1% in July, less than expected</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/13/producer-price-index-july-2024.html</link><description>The producer price index for July was expected to increase 0.2%, according to the Dow Jones consensus estimate.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 15:44:04 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>