<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 10:45:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>New obesity drug data has this Ozempic rival moving</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/new-obesity-drug-data-has-this-ozempic-rival-moving/</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f50e.png</image_url><description>*Together with Monument Trader’s Alliance &amp; CompareCredit Good day, 360! This week we have a special invitation to join Election Trading ALL week. These guys are pros so register to join MTA’s War Room [Happening NOW!]. Be the best prepared trader on the Street! FOCUS LIST🔎 CTM – Up over 30% in the pre-market after […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 15:18:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oil prices rise over 2% after OPEC+ delays production increase by another month</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/oil-prices-rise-over-2-after-opec-delays-production-increase-by-another-month-dfc7236d?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-64360576</image_url><description>Oil futures saw strong gains Monday after the Organization of the Petroleum Exporting Countries said members would wait yet another month before beginning to unwind production cuts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 15:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Barry Diller calls timing of The Washington Post's non-endorsement a 'blunder'</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/11/04/barry-diller-calls-timing-of-the-washington-posts-non-endorsement-a-blunder-jeff-bezos-amazon-presidential-election-candidate.html</link><description>Expedia chairman Barry Diller called the timing of The Washington Post's decision not to endorse a presidential candidate a "blunder."</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 15:39:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stocks waver ahead of presidential election, Nvidia rises on Dow inclusion: Live updates</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/11/03/stock-market-today-live-updates.html</link><description>Stocks struggled to find a direction on Monday as investors geared up for the highly-anticipated U.S. presidential election.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 15:23:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trading as a side hustle?</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/trading-as-a-side-hustle/</link><image_url>https://ragingbull.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/08/favicon.png</image_url><description>Good evening, For most of us, trading is a side hustle. Quite often, members ask me if they should go full-time. Here’s my opinion. Traders who can transition from a side hustle to full-time trading are very skilled. Their skills are so dialed in that, at any time, they can take a small amount of […]</description><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 22:48:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Viking Therapeutics’ weight-loss pill shows ‘great outcome’ in trial</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/viking-therapeutics-stock-jumps-after-great-trial-of-weight-loss-drug-c361dd3b?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-63336632</image_url><description>The stock, which enjoys the unusual position of having all buy ratings from the 13 analysts offering coverage on FactSet, has been on a tear this year, gaining 270% to date in 2024.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 15:26:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines will add first class, revamp cabins for longest flights</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/11/04/singapore-airlines-adds-a-first-class-to-longest-flights.html</link><description>Singapore Airlines will add a first class to its ultra-long-range aircraft and increase the number of business class seats in race for high-spending travelers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 15:09:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Foreign buyers eye Japan's empty houses with millions available for cheap — but experts warn of risks</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/11/04/japans-millions-of-cheap-empty-houses-draw-foreign-interest-.html</link><description>While many places in the world face a housing shortage, Japan is facing the opposite problem: An oversupply of homes on the market.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 15:19:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>🎯My Top Three Trades</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/%f0%9f%8e%afmy-top-three-trades/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/43b88096-8a1b-4958-b6af-463c9d0bd92b/image__8_.png</image_url><description>TODAY– I wanted to extend a special invitation to join me LIVE this morning in the Market Master’s Trading Room @11AM EST. CLICK HERE TO JOIN THIS MORNING! I will be giving you an inside view of how I track down trades with the highest breakout potential… AND I’lll share with you my TOP […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:55:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>U.S. factory orders tumble in September, for fourth drop in the past five months</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/u-s-factory-orders-tumble-in-september-for-fourth-drop-in-the-past-five-months-7a61c4f1?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-694677</image_url><description>Orders for manufactured goods fell 0.5% in September, the Commerce Department said Monday. It is the fourth decline in orders in the past five months.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 15:22:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ford October vehicle sales increase 15.2% from subdued levels due to labor strike in 2023</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/11/04/fords-october-sales.html</link><description>Ford on Monday reported a 15.2% increase in U.S. new vehicles sales last month compared to subdued levels during a union strike in October 2023.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 15:00:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines will add first class, revamp cabins for longest flights</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/11/04/singapore-airlines-adds-a-first-class-to-longest-flights.html</link><description>Singapore Airlines will add a first class to its ultra-long-range aircraft and increase the number of business class seats in race for high-spending travelers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 15:09:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Public offerings, legal wins, and medical breakthroughs driving markets!</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/public-offerings-legal-wins-and-medical-breakthroughs-driving-markets/</link><image_url>https://gen.sendtric.com/countdown/da491fp9pb</image_url><description>Congratulations to the Dodgers, what a beat down! Here’s another BEAT-DOWN… 40 make that 51 straight wins for Jason Bond in the $2,000 Small Account Journey. (*Trading is hard, results not guaranteed and should not be expected to be replicated typically.) Hurry on in … MEGA SALE ENDS IN: FOCUS LIST🔎 EFSH – Up over 60% […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 16:38:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Constellation Energy’s stock is seeing a record selloff despite profit beat</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/why-constellation-energys-stock-is-seeing-a-record-selloff-despite-profit-beat-1c4bbfac?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-65234482</image_url><description>Shares of Constellation Energy Corp. were in danger of a record selloff on Monday and were headed for their lowest prices since before the nuclear-power company signed a 20-year power-purchasing agreement with Microsoft Corp. in September.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 15:11:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Striking Boeing machinists vote on union-backed contract proposal, this time with a warning</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/11/04/striking-boeing-machinists-vote-new-contract.html</link><description>The vote is the third time since September that Boeing's machinists are considering a new labor deal.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 14:27:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Election 2024 live updates: Harris and Trump make last appeals to battleground voters</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/11/04/2024-presidential-election-live-updates-.html</link><description>Kamala Harris and Donald Trump will hold dueling rallies in Pittsburgh and Reading on the campaign's final day, underscoring Pennsylvania's must-win status.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 14:24:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Big News is Powering This Small Cap Higher</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/big-news-is-powering-this-small-cap-higher/</link><image_url>https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXdrGy7wIN9iGuZ7QYq-OxTyPtUb0CyBQr7QUPCCkGmSn8OsVDNv5oits63DQPnRUvSDPoKennbBP-1WLZOWN-rCgudRTgOFtypiHQvmFl0ZMigDipl2RvcvU-OwdeLK0_5F3o8K5ADqLZWM6vZz3-JZz6A?key=QdoPt9nvXXi_TZvNoF8liw</image_url><description>NOW OPEN: Interactive Live Streaming Trade Room Real time trading, detailed education on options and penny stocks available to you RIGHT NOW at no additional cost. Enter the room and trade with us! Google’s strong earnings are powering the markets higher this morning, with S&amp;P500 and Nasdaq futures both signaling another up day to […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 16:33:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10-, 30-year yields dive from 4-month highs after Iowa poll tilts in favor of Harris</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/bond-yields-dive-after-key-iowa-poll-points-to-tight-u-s-election-0d17f91d?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://www.marketwatch.com/rss/marketwatch.gif</image_url><description>Treasury yields broadly fell on Monday, reversing most of the previous session’s action, after a key poll gave Vice President Kamala Harris an edge over former President Donald Trump ahead of Tuesday’s election.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 14:57:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump's closing campaign message is hampered by distractions, disconnect</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/11/03/trump-harris-2024-election-final-week-message.html</link><description>Donald Trump's campaign has faced backlash for several controversial remarks in the final days of his campaign against Vice President Kamala Harris.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 13:51:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quincy Jones, musical maestro and entertainment industry titan, dies at 91</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/11/04/quincy-jones-musical-maestro-and-entertainment-titan-dies-at-91.html</link><description>In a prolific career that spanned more than 70 years, Jones established himself as a behind-the-scenes force and a gifted artist in his own right.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 14:15:12 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>