<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 10:16:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Nancy Pelosi has this stock flying</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/nancy-pelosi-has-this-stock-flying/</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f50e.png</image_url><description>Good day, 360! President Donald Trump is promising us that “The golden age of America begins right now” and that “America’s decline is over.” No matter what side of the political fence you are on, for America’s sake… let’s hope he’s right! As for today… please join us for THIS special event: Trade Of The […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 17:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What is the biggest money mistake people make?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/what-is-the-biggest-money-mistake-people-make-3f90a068?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-27994300</image_url><description>Try to avoid these tactical errors</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 15:13:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What a second Trump administration could mean for your money</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2025/01/21/what-a-second-trump-administration-could-mean-for-your-money.html</link><description>President Donald Trump made many promises that could directly impact many Americans' personal finances. Here's what to watch for in his second term.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 15:04:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jamie Dimon says the U.S. stock market is 'kind of inflated’</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2025/01/22/jamie-dimon-us-stock-market-inflated.html</link><description>The American stock market is in the midst of a multi-year bull run.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:59:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tempus AI Inc. (TEM) Soars 36%: Is This Healthcare Tech Stock a Buy?</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/insider/tempus-ai-inc-tem-soars-36-is-this-healthcare-tech-stock-a-buy/</link><image_url>https://ragingbull.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/08/favicon.png</image_url><description>As I’m writing this, Tempus AI Inc. (NASDAQ: TEM), the healthcare technology company that’s been making waves with its innovative approach to precision medicine and patient care, is up an astonishing 36.1% today. The stock price has surged from $35.15 to $47.84 in just a few hours, leaving investors wondering if this momentum will continue. […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 16:33:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>U.S. oil prices head lower as traders weigh Trump tariff threats, energy policy</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/oil-prices-bounce-as-traders-weigh-trump-tariff-threats-energy-policy-ec754e72?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-15873065</image_url><description>Oil futures headed lower on Wednesday, with U.S. benchmark prices on track to notch a fourth straight session decline as investors weighed the potential impact of President Donald Trump’s energy policies and tariff threats.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 15:13:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>United Airlines' first-quarter outlook outpaces estimates after profits surge to end 2024</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2025/01/21/united-airlines-ual-4q-2024-earnings.html</link><description>United topped analysts' estimates for fourth-quarter earnings and the airline's first-quarter outlook.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:44:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Europe must be prepared for Trump tariffs, European Central Bank chief warns</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2025/01/22/european-central-bank-lagarde-davos.html</link><description>European Central Bank President Christine Lagarde spoke to CNBC at the World Economic Forum in Davos.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:59:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Bank OZK Express: Why This Regional Bank is Zooming Higher</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/the-beef/the-bank-ozk-express-why-this-regional-bank-is-zooming-higher/</link><image_url>https://ragingbull.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/08/favicon.png</image_url><description>Ah, the thrill of a stock on fire! Today’s market action has seen one regional bank making headlines with an impressive 9.70% gain – and I’m here to give you the lowdown. Bank OZK (NASDAQ:OZK) has been flying high all morning, with its shares closing at $49.74 after a dollar change of +$4.40. But what’s […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 16:36:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10-year Treasury yield near lowest level of 2025 as traders keep eye on Trump</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/treasury-yields-continue-to-drift-lower-c035d9a8?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://www.marketwatch.com/rss/marketwatch.gif</image_url><description>Treasury yields were little changed in Wednesday morning trading, a day after 10- and 30-year rates finished at or close to the lowest closing levels of 2025 on the lack of immediate tariffs from President Donald Trump.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 15:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Abnormal Security hires ex-ServiceNow exec as CFO as company starts prepping for IPO</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2025/01/22/abnormal-security-hires-former-servicenow-executive-to-be-cfo.html</link><description>Five months after announcing that it hit $200 million in annualized revenue, Abnormal Security has hired a CFO.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:43:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ECB's Lagarde: Not overly concerned by the export of inflation to Europe</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2025/01/22/ecbs-lagarde-says-not-overly-concerned-by-the-export-of-inflation-to-europe.html</link><description>The European Central Bank will continue to cut interest rates at a gradual pace, the institution's President Christine Lagarde told CNBC.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:59:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Growing a small account this year? Check this out…</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/options-trading/growing-a-small-account-this-year-check-this-out/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/1de0aeee-92d5-4578-8b72-d574edb8ae0d/Screenshot_2025-01-20_at_7.19.42_AM.png?t=1737375619</image_url><description>If you’re starting out with a few thousand dollars there aren’t many trading strategies that work. When I created the $2,000 Small Account Journey I set out on a mission to create the best possible blueprint. I wanted fast growth without taking big risks. There were some headaches early on — which I expected as […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 14:49:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>As Nvidia’s stock gains, one analyst shows why Stargate could be so significant</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/as-nvidias-stock-gains-one-analyst-shows-why-stargate-could-be-so-significant-39b95d61?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-73371904</image_url><description>Will Nvidia become part of the “Trump trade”? Melius Research says the new Stargate joint venture may signal more AI-friendly moves ahead and help the company’s long-term growth trends</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:51:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Microsoft loses status as OpenAI's exclusive cloud provider</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2025/01/21/microsoft-loses-status-as-openais-exclusive-cloud-provider.html</link><description>Microsoft won't be the sole cloud provider for OpenAI but can decide whether to deliver the capacity or allow another company to do it.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:40:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Davos 2025 live updates: Jamie Dimon compares Musk to Einstein; UK finance minister touts U.S. 'special relationship'</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2025/01/22/davos-2025-live-updates-whats-going-on-at-wef-on-wednesday-jan-22-2025.html</link><description>Welcome to CNBC's live blog covering all the latest news, views and action on the third day of the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:50:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Qorvo Inc. Sees Boost from Activist Investor: What’s Behind the Surge?</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/insider/qorvo-inc-sees-boost-from-activist-investor-whats-behind-the-surge/</link><image_url>https://ragingbull.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/08/favicon.png</image_url><description>Today, I want to talk about a stock that’s making headlines with its impressive gains – Qorvo Inc. (QRVO). This semiconductor solutions provider has seen its shares jump by 9.82% today alone, marking one of the biggest percentage increases on the board. As we dig into what’s driving this surge, it becomes clear that activist […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 16:41:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>P&amp;G didn’t raise prices for first time in 6 years, and Q2 earnings still beat</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/p-gs-stock-rallies-as-strength-in-baby-feminine-care-fuel-an-earnings-beat-d033d3fb?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-49505128</image_url><description>P&amp;G’s stock powers up as profit and revenue rise above expectations, and the full-year outlook was affirmed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:44:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meta backs Databricks as the data analytics startup inches toward IPO</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2025/01/22/meta-backs-databricks-as-the-data-analytics-startup-inches-toward-ipo.html</link><description>Meta rarely invests in startups, but it works with Databricks on the Llama open-source models that Meta trains.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:39:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jamie Dimon says he's patched relationship with Musk: 'Elon and I hugged it out'</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2025/01/22/jpmorgans-jamie-dimon-says-hes-patched-relationship-with-elon-musk.html</link><description>Last year, JPMorgan agreed to drop a lawsuit against Tesla. Now, the JPMorgan CEO is calling Musk "our Einstein."</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:28:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>