<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 11:01:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>💥NVDA and PLTR partnerships have these small caps soaring</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/%f0%9f%92%a5nvda-and-pltr-partnerships-have-these-small-caps-soaring/</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/23f0.png</image_url><description>&amp; Altucher’s Investment Network Happy Monday, 360 – Here are some of our top movers today! ⏰ And set a reminder to join Jeff Bishop LIVE @ 11am EST today as he reviews his top trading ideas for the week in the Market Master’s trading room. All are welcome! FOCUS LIST🔎 WBUY – Up over […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 15:02:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>U.S. oil prices edge lower on weak Chinese retail-sales data</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/u-s-oil-prices-drop-nearly-1-on-weak-chinese-retail-sales-data-025a9cac?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-24797281</image_url><description>Oil prices headed lower Monday as concerns over the outlook for energy demand were renewed by a batch of economic data in China that showed retail-sales growth unexpectedly weakened in November.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 15:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why it's gotten more difficult to get a free first-class upgrade</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/12/14/free-first-class-upgrade-frequent-flyers.html</link><description>Airlines are racing to add comforts such as lie-flat seats, entertainment systems with bigger screens and even suites with closing doors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 13:14:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>S&amp;P 500 rises to start the week as Wall Street gets ready for Fed meeting this week: Live  updates</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/12/15/stock-futures-are-little-changed-as-wall-street-gears-up-for-potential-fed-rate-cut-this-week.html</link><description>The S&amp;P 500 rose slightly on Monday as investors awaited a key Federal Reserve meeting slated for this week.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 15:56:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Growing AI chip demand and green energy in play today</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/growing-ai-chip-demand-and-green-energy-in-play-today/</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f50e.png</image_url><description>&amp; Finance Buzz Happy Friday, 360 — whooppee! As always, here are some of our top movers today. We’ve had some MAJOR bangers this week too on our SMS list on some up-and-coming companies. Make sure you text “RAGE” to (888) 404-5747 to get all of our latest HOT STOCK ideas! Trust us, you want […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 16:21:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Social Security Fairness Act is a bad idea</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/the-social-security-fairness-act-is-a-bad-idea-b24ade67?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-29995640</image_url><description>This legislation would allow some workers to double-dip and speeds the exhaustion of the trust fund</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 15:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Many New Jersey drones sightings are 'manned aircraft being misidentified as drones,' FBI says</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/12/14/many-new-jersey-drones-sightings-are-manned-aircraft-being-misidentified-as-drones-fbi-says.html</link><description>The FBI and Department of Homeland Security said on Saturday that ongoing investigations around reported drone sightings over New Jersey have found many reports are, in fact, manned aircraft.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 12:49:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>German Chancellor Olaf Scholz loses confidence vote, clearing the way for February election</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/12/16/german-chancellor-olaf-scholz-loses-confidence-vote.html</link><description>German Chancellor Olaf Scholz on Monday lost a confidence vote in the country's Bundestag, clearing the path for an early election in February.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 15:50:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Big Moves Ahead: Chart Signals Flashing 🔥</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/big-moves-ahead-chart-signals-flashing-%f0%9f%94%a5/</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f680.png</image_url><description>Company-Sponsored by Flora Growth Corp* TODAY’S TOP ALERT! Nasdaq: FLGC Donald Trump ringing the opening bell wasn’t enough to inspire the markets today. The major indexes are essentially breakeven as of this writing… But that’s NOT the case for my “tactical trade” ideas from yesterday and today, both of which are RIPPING. Yesterday’s idea was […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 18:09:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Broadcom is having an ‘Nvidia moment’ as stock swells further</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/broadcom-is-having-a-nvidia-moment-as-stock-swells-further-6fcb18e1?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-63177709</image_url><description>The newest member of the trillion-dollar market-cap club is looking ahead to a “likely sharp new product ramp” in the second half of 2025, according to an analyst.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How China's satellite megaprojects are challenging Elon Musk's Starlink</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/12/15/chinas-satellite-megaprojects-are-challenging-elon-musks-starlink.html</link><description>China's Qianfan, Guo Wang and Honghu-3 projects have plans to put 38,000 low earth orbit satellites into space.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 13:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bitcoin rises to new record above $106,000 ahead of this week's Fed decision</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/12/16/crypto-market-today.html</link><description>Bitcoin rallied to a new all-time high Sunday evening as investors awaited the Federal Reserve's final interest rate decision of the year.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 15:44:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>0DTEs = Gangsters Only</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/0dtes-gangsters-only/</link><image_url>https://gen.sendtric.com/countdown/tnesedhpo1</image_url><description>Quick Headsup: Live 0DTE trading today with JW at 12:30pm EST. It’s happening the same time his EPIC sale is ending in LottoX. That’s in just… What is 0DTE trading? 0DTEs are fast-paced trades expire the very next day, hence the name ZERO DAYS TO EXPIRATION (ODTE.) Who trades ‘em? Gangstas… Take it from K-Dogg: […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 17:21:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This hot AI stock is set to harness huge opportunity as ‘demand mojo’ plays out</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/this-hot-ai-stock-is-set-to-harness-huge-opportunity-as-demand-mojo-drives-momentum-fcb28d88?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-19291693</image_url><description>“SoundHound represents an underappreciated pure play AI company,” according to Wedbush analyst Dan Ives.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 15:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From growth to gone: GM’s Cruise robotaxi business is latest growth initiative to falter</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/12/15/end-of-gm-cruise-driverless-robotaxi.html</link><description>The driverless ride-hailing service was supposed to be the shining star of GM's growth plans, leading to $50 billion in revenue by the end of this decade.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 13:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>French broadcaster Canal+ shares fall 20% in London listing after spinoff from Vivendi</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/12/16/production-company-canal-shares-fall-in-london-listing.html</link><description>Shares in French broadcaster Canal+ fell over 13% following their London stock market debut Monday.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 15:42:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prostate cancer breakthrough has this small cap soaring</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/prostate-cancer-breakthrough-has-this-small-cap-soaring/</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f50e.png</image_url><description>&amp; Masterworks Good day, 360! Here are some of our top movers today. And look out for a special invitation to join Jason Bond tonight at 8pm EST for 7 Secrets to Grow a $2,000 Account. He’s been killing it for over a YEAR so you need to learn his strategy for growing a small […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 14:46:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why the investor craze for Ozempic and rival weight-loss drugs may resume next year</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/why-the-investor-craze-for-ozempic-and-rival-weight-loss-drugs-may-resume-next-year-055c2d92?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-809249</image_url><description>Novo Nordisk’s takeover of Catalent and the Danish firm’s push to launch a new generation of drugs could boost the importance of GLP agonists in 2025, Barclays analysts said</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 15:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why fast-food companies like KFC and Chick-fil-A are betting on chicken tenders again</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/12/14/kfc-chick-fil-a-bet-big-on-chicken-tenders.html</link><description>Fast-food companies like KFC, Taco Bell and McDonald's are getting back into chicken tenders to boost sales and capitalize on the next chicken trend.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 02:53:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Softbank CEO and Trump to announce $100 billion investment in U.S. by firm</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/12/16/softbank-ceo-to-announce-100-billion-investment-in-us-during-visit-with-trump.html</link><description>The money will be deployed before the end of Trump's term.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:27:47 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>