<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:49:10 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>“Worst July in 10 Years” – but my positions went ⬆️</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/worst-july-in-10-years-but-my-positions-went-%e2%ac%86%ef%b8%8f/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/c74d1bed-6b1f-4630-8a05-e0f14c49ea4f/image__8_.png?t=1722614624</image_url><description>*sponsored by Hey gang, Jeff Bishop here! In the online world, they call it “blackpilling”. That’s when you take a completely negative view of everything. The whole “What’s the point?!” attitude. In July, a lot of traders were feeling that. We had our worst market day in 2 years. And when you tally it all […]</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 12:38:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>My grandfather co-signed my cousin’s student loan. After my grandfather died, my cousin skipped town. Will the estate have to pay the debt?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/im-appalled-my-grandfather-co-signed-his-grandsons-student-loan-after-my-grandfather-died-my-cousin-skipped-town-will-the-estate-have-to-pay-the-debt-40b78608?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-54533295</image_url><description>“The loan is now in default, and I have no idea where this grandson is.”</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A little-known law has forced more than 120,000 veterans to return payouts they received to leave the military, new data shows</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/03/more-than-120000-veterans-return-payouts-due-to-federal-law.html</link><description>A federal law forced thousands of disabled veterans over the years to return the sizeable payouts they received to leave the military.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 20:38:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Warren Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway sold nearly half its stake in Apple</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/03/warren-buffetts-berkshire-hathaway-sold-nearly-half-its-stake-in-apple.html</link><description>Berkshire disclosed an $84.2 billion stake in Apple at the end of the second quarter, suggesting that Buffett offloaded more than 49% of the tech stake.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 18:35:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Did I Trade Today’s Bloodbath</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/how-did-i-trade-todays-bloodbath/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/56e2d078-2f06-4e6c-a921-51aa41c79225/image__8_.png?t=1722609683</image_url><description>*sponsored by Good morning, Guys &amp; Gals! JW here. Questions for you: Are you struggling in these red markets? Are you in need of options education? Do you overtrade daily or often? Are you a BUSY trader who can’t spend all day watching trades? If you answered YES to any or all of these then […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 17:20:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Medicare patients could get emergency treatment at home under new bill</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/medicare-patients-could-get-emergency-treatment-at-home-under-new-bill-aa394ca3?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-84181409</image_url><description>A new proposal in Congress would allow older Medicare recipients to receive emergency medical services at home rather than having to be transported to a hospital for care, which could help them avert potential health and financial consequences resulting from a hospital visit.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:21:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Harris campaign says Trump is 'running scared' after he offers Fox debate</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/03/harris-trump-fox-debate-election.html</link><description>Donald Trump previously said he was willing to debate Kamala Harris multiple times.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 19:32:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Warren Buffett raises Berkshire cash level to record $277 billion after slashing stock holdings</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/03/berkshire-hathaway-earnings-2024-q2.html</link><description>Berkshire Hathaway's cash pile swelled to a record $276.9 billion as Warren Buffett continued dumping his one-time favorite Apple stake.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 15:26:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to try and grow $2,000</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/how-to-try-and-grow-2000/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/9926d431-4b45-4e72-944d-4b459d9bb9ed/HubSpot-logo-color-LynseyMcHugh.png?t=1722528788</image_url><description>*sponsored by Hi guys and gals. For the better part of 18-months I’ve been working on a service I call the $2,000 Small Account Journey. This is an options trading blueprint for small accounts. While some of my $2,000 balances haven’t gone up a lot, or even down, I’ve been able run one to […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 18:57:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>You’ll know AI has taken over when we no longer value money</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/youll-know-ai-has-taken-over-when-we-no-longer-value-money-d9be40a8?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-724370</image_url><description>A future where machines organize, decide and execute all economic activities is no future at all.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:16:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gender identity dispute surrounding boxers Lin Yu-ting and Imane Khelif condemned by IOC president</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/03/iocs-bach-condemns-gender-identity-dispute-with-boxers-yu-ting-khelif.html</link><description>International Olympic Committee President Thomas Bach said concerns over the gender of boxers Imane Khelif and Lin Yu-ting was "totally unacceptable."</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 18:16:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump agrees to debate Harris on Fox News Sept. 4</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/03/trump-agrees-to-fox-news-offer-of-debate-with-vp-harris-on-sept-4.html</link><description>U.S. Republican presidential nominee Donald Trump has agreed to a Fox News offer to hold a debate with Democratic U.S. Vice President Kamala Harris on Sept. 4.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 15:18:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chinese co makes remote robot surgery breakthrough</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/insider/chinese-co-makes-remote-robot-surgery-breakthrough/</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f525.png</image_url><description>Good day, 360! Here are our top investing ideas today. And don’t forget to join us in Market Masters – the hottest trading room around 🔥. Be the best prepared trader on the Street! FOCUS LIST🔎 AMD – Up over 8% in pre, after reporting better than expected earnings and raised forecast on the back […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 16:40:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is there a blood test for Alzheimer’s? Yes, but it isn’t at your doctor’s office yet.</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/is-there-a-blood-test-for-alzheimers-yes-but-it-isnt-at-your-doctors-office-yet-a19e83f8?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-83700364</image_url><description>A blood test has greater success than doctors in determining whether someone has memory loss due to Alzheimer’s disease, a new study found.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:12:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin withdraws plea deal for accused 9/11 terrorists</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/02/defense-secretary-lloyd-austin-withdraws-plea-deal-for-accused-9/11-terrorists.html</link><description>The deal had been announced on Wednesday.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 02:54:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dow closes down 600 points, Nasdaq enters correction after weak jobs report: Live updates</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/01/stock-market-today-live-updates.html</link><description>Stocks slid Friday as a much weaker-than-anticipated jobs report for July ignited worries that the economy could be falling into a recession.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 14:41:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Market Turnaround: What’s Hot Right Now 🔥</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/market-turnaround-whats-hot-right-now-%f0%9f%94%a5/</link><image_url>https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXcRqfDCYQVcWARRAFx1q6g11-hvj9uRFP_dSJUkUxZhJzxCOmEc9DjhsuSNR1K5l7QXCk2fpV3xUT4CUanmpIReZgh12jG8RD6mM8vw07lOOSuytVQiD-f0vL1-8WqF5gIQE-tcr6AL4SsauurOepflkm1P?key=j6FwfEEb-ONODqctQtifUA</image_url><description>Good evening, Folks. Jeff Bishop here! I don’t know about you, but Friday sure felt like a great way for me to end the week. It was a very choppy week, and a few trades didn’t go my way, but when I saw the market start to turn the corner on Friday, I knew it […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 13:53:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Making billionaires pay more in taxes is only fair — even millionaires want it</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/making-billionaires-pay-more-in-taxes-is-only-fair-even-millionaires-want-it-2b03be6d?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-312981</image_url><description>Finance ministers of the G20 nations agree that the ultra-rich should pay their fair share.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:04:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tech stocks see steepest three-week slump in two years, led by plunge in Amazon and Intel</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/02/tech-stocks-wrap-up-steepest-three-week-slump-in-two-years-led-by-plunge-in-amazon-and-intel.html</link><description>With quarterly earnings largely in the rearview mirror, Wall Street is troubled by what it's seeing out of Silicon Valley.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 00:12:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summer Olympics viewership is up — and Snoop Dogg is part of the buzz</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/03/paris-summer-olympics-snoop-dogg.html</link><description>Viewership for the Summer Olympics in Paris is up on NBC and Peacock, and for many, Snoop Dogg's role on the sidelines has been a draw.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 13:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>