<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 10:26:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>China, quantum computers and new venture capital</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/china-quantum-computers-and-new-venture-capital/</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f525.png</image_url><description>Good day, 360! Here are some of our top movers today. OPEN HOUSE today in Market Masters – the hottest trading room around 🔥. Be the best prepared trader on the Street! FOCUS LIST🔎 ONCO – Up over 80% in the pre-market after Altos Venture reported a 32.5% stake in the company DUO – Up […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 15:26:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CVS’s stock rises nearly 3% on report of meeting with large hedge fund Glenview Capital</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/cvss-stock-rises-nearly-3-on-report-of-meeting-with-large-hedge-fund-glenview-capital-15c6ced9?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-07455118</image_url><description>Gathering signals potential changes to improve shareholder value after the company’s weak stock performance.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 15:25:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Laurene Powell Jobs is betting on these 11 AI startups</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/09/30/laurene-powell-jobs-bets-on-ai-startups.html</link><description>Emerson Collective has participated in AI funding rounds totaling more than $1 billion, according to data provided exclusively to CNBC by Fintrx.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 14:39:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rupert Murdoch’s property group REA ends chase to buy Rightmove after multiple rejected offers</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/09/30/murdochs-rea-group-ends-chase-for-uks-rightmove.html</link><description>Rupert Murdoch's Australian property listing firm REA Group said Monday it would no longer seek to buy UK property portal Rightmove.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 15:22:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Could This Stock Soar Again? 🚀</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/could-this-stock-soar-again-%f0%9f%9a%80/</link><image_url>https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXeidE0t3uis6NXl3cXyCwjB7uYCla0azwKd-XINjJFaEDfwzB8wynnR1sOCXiL31k7PNldgVQA8PPBLxlXGCaAzinz3eIpLed-7h15bin21ZcnxHAE0QPIQTY43u0XImBjtYb9kdquOc2a8o5YrSc9fpvJJ?key=zAD_Xr1YgjsdfhDHHeH3OA</image_url><description>You have a problem… You’re not watching us LIVE right now! Mon – Fri, we’re live streaming and teaching folks just like you how they find some of the best options and stock setups, so why haven’t you joined us? Jump into our Market Masters live trade room Take a peek (right now, it’s free!) […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 16:42:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chicago business-activity index remains in contraction territory for 10th straight month</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/chicago-business-activity-index-remains-in-contraction-territory-for-10th-straight-month-c8164128?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-58167017</image_url><description>The Chicago Business Barometer, the gauge of business activity also known as the Chicago PMI, rose to 46.6 in September from 46.1 in August.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 15:10:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ford aims to boost EV sales, address owner concerns with new benefits program</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/09/30/ford-ev-benefits-program-aims-to-boost-sales.html</link><description>The "Ford Power Promise" program begins Tuesday for customers who purchase or lease a new Ford EV such as the F-150 Lightning or Mustang Mach-E.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 13:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Iran's response to Israel will be a choice between revenge and survival. Markets say it's choosing survival</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/09/30/irans-response-to-israel-is-a-choice-between-revenge-and-survival.html</link><description>Iran's leadership has vowed revenge, but its actions and language suggest — at least so far — a more measured response.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 15:14:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Surprise forecast has traders in a frenzy 🫨</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/surprise-forecast-has-traders-in-a-frenzy-%f0%9f%ab%a8/</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/2705.png</image_url><description>*in partnership with InvestorPlace Media Good day, 360! Here are some of our top movers today. And TOMORROW at 1pm ET, Jeff Bishop will be hosting one of the most widely followed technical analysts in the world in Market Masters – so mark your calendars✅. FOCUS LIST🔎 OCTO – Up over 70% in the pre-market […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 16:46:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Carnival’s stock drops as downbeat net yields outlook offsets record revenue</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/carnivals-stock-drops-as-downbeat-yields-outlook-offsets-an-earnings-beat-on-record-revenue-54f7a715?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-17987285</image_url><description>Carnival’s stock took a hit Monday, after the cruise operator reported record fiscal third-quarter revenue that beat expectations, but provided a downbeat outlook for net yields in the current quarter.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 14:59:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Photos: Hurricane Helene leaves flooding and destruction across the southeastern U.S.</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/09/28/hurricane-helene-photos-florida-destruction-cyclone.html</link><description>President Joe Biden and Vice President Kamala Harris expressed their sympathies for communities ravaged by Hurricane Helene.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 12:02:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Major CVS shareholder plans activist push, will meet with management, sources say</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/09/30/cvs-activist-glenview-karen-lynch.html</link><description>Glenview Capital is expected to meet with CVS management on Monday to discuss its plans for value creation at the struggling business.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 14:39:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>11 for 11… what’s next?</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/11-for-11-whats-next/</link><image_url>https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXcgQcWvxE0ppaAQvYYNrrFJkuR2s_O6iMMwjLlHZN7WwyR7JLyxPTMjhj7SIvcbe1M5GHSG0I50DIrhNITDoawXe5cq3aD4d_tjgj9H85WCz3lL5jvVwE19RERvYnqxUsz7IkqaHQYqQFdJOH0x9kNQFlQ?key=MKIu-pbkXoA0DxPRS3VSHA</image_url><description>Sometimes you got it, sometimes you don’t. Guys and gals, right now, I’ve got it! Over the past 2 weeks, I’ve been hitting on banger trade after banger trade inside Small Account Journey. I’ve closed out 11 trades, and all 11 have been winners. See? *Trading is hard, results not guaranteed and should not […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 20:00:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AT&amp;T exits pay-TV and frees DirecTV to combine with rival Dish</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/at-t-to-sell-controlling-stake-in-directv-to-tpg-for-about-7-6-billion-in-cash-payments-through-2029-50dab8d3?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-97810336</image_url><description>DirecTV promptly announces deal to acquire EchoStar’s video business that includes Dish TV and Sling TV, cementing a combination the two have sought for decades.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 14:56:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mark Cuban warns Elon Musk: Trump’s ‘loyalty is only to himself'</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/09/29/mark-cuban-elon-musk-trumps-warning-loyalty-election.html</link><description>Mark Cuban is supporting Vice President Kamala Harris, while Elon Musk has endorsed ex-President Donald Trump in the 2024 election.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 19:33:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>German inflation drops to 1.8% in September, below expectations</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/09/30/german-inflation-drops-to-1point8percent-in-september-below-expectations.html</link><description>The harmonized German consumer price index eased to 1.8% in September, more than expected, preliminary data from the country's statistics office showed Monday.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 14:07:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Did you watch me do this today 🔍</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/did-you-watch-me-do-this-today-%f0%9f%94%8d/</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f50d.png</image_url><description>Did you watch me do this today 🔍 Afternoon members, Welcome to all new Market Navigator and or Atomic Trade members! I did it again, another “W” this morning for Market Navigator service which is my Options basics program that trades SPY options every morning. I told you last week I would teach you how […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 18:39:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘She’s the queen of CDs’: My mother-in-law, 83, opened 12 CDs at different financial institutions. Should I intervene?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/shes-the-queen-of-cds-my-mother-in-law-83-opened-12-cds-at-different-financial-institutions-should-i-intervene-b89a1258?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-41185071</image_url><description>“Given her advanced age and risk aversion, I question whether pursuing these interest rates and promotional offers is truly worthwhile.”</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 14:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kamala Harris wants to take on price gouging. It's hard to find agreement on what it even is</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/09/29/what-is-price-gouging-kamala-harris-promises-to-fight-inflation.html</link><description>Higher prices, and who or what is to blame for them, have become a central theme in the presidential race, as steep grocery bills frustrate Americans.</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 13:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'No challenges can stop China's progress' Xi Jinping says in 75th anniversary speech</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/09/30/no-challenges-can-stop-chinas-progress-xi-jinping-says-in-75th-anniversary-speech.html</link><description>Chinese President Xi Jinping made no mention of specific countries or trade conflicts in his Monday speech and portrayed Beijing as upholding globalization.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 13:47:22 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>