<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 11:47:39 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>These META trades highlight an underrated trading strategy…</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/jason-bond/these-meta-trades-highlight-an-underrated-trading-strategy/</link><image_url>https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXe8GxLtTCV3G3eF-NJ45Y_OMOIRwy8iTsWlsivNomfh00KlL-7bNNN2pTkWmdND1GvViPVsiLX3p2WbzK7FZtgkwGrragwnzPDPxxYVZYTacvmhKTLw7ovgEVbwh_XVPLTcIYP3Kq7gFoDb6QSEQJUKa4N6?key=0zDl8IL_UdzsSha7wNhqcw</image_url><description>I tacked on some small wins to my track record yesterday, and it got me thinking: You know what’s an underrated part of any trading strategy? Momentum. As traders, we all struggle with patience. We want the big gains now! We want that CHEDDAR! And fast! But there are no traders or investors on the […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 16:26:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 2024 presidential election is entering its most volatile period for the stock market</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/the-2024-presidential-election-is-entering-its-most-volatile-period-for-the-stock-market-50a34b72?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-26462638</image_url><description>There is still no green light for the stock market as the 2024 presidential election season gets into full swing. The S&amp;P 500’s historical performance during election years suggests stocks could experience a lackluster and volatile period between now and Nov. 5.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 16:41:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alaska Airlines and Hawaiian Airlines merger clears Justice Department hurdle, now faces DOT</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/20/alaska-airlines-hawaiian-airlines-merger.html</link><description>The Justice Department didn't file a suit seeking to block the tie-up between Alaska and Hawaiian, but still have to face the DOT.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 16:47:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Britain's Bill Gates': Who is Mike Lynch, the UK tech entrepreneur missing after superyacht sinks?</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/20/who-is-mike-lynch-uk-tech-entrepreneur-missing-in-superyacht-sinking.html</link><description>Mike Lynch was only recently cleared of fraud charges in a landmark trial. Now, in a shock turn of events, he's gone missing after the sinking of a superyacht.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 16:46:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Small cap AI stocks are on fire this morning</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/small-cap-ai-stocks-are-on-fire-this-morning/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/1022e75f-9694-451c-95ba-14ec0069c5e9/image__1_.png</image_url><description>*together with Vantage Point Are you tired of trading “alone in a hole?” See JW’s invitation below (happening) tonight and join us any time (FREE) in the Market Masters Room. Emerge from isolation and make some new friends 👬. FOCUS LIST🔎 AUUD – Up over 100% in pre after announcing launch of faidr 3.1 […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 14:18:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lowe’s misses sales forecasts, says it can’t call a home-improvement bottom</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/lowes-stock-falls-as-sales-miss-expectations-and-outlook-lowered-amid-pressure-on-big-ticket-spending-25716297?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-65680912</image_url><description>Lowe’s stock fell Tuesday, after the home improvement retailer reported fiscal second-quarter sales that missed expectations, as customers continued to hold back on spending on larger do-it-yourself projects.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 16:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Harley-Davidson drops diversity efforts after online pressure</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/20/harley-davidson-drops-diversity-efforts-after-online-pressure-.html</link><description>"We do not have a DEI function today," and Harley-Davidson has not since April 2024, according to the statement.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 16:31:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>S&amp;P 500 slips as Wall Street struggles to maintain comeback's momentum: Live updates</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/19/stock-market-today-live-updates.html</link><description>Wall Street began the week with a rally as the major averages continued to advance after their early August sell-off.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 16:45:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New obesity drug and Fubo wins injunction against Disney</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/new-obesity-drug-and-fubo-wins-injunction-against-disney/</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f50e.png</image_url><description>*sponsored by TradingTips GM! As usual here are today’s biggest movers. And right now we have a great special going on for ALL our services. Why choose one when you can have them all? Call Davis for more info (1-800-585-4488 / davis@ragingbull.com). P.S. Don’t forget to join us in Market Masters to kick the week […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 15:50:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>U.S. job gains have likely been exaggerated. Now we’ll find out by how much.</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/u-s-job-gains-have-likely-been-exaggerated-now-well-find-out-by-how-much-8fe9dd3d?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-40505580</image_url><description>The U.S. created a remarkable 242,000 jobs a month from the spring of 2023 to the spring of 2024, when the economy was thought be slowing down. Or did it?</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 16:27:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GMC expects to outsell its electric truck competitors as it launches new Sierra pickup</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/20/gmc-targets-electric-truck-leadership-against-tesla-ford-rivian.html</link><description>To do so, it will have to top its sibling Chevrolet Silverado EV as well as competitors from Ford Motor, Rivian Automotive and Tesla.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 16:30:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Morgan Stanley International chair among 6 missing after luxury yacht sinks in Sicily</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/20/morgan-stanley-international-chair-reported-missing-in-yacht-sinking.html</link><description>The 56-meter (184 feet) sailing boat, called "The Bayesian," was hit by a violent storm around 4 a.m. local time Monday with 10 crew and 12 passengers on board.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 16:28:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stalking these Calls on LEN</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/stalking-these-calls-on-len/</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f4aa.png</image_url><description>*together with Vantage Point GM, Folks! Looks like a solid trading week shaping up 💪 . This morning’s Bullseye Idea of the WEEK was Calls on LEN — plan released pre-market to members as always. Join me at 11am ET TODAY for the details as we stalk LEN as well as my full market rundown […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 15:48:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wells Fargo to sell commercial-mortgage-servicing unit to Trimont</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/wells-fargo-to-sell-commercial-mortgage-servicing-unit-to-trimont-0af6f7d5?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-55835441</image_url><description>The deal will make Trimont the largest servicer of commercial loans in the United States, the company said.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 16:22:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump says he would offer Tesla CEO Elon Musk a Cabinet slot, but might end EV tax credit</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/19/trump-elon-musk-cabinet-ev-tax-credit.html</link><description>Donald Trump said he would consider ending a $7,500 tax credit for certain new electric vehicles, which could affect Tesla CEO Elon Musk's EV business.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 16:06:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The final 10 minutes of trading may be all that matter this week</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/20/the-final-10-minutes-of-trading-may-be-all-that-matter-this-week.html</link><description>On Monday, about a third of the gains in both the S&amp;P 500 and Nasdaq-100 indexes came during the final 10 minutes or so of trading, JPMorgan noted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 16:10:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Moneyballing the SPY 📊</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/jeff-williams/moneyballing-the-spy-%f0%9f%93%8a/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/431b907b-038a-4010-9804-0cb8fabb1e83/JW_MM_room_image_for_BET.png?t=1723979474</image_url><description>Hi Guys &amp; Gals! Jeff Williams here. You may know me from the daily opening and closing sessions in the Market Master’s Room. Here’s a snapshot of what the room looks like, and me making a LIVE trade alert (also sent out on the app if you can’t be live with me). If you haven’t […]</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 17:20:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kroger expected to price seven-part bond deal that may be the biggest of the year</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/kroger-expected-to-price-seven-part-bond-deal-that-may-be-the-biggest-of-the-year-a18b987b?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-642066</image_url><description>Kroger Co. is expected to price what may be the biggest bond deal of 2024 later Tuesday, a seven-part deal that will be used to help fund its $25 billion planed merger with Albertsons Cos.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 16:14:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eli Lilly's weight loss drug slashes the risk of developing diabetes in long-term trial</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/20/eli-lilly-weight-loss-drug-cuts-risk-of-developing-diabetes-in-trial.html</link><description>The late-stage trial on tirzepatide also found that patients experienced sustained weight loss over the roughly three-year treatment period.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 15:18:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>India flags cricket rights concerns with Disney-Reliance $8.5 billion merger</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/20/india-flags-cricket-rights-concerns-with-disney-reliance-8point5-billion-merger.html</link><description>It is the biggest setback so far to the planned Disney-Reliance merger which aims to create India's biggest entertainment player which will compete with Sony, Zee Entertainment, Netflix and Amazon with a combined 120 TV channels and two streaming services.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 15:43:08 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>