<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 08:10:40 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Increased AI demand has this tiny priced stock surging</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/increased-ai-demand-has-this-tiny-priced-stock-surging/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/1022e75f-9694-451c-95ba-14ec0069c5e9/image__1_.png</image_url><description>*Issuer-paid content from GameSquare Markets are staging a rally today after Japanese markets had a big reversal overnight following one of the worst days ever. Is it time to buy the dip and hold on for new all-time highs? Who knows 🤷. Put your two cents in our biggest LIVE trading room —&gt; Market Master’s. […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:25:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘You’re not stupid enough to have to work in a place like this’: It’s time to give fast-food workers some respect. Could you do what they do?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/youre-not-stupid-enough-to-have-to-work-in-a-place-like-this-its-time-to-give-fast-food-workers-some-respect-could-you-do-what-they-do-b7f719d3?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-88436405</image_url><description>A 39-year-old woman in Parma, Ohio was sentenced to two months working in a fast-food restaurant after throwing a hot bowl in a Chipotle worker’s face.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 13:08:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CVS slashes profit outlook on higher medical costs, says top Aetna executive will leave</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/07/cvs-health-cvs-earnings-q2-2024.html</link><description>CVS said higher medical costs are weighing on its insurance business, and announced Aetna President Brian Kane will step down.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 13:06:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dow futures jump for a second day, up 200 points as Wall Street tries to recoup sell-off: Live updates</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/06/stock-market-today-live-updates.html</link><description>Stock futures popped after Wall Street snapped a three-day losing streak. Investors also looked to claw back more of the losses suffered earlier in the week.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 13:09:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stock market crash, these stocks are holding their own</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/stock-market-crash-these-stocks-are-holding-their-own/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/ead23b97-deed-423d-9ff4-987a0ff3a4dc/manifi_logo.png?t=1722608048</image_url><description>*sponsored by Whew! It’s a bloodbath out there — trade safe… Meanwhile, there are still some big movers today. Check ‘em out. And check US out in the Market Masters Trade Room 🔥. (Don’t forget Jeff’s Bullseye is going out right before the market opens. What’s he gonna pick??? Get on his list quick to find […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 15:08:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘I fear a storm is coming’: I’m nervous about November’s election and another recession. Should I move my money to cash and gold?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/i-fear-a-storm-is-coming-im-nervous-about-novembers-election-and-another-recession-should-i-move-my-money-to-cash-and-gold-1318be33?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-76744313</image_url><description>“I’ve considered parking it all in a location such as Grand Cayman.”</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 13:06:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Markets are counting on the Fed to head off recession with sizable interest rate cuts</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/06/markets-are-counting-on-the-fed-to-head-off-recession-with-sizeable-interest-rate-cuts.html</link><description>How Chair Jerome Powell and his cohorts react likely will go a long way in determining how investors negotiate a turbulent climate.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:45:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Russia hates on the Olympic Games, relishing 'scandals' and controversy in Paris</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/07/what-does-russia-think-about-the-2024-olympic-games.html</link><description>Russia's media has shunned coverage of the Olympic Games in Paris — unless something has been controversial or gone wrong.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 13:08:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>“Worst July in 10 Years” – but my positions went ⬆️</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/worst-july-in-10-years-but-my-positions-went-%e2%ac%86%ef%b8%8f/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/c74d1bed-6b1f-4630-8a05-e0f14c49ea4f/image__8_.png?t=1722614624</image_url><description>*sponsored by Hey gang, Jeff Bishop here! In the online world, they call it “blackpilling”. That’s when you take a completely negative view of everything. The whole “What’s the point?!” attitude. In July, a lot of traders were feeling that. We had our worst market day in 2 years. And when you tally it all […]</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 12:38:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CVS’s stock drops as the healthcare-benefits business continues to hurt profits</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/cvss-stock-drops-after-a-revenue-miss-and-lowered-profit-outlook-amid-challenges-in-health-care-benefits-f7041a28?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-46851347</image_url><description>CVS’s CEO said the company is “taking action” to address its challenges, including making leadership changes in some business segments.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:59:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly mortgage refinance demand soars 16% as rates sink to lowest level in over a year</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/07/weekly-mortgage-refinance-demand-soars-16percent-as-rates-sink-to-lowest-level-in-over-a-year.html</link><description>Mortgage interest rates dropped last week to the lowest level since May 2023, causing a surge in mortgage demand from both homebuyers and especially current homeowners.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:31:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elon Musk 'accountable to no one,' Britain's tech minister says after X owner's comments on UK riots</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/07/uk-riots-elon-musk-accountable-to-no-one-uk-tech-minister-says.html</link><description>Elon Musk can't be held to account by anyone, the U.K.'s technology minister said, adding to criticisms of the billionaire from government officials.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:59:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Did I Trade Today’s Bloodbath</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/how-did-i-trade-todays-bloodbath/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/56e2d078-2f06-4e6c-a921-51aa41c79225/image__8_.png?t=1722609683</image_url><description>*sponsored by Good morning, Guys &amp; Gals! JW here. Questions for you: Are you struggling in these red markets? Are you in need of options education? Do you overtrade daily or often? Are you a BUSY trader who can’t spend all day watching trades? If you answered YES to any or all of these then […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 17:20:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Warner Music’s stock rises after profit matches estimates despite small revenue miss</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/warner-musics-stock-gains-after-profit-beat-offsets-small-revenue-miss-ce676e63?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-43221022</image_url><description>Warner Music Group Corp.’s stock rose 3% premarket Wednesday, after the company matched profit estimates for the second quarter, offsetting a small revenue miss.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:59:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Treasury yields tick higher as global stocks continue rebound</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/07/treasury-yields-higher-as-global-stocks-continue-rebound.html</link><description>Treasury yields were higher early Wednesday as global markets reversed course from Monday's equity sell-off.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:07:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Markets are counting on the Fed to head off recession with sizable interest rate cuts</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/06/markets-are-counting-on-the-fed-to-head-off-recession-with-sizeable-interest-rate-cuts.html</link><description>How Chair Jerome Powell and his cohorts react likely will go a long way in determining how investors negotiate a turbulent climate.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:45:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to try and grow $2,000</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/how-to-try-and-grow-2000/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/9926d431-4b45-4e72-944d-4b459d9bb9ed/HubSpot-logo-color-LynseyMcHugh.png?t=1722528788</image_url><description>*sponsored by Hi guys and gals. For the better part of 18-months I’ve been working on a service I call the $2,000 Small Account Journey. This is an options trading blueprint for small accounts. While some of my $2,000 balances haven’t gone up a lot, or even down, I’ve been able run one to […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 18:57:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New York Times says new digital-only subscribers helped profit rise 41%</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/new-york-times-says-new-digital-only-subscribers-helped-profit-rise-41-c05b5e7c?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-22693639</image_url><description>News-media provider added 300,000 digital-only subscribers, bringing the number to a total of 10.84 million</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:49:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Harris and Walz make Trump focus at Democratic ticket's first rally</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/06/harris-walz-rally-election-trump-vance.html</link><description>Kamala Harris and Tim Walz are up against the Republican ticket of Donald Trump and Sen. JD Vance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 02:04:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Disney beats estimates as combined streaming services turn a profit</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/07/disney-dis-q3-earnings-report-2024.html</link><description>Disney beat estimates as its combined streaming businesses — Disney+, Hulu and ESPN+ — turned a profit for the first time.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:42:06 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>