<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:34:09 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Increased AI demand has this tiny priced stock surging</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/increased-ai-demand-has-this-tiny-priced-stock-surging/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/1022e75f-9694-451c-95ba-14ec0069c5e9/image__1_.png</image_url><description>*Issuer-paid content from GameSquare Markets are staging a rally today after Japanese markets had a big reversal overnight following one of the worst days ever. Is it time to buy the dip and hold on for new all-time highs? Who knows 🤷. Put your two cents in our biggest LIVE trading room —&gt; Market Master’s. […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:25:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘I don’t think the consumer is in trouble’: Debt is going up, but that doesn’t mean a recession is on the way</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/i-dont-think-the-consumer-is-in-trouble-debt-is-going-up-but-that-doesnt-mean-a-recession-is-on-the-way-e22e8d7a?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-70557524</image_url><description>“The prospects for the economy and prospects for the stock market do not go hand in hand,” one economist noted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:23:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elon Musk will interview Trump on Monday night, Republican presidential nominee says</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/06/elon-musk-trump-interview-harris-walz.html</link><description>Donald Trump and Sen. JD Vance are facing Vice President Kamala Harris and Gov. Tim Walz in the 2024 presidential election.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:25:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dow rallies 500 points as Wall Street rebound gains steam: Live updates</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/05/stock-market-today-live-updates.html</link><description>The S&amp;P 500 partially recovered a day after the broad market index notched its worst day in nearly two years as global markets sold off.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:30:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stock market crash, these stocks are holding their own</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/stock-market-crash-these-stocks-are-holding-their-own/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/ead23b97-deed-423d-9ff4-987a0ff3a4dc/manifi_logo.png?t=1722608048</image_url><description>*sponsored by Whew! It’s a bloodbath out there — trade safe… Meanwhile, there are still some big movers today. Check ‘em out. And check US out in the Market Masters Trade Room 🔥. (Don’t forget Jeff’s Bullseye is going out right before the market opens. What’s he gonna pick??? Get on his list quick to find […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 15:08:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bond investors are coping with recession anxiety, extreme volatility</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/bond-investors-are-coping-with-recession-anxiety-extreme-volatility-5a889242?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-63375543</image_url><description>It took only about a week for riskier U.S. corporate bonds with ‘junk’ credit ratings to erase all of their gains this year.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:17:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Markets are counting on the Fed to head off recession with sizeable interest rate cuts</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/06/markets-are-counting-on-the-fed-to-head-off-recession-with-sizeable-interest-rate-cuts.html</link><description>How Chair Jerome Powell and his cohorts react likely will go a long way in determining how investors negotiate a turbulent climate.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:15:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>U.S. crude oil rises as Wall Street rallies, market braces for expected Iran attack against Israel</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/06/crude-oil-prices-today.html</link><description>Oil futures rose on Tuesday as Wall Street sought a turnaround from the prior session's sell-off.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:13:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>“Worst July in 10 Years” – but my positions went ⬆️</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/worst-july-in-10-years-but-my-positions-went-%e2%ac%86%ef%b8%8f/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/c74d1bed-6b1f-4630-8a05-e0f14c49ea4f/image__8_.png?t=1722614624</image_url><description>*sponsored by Hey gang, Jeff Bishop here! In the online world, they call it “blackpilling”. That’s when you take a completely negative view of everything. The whole “What’s the point?!” attitude. In July, a lot of traders were feeling that. We had our worst market day in 2 years. And when you tally it all […]</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 12:38:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oil prices end slightly higher as stock market bounces after Monday plunge</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/oil-prices-edge-higher-as-investors-monitor-iran-israel-tensions-46451933?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-244703</image_url><description>Oil futures rose modestly Tuesday, with support attributed in part to fears a potential retaliatory attack by Iran on Israel could spiral into a threat to crude supply from the Middle East.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:14:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10-year Treasury yield rebounds after hitting its lowest level in more than a year</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/06/us-treasury-yields-in-focus-after-mondays-market-rout.html</link><description>Treasury yields bounced back on Tuesday as investors closely monitored a reversal of the previous day's global market sell-off.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:08:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Where BlackRock's Rick Rieder sees income opportunity amid the market volatility</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/06/where-blackrocks-rick-rieder-sees-income-opportunity-amid-the-market-volatility.html</link><description>Rick Rieder, BlackRock's chief investment officer of global fixed income, said these assets have attractive yields and solid fundamentals.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:03:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Did I Trade Today’s Bloodbath</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/how-did-i-trade-todays-bloodbath/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/56e2d078-2f06-4e6c-a921-51aa41c79225/image__8_.png?t=1722609683</image_url><description>*sponsored by Good morning, Guys &amp; Gals! JW here. Questions for you: Are you struggling in these red markets? Are you in need of options education? Do you overtrade daily or often? Are you a BUSY trader who can’t spend all day watching trades? If you answered YES to any or all of these then […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 17:20:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fed rate cuts could prove to be a double-edged sword when it comes to inflation</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/fed-rate-cuts-could-prove-to-be-a-double-edged-sword-when-it-comes-to-inflation-567af996?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-25275521</image_url><description>A day after U.S. recession fears swept global financial markets, a few things became clear. One of them is that if the Federal Reserve actually delivers as many rate cuts as traders currently expect, it could lead to a new set of problems.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:14:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Microsoft fires back at Delta after massive outage, says airline declined 'repeated' offers for help</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/06/microsoft-fires-back-at-delta-after-outage-says-airline-declined-help.html</link><description>Microsoft said Delta turned down several offers for help during the flight disruptions following the outage.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 18:49:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elon Musk's X sues advertisers over alleged 'massive advertiser boycott' after Twitter takeover</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/06/elon-musks-x-sues-advertisers-over-alleged-massive-advertiser-boycott-after-twitter-takeover.html</link><description>The company formerly known as Twitter filed the lawsuit against the World Federation of Advertisers and member companies Unilever, Mars, CVS Health and Orsted.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:25:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to try and grow $2,000</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/how-to-try-and-grow-2000/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/9926d431-4b45-4e72-944d-4b459d9bb9ed/HubSpot-logo-color-LynseyMcHugh.png?t=1722528788</image_url><description>*sponsored by Hi guys and gals. For the better part of 18-months I’ve been working on a service I call the $2,000 Small Account Journey. This is an options trading blueprint for small accounts. While some of my $2,000 balances haven’t gone up a lot, or even down, I’ve been able run one to […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 18:57:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘I fear a storm is coming’: I’m nervous about November’s election and another recession. Should I move my money to cash and gold?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/i-fear-a-storm-is-coming-im-nervous-about-novembers-election-and-another-recession-should-i-move-my-money-to-cash-and-gold-1318be33?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-76744313</image_url><description>“I’ve considered parking it all in a location such as Grand Cayman.”</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:11:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump, Harris campaigns race to define Democratic running mate Tim Walz</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/06/trump-harris-tim-walz-running-mate.html</link><description>The Kamala Harris and Donald Trump presidential campaigns pushed dueling portraits of newly announced Democratic running mate, Minnesota Gov. Tim Walz.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 18:44:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Markets are counting on the Fed to head off recession with sizeable interest rate cuts</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/06/markets-are-counting-on-the-fed-to-head-off-recession-with-sizeable-interest-rate-cuts.html</link><description>How Chair Jerome Powell and his cohorts react likely will go a long way in determining how investors negotiate a turbulent climate.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:15:59 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>