<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 11:10:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Biotechs and nuclear power for AI in play today 📈</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/biotechs-and-nuclear-power-for-ai-in-play-today-%f0%9f%93%88/</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f525.png</image_url><description>&amp; Morning Brew Good day, 360! Here are some of our top movers today. And don’t forget to join us in Market Masters – the hottest trading room around 🔥. Be the best prepared trader on the Street! FOCUS LIST🔎 PLRZ – Up over 200% in the pre-market after announcing it’s moving forward with expected […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 14:57:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oil prices climb with U.S. crude supplies down a fourth straight week</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/oil-ticks-higher-as-traders-await-fed-decision-inventory-data-bb77844f?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-263878</image_url><description>Oil futures on Wednesday were on track to post a gain for the session after back-to-back losses, with prices getting a lift from official U.S. data showing a fourth consecutive weekly decline in domestic crude inventories.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 16:07:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Here’s what a blockbuster Nissan-Honda merger could mean for the auto industry</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/12/18/what-a-potential-nissan-honda-merger-could-mean-for-the-auto-industry.html</link><description>Nissan and Honda are understood to be exploring a blockbuster merger as the two rival companies seek to stay competitive on the road to full electrification.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 16:06:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dow jumps 200 points ahead of Fed decision as index seeks to avoid 10th straight loss: Live updates</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/12/17/stock-market-today-live-updates.html</link><description>The Federal Reserve is widely expected to lower rates by a quarter point on Wednesday, but the big event is the central bank’s summary of economic projections.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 16:09:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>🎅What you do not know</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/%f0%9f%8e%85what-you-do-not-know/</link><image_url>https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXeQghLhrNFQZ7XjQ_Gvbqzr5Yy7vv0xXREFB08kidoModfDzKKxaZtlOfFxgKhELiskayb1ULYqL7vvrgVlKW84uEofpcWnYSKS6hHxCe2iavmxakCiPzy5dCBgL6l1jBrh5rvpbA?key=CCjlGqVQHMRflBoPTKpy3IHj</image_url><description>*In partnership with Analytica Investor Let me tell you what you don’t know about being on this email list… But first, here’s a summary of what you do know: 1) My Market Navigator service is straightforward, focusing on one security — the world’s most powerful fund, the S&amp;P 500. 2) My Market Navigator “trade of […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 14:13:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>It’s ‘the worst tax deal in America’ — but you still have time to fix it. Here’s how.</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/its-the-worst-tax-deal-in-america-but-you-still-have-time-to-fix-it-heres-how-809a97d7?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-13134477</image_url><description>Reporting large amounts of income on a W-2 form can set up people for a big tax bill, but there are strategies to trim that.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 16:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>U.S. auto sales next year expected to be best since 2019</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/12/18/2025-us-auto-sales-forecast.html</link><description>S&amp;P Global, Edmunds and Cox Automotive expect new auto sales to increase year over year by 2.5% or less to achieve the industry's best results since 2019.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 16:06:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Here’s what a blockbuster Nissan-Honda merger could mean for the auto industry</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/12/18/what-a-potential-nissan-honda-merger-could-mean-for-the-auto-industry.html</link><description>Nissan and Honda are understood to be exploring a blockbuster merger as the two rival companies seek to stay competitive on the road to full electrification.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 16:06:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Worthington Enterprise: A Metal Fabrication Giant</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/the-worthington-enterprise-a-metal-fabrication-giant/</link><image_url>https://ragingbull.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/08/favicon.png</image_url><description>Hey there, folks! It’s your boy Jeff Bishop here. Today we’re gonna talk about a company that’s been around for over 60 years – Worthington Enterprises Inc., or WOR as you might know it on the stock market. Now, I’m not here to give you investment advice or tell you whether this stock is going […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 11:44:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bill to prevent government shutdown includes raise for Congress. It’s the first pay hike in 16 years.</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/bill-to-prevent-government-shutdown-includes-raise-for-congress-itsthe-first-pay-hike-in-16-years-4c06b8e7?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-62479765</image_url><description>Congressional leaders have put forward a giant spending package to avoid a partial government shutdown, and one provision aims to deliver the first pay raise for lawmakers in about 16 years.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>International markets face an uncertain 2025. Here's what to look out for</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/12/18/international-markets-face-an-uncertain-2025-heres-what-to-look-out-for.html</link><description>Ramifications of President-elect Donald Trump's tariffs, as well as weak growth forecasts, are weighing on international equity markets.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 15:01:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>European stocks rise as investors monitor UK economic data; Renault jumps 5%</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/12/18/european-markets-live-updates-fed-decision-ahead-data-and-stocks.html</link><description>European stocks were higher on Wednesday as investors awaited the latest monetary policy decision by the U.S. Federal Reserve.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 16:03:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>﻿The Unlikely Hero of the Market: A Closer Look at Maison Solutions, Inc. (MSS)</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/the-unlikely-hero-of-the-market-a-closer-look-at-maison-solutions-inc-mss/</link><image_url>https://ragingbull.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/08/favicon.png</image_url><description>Folks, let me tell you about a stock that’s been flying under the radar lately – MSS, or Maison Solutions, Inc. Now, I’m not here to make any investment recommendations, but I want to give you an honest look at this company and its prospects. First off, let’s talk about what they do. This is […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 10:45:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bill Belichick is used to coaching millionaires, so he’ll be right at home in NIL-era college football</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/bill-belichick-is-used-to-coaching-millionaires-so-hell-be-right-at-home-in-todays-college-football-0c0fb91a?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-36979680</image_url><description>With Belichick, a legendary NFL coach, at the helm the University of North Carolina will reportedly increase its pot of name, image and likeness football funds fivefold to $20 million.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 15:53:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Fed has a big interest rate decision coming Wednesday. Here's what to expect</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/12/17/the-fed-has-a-big-interest-rate-decision-coming-wednesday-heres-what-to-expect.html</link><description>Traders are pricing in a near certainty that the Fed on Wednesday will lower its key rate by a quarter percentage point.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 14:41:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Fed has a big interest rate decision coming Wednesday. Here's what to expect</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/12/17/the-fed-has-a-big-interest-rate-decision-coming-wednesday-heres-what-to-expect.html</link><description>Traders are pricing in a near certainty that the Fed on Wednesday will lower its key rate by a quarter percentage point.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 14:41:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>﻿The Wild Ride of Syntec Optics Holdings Inc: A High-Flying Stock with a Bumpy History</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/the-wild-ride-of-syntec-optics-holdings-inc-a-high-flying-stock-with-a-bumpy-history/</link><image_url>https://ragingbull.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/08/favicon.png</image_url><description>Hey there, folks! It’s your boy Jeff Bishop here. Today we’re diving into the world of high-tech investing and exploring one stock that’s been making waves in the industry – Syntec Optics Holdings Inc (OPTX). This company has seen some crazy price swings over the past few weeks, with a whopping 98.31% increase in just […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 10:42:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>General Mills’ refrigerated-dough sales disappoint as holiday baking season starts</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/general-mills-stock-drops-as-lowered-profit-outlook-offsets-quarterly-earnings-beat-64c5c00d?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-73868645</image_url><description>General Mills’ stock was falling Wednesday after a cut to the company’s full-year profit outlook overshadowed a big quarterly earnings beat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 15:44:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How employees are embracing coffee badging as a soft revolt against office mandates</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/12/18/how-coffee-badging-became-a-revolt-against-return-to-office-mandates.html</link><description>During the pandemic, 'quiet quitting' dominated as worker demand surged. Now, with a tighter job market, 'coffee badging' is trending.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 14:32:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Germany’s auto giants were already reeling. Now Trump wants to turn them into American companies</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/12/17/vw-bmw-and-mbg-german-auto-giants-brace-for-trumps-tariff-threats.html</link><description>For Germany, the prospect of U.S. tariffs on European autos comes at a time when it's top original equipment manufacturers are already reeling.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 11:01:51 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>