<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 06:53:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Plan your trade and trade your plan!</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/insider/plan-your-trade-and-trade-your-plan/</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f4a5.png</image_url><description>Try SPY💥 I Market Masters I Drops Monday🎯 Good evening, Folks! This is Jeff Bishop and work closely with Jeff Williams in the Market Masters Room. Tomorrow I’d like you to join me LIVE at 11AM EST MONDAY for a special market rundown as well as my thoughts behind my Bullseye Pick of the Week. […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 14:12:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>UPS’s stock dives after earnings fall below forecasts, outlook is trimmed</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/upss-stock-dives-after-profit-and-revenue-miss-expectations-full-year-outlook-is-trimmed-33510741?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-07420392</image_url><description>Shares of United Parcel Service Inc. took a dive in early trading Tuesday, after the package delivery giant reported second-quarter earnings that fell below expectations, amid revenue weakness in the domestic business.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 11:48:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GM far exceeds second-quarter estimates, will restructure struggling China business</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/23/general-motors-gm-earnings-q2-2024.html</link><description>GM's North American operations, driven by truck sales, were largely responsible for the company's second-quarter beat and guidance raise.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 11:40:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stock futures are little changed as traders await key earnings reports: Live updates</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/22/stock-market-today-live-updates.html</link><description>The three major indexes were slightly lower on Tuesday ahead of earnings reports from major companies.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 11:52:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eyes on This Momentum Stock! 🔥</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/insider/eyes-on-this-momentum-stock-%f0%9f%94%a5/</link><image_url>https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXfsHn019VnwmfJCZj87xuzaeWBaT__ckWJsu-MFD3ObMxQo_5GC89k9x8bjKBwYBNc9nt2Kxx_VK2eRGKFdyJ8EZaUtmnVPMWKKHt6Aid0WmGOVEjjwRnVkkgIaG5YxzdXZwdneeRbByL-Oy8z8K0tBRcsU?key=jlWHzQzXht1Yq8KsV_XuYA</image_url><description>📈 Join us for LIVE TRADING action all day long in the 📈 Market Master’s trading room Now, at absolutely no cost to our readers ✅Just one click, and you’re in! GM, Jeff here! It looks like the market is trying to stage a comeback on the final day of this week after several rough […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 14:20:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>There’s a risk of a toxic reaction from Fed rate cuts, this bond-market strategist says</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/theres-a-risk-of-a-toxic-reaction-from-fed-rate-cuts-this-bond-market-strategist-says-3b8e5664?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-37876327</image_url><description>Jim Bianco, the president and macro strategist of Bianco Research, says the market and the Fed have two very different ideas on what neutral rates are.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 11:41:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GM indefinitely delays Cruise Origin autonomous vehicle</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/23/gm-cruise-origin-autonomous-vehicle-indefinitely-delayed.html</link><description>General Motors is indefinitely delaying production of its Origin autonomous vehicle as its embattled Cruise self-driving unit attempts to relaunch operations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 11:30:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Harris heads on campaign trail as favorite for Democratic nomination: Live Updates</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/23/live-updates-harris-nomination-biden-endorsements-trump.html</link><description>U.S. Vice President Kamala Harris has won a majority of key Democratic endorsements and formally heads on the campaign trail.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 11:46:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Did you miss boot camp and need a doctor’s note? We got you covered 🎥</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/pennypro/did-you-miss-boot-camp-and-need-a-doctors-note-we-got-you-covered-%f0%9f%8e%a5/</link><image_url>https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXfwINhuJ2-nkiSNdOSokY1XPgUdqNR4_8FfLOtXe9M4gRPVbSbAb2k5MWUz7TT0h42Ra76g6aGykdoJABfPOLXfByIOdBn4UWwOTyL6NR_2gqvrjLYkf0Ucn6jkfstpZ1aZRo4k2EiDYswr3VdKZ-xKRx4x?key=QudxO7LTgvPEtQ4Q__v_qA</image_url><description>💥MARKET NAVIGATOR &amp; ATOMIC TRADES💥 DEAL ENDS @ MIDNIGHT BUNDLE &amp; SAVE BIG HERE! Howdy gang! Jeff Williams (JW) here, did you miss my boot camp earlier this week? I took some time to go over how I try to simplify my options trading in the morning and how I hunt down the best penny […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 19:53:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘I’m not voting’: Why should Donald Trump, Kamala Harris or anyone else make a difference to my finances? I’ll never be able to retire and I’m always broke.</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/im-not-voting-why-should-donald-trump-kamala-harris-or-anyone-else-make-a-difference-to-my-finances-ill-never-be-able-to-retire-and-im-always-broke-b994026b?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-35580339</image_url><description>“I am in my 50s and still renting. I cannot afford to buy a house.”</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coca-Cola is about to report earnings. Here's what Wall Street expects</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/23/coca-cola-ko-q2-2024-earnings.html</link><description>Shares of Coke have risen 9% this year, bringing its market cap up to $282.3 billion.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 11:25:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Porsche shares fall 4% after automaker cuts 2024 outlook on aluminium alloy shortage</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/23/porsche-shares-fall-as-automaker-cuts-2024-outlook-on-aluminium-alloy-shortage.html</link><description>Shares in automaker Porsche fell on Tuesday after the company cut its 2024 outlook, citing a shortage of special aluminium alloys.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 11:45:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Takeovers, mergers and asset purchases</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/takeovers-mergers-and-asset-purchases/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/1022e75f-9694-451c-95ba-14ec0069c5e9/image__1_.png</image_url><description>Good day, 360! Here are our top investing ideas today. And don’t forget to join us in Market Masters – the hottest trading room around 🔥. Be the best prepared trader on the Street! FOCUS LIST🔎 ADTX – Up over 80% in pre after amended merger agreement with Evofem, targeting September 30 closing GDTC – […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 19:12:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The ‘first state’ tops list of best places to retire</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/the-first-state-tops-list-of-best-places-to-retire-6303afeb?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-68956698</image_url><description>Delaware moves up in the rankings, while last year’s best pick, Iowa, falls to ninth place.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 11:27:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>European officials get excited about Kamala Harris — but are still hedging their bets</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/23/us-election-eu-officials-excited-about-kamala-harris.html</link><description>The U.S. election just '"got way more interesting," a senior EU diplomat told CNBC Monday.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 10:35:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Palestinian rivals Hamas and Fatah sign reconciliation agreement in China</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/23/palestinian-rivals-hamas-and-fatah-sign-reconciliation-agreement-in-china-.html</link><description>This is far from the first time the rival groups have signed reconciliation pacts, only to return to hostilities due to persistent disagreements.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 11:43:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gamma Trigger Strikes Again! ⚡</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/gamma-trigger-strikes-again-%e2%9a%a1/</link><image_url>https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXcxvmZ0bf-KWAqv9LzNGfhpW4oAdYlfpEI9_GxcNlSAHZ-6Iuz8NYYmycY4FjwNy430ZmwIptLrj483TxbCaW1mJBGfYdBzj3yQpQT25NDPBYMQfdDrVPJYw9eXrv9ku-nFu9mo7w_na0y3Ol6FGT4YDTYx?key=32S7a6jOz5UOdFFJKBUdXA</image_url><description>Reminder: JW’s Options Class 7ET Did you catch the new long-term lithium play I showed you this morning? That stock ended up 21% higher today. That could be the start, so make sure you keep it on your list. At this price, I think it is a “no-brainer” to at least look into right now. […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 19:27:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Politics could start to matter to markets again as Election Day nears. Here’s what investors will be watching.</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/politics-could-start-to-matter-to-markets-again-as-election-day-nears-heres-what-investors-will-be-watching-1b3d053d?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-68979518</image_url><description>President Joe Biden’s decision not to seek a second term doesn’t appear to be having much of an effect on markets — but that could change once fall arrives and, with it, the final stretch of the presidential campaign.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 11:23:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Farnborough Air Show kicks off with $51 billion in deals as Airbus shows off new ultra long-haul jet</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/23/farnborough-air-show-51-billion-deals-on-day-one-a321xlr-on-show.html</link><description>Airbus flew the A321XLR for the first time since it was certified, but its U.S. rival Boeing dominated on the deal-making front.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 09:29:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Delivery Hero, Glovo targeted in EU cartel investigation</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/23/delivery-hero-glovo-targeted-in-eu-cartel-investigation.html</link><description>EU antitrust regulators have launched a probe into Delivery hero and Glovo on concerns the two firms may have taken part in an online food delivery cartel.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 10:58:20 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>