<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 07:09:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>These META trades highlight an underrated trading strategy…</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/jason-bond/these-meta-trades-highlight-an-underrated-trading-strategy/</link><image_url>https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXe8GxLtTCV3G3eF-NJ45Y_OMOIRwy8iTsWlsivNomfh00KlL-7bNNN2pTkWmdND1GvViPVsiLX3p2WbzK7FZtgkwGrragwnzPDPxxYVZYTacvmhKTLw7ovgEVbwh_XVPLTcIYP3Kq7gFoDb6QSEQJUKa4N6?key=0zDl8IL_UdzsSha7wNhqcw</image_url><description>I tacked on some small wins to my track record yesterday, and it got me thinking: You know what’s an underrated part of any trading strategy? Momentum. As traders, we all struggle with patience. We want the big gains now! We want that CHEDDAR! And fast! But there are no traders or investors on the […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 16:26:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mortgage rates fall, but buyer demand drops to 6-month low</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/mortgage-rates-fall-but-buyer-demand-drops-to-6-month-low-d08482f6?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-86589954</image_url><description>Mortgage applications fell 10.1% in the last week, the Mortgage Bankers Association said.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Inflation has led to a strong U.S. dollar. But that's not always a good thing.</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/21/how-a-strong-dollar-can-backfire-on-american-consumers-businessess.html</link><description>A strong dollar may reflect economic strength, but it can have downsides for American consumers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 11:02:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Macy’s cuts sales forecast as department stores struggle to draw shoppers</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/21/macys-m-q2-2024-earnings.html</link><description>Macy's beat quarterly earnings expectations but it cut its sales forecast for the full year.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 12:03:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Small cap AI stocks are on fire this morning</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/small-cap-ai-stocks-are-on-fire-this-morning/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/1022e75f-9694-451c-95ba-14ec0069c5e9/image__1_.png</image_url><description>*together with Vantage Point Are you tired of trading “alone in a hole?” See JW’s invitation below (happening) tonight and join us any time (FREE) in the Market Masters Room. Emerge from isolation and make some new friends 👬. FOCUS LIST🔎 AUUD – Up over 100% in pre after announcing launch of faidr 3.1 […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 14:18:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vector Group’s stock up 6% on deal to be acquired by Japan’s JT Group in $2.4 billion tobacco deal</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/vector-groups-stock-up-6-after-agreeing-to-be-acquired-by-jt-group-in-2-4-billion-deal-1b5dca0e?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-75213965</image_url><description>JT, which makes and sells some of the best-known cigarette brands — including Winston and Camel outside the U.S. — will pay $15 a share in cash, equal to a 29.9% premium over Vector’s 60-day volume-weighted average share price.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 11:56:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Health-care system Sesame to offer compounded versions of Wegovy through new $249 weight loss program</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/21/sesame-to-offer-compounded-wegovy-through-weight-loss-program.html</link><description>Sesame is offering compounded semaglutide — the active ingredient in Wegovy and Ozempic — to help users access obesity and diabetes treatments amid shortages.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 11:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Pick a number': Strategist says the U.S. dollar will drift much lower against the Japanese yen</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/21/usdjpy-strategist-expects-dollar-to-drift-much-lower-against-the-yen.html</link><description>The U.S. dollar is likely to continue to drift lower against the Japanese yen over the coming months, according to one market strategist.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 11:52:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New obesity drug and Fubo wins injunction against Disney</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/new-obesity-drug-and-fubo-wins-injunction-against-disney/</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f50e.png</image_url><description>*sponsored by TradingTips GM! As usual here are today’s biggest movers. And right now we have a great special going on for ALL our services. Why choose one when you can have them all? Call Davis for more info (1-800-585-4488 / davis@ragingbull.com). P.S. Don’t forget to join us in Market Masters to kick the week […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 15:50:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This S&amp;P 500 hot streak is actually a warning sign for your stocks</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/this-s-p-500-hot-streak-is-actually-a-warning-sign-for-your-stocks-385da1ff?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-861633</image_url><description>15 consecutive quarters of revenue growth for S&amp;P 500 companies — not enough to support current prices.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 11:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jennifer Lopez files for divorce from Ben Affleck</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/21/jennifer-lopez-files-for-divorce-from-ben-affleck.html</link><description>The pair split after more than two decades of playing the on-and-off game.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 08:42:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>China calls EU tariffs on EVs unfair, says it will take necessary measures to defend industry</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/21/china-calls-eu-tariffs-on-evs-unfair-says-it-will-defend-industry.html</link><description>Beijing said it continues to believe the EU's probe into China's subsidies for EVs are promoting unfair competition in the name of fair competition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 11:19:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stalking these Calls on LEN</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/stalking-these-calls-on-len/</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f4aa.png</image_url><description>*together with Vantage Point GM, Folks! Looks like a solid trading week shaping up 💪 . This morning’s Bullseye Idea of the WEEK was Calls on LEN — plan released pre-market to members as always. Join me at 11am ET TODAY for the details as we stalk LEN as well as my full market rundown […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 15:48:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>U.K. competition watchdog drop probes into Google and Apple app stores</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/u-k-competition-watchdog-drop-probes-into-google-and-apple-app-stores-f7fc3ed4?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-83961842</image_url><description>The Competition and Markets Authority said it plans to use new powers given to it in May to address its concerns about abuses of Google and Apple’s dominant market positions</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 11:44:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Michelle Obama: Trump used 'misogynistic, racist lies' to 'try to make people fear us'</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/21/michelle-obama-trump-harris-dnc-election.html</link><description>Michelle Obama drew explicit contrasts between Kamala Harris and Donald Trump.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 06:07:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The world's largest steel industry is going through a 'winter' amid a supply glut and weak demand</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/21/the-worlds-largest-steel-industry-is-going-through-a-winter-amid-a-supply-glut-and-weak-demand-.html</link><description>The Chinese steel industry is caught "between a rock and a hard place" as steel makers' margins are getting increasingly squeezed by weak demand, Bank of America executive said.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 10:15:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Moneyballing the SPY 📊</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/jeff-williams/moneyballing-the-spy-%f0%9f%93%8a/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/431b907b-038a-4010-9804-0cb8fabb1e83/JW_MM_room_image_for_BET.png?t=1723979474</image_url><description>Hi Guys &amp; Gals! Jeff Williams here. You may know me from the daily opening and closing sessions in the Market Master’s Room. Here’s a snapshot of what the room looks like, and me making a LIVE trade alert (also sent out on the app if you can’t be live with me). If you haven’t […]</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 17:20:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>It’s not just stocks — there’s another market reaching into thin air, this banking giant says</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/its-not-just-stocks-theres-another-market-reaching-into-thin-air-this-banking-giant-says-6f3e54ad?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-09026965</image_url><description>The euro has been on a roll even as European data has been underwhelming.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Obama says 'America is ready for a new chapter' with Harris, Walz</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/21/obama-says-america-is-ready-for-a-new-chapter-with-harris-walz.html</link><description>Barack Obama, who preceded Donald Trump in the White House, praised President Joe Biden, who served as his vice president.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 04:55:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ukraine carries out one of the largest ever drone attacks on Moscow as Kursk incursion continues</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/21/ukraine-carries-out-one-of-largest-ever-drone-attacks-on-moscow.html</link><description>The tides of the Russia-Ukraine war, largely carried out through artillery and drone advances, changed earlier this month.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 10:02:07 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>