<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 10:35:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Monkey pox and skincare</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/monkey-pox-and-skincare/</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f50e.png</image_url><description>Here are our top movers today. And don’t forget to join us in the Market Masters Trading Room. And while you’re at it, check out Jason’s Back-to-School special below— only 47 seats remain — back to school equals more time for trading, hell ya! FOCUS LIST🔎 ELAB – Up over 45% in the pre-market after […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 15:26:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>U.S. durable-goods orders rise moderately in July — excluding volatile transportation sector</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/u-s-durable-goods-surge-in-july-on-volatile-transportation-orders-fea3f0aa?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-871080</image_url><description>Orders at U.S. factories for long-lasting goods, such as new cars or machinery, jumped 9.9% in July, beating a 4% forecast. Orders have risen in five of the last six months.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 15:34:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A 'man-made disaster' could make it trickier to buy or sell a home in some areas this fall, real estate expert says</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/26/how-national-flood-insurance-program-deadline-may-affect-home-buyers.html</link><description>Looming expiration for the largest U.S. flood insurance program may hold up some home sales this fall, just as the Federal Reserve is expected to cut interest rates.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 13:44:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dow rallies 200 points to new record, completing comeback from early August rout: Live updates</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/25/stock-futures-are-little-after-fed-signals-rate-cuts-are-imminent.html</link><description>The Dow rallied to a new record high after a winning week for stocks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 15:30:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FAQ’s for $2,000 challenge</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/jason-bond/faqs-for-2000-challenge/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/68125782-323e-44f3-a097-c2126548be30/subscribe.jpg?t=1724522893</image_url><description>Saturday is for setting $2,000 Small Account Journey goals. But first… There are only 100 54 seats left in my BACK TO SCHOOL SALE. Be sure to apply coupon code: SAVE60 The coupon lowers $1,497 yearly to $598 grandfathered Or $2,497 for a 5 year membership to $998 [BEST DEAL] Top 10 FAQ for the $2,000 […]</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 19:41:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Activist Elliott lays out how to fix Southwest Airlines and its stock</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/southwests-stock-gains-after-activist-elliott-lays-out-how-to-fix-the-airline-a3a49a71?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-76714708</image_url><description>Shares of Southwest Airlines Co. got a lift toward a six-week high Monday after activist investor Elliott Management sent a letter to shareholders explaining why the air carrier needs new leadership.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 15:33:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Harris campaign says it has raised $40 million since her convention speech</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/25/harris-campaign-fundraising-dnc-trump-election.html</link><description>The windfall brings the total raised for Harris’ election efforts to $540 million since President Joe Biden dropped out last month.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 10:58:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The end of a dream: What happens when an Olympian's career is over</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/video/2024/08/26/the-end-of-a-dream-what-happens-when-an-olympians-career-is-over.html</link><description>"It's the one inevitability. It doesn't matter how successful you are as an athlete or how long or short your career is. Once you start, the one guarantee is that at some point it will stop," said Katherine Grainger, retired British rower and Chair of UK Sport.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 15:18:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Big growth trading just 5 contracts? (see how)</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/jason-bond/big-growth-trading-just-5-contracts-see-how/</link><image_url>https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXd82rAp1nMJ5kXivwKJfv4qko4k4JcwLjlxxIlBvvrI2RB_uDkGI2GSNexNVjjIUEZxCBODOrl3nGQb95KXUsuzlLz-JVBYIrdXRi6I5ZUbreeLX7LOKiRHCLSw7X2u8Ps5BmycWyJ1pqRo0-MDk8NX3xc?key=rmwVk4-eWN23QTatwO_mTQ</image_url><description>Happy Friday! Rate cut coming in September! Let’s go! When you see a trader post about growing their accounts “fast”, two drawbacks pop in your mind: Taking on a lot of risk Trading big position sizes The theory is you can’t have big rewards without big risks, so finding lots of growth means finding a […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 17:50:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Low-income consumers are still struggling. Now the cracks are starting to show for higher-income ones, survey finds.</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/low-income-consumers-are-still-struggling-now-the-cracks-are-starting-to-show-for-higher-income-ones-survey-finds-82fecf17?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-52155228</image_url><description>Mizuho said Monday its August consumer survey found that low-income consumers, who account for 22% of total U.S. household spending, are continuing to struggle. But the cracks were also starting to show for higher-income consumers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 14:53:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump says Musk wouldn't have time to be in his White House cabinet, but could 'consult'</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/25/trump-elon-musk-white-house-cabinet-election-republicans.html</link><description>Elon Musk and Donald Trump have formed an unlikely alliance ahead of the 2024 election against Kamala Harris.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 23:38:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Who is Telegram founder Pavel Durov — and why was he arrested?</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/26/who-is-telegram-founder-pavel-durov-and-why-was-he-arrested.html</link><description>The chief executive officer of Telegram, Pavel Durov, was arrested and placed in custody for alleged offenses related to the app, sources told AFP.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 15:15:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Big asset sale to QCOM has this tiny cap soaring</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/big-asset-sale-to-qcom-has-this-tiny-cap-soaring/</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f525.png</image_url><description>Good day, 360! Here are our top investing ideas today. And don’t forget to join us in Market Masters – the hottest trading room around 🔥. Be the best prepared trader on the Street! FOCUS LIST🔎 SQNS – Up over 200% in the pre-market after announcing sale of 4G IoT technology to Qualcomm for $200million […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 17:48:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IBM closing research unit in China, Wall Street Journal reports</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/ibm-closing-research-unit-in-china-wsj-fb25b5c5?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-42440456</image_url><description>IBM is reportedly cutting 1,000 jobs after its revenue from China fell nearly 20% in 2023.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 14:47:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Boeing Starliner returning empty as NASA turns to SpaceX to bring astronauts back from ISS</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/24/nasa-boeing-starliner-decision-return-empty-spacex-astronauts-iss.html</link><description>Boeing will return its capsule from the International Space Station without the NASA astronauts that Starliner delivered to orbit.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 21:44:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Russia launches massive missile and drone attack on Ukraine, Kyiv says</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/26/russia-launches-massive-missile-and-drone-attack-on-ukraine-kyiv-says.html</link><description>Power cuts and water supply outages were reported in numerous places, including parts of Kyiv, as officials said the attack targeted critical infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 13:29:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Big new contracts and revenue growth have these stocks moving</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/insider/big-new-contracts-and-revenue-growth-have-these-stocks-moving/</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f3a3.png</image_url><description>*together with Brooks Enterprises Good day, 360! Here are some top movers today! And don’t forget to join us in Market Masters. And see below for news about our All-Access special offer closing soon… what a value! Time to fish or cut bait 🎣. FOCUS LIST🔎 AIRI – Up over 50% in the pre market […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 15:18:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>McKesson to acquire controlling stake in Core Ventures for $2.49 billion in cash</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/mckesson-to-acquire-controlling-stake-in-core-ventures-for-2-49-billion-in-cash-08754090?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-02803550</image_url><description>McKesson said it hopes to “bring advanced treatments and improved care experiences to patients, while also reducing the overall cost of care.”</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 13:47:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dozens of colleges see financial aid turmoil impacting freshman class makeups</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/24/dozens-of-colleges-see-financial-aid-turmoil-impacting-freshman-class-makeups.html</link><description>Education Secretary Miguel Cardona vows “to do better” as administrators say this year’s FAFSA debacle is already leaving its mark on campuses.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 20:06:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Israel-Hezbollah escalation has arrived. What next for the Middle East?</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/26/the-israel-hezbollah-escalation-has-arrived-what-next-for-the-middle-east.html</link><description>A series of cross-border attacks between Israel and Hezbollah over the weekend sparked fears of a wider regional conflict, but an "all-out war" appears to have been averted, for now.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 12:19:37 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>