<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 06:57:01 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Strong earnings have traders eyeing these stocks</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/strong-earnings-have-traders-eyeing-these-stocks/</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f525.png</image_url><description>Good day, 360! Here are our top investing ideas today. And don’t forget to join us in Market Masters – the hottest trading room around 🔥. Be the best prepared trader on the Street! FOCUS LIST🔎 AISP – Up over 25% in pre after reporting better than expected earnings BLRX – Up over 7% […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 15:41:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>History shows investors should keep a tight leash on risk once the Fed cuts rates, strategist says</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/history-shows-investors-should-keep-a-tight-leash-on-risk-once-the-fed-cuts-rates-strategist-says-085ddf09?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-38955431</image_url><description>Trimming stock positions depends on the reason for the Fed reducing borrowing costs</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:33:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ford upgrades Lincoln Navigator to include spa mode, 48-inch display for videos and gaming</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/15/ford-2025-lincoln-navigator-spa-mode-48-inch-display-for-gaming.html</link><description>The new features come as the automaker has redesigned the exterior and interior of the Lincoln Navigator for the 2025 model year.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:54:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bayer shares soar 12% after key U.S. legal win against Roundup cancer claims</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/16/bayer-shares-soar-after-us-legal-win-against-roundup-cancer-claims.html</link><description>Bayer shares rose as the company said it scored a legal victory in its suit over claims that exposure to its popular Roundup weed killer led to cancer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Earnings Surprise: A BIG Day Ahead ⚡</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/earnings-surprise-a-big-day-ahead-%e2%9a%a1/</link><image_url>https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXc3pLn0h-4ZzHgvO4WTQTIV-9Yh_i5YcnA5O-cvRgk_qvrERGH-zXvHdvvA4RuEGMMHG0DXpY14b8Py7uWk2LpIixn889iUfDF4WVvp04tm1g8cV852ZUIR4E3dNgPuAZPZiJWc6j6Tcor7g1MlIjpPivaU?key=zeUTABTn7nsyu8_tIqkASQ</image_url><description>NOW OPEN: Interactive Live Streaming Trade Room Real-time trading, detailed education on options and penny stocks available to you RIGHT NOW at no cost. Enter the room and trade with us! We are at a pivotal time for the market right now. We just witnessed the fastest volatility decline ever while the markets miraculously […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 15:39:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Revolut share sale values U.K. fintech at $45 billion ahead of planned IPO</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/revolut-share-sale-values-u-k-fintech-at-45-billion-ahead-of-planned-ipo-bd3f5056?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-51439200</image_url><description>Revolut on Friday said a secondary share sale was set at valuation of $45 billion, making it Europe’s most valuable privately-owned technology company.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Columbia University president resigns months after Israel-Hamas war protests roiled campus</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/14/columbia-university-president-quits-months-after-handling-of-gaza-war-protests.html</link><description>Columbia University President Minouche Shafik said she resigned on Wednesday, nearly four months after overseeing the university's handling of campus protests over Israel's war in Gaza.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 00:27:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Europe stocks higher to round off winning week; Sterling gains after slew of UK data</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/16/europe-stocks-head-for-higher-open-to-round-off-winning-week.html</link><description>European stocks were higher as the Stoxx 600 index continues to climb.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:41:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New CEOs and positive earnings have these stocks moving</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/commentary/new-ceos-and-positive-earnings-have-these-stocks-moving/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/1022e75f-9694-451c-95ba-14ec0069c5e9/image__1_.png</image_url><description>Good day, 360! Here are our top investing ideas today. And TODAY, Jason is opening up the Roadmap Room for live trading with him today at 12EST. Bring your lunch 🥪 and your market optimism! FOCUS LIST🔎 VIRX – Up over 20% in the pre-market after reporting Q2 financial results and positive Phase 2 data […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:18:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘He’s taunting me’: I loaned my son $30,000 to buy a house in 2012. I need it back. He says ‘the five-year window’ for repayment has closed. What can I do?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/hes-taunting-me-i-loaned-my-son-30-000-to-buy-a-house-in-2012-i-need-it-back-he-says-the-five-year-window-for-repayment-has-closed-what-can-i-do-4ea51c07?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-57006074</image_url><description>“I live off a modest pension and Social Security. I love my house, but it needs upgrading.”</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 10:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Harris to endorse protections for renters and removal of key tax benefits for Wall St. investors buying homes</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/15/harris-to-endorse-protections-for-renters-and-removal-of-key-tax-benefits-for-wall-st-investors-buying-homes.html</link><description>Harris has begun to provide details about her policy positions after abruptly becoming the Democratic nominee.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 00:24:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alibaba, JD.com results underscore the slowdown in Chinese consumer demand</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/16/alibaba-jdcom-results-underscore-the-slowdown-in-chinese-consumer-demand.html</link><description>Second-quarter results from Chinese e-commerce giants Alibaba and JD.com indicate a weak market, with domestic and foreign players struggling to attract customers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 10:49:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Big partnerships and earnings have these stocks moving</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/big-partnerships-and-earnings-have-these-stocks-moving/</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f525.png</image_url><description>Good day, 360! Here are our top investing ideas today. And don’t forget to join us in Market Masters – the hottest trading room around 🔥. Be the best prepared trader on the Street! FOCUS LIST🔎 CXAI – Up over 50% in the pre-market after announcing Q2 earnings and largest “expansion” deal and strategic multi-year […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 16:14:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘I want so badly to help her’: My girlfriend made a $60,000 ‘error of judgment’ at work. Should I take out a HELOC or dip into my 401(k) to bail her out?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/i-want-so-badly-to-help-her-my-girlfriend-made-a-60-000-error-of-judgment-at-work-should-i-take-out-a-heloc-or-dip-into-my-401-k-to-bail-her-out-edc7ac5f?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-43309268</image_url><description>“If she doesn’t repay the money, she believes she will lose her $100,000 job and possibly be sued for the $60,000.”</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 10:29:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cisco shares have best day since 2020 on earnings beat, plans to cut 7% of workforce</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/15/cisco-stock-has-best-day-since-2020-on-earnings-beat-7percent-job-cuts.html</link><description>Cisco shares jumped on Thursday and were on pace for their best day since November 2020, after the networking company announced layoffs and an earnings beat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 21:32:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>After medic's rape and murder, Indian doctors stage 24-hour nationwide strike</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/16/after-medics-rape-and-murder-indian-doctors-stage-24-hour-nationwide-strike.html</link><description>The Indian Medical Association has called for a suspension of non-emergency medical services from Saturday 6 am local time.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 09:42:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This tiny cap is soaring after winning its appeal 💪</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/this-tiny-cap-is-soaring-after-winning-its-appeal-%f0%9f%92%aa/</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f50e.png</image_url><description>Good day, 360! Here are our top movers today. And don’t forget to join us in Market Masters all day today. Jeff Bishop will be LIVE in there at 11AM with Bullseye Trades so get in there and… be the best prepared trader on the Street! FOCUS LIST🔎 TRNR – Up over 50% in the […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:24:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘Not tipping 20% makes you look like a fascist’: Why has tipping, once branded as un-American and anti-democratic, become such a hot political issue?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/not-tipping-20-makes-you-look-like-a-fascist-why-has-tipping-once-branded-as-un-american-and-anti-democratic-become-such-a-hot-political-issue-2c6faa14?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-88436405</image_url><description>Tipped workers may comprise only 2.5% of the workforce, but all of us are tippers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 10:27:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg receives letter from lawmakers concerned about illicit drug ads on Facebook and Instagram</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/15/lawmakers-letter-to-meta-ceo-mark-zuckerberg-about-illicit-drug-ads.html</link><description>A bipartisan group of lawmakers sent Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg a letter expressing concern about illicit drug advertisements running on the company's apps.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 21:27:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Japan's Nikkei soars over 3% to clock best week in 4 years amid a broad rally in Asia markets</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/16/asia-markets.html</link><description>Traders in Asia digested non-oil exports data from Singapore, which massively beat Reuters' poll expectations</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 08:39:46 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>