<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 01:05:43 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>“Worst July in 10 Years” – but my positions went ⬆️</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/worst-july-in-10-years-but-my-positions-went-%e2%ac%86%ef%b8%8f/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/c74d1bed-6b1f-4630-8a05-e0f14c49ea4f/image__8_.png?t=1722614624</image_url><description>*sponsored by Hey gang, Jeff Bishop here! In the online world, they call it “blackpilling”. That’s when you take a completely negative view of everything. The whole “What’s the point?!” attitude. In July, a lot of traders were feeling that. We had our worst market day in 2 years. And when you tally it all […]</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 12:38:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>U.S. stock futures and crypto prices sink after a painful week on Wall Street</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/u-s-stock-futures-slide-further-after-a-wild-week-on-wall-street-640e7707?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-43469387</image_url><description>U.S. stock-market futures fell late Sunday, after a volatile week on Wall Street that saw the Nasdaq fall into correction territory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 04:09:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How sustainable diaper brand Kudos is taking on industry giants — with a Target rollout</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/04/kudos-sustainable-diapers-target-stores.html</link><description>Kudos has sought to make a better, more sustainable diaper that uses cotton instead of plastic in its bid to disrupt the consumer products industry.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 22:55:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Japan stocks plunge over 8%, hovering near bear market territory, as Asia shares extend sell-off</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/05/asia-markets.html</link><description>Investors will look toward key trade data from China and Taiwan this week, as well as central bank decisions from Australia and India.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 05:35:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Did I Trade Today’s Bloodbath</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/how-did-i-trade-todays-bloodbath/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/56e2d078-2f06-4e6c-a921-51aa41c79225/image__8_.png?t=1722609683</image_url><description>*sponsored by Good morning, Guys &amp; Gals! JW here. Questions for you: Are you struggling in these red markets? Are you in need of options education? Do you overtrade daily or often? Are you a BUSY trader who can’t spend all day watching trades? If you answered YES to any or all of these then […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 17:20:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>China’s Caixin PMI signals pickup in services-sector activity</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/china-caixin-pmi-signals-pickup-in-services-sector-activity-update-91c832eb?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://www.marketwatch.com/rss/marketwatch.gif</image_url><description>A private gauge of China’s services sector signaled that activity expanded at a faster pace in July compared with a month ago, in contrast with the trend seen in official data.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 03:49:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why pharmacy chains like Walgreens and CVS are shuttering locations</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/04/why-pharmacy-chains-like-walgreens-and-cvs-are-shuttering-locations.html</link><description>Walgreens is citing macro issues, like a worsening consumer environment and pressure on pharmacy margins, while grappling with its own set of issues.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 17:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>High temperatures scorch China, spiking power demand</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/05/high-temperatures-scorch-china-spiking-power-demand.html</link><description>The national weather forecaster on Monday cautioned of potential fire hazards caused by excessive power consumption and excessive electrical loads.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 05:32:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to try and grow $2,000</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/how-to-try-and-grow-2000/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/9926d431-4b45-4e72-944d-4b459d9bb9ed/HubSpot-logo-color-LynseyMcHugh.png?t=1722528788</image_url><description>*sponsored by Hi guys and gals. For the better part of 18-months I’ve been working on a service I call the $2,000 Small Account Journey. This is an options trading blueprint for small accounts. While some of my $2,000 balances haven’t gone up a lot, or even down, I’ve been able run one to […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 18:57:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stock-market investors went from cheering a ‘Goldilocks’ economy to fearing recession. Here’s what’s next.</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/stock-market-investors-went-from-cheering-a-goldilocks-economy-to-fearing-recession-heres-whats-next-cb754e50?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-62291712</image_url><description>Stock-market investors have spent most of 2024 celebrating a ”Goldilocks” economy running neither too hot nor too cold. A run of weak U.S. economic data to begin August is now stoking fears that the bears have come home.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 01:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ex-Trump White House officials, dozens of Republicans endorse Harris</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/04/trump-white-house-kamala-harris-election.html</link><description>Kamala Harris has surged in polls since President Joe Biden dropped out and endorsed her in July.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 16:09:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>UBS says 'going into Japan now is like catching a falling knife,' warns stock sell-off will continue</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/05/japans-stock-sell-off-will-continue-as-yen-strengthens-ubs.html</link><description>The Nikkei 225 and the Topix extended their declines, falling past 7% on the day, and hovering close to bear market territory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 05:20:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chinese co makes remote robot surgery breakthrough</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/insider/chinese-co-makes-remote-robot-surgery-breakthrough/</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f525.png</image_url><description>Good day, 360! Here are our top investing ideas today. And don’t forget to join us in Market Masters – the hottest trading room around 🔥. Be the best prepared trader on the Street! FOCUS LIST🔎 AMD – Up over 8% in pre, after reporting better than expected earnings and raised forecast on the back […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 16:40:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Corporate profit growth is on pace for its best quarter since just before 2022’s inflation spell</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/corporate-profit-growth-is-on-pace-for-its-best-quarter-since-just-before-2022s-inflation-spell-53d87996?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-82382833</image_url><description>After last week’s quarterly-results megastorm, second-quarter earnings season is roughly three-quarters of the way through.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 01:37:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Retiring Corvette 'godfather' on EVs, spinoff and a performance SUV</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/04/retiring-corvette-godfather-on-evs-spinoff-and-a-performance-suv.html</link><description>The "godfather" of GM's modern day Corvettes Tadge Juechter retired Wednesday after roughly 47 years with the automaker, including 31 years devoted to Corvette.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 14:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>No passports needed: Singapore launches biometric immigration processing at Changi Airport</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/05/no-passports-needed-singapore-launches-biometric-processing-at-airport.html</link><description>Singapore launches trials for travelers to clear immigration at Changi Airport using biometric data in lieu of passport checks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 04:58:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Market Turnaround: What’s Hot Right Now 🔥</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/market-turnaround-whats-hot-right-now-%f0%9f%94%a5/</link><image_url>https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXcRqfDCYQVcWARRAFx1q6g11-hvj9uRFP_dSJUkUxZhJzxCOmEc9DjhsuSNR1K5l7QXCk2fpV3xUT4CUanmpIReZgh12jG8RD6mM8vw07lOOSuytVQiD-f0vL1-8WqF5gIQE-tcr6AL4SsauurOepflkm1P?key=j6FwfEEb-ONODqctQtifUA</image_url><description>Good evening, Folks. Jeff Bishop here! I don’t know about you, but Friday sure felt like a great way for me to end the week. It was a very choppy week, and a few trades didn’t go my way, but when I saw the market start to turn the corner on Friday, I knew it […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 13:53:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A viral chart suggests a recession is coming after the Fed cuts interest rates — but don’t panic yet</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/a-viral-chart-suggests-a-recession-is-coming-after-the-fed-cuts-interest-rates-but-dont-panic-yet-52bd9794?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-31384480</image_url><description>A viral chart made the rounds on social media showing the correlation to recessions and peak interest rates.</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 23:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A little-known law has forced more than 120,000 veterans to return payouts they received to leave the military, new data shows</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/03/more-than-120000-veterans-return-payouts-due-to-federal-law.html</link><description>A federal law forced thousands of disabled veterans over the years to return the sizeable payouts they received to leave the military.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 20:38:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Taiwan under pressure to bolster its defense as Trump-Harris presidential race stokes policy concerns</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/05/taiwan-under-pressure-to-bolster-defense-amid-trump-harris-election-race.html</link><description>Experts say that Taiwan is under more pressure to build up its defense capabilities and deterrence in the face of uncertainty in the upcoming U.S. elections.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 04:57:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>