<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 15:50:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Great earnings have these stocks firing</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/great-earnings-have-these-stocks-firing/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/1022e75f-9694-451c-95ba-14ec0069c5e9/image__1_.png</image_url><description>*sponsored by The Market Master’s Trading Room is open today but will be a little quiet, as we mourn the loss of JW’s stock market faithful companion, Bentley. Although Bentley could not “legally” tell someone to buy or sell a stock, a bark or two from him when JW was digging in it gave you […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 16:32:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rocket Lab’s Archimedes engine test ‘a significant catalyst’ for new Neutron rocket, Cantor says</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/rocket-labs-archimedes-engine-test-a-significant-catalyst-for-new-neutron-rocket-cantor-says-33246374?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-76307893</image_url><description>Rocket Lab reported a 71% second-quarter revenue hike after the market close Thursday. The company also said that it successfully fired its Archimedes engine for the first time. Rocket Lab shares are up 14.6% Friday.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 20:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wall Street will get key insight on the consumer, inflation in the week ahead as recession fears swirl</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/09/wall-street-will-get-key-insight-on-the-consumer-inflation-in-the-week-ahead-as-recession-fears-swirl.html</link><description>With growth concerns moving to the fore, how the U.S. consumer is faring could be key to understanding what's next for markets and the economy.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 20:45:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>S&amp;P 500 rises, sharply curtails week's losses in major comeback from rout: Live updates</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/08/stock-market-today-live-updates.html</link><description>The S&amp;P 500 managed to erase its losses for the week.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 20:49:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Major players are buying puts. Why?</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/major-players-are-buying-puts-why/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/f6b0f870-08e8-4670-8536-5c31a102981f/image__14_.png?t=1723125974</image_url><description>*sponsored by We haven’t seen this since the-pandemic-that-shall-not-be-named. My trading partner Taiku pointed something out to me Tuesday that really opened my eyes to what’s going on in the markets. Yeah, we had a big sell-off earlier this week and the VIX spiked. But that’s not the real story… the VIX gradually went back down […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 18:33:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oil prices snap streak of 4 straight losing weeks</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/oil-prices-on-track-to-snap-streak-of-4-straight-losing-weeks-91fa214e?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-61265597</image_url><description>Worries over the U.S. economic outlook eased and traders braced for potential retaliatory strikes by Iran and its proxies against Israel after the assassination of a top Hamas official in Tehran last week.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 20:38:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jeremy Siegel backs off on calls for the Fed to do an emergency interest rate cut</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/08/jeremy-siegel-backs-off-on-calls-for-fed-to-do-an-emergency-rate-cut.html</link><description>Siegel no longer thinks it's vital for an emergency interest rate reduction, but still wants policymakers to cut quickly and aggressively.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 20:36:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Plane with 62 people aboard crashes in fiery wreck in Brazil's Sao Paulo state</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/09/plane-crash-brazil-sao-paulo-vinhedo.html</link><description>The firefighters corps confirmed that the plane fell in the city of Vinhedo, but did not offer more details.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 20:37:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AstraZeneca partners with tiny Biotech</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/astrazeneca-partners-with-tiny-biotech/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/429efb2a-1efa-4c3e-a6fb-b3e7aa96593b/Screenshot_2024-07-08_at_10.10.56_AM.png?t=1723119686</image_url><description>*together with Brooks Enterprises Good day, 360! Here are our TOP movers today. And don’t forget to join us in Market Masters Trading Room. Even freeloaders are welcome… FOCUS LIST🔎 CDT – up over 100% in the pre-market after entering into exclusive license agreement with AstraZeneca for multiple assets to advance potential first-in-class treatments WENA […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 14:39:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Steak, dinner and more men: These have been keys to Sweetgreen’s recent growth</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/steak-dinner-and-more-men-these-have-been-keys-to-sweetgreens-recent-growth-910eb0ca?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-53094770</image_url><description>Sweetgreen’s stock soars as a key sales-growth metric reaches its highest level in two years and new initiatives pay off.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 20:23:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stellantis laying off 2,450 plant workers due to discontinuation of Ram 'Classic' pickup truck</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/09/stellantis-layoff-workers-ram-pickup-truck.html</link><description>Stellantis will indefinitely lay off up to 2,450 U.S. plant workers later this year as it discontinues production of an older version of its Ram 1500 pickup.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 19:37:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Markets no longer think the Fed needs to be as aggressive with interest rate cuts</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/09/markets-no-longer-think-the-fed-needs-to-be-as-aggressive-with-rate-cuts.html</link><description>Market pricing points to about a coin flip between the probability of a quarter-point or half-point reduction in September.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 20:36:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Here is How I Made a DASH for Profits Today</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/here-is-how-i-made-a-dash-for-profits-today/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/7d541802-61eb-49e7-b9e0-f72fd3e7e0d5/image__11_.png?t=1723059136</image_url><description>*sponsored by Man, what a day! If you are a Bullseye Unlimited member, you saw this email in your inbox this morning. Then, I hope you jumped in the Alpha Chamber with me and my members LIVE to stalk my top idea today – DoorDash (DASH)… (Just look at all that action in the […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 03:59:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Boeing bondholders get defensive ahead of potential downgrade to junk</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/boeing-bondholders-get-defensive-ahead-of-potential-downgrade-to-junk-2ff5d84e?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-59068556</image_url><description>Boeing’s bondholders have adopted a defensive trade in the last week of selling certain longer-dated notes and buying other, more recently issued bonds that will pay them more if the aerospace giant’s credit is downgraded.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 20:06:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10-year Treasury yield dips as traders weigh state of U.S. economy after latest data</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/09/10-year-treasury-yield-dips-after-jobs-data-fuels-stock-rally.html</link><description>U.S. Treasury yields were slightly lower early Friday as investors continue to assess weekly jobless claims data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 19:24:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jeremy Siegel backs off on calls for the Fed to do an emergency interest rate cut</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/08/jeremy-siegel-backs-off-on-calls-for-fed-to-do-an-emergency-rate-cut.html</link><description>Siegel no longer thinks it's vital for an emergency interest rate reduction, but still wants policymakers to cut quickly and aggressively.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 20:36:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Earnings beats and Lumen continues its big run</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/earnings-beats-and-lumen-continues-its-big-run/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/02d374ec-cfab-48b6-bc0d-765dd58bbe50/masterworks_logo.png?t=1722955325</image_url><description>*sponsored by Good day, 360! Here are our top investing ideas today. And don’t forget to join us in Market Masters – the hottest trading room around 🔥. Be the best prepared trader on the Street! *sponsored by MasterWorks Billionaires wanted it, but 54,578 everyday investors got it first… and profited When incredibly rare and […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 17:31:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elizabeth Warren probes student-loan transfer that tanked borrowers’ credit scores</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/warren-probes-student-loan-transfer-that-tanked-borrowers-credit-scores-1df9bad4?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-19241528</image_url><description>The letter to student-loan servicers and credit-reporting agencies is the latest example of scrutiny from the U.S. senator and consumer advocates.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 19:59:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump says he should get a say on Federal Reserve interest rate decisions</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/08/trump-says-he-should-get-a-say-on-federal-reserve-interest-rate-decisions.html</link><description>The comments seem to reinforce reporting earlier this year that advisors close to Trump are looking at a host of changes for the Fed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 19:22:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bitcoin bounces back above $60,000 as cryptocurrency's rise continues to end week: CNBC Crypto World</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/video/2024/08/09/bitcoin-bounces-back-above-60000-cryptocurrency-rise-continues-end-week-cnbc-crypto-world.html</link><description>CNBC Crypto World features the latest news and daily trading updates from the digital currency markets and provides viewers with a look at what's ahead with high-profile interviews, explainers, and unique stories from the ever-changing crypto industry. On today's show, Ben McMillan, chief investment officer of IDX Digital Assets, weighs in on this week's volatility and Resy co-founder Ben Leventhal explains how his new web3 project would allow for diners to pay for meals in crypto.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 20:21:34 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>