<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 06:56:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>New CEOs and positive earnings have these stocks moving</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/commentary/new-ceos-and-positive-earnings-have-these-stocks-moving/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/1022e75f-9694-451c-95ba-14ec0069c5e9/image__1_.png</image_url><description>Good day, 360! Here are our top investing ideas today. And TODAY, Jason is opening up the Roadmap Room for live trading with him today at 12EST. Bring your lunch 🥪 and your market optimism! FOCUS LIST🔎 VIRX – Up over 20% in the pre-market after reporting Q2 financial results and positive Phase 2 data […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:18:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Most American retirees wouldn’t be able to replace Social Security on their own</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/happy-birthday-social-security-lets-not-rush-to-blow-out-your-candles-f7acd8f4?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-345319</image_url><description>On its 89th birthday, Social Security remains Americans’ primary source for retirement income.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 11:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>White House says negotiated prices for Medicare drugs will save U.S. $6 billion, beneficiaries $1.5 billion in first year</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/15/medicare-releases-prices-for-first-10-drugs-subject-to-negotiations.html</link><description>It is a milestone in a controversial process that aims to make costly medications more affordable for older Americans but is strongly opposed by drugmakers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 11:14:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alibaba shares dip 3% after quarterly earnings miss expectations despite cloud acceleration</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/15/alibaba-shares-dip-3percent-after-quarterly-earnings-miss-expectations-despite-cloud-acceleration.html</link><description>Alibaba continues to face headwinds in its core e-commerce business amid rising competition and a cautious Chinese consumer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 11:43:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Big partnerships and earnings have these stocks moving</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/big-partnerships-and-earnings-have-these-stocks-moving/</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f525.png</image_url><description>Good day, 360! Here are our top investing ideas today. And don’t forget to join us in Market Masters – the hottest trading room around 🔥. Be the best prepared trader on the Street! FOCUS LIST🔎 CXAI – Up over 50% in the pre-market after announcing Q2 earnings and largest “expansion” deal and strategic multi-year […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 16:14:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deere’s stock pops premarket after earnings sweep past lowered estimates</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/deeres-stock-pops-premarket-after-earnings-sweep-past-estimates-fb0ae82a?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-91953140</image_url><description>Deere &amp; Co.’s stock rose 4% early Thursday, after the agricultural and construction machinery maker swept past lowered earnings estimates for its fiscal third quarter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 11:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Inside the $93 million Wall Street heist that stemmed from Russia</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/15/inside-the-93-million-wall-street-heist-that-stemmed-from-russia.html</link><description>CNBC podcast "The Crimes of Putin's Trader" recounts the rise and fall of Vladislav Klyushin and his business empire. He was just released from a U.S. prison in a prisoner swap.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 11:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adyen tops profit forecast on market expansion and slower hiring, shares jump</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/15/adyen-tops-profit-forecast-on-market-expansion-and-slower-hiring-shares-jump.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 10:16:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This tiny cap is soaring after winning its appeal 💪</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/this-tiny-cap-is-soaring-after-winning-its-appeal-%f0%9f%92%aa/</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f50e.png</image_url><description>Good day, 360! Here are our top movers today. And don’t forget to join us in Market Masters all day today. Jeff Bishop will be LIVE in there at 11AM with Bullseye Trades so get in there and… be the best prepared trader on the Street! FOCUS LIST🔎 TRNR – Up over 50% in the […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:24:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Three different factors could trigger the third wave of a stock market pullback, says strategist</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/three-different-factors-could-trigger-the-third-wave-of-a-stock-market-pullback-says-strategist-1225820b?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-17605687</image_url><description>Dhaval Joshi, chief strategist of BCA Research’s Counterpoint service, says an analysis of the “price complexity” shows that the yen carry trade and the AI bubble are one and the same trade, and that any of three factors could torpedo it.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 11:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Columbia University president resigns months after Israel-Hamas war protests roiled campus</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/14/columbia-university-president-quits-months-after-handling-of-gaza-war-protests.html</link><description>Columbia University President Minouche Shafik said she resigned on Wednesday, nearly four months after overseeing the university's handling of campus protests over Israel's war in Gaza.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 02:34:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ukraine must decide how its Russian incursion ends — advance further or retreat before it's too late</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/15/how-will-ukraines-incursion-into-russia-end.html</link><description>Ukraine must decide whether to try to hold or advance its incursion, or to withdraw now before Russia mounts what could be a furious and deadly response.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 09:43:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Great earnings have these stocks firing</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/great-earnings-have-these-stocks-firing/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/1022e75f-9694-451c-95ba-14ec0069c5e9/image__1_.png</image_url><description>*sponsored by The Market Master’s Trading Room is open today but will be a little quiet, as we mourn the loss of JW’s stock market faithful companion, Bentley. Although Bentley could not “legally” tell someone to buy or sell a stock, a bark or two from him when JW was digging in it gave you […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 16:32:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I have my RMD all figured out, except for one thing: Which investments should I take it from?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/i-have-my-rmd-all-figured-out-except-for-one-thing-which-investments-should-i-take-it-from-9e35bcf5?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-05459996</image_url><description>If you don’t specify exactly what you want to do, your bank may pull your required minimum distribution equally from all your holdings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 11:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Starbucks is giving incoming CEO Brian Niccol $85 million in cash and stock as he departs Chipotle</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/14/starbucks-new-ceo-brian-niccol-compensation-chipotle.html</link><description>Starbucks plans to pay incoming CEO Brian Niccol $10 million in cash and $75 million in equity awards when he joins the company from Chipotle.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 01:16:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wizz Air launches $550 'all you can fly' annual subscription pass</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/14/wizz-air-launches-550-all-you-can-fly-annual-subscription-pass.html</link><description>Travelers in Europe can now take unlimited flights for 499 euros ($550) a year under a new travel subscription service from budget carrier Wizz Air.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 09:40:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Major players are buying puts. Why?</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/major-players-are-buying-puts-why/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/f6b0f870-08e8-4670-8536-5c31a102981f/image__14_.png?t=1723125974</image_url><description>*sponsored by We haven’t seen this since the-pandemic-that-shall-not-be-named. My trading partner Taiku pointed something out to me Tuesday that really opened my eyes to what’s going on in the markets. Yeah, we had a big sell-off earlier this week and the VIX spiked. But that’s not the real story… the VIX gradually went back down […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 18:33:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>6 ways to build a successful retirement</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/6-ways-to-build-a-successful-retirement-3ec635b1?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-67222760</image_url><description>What people in their 50s, 60s and 70s should know about navigating life after work</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 11:25:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump packs economic speech with personal attacks on Harris</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/14/trump-economy-speech-north-carolina.html</link><description>The speech came as the Trump campaign retools its message after President Joe Biden withdrew his reelection bid and endorsed Harris as his replacement.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 00:08:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>European markets higher as investors digest UK growth, cooler-than-expected U.S. inflation</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/15/european-markets-updates-stocks-news-inflation-data-and-earnings.html</link><description>European stocks opened higher Thursday as investors digest cooler-than-expected inflation readings in the U.S and U.K.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 09:39:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>