<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 11:03:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Monday Q&amp;A for members</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/monday-qa-for-members/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/d1503f5a-978b-410e-b6b6-b3b08d1d21ac/image.png</image_url><description>Good morning RagingBull family! Jeff Bishop here. I know Jason has been messaging you, but I’m taking over today and here’s why: I’m receiving questions from members. Questions specific to the agendas of Jason Bond and myself in our new and highest-tier program, Black Label. Many are interested in a few specific topics… Allow me […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 15:34:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oil extends strong start to 2025 on signs of strong demand for Mideast crude</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/oil-extends-strong-start-to-2025-on-signs-of-strong-demand-for-mideast-crude-3fd4b1e3?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-15873065</image_url><description>Oil futures rose Monday, looking to build on recent strength that saw crude end at nearly three-month highs last week, boosted by hopes around further stimulus from China and signs of strong demand for Middle Eastern crude.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 15:35:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amazon's Ring announces smart smoke alarm as CES tech palooza kicks off</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2025/01/06/amazons-ring-announces-smart-smoke-alarm-as-ces-kicks-off.html</link><description>Kidde and Ring will launch two models in April, along with a $5-per-month smoke monitoring subscription service.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 15:49:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Europe stocks pare gains, autos cool as Trump denies tariff report; Chip stocks climb</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2025/01/06/european-markets-live-updates-stocks-news-data-and-earnings.html</link><description>European markets were higher on Monday, driven by technology and automotive stocks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 15:53:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This stock is tearing off shorts faces on no news</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/this-stock-is-tearing-off-shorts-faces-on-no-news/</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f50e.png</image_url><description>Happy New Year, 360! Here are some of our top movers today! And if you read this email, you can’t miss Jeff’s 2024 Bullseye pricing is still in effect… but only for a few more days!!! Get in there and be the best prepared trader on the Street! FOCUS LIST🔎 TGL – Up over 300% […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 15:49:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nvidia’s stock heads for record close as AI chip trade reloads for fresh run higher</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/nvidias-stock-heads-for-record-close-as-ai-chip-trade-reloads-for-fresh-run-higher-d5dd2961?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-68948140</image_url><description>Foxconn earnings offer upbeat signs about the Blackwell ramp, and Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang’s upcoming CEO keynote could further support the semiconductor sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 15:25:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lucid reports record quarterly vehicle deliveries, meets production target</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2025/01/06/lucid-deliveries-q4-2024.html</link><description>Lucid Group on Monday reported record quarterly vehicle deliveries for the fourth quarter and confirmed production of more than 9,000 vehicles in 2024.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 15:44:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump lawyers seek to block sentencing in New York hush money case with appeal</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2025/01/06/trump-appeal-new-york-hush-money-sentencing.html</link><description>A New York judge last week rejected a request by President-elect Trump to dismiss a case where he was found guilty of falsifying business records.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 15:44:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Takeovers, drones and reverse splits to kick off the New Year</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/takeovers-drones-and-reverse-splits-to-kick-off-the-new-year/</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f50e.png</image_url><description>Happy New Year, 360! Here are some of our top movers today! And if you read this email, you can’t miss Jeff’s 2024 Bullseye pricing is still in effect… but only for a few more days!!! Get in there and be the best prepared trader on the Street! FOCUS LIST🔎 VSME – up over 50% […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 16:56:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GrabAGun names Donald Trump Jr. as adviser in bid to lift stock-listing visibility</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/grabagun-names-donald-trump-jr-as-adviser-in-bid-to-lift-stock-listing-visibility-49bd5e0d?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-65607814</image_url><description>GrabAGun on Monday named Donald J. Trump Jr. an adviser and announced he will be an equity shareholder once the online gun retailer goes public in the coming months to become the latest stock with direct involvement from the Trump family.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 15:13:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump lawyers seek to block sentencing in New York hush money case with appeal</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2025/01/06/trump-appeal-new-york-hush-money-sentencing.html</link><description>A New York judge last week rejected a request by President-elect Trump to dismiss a case where he was found guilty of falsifying business records.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 15:44:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dow rises more than 200 points, Nvidia leads chip stocks higher: Live updates</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2025/01/05/stock-market-today-live-updates.html</link><description>Chip stocks led the broader market gains after Foxconn announced record fourth-quarter revenue.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 15:39:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>💥Ended the year with something new</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/%f0%9f%92%a5ended-the-year-with-something-new/</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f3af.png</image_url><description>Hey Folks, Jeff here with a RECAP on yesterday’s Bullseye. With the BIG market drop on Friday and gap DOWN Monday morning, I waited for things to settle down a bit before settling on my #1 Pick of the Week. With the major indexes getting whacked the last couple of days, I was not […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 18:15:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>These government workers will benefit after Biden signs new Social Security law</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/congress-passed-the-social-security-fairness-act-millions-of-people-could-see-more-in-benefits-as-a-result-b7f91740?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-34527987</image_url><description>President Joe Biden signed a bill on Sunday that will repeal two laws previously preventing many public employees from receiving Social Security benefits.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 15:06:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump reportedly considering important alteration to tariff plans</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2025/01/06/trump-reportedly-considering-important-alteration-to-tariff-plans.html</link><description>President-elect Donald Trump is considering a plan that still would apply tariffs to all nations but narrow the impact.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 15:16:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Global chip stocks climb as Foxconn's bumper results show a continuation of the AI boom</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2025/01/06/global-chip-stocks-climb-on-foxconn-results-ai-server-demand.html</link><description>Global semiconductor stocks climbed on Monday after Foxconn posted record fourth-quarter revenue, suggesting the AI boom has far more room to run.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 15:33:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Unlocking the Potential of Mesoblast Ltd. (MESO): A Biotech Giant on the Rise</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/unlocking-the-potential-of-mesoblast-ltd-meso-a-biotech-giant-on-the-rise/</link><image_url>https://ragingbull.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/08/favicon.png</image_url><description>As a seasoned investor, I’m always on the lookout for companies that have what it takes to make a significant impact in their respective industries. One such company is Mesoblast Ltd., a biopharmaceutical firm that’s been making waves with its innovative mesenchymal lineage adult stem cell technology platform. A Brief History Founded by Silviu Itescu […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 16:42:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bond yields edge higher on reports of Trump tariff plans</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/bond-yields-rise-as-key-data-looms-0e026bca?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://www.marketwatch.com/rss/marketwatch.gif</image_url><description>Yields on U.S. government debt were edging up Monday morning as traders focused on reports relating to incoming-President Donald Trump’s approach to applying tariffs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 15:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump's election certification set to begin on anniversary of 2021 Capitol riot</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2025/01/06/congress-trump-harris-election-certification-jan-6.html</link><description>President-elect Donald Trump won the 2024 election against Vice President Kamala Harris, who will preside over Congress as it certifies the results.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 15:08:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Disney to combine its Hulu+ Live TV with streamer Fubo</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2025/01/06/disney-hulu-live-tv-fubo.html</link><description>Both Hulu+ Live TV and Fubo are streaming services that mimic the traditional cable TV bundle, offering linear TV networks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 15:27:58 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>