<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 06:49:30 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Did you miss boot camp and need a doctor’s note? We got you covered 🎥</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/pennypro/did-you-miss-boot-camp-and-need-a-doctors-note-we-got-you-covered-%f0%9f%8e%a5/</link><image_url>https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXfwINhuJ2-nkiSNdOSokY1XPgUdqNR4_8FfLOtXe9M4gRPVbSbAb2k5MWUz7TT0h42Ra76g6aGykdoJABfPOLXfByIOdBn4UWwOTyL6NR_2gqvrjLYkf0Ucn6jkfstpZ1aZRo4k2EiDYswr3VdKZ-xKRx4x?key=QudxO7LTgvPEtQ4Q__v_qA</image_url><description>💥MARKET NAVIGATOR &amp; ATOMIC TRADES💥 DEAL ENDS @ MIDNIGHT BUNDLE &amp; SAVE BIG HERE! Howdy gang! Jeff Williams (JW) here, did you miss my boot camp earlier this week? I took some time to go over how I try to simplify my options trading in the morning and how I hunt down the best penny […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 19:53:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Don’t buy the dip as the summer slump is officially here, says Goldman strategist</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/dont-buy-the-dip-as-the-summer-slump-is-officially-here-says-goldman-strategist-0fa63c56?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-27971393</image_url><description>Wading in for bargains right now is not the way to go, says Goldman Sachs’ tactical strategist Scott Rubner, who offers seasonal caution.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 11:49:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Can Boeing get back to its glory days?</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/18/boeing-path-forward.html</link><description>Boeing's leaders say they have charted a path forward to fix the company. They still have plenty of people to convince.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 11:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Britain will be a friend and a partner': UK's Starmer aims to overhaul EU relations at key summit</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/18/uks-starmer-aims-to-overhaul-eu-relations-as-trump-spectre-looms.html</link><description>The U.K.'s new Labour Prime Minister Keir Starmer is seeking to reset fractured relations with Europe as he hosts more than 45 heads of state at a summit.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 11:45:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Takeovers, mergers and asset purchases</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/takeovers-mergers-and-asset-purchases/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/1022e75f-9694-451c-95ba-14ec0069c5e9/image__1_.png</image_url><description>Good day, 360! Here are our top investing ideas today. And don’t forget to join us in Market Masters – the hottest trading room around 🔥. Be the best prepared trader on the Street! FOCUS LIST🔎 ADTX – Up over 80% in pre after amended merger agreement with Evofem, targeting September 30 closing GDTC – […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 19:12:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tech selloff erases $1.1 trillion of ‘Magnificent Seven’ market cap in five days</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/tech-selloff-has-erased-1-1-trillion-of-magnificent-seven-market-cap-in-5-days-94745798?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-62709566</image_url><description>The seven Big Tech companies collectively shed more than $500 billion in market cap on Wednesday alone.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 11:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden says he might quit presidential race if 'medical condition' emerged</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/17/biden-presidential-race-medical-condition.html</link><description>Biden, 81, has come under increasing pressure from members of his own party to withdraw from the race following his disastrous debate with Trump, 78.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 02:02:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>China's Communist Party removes ex-foreign, defence ministers from top body</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/18/chinas-communist-party-removes-ex-foreign-defence-ministers-from-top-body.html</link><description>The ruling Communist Party ended its long-delayed third plenum on Thursday, a meeting of the 205-member Central Committee held roughly once every five years to map out the general direction of the country's long-term social and economic policies.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 11:25:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gamma Trigger Strikes Again! ⚡</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/gamma-trigger-strikes-again-%e2%9a%a1/</link><image_url>https://lh7-us.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXcxvmZ0bf-KWAqv9LzNGfhpW4oAdYlfpEI9_GxcNlSAHZ-6Iuz8NYYmycY4FjwNy430ZmwIptLrj483TxbCaW1mJBGfYdBzj3yQpQT25NDPBYMQfdDrVPJYw9eXrv9ku-nFu9mo7w_na0y3Ol6FGT4YDTYx?key=32S7a6jOz5UOdFFJKBUdXA</image_url><description>Reminder: JW’s Options Class 7ET Did you catch the new long-term lithium play I showed you this morning? That stock ended up 21% higher today. That could be the start, so make sure you keep it on your list. At this price, I think it is a “no-brainer” to at least look into right now. […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 19:27:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Infosys meets earnings estimate as sales edge past consensus</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/infosys-meets-earnings-estimate-as-sales-edge-past-consensus-bc4905ec?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-32929669</image_url><description>Indian outsourcing giant Infosys reported growing profits as it forecast a slight pickup in sales growth for the year.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 11:37:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>United Airlines profit jumps 23%, but third-quarter forecast disappoints amid industry overcapacity</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/17/united-ual-earnings-q2-2024.html</link><description>United and Delta have benefited from an increase in consumers' shift to premium cabins.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 23:59:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nokia shares slide 8% after posting lowest quarterly net sales figure since 2015</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/18/nokia-shares-slide-after-posting-weak-quarterly-net-sales-figure.html</link><description>Shares of Finnish telecom firm Nokia plunged after a steep drop in sales and operating profit in the second quarter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 09:52:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump survives g, stock up 50%</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/trump-survives-g-stock-up-50/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/1022e75f-9694-451c-95ba-14ec0069c5e9/image__1_.png</image_url><description>Good morning, 360! Don’t forget to join us today for LIVE trading in the Market Master’s Room — and for OPTIONS BOOTCAMP with JW starting TONIGHT at 7pm EST. Be the best prepared trader on the Street! FOCUS LIST🔎 DJT – Up over 50% in the pre-market after defiant Trump survives and shrugs off assassination […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 17:48:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Slowdown in U.K. jobs market could pave way for BoE interest rate cut, Deutsche Bank says</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/slowdown-in-u-k-jobs-market-could-pave-way-for-boe-interest-rate-cut-deutsche-bank-says-bbc379d8?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-58404865</image_url><description>The Office for National Statistics data shows a slowdown in the U.K.’s labor market that could see the Bank of England cut interest rates at its upcoming meeting on August 1</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 11:31:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>House Democrats circulate letter urging DNC not to rush Biden nomination</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/16/house-democrats-letter-dnc-biden-nomination.html</link><description>President Biden has faced mounting pressure to drop out of the race after his debate flop against Donald Trump in June.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 23:20:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TSMC second-quarter profit beats expectations as AI chip boom continues</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/18/tsmc-q2-2024-earnings.html</link><description>TSMC on Thursday beat revenue and profit expectations in the second quarter, as demand for advanced chips used in AI applications continue to surge.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 09:50:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tesla’s Lithium Bet 🔋</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/teslas-lithium-bet-%f0%9f%94%8b/</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/2668.png</image_url><description>♨️ Hot Pennies I Trade SPY 📈I Drops Monday🎯 Happy weekend, Folks! With the rise of electric vehicles — I’m a happy Tesla owner as of last year — and lithium batteries in general, the silvery metal has been dubbed “white gold.” Massive government subsidies and a global push toward cleaner energy have turned what were […]</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 16:43:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘I’m not jealous — just genuinely curious’: How can a woman work from home and mind her 3-year-old child at the same time?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/im-not-jealous-just-genuinely-curious-how-can-a-woman-work-from-home-and-mind-her-3-year-old-child-at-the-same-time-14a9c311?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-80401724</image_url><description>“What do you all think about employees who work from home and have little kids to watch at the same time?”</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 11:23:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rep. Adam Schiff calls on Biden to drop out of election contest, warns of losing Congress</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/17/rep-adam-schiff-calls-on-biden-to-drop-out-of-election-contest-warns-of-losing-congress.html</link><description>Rep. Adam Schiff is one of the most prominent Democrats to urge President Joe Biden to let another nominee face Donald Trump in the presidential election.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 23:19:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Volvo Cars jumps 7% after reporting a record core operating profit</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/18/volvo-cars-jumps-7percent-after-reporting-a-record-core-operating-profit.html</link><description>Shares of Volvo Cars rose sharply on Thursday after the company reported a jump in annual operating profit for the second quarter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 09:21:17 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>