<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 07:21:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Earnings and a potential kidney disease breakthrough</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/earnings-and-a-potential-kidney-disease-breakthrough/</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f50e.png</image_url><description>Good day, 360! Here are our top investing ideas today. And special invitation to trade Jeff’s Pick of the Day with him this morning in the Market Masters Room – his Back to School Special ends tonight! Grab one of the 12 seats left! FOCUS LIST🔎 XRTX – Up over 50% in pre after highlights […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 14:42:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>September is the market’s cruelest month — except in presidential election years</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/september-is-the-markets-cruelest-month-except-in-presidential-election-years-fcf5a883?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-96990716</image_url><description>Plus: 5 sectors and 9 stocks to keep on your portfolio’s radar.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 12:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cord cutters prepare for political ad blitz as campaigns flood Roku, Hulu ahead of election</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/29/cord-cutters-getting-political-ad-blitz-as-campaigns-flood-roku-hulu.html</link><description>Connected TV are capturing more political advertising dollars than ever as campaigns rush to reach prospective voters.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 12:16:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alibaba jumps 4% in premarket after it completes three-year regulatory overhaul</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/30/alibaba-shares-jump-as-it-completes-three-year-regulatory-overhau.html</link><description>Alibaba has completed a three-year regulatory "rectification" process following an antitrust fine it received for monopolistic practices in 2021, China's market regulator said on Friday.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 12:01:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Positive earnings and advanced talks have these stocks moving</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/positive-earnings-and-advanced-talks-have-these-stocks-moving/</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f50e.png</image_url><description>*sponsored by StocksToTrade Good day, 360! Here are some BIG movers today. Have a great trading day out there. Be the best prepared trader on the Street! FOCUS LIST🔎 WALD – Up over 20% in the pre-market after reporting a 26% net revenue surge in Q2 NRSN – Up over 14% in pre after reports […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 14:53:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bank of America sees potential for a reversal in bond yields</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/bank-of-america-sees-potential-for-a-reversal-in-bond-yields-8b66a0ea?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-93700054</image_url><description>Strategists at Bank of America says there’s a potential for a reversal in bond yields, particularly at the long end.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 12:04:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Here's how data centers became a billion-dollar real estate investment</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/30/how-data-centers-became-billion-dollar-real-estate-investment.html</link><description>The U.S. has most of the world's data centers. The concentration has caused the value of the land they're built on to soar. Investors are putting money to work.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 11:02:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CNBC's Inside India newsletter: A tale of tier 2 cities</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/29/cnbcs-inside-india-newsletter-a-tale-of-tier-2-cities.html</link><description>India's economic map is being redrawn.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 12:00:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The markets will rise or fall with NVDA</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/the-markets-will-rise-or-fall-with-nvda/</link><image_url>https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXfe8P92-5uyguiJuMiA9h3fDsiCQI1wUyTLRa94tZG-17i9cxuaxVfusu4ltGGlNZU28Zp-_ePtI8Bduc_f--i8hpwXeXMSvM7KVYzH1_QrN0d0fJrTP42QOr83HZ7vGi3r94i9AIfn4-Tt1hlcLJ4xK3c?key=wzDPWAWiCLa6IwPlXhf90w</image_url><description>GM! Jeff Bishop here. Today is like the Super Bowl of earnings. NVIDIA releases its numbers after market close today, and like the Big Game, it’s something everyone has to watch. I’ll be watching, too, but that’s all I’ll do. I understand the temptation to want to get in on the action. Believe me, I […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 14:48:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The ‘Low-Wage 100’ spend more on share buybacks that enrich executives than on their businesses. Lawmakers are taking note.</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/the-low-wage-100-spend-more-on-share-buybacks-that-enrich-executives-than-on-their-businesses-lawmakers-are-taking-note-e9515a44?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-36426294</image_url><description>A new report on the 100 S&amp;P 500 companies with the lowest median pay finds the buyback machine is still in overdrive.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elon Musk's X can proceed to trial in case against Media Matters after Texas judge denies dismissal request</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/29/judge-rules-against-media-matters-request-to-dismiss-lawsuit-by-x.html</link><description>A federal judge in Texas has ruled against Media Matters and its request to dismiss a lawsuit filed by Elon Musk's X</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 05:05:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This 29-year-old from one of London's poorest neighborhoods became a millionaire after selling his influencer marketing firm</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/30/how-a-29-year-old-became-a-millionaire-after-growing-up-poor-in-london.html</link><description>Timothy Armoo grew up poor on a council estate in South London. Here's how he became a millionaire before the age of 30.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 11:23:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Just crossed $30K – what next?</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/jason-bond/just-crossed-30k-what-next/</link><image_url>https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXceUDCa9EHJHRQMpl1pXRG7yG7O5svMaCnL5_e-WbRUG5OrAHSDFOHjT1w_CVGvKezurtpT9FIi123duBvVKH2ipKwAbARAeoqQpt7OUurDN8TpqMjApnFzcCo5iGNNxiCB7pvG5nXhonsBp5AfN4zwmY-M?key=gb2z3jwfiPFE1uaNZd35Aw</image_url><description>Another milestone for the Small Account Journey has just been crossed. Last Friday, my small trading account crossed $30,000+. I started that account with just $2,000 a few months ago. That’s INSANE. But instead of just showing you all these great trades, I want to run through 3 reasons why I was able to pull […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 21:20:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>We’re in our 60s and plan to claim Social Security at 70. Does delaying for maximum benefits really make sense?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/were-in-our-60s-and-plan-to-claim-social-security-at-70-does-delaying-for-maximum-benefits-really-make-sense-2dd2264f?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-87605678</image_url><description>“I am planning to apply for Social Security at 70 to get the higher benefits.”</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Here’s how much athletes at the Paris Paralympics earn for winning medals</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/30/paralympics-heres-how-much-athletes-earn-for-winning-medals.html</link><description>While the International Paralympic Committee does not dole out prize money for winning medals, several countries do reward their athletes with medal bonuses.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 04:01:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Euro zone inflation falls to 3-year low of 2.2%, backing September rate cut case</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/30/euro-zone-inflation-august-2024.html</link><description>Economics polled by Reuters had forecast a decline to 2.2% in August, down from 2.6% in July.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 11:12:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Was this worth playing hooky for today 🤔</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/total-alpha/was-this-worth-playing-hooky-for-today-%f0%9f%a4%94/</link><image_url>https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f64f.png</image_url><description>Good afternoon, Folks! Jeff Bishop here. Jason, Taiku &amp; I will be in the Market Master’s Room this week to help cover for JW while he is taking some time to be with his family during this difficult time 🙏. Look out for emails but I hope you were able to join me this morning […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 21:19:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Emergent BioSolutions’ stock soars 23% after FDA approves its smallpox vaccine for mpox</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/emergent-biosolutions-stock-soars-23-after-fda-approves-its-smallpox-vaccine-for-mpox-dcfe6d5b?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-72258343</image_url><description>The Emergent vaccine is now the second one to win FDA approval after one developed by Danish biotech Bavarian Nordic.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 11:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Harris defends border record, rips Trump for killing bipartisan bill</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/29/harris-interview-values-on-border-security-have-not-changed.html</link><description>Democratic nominee Kamala Harris and running mate Tim Walz held their first interview since President Joe Biden dropped his reelection bid against Donald Trump.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 03:15:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>China’s Zeekr targets global markets with its electric SUV, priced to undercut Tesla’s Model Y</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/30/chinas-zeekr-to-launch-first-electric-suv-priced-to-undercut-teslas-model-y.html</link><description>China's electric vehicle company, Zeekr, announced Friday that it will launch its first SUV in China on Sep. 20, starting at US$33,700, to compete with Tesla.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 08:21:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>