<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 06:53:24 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Market Turnaround: What’s Hot Right Now 🔥</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/market-turnaround-whats-hot-right-now-%f0%9f%94%a5/</link><image_url>https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXcRqfDCYQVcWARRAFx1q6g11-hvj9uRFP_dSJUkUxZhJzxCOmEc9DjhsuSNR1K5l7QXCk2fpV3xUT4CUanmpIReZgh12jG8RD6mM8vw07lOOSuytVQiD-f0vL1-8WqF5gIQE-tcr6AL4SsauurOepflkm1P?key=j6FwfEEb-ONODqctQtifUA</image_url><description>Good evening, Folks. Jeff Bishop here! I don’t know about you, but Friday sure felt like a great way for me to end the week. It was a very choppy week, and a few trades didn’t go my way, but when I saw the market start to turn the corner on Friday, I knew it […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 13:53:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This strategist is predicting a big rally after the Fed decision. He’s been more right than wrong this year.</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/this-strategist-is-predicting-a-big-rally-after-the-fed-decision-hes-been-more-right-than-wrong-this-year-d3097d50?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-49554698</image_url><description>Thomas Lee, the usually optimistic co-founder and head of research at Fundstrat Global Advisor, is expecting a small-cap-led rally.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 11:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why orange juice is so expensive</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/31/why-us-citrus-is-facing-a-shortage-crisis.html</link><description>Orange juice futures are hitting records as growers lose millions of dollars annually. U.S. citrus production is plummeting amid weather and disease extremes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 11:02:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stock futures rise as Wall Street awaits Fed decision: Live updates</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/30/stock-market-today-live-updates.html</link><description>Stock futures rose Wednesday as investors parsed the latest earnings reports and readied for the Federal Reserve monetary policy decision.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 11:50:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sat. &amp; Sun. FREE 12p et workshops</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/sat-sun-free-12p-et-workshops/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/c2979b17-269d-4eda-9da2-7cc446411f47/JBP-2020-Email-Header.jpg?t=1721173784</image_url><description>$2k Small Account Journey Trading Is Hard! Right?! Are You Overtrading? I Have At Times! FREE TRAINING: Saturday and Sunday at 12pm EST FREE in the Market Masters Chat Room Back To The Basics Workshop: Come Learn My #1 Small-Cap Pattern Results not typical. Trading is hard. Nothing is guaranteed. As I look […]</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 17:31:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A surprise Fed rate cut might be good for consumers — but not for the stock market</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/a-surprise-fed-rate-cut-might-be-good-for-consumers-but-not-for-the-stock-market-caf794b2?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-739658</image_url><description>Investors are clamoring for affirmation the Fed will begin cutting rates in September. But a surprise easing on Wednesday likely wouldn’t go over well.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 11:36:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ford reveals 2025 Maverick pickup with new technologies, hybrid options</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/31/2025-ford-maverick-pickup-new-tech-hybrid-options.html</link><description>Ford Motor has redesigned its small Maverick pickup truck, adding more technology, new performance and hybrid options to the vehicle.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 11:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Euro zone inflation rises to 2.6% in July, above expectations</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/31/euro-zone-inflation-july-2024.html</link><description>Headline inflation in the euro zone unexpectedly rose to 2.6% in July, the European Union's statistics agency said Wednesday.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 11:37:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chevrolet signs a supply deal with this tiny stock</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/chevrolet-signs-a-supply-deal-with-this-tiny-stock/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/1022e75f-9694-451c-95ba-14ec0069c5e9/image__1_.png</image_url><description>Good day, 360! Here are our top investing ideas today. And don’t forget to join us in Market Masters – the hottest trading room around 🔥. Be the best prepared trader on the Street! FOCUS LIST🔎 WINT – Up over 100% in pre after providing update on Istaroxime clinical development and upcoming clinical trial data […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 16:16:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Microsoft and AMD earnings show that AI remains a game of optics</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/microsoft-and-amd-earnings-show-that-ai-remains-a-game-of-optics-27e0a5dd?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-15499879</image_url><description>The dichotomy in Wall Street’s reactions to the results from Microsoft Corp. and Advanced Micro Devices Inc. — two tech giants that have been investing heavily in AI — is a perfect example of the AI optics game.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 11:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump to speak at Black journalists convention, as Harris erases his lead in polls</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/31/trump-black-journalist-convention-nabj.html</link><description>The event gives former President Donald Trump an opportunity to directly appeal to voters of color as he campaigns against Vice President Kamala Harris.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 10:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AMD jumps 9% in premarket trading as global chip stocks rally after earnings and geopolitics lift sector</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/31/amd-nvidia-jump-as-chip-stocks-rally-from-earnings-geopolitics-boost.html</link><description>Shares of global semiconductor firms were boosted by some positive tech earnings and a report of potentially less severe U.S. export restrictions on China.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 11:03:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Whoa, Did You See the Market Today? 📉</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/editorial/whoa-did-you-see-the-market-today-%f0%9f%93%89/</link><image_url>https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXfLqkKf1L5t3pYrb1o9ftXBq8m_ieOTWaQ3C18E29QgPUdSYAZ_FHzRJ0V9OZ4IS5E1AH4V08OKYcapzmBdbohzs3SoBXoLDSvlBbM-UDolOOzbky4en0Yaqi01OCkuhSdexU49cTi0cZUzbl19zTD9jkOm?key=j9OsXDoZ3BMs6oOXNl5I7Q</image_url><description>Quick Reminder: JW’s Market Navigator Special Trial is over this evening — so take advantage today and trade the SPY with him and his gang! Just this morning, I said the QQQ had to hold above $475, or else we were headed for a big drop. If you haven’t looked at your portfolio today, I’d […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 15:20:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple earnings will be all about this one clue</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/apple-earnings-will-be-all-about-this-one-clue-591385f6?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-623189</image_url><description>Apple’s June-quarter earnings report isn’t typically one to write home about, but there’s still value to it.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 11:10:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Harris directly challenges Trump to debate: 'Say it to my face'</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/30/harris-atlanta-rally-rsvp-megan-thee-stallion.html</link><description>Vice President Kamala Harris goaded Donald Trump at a rally in Atlanta before a roaring crowd of more than 10,000 supporters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 05:58:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Iran says Israel will 'pay heavy price' after death of top Hamas leader Ismail Haniyeh</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/31/iran-says-israel-will-pay-heavy-price-after-death-of-ismail-haniyeh.html</link><description>Iranian supreme leader Ayatollah Khamenei said in a statement that Israel "has prepared the ground for severe punishment with this action."</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 10:29:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Big earnings beats have these stocks moving</title><link>https://ragingbull.com/insider/big-earnings-beats-have-these-stocks-moving/</link><image_url>https://media.beehiiv.com/cdn-cgi/image/fit=scale-down,format=auto,onerror=redirect,quality=80/uploads/asset/file/1022e75f-9694-451c-95ba-14ec0069c5e9/image__1_.png</image_url><description>*sponsored by Sica Media Good morning, 360! Don’t forget to join us today for LIVE trading in the Market Master’s Room. Be the best prepared trader on the Street! FOCUS LIST🔎 TUSK – Up over 34% in the pre-market after settlement agreement with PREPA for $188.4 million FEIM – Up over 30% in pre […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 16:22:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Intel earnings: Can the company cut its way to an improved position?</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/intel-earnings-can-the-company-cut-its-way-to-an-improved-position-916feb45?mod=mw_rss_topstories</link><image_url>https://images.mktw.net/im-806855</image_url><description>Intel is expected to post a decline in adjusted profit when it reports earnings Thursday, and job cuts reportedly are on the horizon.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 11:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump address to Black journalist convention prompts co-chair Karen Attiah to quit</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/30/trump-speak-black-journalists-nabj-co-chair-quits.html</link><description>Republican presidential nominee Donald Trump is set to address the National Association of Black Journalists convention in Chicago on Wednesday.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 05:14:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bank of England rate cut is a close call even with inflation on target</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/31/bank-of-englands-rate-cut-is-on-a-knife-edge.html</link><description>Members of the central bank's voting Monetary Policy Committee are divided.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 10:25:06 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>