<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Individual feed for https://barbend.com/feed</title><link>https://barbend.com/feed</link><description>Individual feed output.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:19:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Use Pause Squats to Evolve Your Training</title><link>https://barbend.com/evolve-pause-squat-training/</link><image_url>https://www.youtube.com/embed/bkEHUQmIhaU</image_url><description>2018 World’s Strongest Man (WSM) Hafþór Björnsson’s coach, Sebastian Oreb, recently talked about a game-changing movement in his strength training jou...</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Do You Need to Train Abs Directly?</title><link>https://barbend.com/train-abs-directly/</link><image_url>https://www.youtube.com/embed/vub-pjymoZk</image_url><description>“People think ab training is different, but it’s the same as training other muscles,” said Dr. Mike Israetel. Abs, like any muscle, respond to fundame...</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 13 Best BCAA Supplements of 2025, Expert Tested and Approved</title><link>https://barbend.com/best-bcaa-supplement/</link><image_url>https://www.youtube.com/embed/XilYpSq1Dzs</image_url><description>Once a niche athletic supplement, branched-chain amino acids (BCAAs) have exploded in popularity as a means to potentially improve muscle retention, e...</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 21:01:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 10 Best Greens Powders of 2025, Tested, Chosen, and Approved by a Dietitian</title><link>https://barbend.com/best-greens-powder/</link><image_url>https://www.youtube.com/embed/cNwZM9gvEEI</image_url><description>Getting enough fruits and vegetables daily can be tough, especially if you’re a picky eater or have a busy schedule. The Dietary Guidelines for Americ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 21:01:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Best Treadmills for Your Home in 2025, Reviewed by Personal Trainers</title><link>https://barbend.com/best-treadmill/</link><image_url>https://www.youtube.com/embed/cBsbqG9eUF0</image_url><description>When conjuring up thoughts of the best cardio machines, treadmills typically cross your mind first. From compact treadmills ideal for apartment-dwelli...</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 21:01:23 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>