<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Individual feed for https://barbend.com/feed</title><link>https://barbend.com/feed</link><description>Individual feed output.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 14:05:44 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>You Live Longer If You Intermittent Fast? Yes! But Not How You Think</title><link>https://barbend.com/live-longer-intermittent-fast/</link><image_url>https://www.youtube.com/embed/4pM0KEYKCaI</image_url><description>Intermittent fasting (IF) involves alternating between periods of eating and fasting. Many experts praise IF for its potential benefits, including imp...</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Elite Athletes Recover From Achilles Injuries</title><link>https://barbend.com/achilles-injuries-recovery-elite-athletes/</link><image_url>https://www.youtube.com/embed/BfUQkWOKlV4</image_url><description>There was a ton of exciting action on the competition floor at the 2024 Rogue Invitational in Aberdeen, Scotland. Remind Me: Gabriela Migała and Henri...</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 16:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Check Out the Results of Eddie Hall’s 90-Day Carnivore Diet</title><link>https://barbend.com/eddie-hall-carnivore-diet-results/</link><image_url>https://www.youtube.com/embed/uK5U4EGxF-E</image_url><description>Could there be a more aptly-named diet for an athlete with the moniker “The Beast” than the carnivore Diet? Eddie Hall does not consume carbs. Or, rat...</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Client Retention Up, Coach Pay and Membership Rates Still Need Work, Says 2024 State of the Industry Report</title><link>https://barbend.com/2024-state-of-the-industry-report-crossfit-gyms/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>For the fifth straight year, gym business mentorship company Two-Brain Business has released its annual State of the Industry Report, a comprehensive ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jay Cutler Refuses to Start Chest Day Without Training a Completely Unrelated Body Part</title><link>https://barbend.com/jay-cutler-unconventional-chest-day/</link><image_url>https://www.youtube.com/embed/TxXtv6qsZvc</image_url><description>If it ain’t broke, don’t fix it. Like most bodybuilders, Jay Cutler is a creature of habit. Even though the four-time Mr. Olympia no longer trains to ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 20:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>