<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Individual feed for https://healthshoutout.com/feed</title><link>https://healthshoutout.com/feed</link><description>Individual feed output.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 12:36:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Disease Severity Staging System for  NOTCH3 -Associated Small Vessel Disease, Including CADASIL</title><link>https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamaneurology/fullarticle/2827600</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>This cohort study designed a disease severity staging system to capture the broad clinicoradiological severity spectrum of NOTCH3-associated small ves...</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seeding-competent TDP-43 persists in human patient and mouse muscle</title><link>https://www.science.org/doi/abs/10.1126/scitranslmed.adp5730?af=R</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Science Translational Medicine, Volume 16, Issue 775, November 2024. &lt;p&gt;The post Seeding-competent TDP-43 persists in human patient and mouse muscle f...</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Erratum for the Research Article “Platelet-derived growth factor C signaling is a potential therapeutic target for radiation proctopathy” by W. Lu et al.</title><link>https://www.science.org/doi/abs/10.1126/scitranslmed.adu4658?af=R</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Science Translational Medicine, Volume 16, Issue 775, November 2024. &lt;p&gt;The post Erratum for the Research Article “Platelet-derived growth factor C si...</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Erratum for the Research Article “Neural landscape is associated with functional outcomes in irradiated patients with oropharyngeal squamous cell carcinoma” by S. Islam et al.</title><link>https://www.science.org/doi/abs/10.1126/scitranslmed.adu4652?af=R</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Science Translational Medicine, Volume 16, Issue 775, November 2024. &lt;p&gt;The post Erratum for the Research Article “Neural landscape is associated with...</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Childhood-onset lupus nephritis is characterized by complex interactions between kidney stroma and infiltrating immune cells</title><link>https://healthshoutout.com/scitranslmed-adl1666/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Science Translational Medicine, Volume 16, Issue 775, November 2024. &lt;p&gt;The post Childhood-onset lupus nephritis is characterized by complex interacti...</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>