<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Individual feed for https://medicalxpress.com/rss-feed/</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/rss-feed/</link><description>Individual feed output.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 06:35:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Study shows that an anti-inflammatory diet could extend overall survival after treatment for stage III colon cancer</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-anti-inflammatory-diet-survival-treatment.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Patients with colon cancer who consumed an anti-inflammatory diet during a Phase III clinical trial showed longer overall survival post-treatment comp...</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 11:05:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Does a culturally tailored quality of life intervention benefit Latina breast cancer survivors and caregivers?</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-05-culturally-tailored-quality-life-intervention.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>A randomized controlled trial assessed the benefits of a group-based intervention that fosters communication and coping skills in a culturally tailore...</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 08:10:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The hearts of female elite athletes adapt differently than those of male elite athletes, research reveals</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-05-hearts-female-elite-athletes-differently.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Intensive exercise and sport changes the heart of an athlete. Research led by Amsterdam UMC shows that the hearts of female athletes have different ch...</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 08:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sea change in cancer care requires urgent action to strengthen oncology workforce and care delivery, say researchers</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-05-sea-cancer-requires-urgent-action.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Rapid advances in cancer treatment have benefited many people, but urgent change is needed in Canada's cancer care workforce to ensure patient care, a...</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 05:10:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Plastic particles found in food could harm the body</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-05-plastic-particles-food-body.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Results from a new animal study suggest that microscopic plastic particles found in food and beverages may affect glucose metabolism and harm organs s...</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 21:50:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>