<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Individual feed for https://new.nsf.gov/rss/rss_www_news.xml</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/rss/rss_www_news.xml</link><description>Individual feed output.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 02:25:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>'Far out' blazar discovery suggests early universe had more supermassive black holes than previously thought</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/far-out-blazar-discovery-suggests-early-universe-had-more</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Scientists have discovered the most distant and therefore oldest blazar ever seen. Labeled J0410–0139, the blazar is at the center of a galaxy 12.9 bi...</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 20:29:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI vs. supercomputers: New AI-based method solves complex equations faster and uses less computing power</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/ai-vs-supercomputers-new-ai-based-method-solves-complex</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>A new artificial intelligence-based method quickly solves complex math equations used broadly across many industries — and it's faster running on a pe...</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 19:37:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists devise new method to detect permanent distortions in space-time left by massive supernova explosions</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/scientists-devise-new-method-detect-permanent-distortions</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Scientists have presented a new way to detect permanent distortions in the fabric of space-time predicted to be caused by certain supernovae explosion...</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 22:36:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paper-based sensors may lead to rapid detection of heart attacks</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/paper-based-sensors-may-lead-rapid-detection-heart-attacks</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>When individuals experience acute myocardial infarction, also known as a heart attack, time is precious. Detection and diagnosis of a heart attack hav...</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 17:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSF congratulates recipients of the prestigious National Medal of Science and National Medal of Technology and Innovation awards</title><link>https://new.nsf.gov/news/nsf-congratulates-recipients-prestigious-national-medal</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>President Joe Biden revealed the newest honorees of the recipients of the National Medal of Science and the National Medal of Technology and Innovatio...</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 19:03:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>