<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Individual feed for https://www.sciencedaily.com/rss/top/science.xml</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/rss/top/science.xml</link><description>Individual feed output.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 10:49:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Discovery of dopamine receptors in a previously overlooked part of the brain sheds light on the complex circuitry for anxiety and depression</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/05/250507152241.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Researchers have discovered distinct roles for two dopamine receptors located on nerve cells within the portion of the brain that controls approach vs...</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 20:22:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are you curious? It might help you stay sharp as you age</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/05/250507141038.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Psychology literature has shown that curiosity tends to decline with age. Psychologists shows one type of curiosity can increase well into old age, co...</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 19:10:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The world's wealthiest 10% caused two thirds of global warming since 1990</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/05/250507130519.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Wealthy individuals have a higher carbon footprint. A new study quantifies the climate outcomes of these inequalities. It finds that the world's wealt...</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 18:05:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New study tracks air pollution and CO2 emissions across thousands of cities worldwide</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/05/250507130516.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>In a sweeping new study of more than 13,000 urban areas worldwide, researchers have mapped air pollution levels and carbon dioxide emissions, providin...</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 18:05:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The atmospheric memory that feeds billions of people: Newly discovered mechanism for monsoon rainfall</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/05/250507130511.htm</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Across the globe, monsoon rainfall switches on in spring and off in autumn. Until now, this seasonal pattern was primarily understood as an immediate ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 18:05:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>