<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 07:43:32 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Meta Shares Rally As Tech Giant’s Aggressive AI Investments Start Paying Off</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/roberthart/2024/08/01/meta-shares-rally-as-tech-giants-aggressive-ai-investments-start-paying-off/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66ab6220f4d4154841cf460e/0x0.jpg?width=960&amp;precrop=4296%2C2418%2Cx0%2Cy59</image_url><description>Meta has bucked the trend of other big tech companies like Microsoft and Tesla, whose shares tanked after they revealed soaring spending on AI but few concrete pathways to profit from the technology.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 12:31:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stopping a runaway train</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/stopping-a-runaway-train/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>It feels urgent because it is. But by the time the train is running away, it might be too late. The better strategy is to not sign up for trains that are likely to run away. The first principle of risk reduction is to figure out if you can stop it later. If you can&amp;#8217;t, [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 10:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Today’s NYT Mini Crossword Clues And Answers For Thursday, August 1</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/paultassi/2024/08/01/todays-nyt-mini-crossword-clues-and-answers-for-thursday-august-1/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66a443f5e74a26761c258a2c/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>Looking for help with today's NYT Mini Crossword puzzle? Here are some hints and answers for the puzzle.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 12:30:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The tooth fairy</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/07/the-tooth-fairy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Make a list of things you used to believe. Fervently, certainly, completely. Things that you were sure of, but now, with the passage of time and the benefit of experience, you know to be incorrect or incomplete. Of course, it&amp;#8217;s not just mythical creatures beloved by children. It&amp;#8217;s our adherence to a social norm, loyalty [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 08:46:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Human-Centric Leadership: The Key To A Tech Company’s Success At Scale</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2024/08/01/human-centric-leadership-the-key-to-a-tech-companys-success-at-scale/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/663bfa8624a5b36cfea4171e/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>Leading a company with a human-centric mindset can be the difference between languishing behind your competitors and achieving success at scale.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The last little bit</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/07/the-last-little-bit/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>Important hills usually get much steeper at the top. 99% of the training in competitive athletics is devoted to the last 1% of performance. A tenth of a second. The same is true for squeezing the last bit of performance out of a car, a grape or a semiconductor. And healthcare, luxury goods and science [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 09:14:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ENGLAND’S YOTES COURT VINEYARD IS LETTING NATURE DO THE WORK</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/christophermarquis/2024/08/01/englands-yotes-court-vineyard-is-letting-nature-do-the-work/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66a8c58af20c7ae2e57ea0ea/0x0.jpg?width=960&amp;precrop=4328%2C2027%2Cx0%2Cy312</image_url><description>Yotes Court Vineyard in Kent combines regenerative agriculture and innovative grape varieties to enhance sustainability and wine quality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 12:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What are you thinking about?</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/07/what-are-you-thinking-about/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>A philosopher can spend a month, a year or a career thinking about one knotty problem. Making assertions, testing theories, understanding how others are thinking about it as well. But this exercise shouldn&amp;#8217;t be reserved for academics. What are you working on? When will you change your mind? What can you learn, what can you [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 09:16:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Human Touch: Why Putting People First Defines Tech Leadership</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2024/08/01/the-human-touch-why-putting-people-first-defines-tech-leadership/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/654501b12845116962a18280/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>At the heart of every successful technological innovation is a team of talented individuals driven by passion and creativity.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 12:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>“It seems…”</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/07/it-seems/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>What a simple verb. A five-letter modifier that opens the door to discussion. If we state something as a fact, we&amp;#8217;re asking for an argument. But seems opens the door to learning and discussion. What are you seeing that I&amp;#8217;m not seeing?</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 08:08:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>