<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 02:03:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>UFC Castoff Spurned Again As PFL President Says ‘We’re Not Interested’</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2024/08/03/ufc-castoff-spurned-again-as-pfl-president-says-were-not-interested/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66a5e8053197d9da9c82e7af/0x0.jpg?width=960&amp;precrop=3122%2C1755%2Cx0%2Cy161</image_url><description>Muhammad Mokaev is in a tough spot. A week after he was discarded by the UFC, the PFL doubled-up on the concept declaring they were not interested in signing him.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 05:57:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Infamy</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/infamy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>We&amp;#8217;ve gotten so hung up on famous that it&amp;#8217;s easy to forget that there are two kinds of renown. Being known for lowering the standards of discourse, cheating, or whining is a choice, but why would you trade your reputation to become infamous?</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 09:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>These AI-Powered Uses Cases Will Help You Reduce Customer Churn</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2024/08/03/learn-how-these-ai-powered-use-cases-reduce-customer-churn/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/607d6981c65d8f87c98148de/0x0.jpg?width=960&amp;precrop=1273%2C716%2Cx0%2Cy65</image_url><description>Learn how AI assumes a key role for distributors and their sales teams by generating customer-specific insights that helps reduce churn.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stopping a runaway train</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/stopping-a-runaway-train/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>It feels urgent because it is. But by the time the train is running away, it might be too late. The better strategy is to not sign up for trains that are likely to run away. The first principle of risk reduction is to figure out if you can stop it later. If you can&amp;#8217;t, [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 10:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>UFC 307: 2 Huge Fights Announced For Salt Lake City Show</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2024/08/02/ufc-307-2-huge-fights-announced-for-salt-lake-city-show/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66ada35cf6e303ef59161a61/0x0.jpg?width=960&amp;precrop=4041%2C2271%2Cx0%2Cy0</image_url><description>UFC 307 is still a few months away, but the card is coming together nicely. Though the main event isn't official, the UFC just signed two exciting fights for the event.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 04:37:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The tooth fairy</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/07/the-tooth-fairy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>Make a list of things you used to believe. Fervently, certainly, completely. Things that you were sure of, but now, with the passage of time and the benefit of experience, you know to be incorrect or incomplete. Of course, it&amp;#8217;s not just mythical creatures beloved by children. It&amp;#8217;s our adherence to a social norm, loyalty [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 08:46:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Today’s NYT Mini Crossword Clues And Answers For Saturday, August 2nd</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2024/08/02/todays-nyt-mini-crossword-clues-and-answers-for-saturday-august-2nd/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66ad93159698a3280d18584c/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>Looking for help with today's NYT Mini Crossword puzzle? Here are some hints and answers for the puzzle.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 03:34:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The last little bit</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/07/the-last-little-bit/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Important hills usually get much steeper at the top. 99% of the training in competitive athletics is devoted to the last 1% of performance. A tenth of a second. The same is true for squeezing the last bit of performance out of a car, a grape or a semiconductor. And healthcare, luxury goods and science [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 09:14:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>UFC 305 Card: Every Fight Scheduled For Perth, Australia Show</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2024/08/02/ufc-fight-card-305-every-fight-scheduled-for-perth-australia-show/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66ad8cb63c5ccb8449263a02/0x0.jpg?width=960&amp;precrop=4326%2C2435%2Cx0%2Cy447</image_url><description>The RAC Arena in Perth, Australia, will rock, and the fans will be loudly supporting the local fighters on Saturday, August 17, for UFC 305.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 03:12:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What are you thinking about?</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/07/what-are-you-thinking-about/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>A philosopher can spend a month, a year or a career thinking about one knotty problem. Making assertions, testing theories, understanding how others are thinking about it as well. But this exercise shouldn&amp;#8217;t be reserved for academics. What are you working on? When will you change your mind? What can you learn, what can you [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 09:16:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>