<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 11:47:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>In Photos: First-Ever Moon-Earth Flyby From Jupiter-Bound Spacecraft</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jamiecartereurope/2024/08/20/in-photos-first-ever-moon-earth-flyby-from-jupiter-bound-spacecraft/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66c4b60b18b9a443a4db31f6/0x0.jpg?width=960&amp;precrop=2540%2C1428%2Cx4%2Cy0</image_url><description>In the first-ever lunar-Earth flyby, the European Space Agency's JUICE spacecraft flew over South East Asia and the Pacific Ocean.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 16:43:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Non-professional writers</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/non-professional-writers/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Nobody asks you to design a bridge, write a sonnet or do open heart surgery. We leave these essential tasks to trained professionals. But many job descriptions carry the unstated addendum, “and write.” Write memos, proposals, and even instruction manuals. The local supermarket is reducing its hours for the summer (well deserved). The sign they […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 09:25:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bluesound Unveils Three New NODE Wireless Music Streamers</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/marksparrow/2024/08/20/bluesound-unveils-three-new-node-wireless-music-streamers/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66c4b14a144b7b6edf4c1f3d/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>The three new wireless streamers from Bluesound are the NODE NANO, NODE and NODE ICON. From entry level to flagship, these streamers have all been redesigned.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 16:25:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The prevailing conditions</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/the-prevailing-conditions/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>It doesn’t matter how hard you try, you’re not going to change the direction of the wind. That doesn’t mean you can’t get good at sailing, though. And yes, if we do try, we can change the conditions in our household, community or workplace. It might feel like wind, but it’s caused by us and […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 09:41:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New WhatsApp Update Should Stop You Using RCS On Your iPhone</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/zakdoffman/2024/08/20/forget-iphone-16-and-ios-18-whatsapp-update-should-stop-you-using-rcs/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66c4aa8b2953c90d3a79a343/0x0.jpg?width=960&amp;precrop=1193%2C849%2Cx135%2Cy345</image_url><description>Forget iOS 18 and RCS—WhatsApp’s clever new trick could be its biggest update in years.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 16:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The landlord and the creative coach</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/the-landlord-and-the-creative-coach/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>The conflict is real. “Jean-Michel [Basquiat] called,” Mr. Warhol wrote in his diary on Sept. 5, 1983. “He’s afraid he’s just going to be a flash in the pan. And I told him not to worry, that he wouldn’t be. But then I got scared because he’s rented our building on Great Jones and what […]</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 09:47:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Find Salewa Kits In ‘Escape From Tarkov’ For The Shortage Quest</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/mikestubbs/2024/08/20/how-to-find-salewa-kits-in-escape-from-tarkov-for-the-shortage-quest/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66b73ec97121a75d66f8943e/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>One of the more annoying quests in the early stages of an Escape From Tarkov wipe is actually very easy if you know where to look for Salewa kits.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 16:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In defense of the hard parts</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/in-defense-of-the-hard-parts/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Yesterday’s post was a little glib. Without a doubt, we add more value when we focus on the emotional labor of important work, leaving others the chance to create commodities. But the repetitive, difficult nature of leaning into commodity production can give us insight, humility and skill. It helps us understand just how hard the […]</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 10:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gun Violence In Rural America Rises When Deer Hunting Season Begins</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/grrlscientist/2024/08/20/gun-violence-in-rural-america-rises-when-deer-hunting-season-begins/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66c4809ca09a9201343b9f81/0x0.jpg?width=960&amp;precrop=1280%2C721%2Cx0%2Cy88</image_url><description>Is there an association between opening the deer hunting season and shootings in rural US counties?</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 16:05:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The hard parts (and the important parts)</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/the-hard-parts-and-the-important-parts/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>The hard parts of what you do all day can feel fraught. It’s heavy lifting. Emergencies. Dangerous labor. The stakes are high and the work can be difficult. The important parts of what you do all day are valuable to someone else. This is what you’re getting paid for–solving a customer’s problems. A simple example: […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 08:23:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>