<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 13:26:01 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>How To Maximize (And Minimize) Technology To Boost Sustainability</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/councils/forbestechcouncil/2024/08/21/how-to-maximize-and-minimize-technology-to-boost-sustainability/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66c5f061a10e705ab2b467bb/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>Balancing leveraging technology for more sustainable operations with leaning on energy-consuming digital tools and processes can be a complicated challenge.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 18:15:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anonymity and Bugs Bunny</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/anonymity-and-bugs-bunny/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>I came across this (ironically) anonymous quote recently: “The offline world is full of sticks, but the internet only has carrots.” When we come together in groups, it can bring out the best in people. When those groups are anonymous, porous and transient, though, the opposite can happen. And mobs never helped anyone, ever.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 09:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Vertigo 70mm Print Headlines “Big &amp; Loud” Season At New York’s Paris Theater</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/bennyhareven/2024/08/21/new-vertigo-70mm-print-headlines-big--loud-season-at-new-yorks-paris-theater/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66c61639e1211d5a7d993a10/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>For fans of 70mm film New York is the place to be this weekend as the ‘Big &amp; Loud’ season returns to The Paris Theater in Manhattan.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 17:37:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Non-professional writers</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/non-professional-writers/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Nobody asks you to design a bridge, write a sonnet or do open heart surgery. We leave these essential tasks to trained professionals. But many job descriptions carry the unstated addendum, “and write.” Write memos, proposals, and even instruction manuals. The local supermarket is reducing its hours for the summer (well deserved). The sign they […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 09:25:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rembrandt Created His Own Gold-Like Paint For The Night Watch</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/evaamsen/2024/08/21/rembrandt-created-his-own-gold-like-paint-for-the-night-watch/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66c60fe3c671c1a881066186/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>Researchers at the Rijksmuseum in Amsterdam used chemistry methods to learn how Rembrandt mixed different pigments to create a realistic color gold in The Night Watch.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 17:05:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The prevailing conditions</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/the-prevailing-conditions/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>It doesn’t matter how hard you try, you’re not going to change the direction of the wind. That doesn’t mean you can’t get good at sailing, though. And yes, if we do try, we can change the conditions in our household, community or workplace. It might feel like wind, but it’s caused by us and […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 09:41:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Beats Studio Pro Just Gained A New Audio Feature: How To Get It</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2024/08/21/beats-studio-pro-just-gained-a-new-audio-feature-how-to-get-it/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66c60de96236e003b7d44a91/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>If you have a pair of Beats Studio Pro headphones, they’ve suddenly gained a new, more sociable, listening feature.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 17:00:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The landlord and the creative coach</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/the-landlord-and-the-creative-coach/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>The conflict is real. “Jean-Michel [Basquiat] called,” Mr. Warhol wrote in his diary on Sept. 5, 1983. “He’s afraid he’s just going to be a flash in the pan. And I told him not to worry, that he wouldn’t be. But then I got scared because he’s rented our building on Great Jones and what […]</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 09:47:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NIST Ratifies Quantum Safe Algorithms Co-Developed By IBM Research</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/karlfreund/2024/08/21/nist-ratifies-quantum-safe-algorithms-co-developed-by-ibm-research/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/668d870e917845053aa448f6/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>The new algorithms have now been approved by the US NIST for use.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 16:58:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In defense of the hard parts</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/in-defense-of-the-hard-parts/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Yesterday’s post was a little glib. Without a doubt, we add more value when we focus on the emotional labor of important work, leaving others the chance to create commodities. But the repetitive, difficult nature of leaning into commodity production can give us insight, humility and skill. It helps us understand just how hard the […]</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 10:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>