<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 08:10:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>CrowdStrike Reveals What Happened, Why—And What’s Changed</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/kateoflahertyuk/2024/08/07/crowdstrike-reveals-what-happened-why-and-whats-changed/</link><description>CrowdStrike has published its Root Cause Analysis report, an investigation into what caused the IT outage in July. Here's what it says.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 13:03:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Misunderstanding bigness</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/misunderstanding-bigness/</link><description>IBM spent a fortune fighting calls for them to be broken up. So did AT&amp;T and Microsoft. In all three cases, there’s plenty of evidence that they would have been better off if they had simply broken themselves up. Microsoft is still recovering and IBM never will. One computer company, one phone company, one software […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 09:09:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mobile Ads: Best Practices, Benefits And Challenges</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2024/08/07/mobile-ads-best-practices-benefits-and-challenges/</link><description>If you’re ready to pan for gold in mobile advertising, keep concerns like data, privacy and user experience in mind.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The challenge of “a risky scheme”</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/the-power-of-a-risky-scheme/</link><description>New ideas aren’t adopted all at once. A few people go first while the rest of us watch to see how it goes. “Look, Mikey, he likes it!” This is the story of tech innovations, dance crazes and even food. Ideas spread horizontally, and people who prefer the status quo will embrace an idea only […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 09:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seven Business Development Tips For B2B Tech Startups</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2024/08/07/seven-business-development-tips-for-b2b-tech-startups/</link><description>By developing an effective business development plan, you can draw a roadmap to achieve all your goals easily in the long run.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Learning in August</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/learning-in-august/</link><description>What better time? An hour a day for a month and you can learn a skill you’ll have forever. Beach reads are a fine way to chill out, but a month spent to learn a skill is a fine way to take advantage of a quiet time. My brand new course on Strategy is now […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 09:47:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Digital Control Tower: Beyond Supply Chain And Manufacturing</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2024/08/07/the-digital-control-tower-beyond-supply-chain-and-manufacturing/</link><description>For many businesses, the digital control tower has become a transformative tool that offers visibility, agility and efficiency.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Reclaiming “fiasco”</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/reclaiming-fiasco/</link><description>Usually modified with “total,” the failure might not be as bad as we fear. The origin of the word probably comes from Italian, a long time ago. The person who loses a round in a game has to buy the next bottle for the group (from: flask). Which means that there is going to be […]</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 09:24:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wegovy And Zepbound Doses Available Again After Months Of Shortages, FDA Says—But Supplies Are Still Limited</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/roberthart/2024/08/07/wegovy-and-zepbound-doses-available-again-after-months-of-shortages-fda-says-but-supplies-are-still-limited/</link><description>Novo and Lilly have struggled to keep up with demand for semaglutide and tirzepatide—generic names for Ozempic, Wegovy, Mounjaro and Zepbound—and there have been reports people with diabetes have struggled to access the drugs as more people use them to lose weight.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:28:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Mississippi River paradox</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/the-mississippi-river-paradox/</link><description>There’s no water in that river that was there ten years ago. The boundaries have shifted in that time as well, there’s no riverbank that’s exactly where it was. And the silt and the fish have all moved too. So, what’s “the Mississippi River”? It’s a label, a placeholder, and a marker–when the Mississippi does […]</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 08:06:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Rise Of Labs: Driving Innovation In Modern Enterprises</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2024/08/07/the-rise-of-labs-driving-innovation-in-modern-enterprises/</link><description>A strategic approach to developing successful labs can better enable enterprises to achieve more with less, save money and create new revenue opportunities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Infamy</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/infamy/</link><description>We’ve gotten so hung up on famous that it’s easy to forget that there are two kinds of renown. Being known for lowering the standards of discourse, cheating, or whining is a choice, but why would you trade your reputation to become infamous?</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 09:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Farewell To Fighting: It’s Time To Embrace A Go-To-Market Offense</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2024/08/07/farewell-to-fighting-its-time-to-embrace-a-go-to-market-offense/</link><description>If you want your CS team to be a revenue driver, you must go beyond asking them to hit a number.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stopping a runaway train</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/stopping-a-runaway-train/</link><description>It feels urgent because it is. But by the time the train is running away, it might be too late. The better strategy is to not sign up for trains that are likely to run away. The first principle of risk reduction is to figure out if you can stop it later. If you can’t, […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 10:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Generative AI Will Replace Everything: Rethinking User Experience</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2024/08/07/generative-ai-will-replace-everything-rethinking-user-experience/</link><description>Generative and conversational AI will cause companies to rethink how they approach user experience in the coming years.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 11:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The tooth fairy</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/07/the-tooth-fairy/</link><description>Make a list of things you used to believe. Fervently, certainly, completely. Things that you were sure of, but now, with the passage of time and the benefit of experience, you know to be incorrect or incomplete. Of course, it’s not just mythical creatures beloved by children. It’s our adherence to a social norm, loyalty […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 08:46:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CVS Health CEO Takes Charge At Aetna After Insurer’s Latest Miss</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brucejapsen/2024/08/07/cvs-health-ceo-to-take-charge-at-aetna-after-insurers-latest-miss/</link><description>CVS Health CEO Karen Lynch is taking over “day-to-day management” of the company’s Aetna health insurance business after its latest poor performance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 11:30:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The last little bit</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/07/the-last-little-bit/</link><description>Important hills usually get much steeper at the top. 99% of the training in competitive athletics is devoted to the last 1% of performance. A tenth of a second. The same is true for squeezing the last bit of performance out of a car, a grape or a semiconductor. And healthcare, luxury goods and science […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 09:14:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Startup Raised $25 Million To Keep Data Safe While Training AI</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/kirkogunrinde/2024/08/07/this-startup-raised-25-million-to-keep-data-safe-while-training-ai/</link><description>“Confidential computing” startup Anjuna aims to make it possible for its customers to use sensitive data for a variety of tasks without compromising privacy.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What are you thinking about?</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/07/what-are-you-thinking-about/</link><description>A philosopher can spend a month, a year or a career thinking about one knotty problem. Making assertions, testing theories, understanding how others are thinking about it as well. But this exercise shouldn’t be reserved for academics. What are you working on? When will you change your mind? What can you learn, what can you […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 09:16:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adjusting Your Security Speed To Keep Pace With SaaS Risks</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2024/08/07/adjusting-your-security-speed-to-keep-pace-with-saas-risks/</link><description>The interconnected nature of SaaS offerings means that a vulnerability in one application can affect the entire supply chain.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Secretive Billionaire Thinks He Can Cure HIV. Here’s Why.</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/katiejennings/2024/08/07/this-secretive-billionaire-thinks-he-can-cure-hiv-heres-why/</link><description>By bringing together top doctors, scientists and engineers, Terry Ragon believes he can succeed where major governments have failed and cure one of the world’s wiliest viruses.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Winning AI: A Three-Legged Stool</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2024/08/07/winning-ai-a-three-legged-stool/</link><description>By focusing on using AI to make your company better, you’ll more easily, reliably, safely and quickly recognize gains from the three legs of the generative AI industry.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 11:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From Cab To Console, Einride’s First Remote Electric RoboTruck Driver</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/edgarsten/2024/08/07/from-cab-to-console-einrides-first-remote-electric-robotruck-driver/</link><description>After a decade in the cab of big rigs, Tiffany Heathcott is still delivering the goods aboard commercial trucks, only she's far from the drivers seat.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 11:09:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hurricane Irma Inspired Engineers To Invent Self-Watering Planter</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/marksparrow/2024/08/07/hurricane-irma-inspired-engineers-to-invent-self-watering-planter/</link><description>If you love your house plants but don't want to give up vacations, this self-watering planter can keep up to five house plants happy and healthy by creating its own water</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 11:04:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Another Profitable Quarter For Oscar Health As Obamacare Business Grows</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brucejapsen/2024/08/07/another-profitable-quarter-for-oscar-health-as-obamacare-business-grows/</link><description>Oscar Health reported $56 million in net income – its second quarterly profit in the company’s 12-year history – as the provider of Obamacare grows its market share.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 11:00:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Insurance Organizations Should Know About Open-Source AI</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2024/08/07/what-insurance-organizations-should-know-about-open-source-ai/</link><description>The integration of open-source AI solutions has been transformative in the insurance industry, offering a new level of transparency and collaboration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NASA Urges Public To Leave The City For The Perseid Meteor Shower This Weekend</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jamiecartereurope/2024/08/07/nasa-urges-public-to-leave-the-city-for-the-perseid-meteor-shower-this-weekend/</link><description>According to NASA, here's when and how to best see the Perseid meteor shower this weekend, as well as where to look and why to dress warmly.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 10:55:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Flighty 4.0: The iPhone Flight Tracking App Just Launched A Major Upgrade</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2024/08/07/flighty-40-the-iphone-flight-tracking-app-just-launched-a-major-upgrade/</link><description>The latest version of the popular flyer’s app adds a new feature which not only predicts delays but tells you why you’re waiting.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 10:00:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The ‘Escape From Tarkov’ Wipe Probably Isn’t Coming This Week Afterall</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/mikestubbs/2024/08/07/the-escape-from-tarkov-wipe-probably-isnt-coming-this-week-afterall/</link><description>Some new info from members of the Escape From Tarkov development team suggests that the next wipe might not launch this week as we initially thought.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 09:56:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How The U.S. Could Transform Its Drone Industry For The Price Of One F-35</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidhambling/2024/08/07/how-the-us-could-transform-its-drone-industry-for-the-price-of-one-f-35/</link><description>George Matus, founder and CEO of drone maker Teal, argues that a just small investment would enable the Pentagon to mass produce small combat drones at low cost.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 09:40:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Harnessing Generative AI For Sustainable Food Systems Innovation</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/daphneewingchow/2024/08/07/harnessing-generative-ai-for-sustainable-food-systems-innovation/</link><description>Generative AI is emerging as a game-changer in driving innovation, with significant social and environmental potential at the food-health-climate nexus.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 09:32:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ozempic Maker Novo Nordisk Sinks On Disappointing Earnings</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/roberthart/2024/08/07/ozempic-maker-novo-nordisk-sinks-on-disappointing-earnings-amid-booming-demand-for-weight-loss-and-diabetes-drugs/</link><description>Novo Nordisk’s growth has slowed in recent weeks as the company struggles to produce enough semaglutide to meet stellar demand for Wegovy and Ozempic.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 09:19:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple iPhone 16, iPhone 16 Pro Release Date: New Report Reveals Extraordinary Strategy</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2024/08/07/apple-iphone-16-iphone-16-pro-release-date-new-report-reveals-extraordinary-strategy/</link><description>It’s a little over a month, it seems, before Apple will announce its next iPhones—and an industry heavyweight just disclosed an interesting theory.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 08:56:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Google Updates Millions Of Pixel Phones—Dangerous New Threat Confirmed</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/zakdoffman/2024/08/07/google-pixel-8a-pixel-8-pro-android-update-warning-pixel-9-and-android-15-coming/</link><description>You must update your device as soon as possible.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 08:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>