<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 06:56:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Multi-Sector Partnerships: Key To Catalyzing Climate, Education And Health Impact In Asia</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/philanthropy-asia-alliance/2024/08/16/multi-sector-partnerships-key-to-catalyzing-climate-education-and-health-impact-in-asia/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66b36f7b89d5c8fbeeb4ec4d/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>In partnership with key stakeholders in the public and private sectors, Asia’s philanthropy sector has the potential to tackle some of the world's greatest challenges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:53:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The hard parts (and the important parts)</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/the-hard-parts-and-the-important-parts/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>The hard parts of what you do all day can feel fraught. It’s heavy lifting. Emergencies. Dangerous labor. The stakes are high and the work can be difficult. The important parts of what you do all day are valuable to someone else. This is what you’re getting paid for–solving a customer’s problems. A simple example: […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 08:23:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Winning Over Gen Z: Tech Strategies To Attract, Train And Retain The Emerging Workforce</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/councils/forbestechcouncil/2024/08/16/winning-over-gen-z-tech-strategies-to-attract-train-and-retain-the-emerging-workforce/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/6318cca5a78e6d3524d70386/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>With a tight labor market, business leaders must find ways to attract and retain Gen Z workers while adding value to their businesses.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The paradox of lottery thinking</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/the-paradox-of-lottery-thinking/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Tim Brownson points us to this recent poll of people in Great Britain. About one out of four people surveyed (of all ages) believe that they could qualify for the Olympics if they trained for the next four years. This is absurd. It’s the very absurdity of it that makes it common. “I could do […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 09:27:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mpox Vaccine Maker’s Shares Continue Rising As Concern Over Virus Outbreak Grows</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/roberthart/2024/08/16/mpox-vaccine-makers-shares-continue-rising-as-concern-over-virus-outbreak-grows/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66bf28d935123c881510951d/0x0.jpg?width=960&amp;precrop=3600%2C2026%2Cx0%2Cy176</image_url><description>There are several vaccines approved to use against mpox and stock for the favored shot have risen more than 40% this week.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:34:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Long-term selfish</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/long-term-selfish/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Everyone is selfish. We do things that increase our chances of survival, help us achieve our goals and give us a story we can tell ourselves about our role in the community. But short-term selfish is something we try to grow out of. Short-term selfish runs a red light because we’re in a hurry. It […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 09:34:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Understanding Experience Creep: How Laggard Industries Can Catch Up</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/councils/forbestechcouncil/2024/08/16/understanding-experience-creep-how-laggard-industries-can-catch-up/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66be3c989517550736259e03/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>Leveraged in the right way, AI can enhance customer engagement, enable data analysis, automate processes, give strategic guidance and improve decision-making.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Multiple choice</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/multiple-choice/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>“None of the above” is often the best option. We’re regularly confronted with multiple-choice questions. The foundation is already established, the options are already limited, do you want this or that? But the real questions lie in the assumptions that happened before you were even asked. When a developer brings you six website options, they’re […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 09:12:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Integrated Data Ecosystems Could Transform The Construction Industry</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/councils/forbestechcouncil/2024/08/16/integrated-data-ecosystems-could-transform-the-construction-industry/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66be3aa2e59c339afe475a6a/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>I believe the free movement of data between systems and workflows is the next great unlock in construction productivity.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mediocrity and perfectionism</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/mediocrity-and-perfectionism/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>It’s surprising to realize that they’re the same. They are both places to hide. When we ship average work, it’s not our fault. We’re simply doing what the manual says, and if you don’t like it, blame the culture and the system. And when we hold back on shipping because it isn’t perfect, we’re also […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 09:31:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>