<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 06:58:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Warning Issued As Hackers Fake Google’s 2FA App To Steal Your Data</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/daveywinder/2024/08/02/warning-issued-as-hackers-fake-googles-2fa-app-to-steal-your-data/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66aca5e133adbe4d46fb3bb0/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>Google ads for Google Authenticator on Google search may not be genuine even when verified by Google. The worrying case of a fake 2FA app malware attack.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 11:48:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Infamy</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/infamy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>We&amp;#8217;ve gotten so hung up on famous that it&amp;#8217;s easy to forget that there are two kinds of renown. Being known for lowering the standards of discourse, cheating, or whining is a choice, but why would you trade your reputation to become infamous?</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 09:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Using AI And Data To Get Hyperpersonal With Customers</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2024/08/02/using-ai-and-data-to-get-hyperpersonal-with-customers/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66abb627b2b6be2f0dae5589/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>Knowing a customer inside and out and delivering highly tailored products and services across all channels has become a key goal for marketers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 11:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stopping a runaway train</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/stopping-a-runaway-train/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>It feels urgent because it is. But by the time the train is running away, it might be too late. The better strategy is to not sign up for trains that are likely to run away. The first principle of risk reduction is to figure out if you can stop it later. If you can&amp;#8217;t, [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 10:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Olympic Medallists Champion The Environment During Paris 2024</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/clairepoolesp/2024/08/02/olympic-medallists-champion-the-environment-during-paris-2024/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66a7579eec30680e32bf14a6/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>Paris 2024 athletes are using their visibility to raise awareness on climate and biodiversity, from skateboarder Rayssa Leal, Rugby 7s Alena Olsen and rower Imogen Grant</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 11:41:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The tooth fairy</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/07/the-tooth-fairy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Make a list of things you used to believe. Fervently, certainly, completely. Things that you were sure of, but now, with the passage of time and the benefit of experience, you know to be incorrect or incomplete. Of course, it&amp;#8217;s not just mythical creatures beloved by children. It&amp;#8217;s our adherence to a social norm, loyalty [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 08:46:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kamala Harris Memes Helped Launch Her Campaign With A Bang. Can It Last?</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jacobwendler/2024/08/02/kamala-harris-memes-helped-launch-her-campaign-with-a-bang-can-it-last/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66ac2470b541c7ba39b518b3/0x0.jpg?width=960&amp;precrop=3534%2C1988%2Cx0%2Cy14</image_url><description>The Harris campaign is betting big on content creators to keep the momentum going after a viral first week.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The last little bit</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/07/the-last-little-bit/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Important hills usually get much steeper at the top. 99% of the training in competitive athletics is devoted to the last 1% of performance. A tenth of a second. The same is true for squeezing the last bit of performance out of a car, a grape or a semiconductor. And healthcare, luxury goods and science [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 09:14:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Global Shift To Vulnerable VPNs: Is The VPN Doomed?</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2024/08/02/the-global-shift-to-vulnerable-vpns-is-the-vpn-doomed/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/62027d69dec788bb92b9a317/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>Zero trust and SASE frameworks provide an advantage in this regard, offering built-in compliance features and the flexibility to adapt to evolving regulatory landscapes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What are you thinking about?</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/07/what-are-you-thinking-about/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>A philosopher can spend a month, a year or a career thinking about one knotty problem. Making assertions, testing theories, understanding how others are thinking about it as well. But this exercise shouldn&amp;#8217;t be reserved for academics. What are you working on? When will you change your mind? What can you learn, what can you [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 09:16:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>