<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 07:09:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Content Distributors Must Take Heed In The Wake Of The Recent Global Cyber Outage</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/councils/forbestechcouncil/2024/08/21/content-distributors-must-take-heed-in-the-wake-of-the-recent-global-cyber-outage/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66c4b827fd30c69e7266ad9c/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>The Crowdstrike incident serves as a stark reminder of the potential risks of interconnectivity in a digital, cloud-based society.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anonymity and Bugs Bunny</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/anonymity-and-bugs-bunny/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>I came across this (ironically) anonymous quote recently: “The offline world is full of sticks, but the internet only has carrots.” When we come together in groups, it can bring out the best in people. When those groups are anonymous, porous and transient, though, the opposite can happen. And mobs never helped anyone, ever.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 09:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>LEGO ‘Super Mario Kart’ Is Finally Here, But Not As You May Hope</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/mattgardner1/2024/08/21/lego-super-mario-kart-is-finally-here-but-not-as-you-may-hope/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66c5c4baccb730cfebdf903a/0x0.jpg?width=960&amp;precrop=1711%2C802%2Cx266%2Cy561</image_url><description>‘Mario Kart’ has finally been committed to LEGO bricks, but collectors looking for a display piece probably won’t find what they’re looking for.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 11:49:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Non-professional writers</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/non-professional-writers/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Nobody asks you to design a bridge, write a sonnet or do open heart surgery. We leave these essential tasks to trained professionals. But many job descriptions carry the unstated addendum, “and write.” Write memos, proposals, and even instruction manuals. The local supermarket is reducing its hours for the summer (well deserved). The sign they […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 09:25:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Embracing Autonomous Building Technology: You Must Do Your Homework</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/councils/forbestechcouncil/2024/08/21/embracing-autonomous-building-technology-you-must-do-your-homework/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66c4b6285ef0136e389738e1/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>Over the next decade, advanced ML- and AI-driven solutions will become more prevalent, as organizations upgrade from “IoT,” “smart” and “connected” technology sets.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 11:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The prevailing conditions</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/the-prevailing-conditions/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>It doesn’t matter how hard you try, you’re not going to change the direction of the wind. That doesn’t mean you can’t get good at sailing, though. And yes, if we do try, we can change the conditions in our household, community or workplace. It might feel like wind, but it’s caused by us and […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 09:41:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Digital Rx: Arogga Fights Counterfeit Meds In Bangladesh</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/geristengel/2024/08/21/digital-rx-arogga-fights-counterfeit-meds-in-bangladesh/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66c3ba6bb69e4e9fcffc9caa/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>Arogga—an ecommerce pharmacy—is tackling counterfeit medication in Bangladesh. Female investors helped the female founder overcome the challenges of the VC winter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 11:44:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The landlord and the creative coach</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/the-landlord-and-the-creative-coach/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>The conflict is real. “Jean-Michel [Basquiat] called,” Mr. Warhol wrote in his diary on Sept. 5, 1983. “He’s afraid he’s just going to be a flash in the pan. And I told him not to worry, that he wouldn’t be. But then I got scared because he’s rented our building on Great Jones and what […]</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 09:47:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Future-Proofing Your Organization: Finance Embraces The Digital Revolution</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/councils/forbestechcouncil/2024/08/21/future-proofing-your-organization-finance-embraces-the-digital-revolution/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/649f2a00eb04efff54d23657/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>The digital revolution in finance represents a pivotal opportunity to redefine the finance function's role within the organization.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In defense of the hard parts</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/in-defense-of-the-hard-parts/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Yesterday’s post was a little glib. Without a doubt, we add more value when we focus on the emotional labor of important work, leaving others the chance to create commodities. But the repetitive, difficult nature of leaning into commodity production can give us insight, humility and skill. It helps us understand just how hard the […]</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 10:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>