<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 12:07:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Microsoft Update Warning—‘Malicious’ New Attack Steals Bitcoin, Ethereum, Crypto From Windows Users</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/zakdoffman/2024/08/16/microsoft-windows-warning-malicious-new-attack-steals-all-your-bitcoin-ethereum-crypto/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66bf0f195043f3abba412101/0x0.jpg?width=960&amp;precrop=1528%2C1007%2Cx1032%2Cy651</image_url><description>Exclusive—Do not let this dangerous new crypto stealing threat onto your PC.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The hard parts (and the important parts)</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/the-hard-parts-and-the-important-parts/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>The hard parts of what you do all day can feel fraught. It’s heavy lifting. Emergencies. Dangerous labor. The stakes are high and the work can be difficult. The important parts of what you do all day are valuable to someone else. This is what you’re getting paid for–solving a customer’s problems. A simple example: […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 08:23:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Katie Ledecky Has POTS, Postural Orthostatic Tachycardia Syndrome</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brucelee/2024/08/16/katie-ledecky-has-pots-postural-orthostatic-tachycardia-syndrome/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66bf6c55e934860255c33c77/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>Nine-time U.S. Olympic gold medalist swimmer Katie Ledecky has had to deal with POTS, postural orthostatic tachycardia syndrome, since being diagnosed in 2015.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 16:26:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The paradox of lottery thinking</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/the-paradox-of-lottery-thinking/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Tim Brownson points us to this recent poll of people in Great Britain. About one out of four people surveyed (of all ages) believe that they could qualify for the Olympics if they trained for the next four years. This is absurd. It’s the very absurdity of it that makes it common. “I could do […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 09:27:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Steve Wozniak Cofounded Startup Aims To Be A One-Stop Shop For Space-Based Data</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/allisonbeck/2024/08/16/this-steve-wozniak-cofounded-startup-aims-to-be-a-one-stop-shop-for-space-based-data/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66bf5fc36bf2af24850e2b9f/0x0.jpg?width=960&amp;precrop=2559%2C1439%2Cx0%2Cy0</image_url><description>Privateer, cofounded by Apple and NASA vets, wants to make satellite data as ubiquitous as GPS with a platform providing insight on disasters, logistics and even pirates.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 15:53:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Long-term selfish</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/long-term-selfish/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Everyone is selfish. We do things that increase our chances of survival, help us achieve our goals and give us a story we can tell ourselves about our role in the community. But short-term selfish is something we try to grow out of. Short-term selfish runs a red light because we’re in a hurry. It […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 09:34:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mpox, Explained: What To Know About Variants, Vaccines And Where Outbreaks Are After WHO Sounds Alarm</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/roberthart/2024/08/16/mpox-explained-what-to-know-about-variants-vaccines-and-where-outbreaks-are-after-who-sounds-alarm/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66bf652df72659103f85a8aa/0x0.jpg?width=960&amp;precrop=3000%2C1689%2Cx0%2Cy165</image_url><description>Officials in Pakistan said they are investigating a confirmed case of mpox to see whether the variant involved is the same linked to the growing outbreak in central Africa.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 15:42:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Multiple choice</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/multiple-choice/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>“None of the above” is often the best option. We’re regularly confronted with multiple-choice questions. The foundation is already established, the options are already limited, do you want this or that? But the real questions lie in the assumptions that happened before you were even asked. When a developer brings you six website options, they’re […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 09:12:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Victrola Unveils Automatic Turntable For Vinyl With Bluetooth Built In</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/marksparrow/2024/08/16/victrola-unveils-automatic-turntable-for-vinyl-with-bluetooth-built-in/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66bf6309703c1e59bdbfce58/0x0.jpg?width=960&amp;precrop=1200%2C933%2Cx0%2Cy141</image_url><description>If you're looking for a fuss-free vinyl turntable, the Victrola Automatic does everything including transmitting to powered speakers and headphones via Bluetooth.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 15:37:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mediocrity and perfectionism</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/mediocrity-and-perfectionism/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>It’s surprising to realize that they’re the same. They are both places to hide. When we ship average work, it’s not our fault. We’re simply doing what the manual says, and if you don’t like it, blame the culture and the system. And when we hold back on shipping because it isn’t perfect, we’re also […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 09:31:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>