<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 06:52:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The Future Of Retail Trading: Bots And Automated Tools</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2024/07/31/the-future-of-retail-trading-bots-and-automated-tools/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/62e00f7a264882142d133856/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>The democratization of trading tools has made automated platforms accessible to retail traders.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 11:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The tooth fairy</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/07/the-tooth-fairy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>Make a list of things you used to believe. Fervently, certainly, completely. Things that you were sure of, but now, with the passage of time and the benefit of experience, you know to be incorrect or incomplete. Of course, it&amp;#8217;s not just mythical creatures beloved by children. It&amp;#8217;s our adherence to a social norm, loyalty [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 08:46:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meet The 26-Year-Old Building A Billion Dollar Prediction Marketplace</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ninabambysheva/2024/07/31/meet-the-26-year-old-building-a-billion-dollar-prediction-marketplace/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66a7dd662878813309bb9e72/0x0.jpg?width=960&amp;precrop=1920%2C1080%2Cx0%2Cy0</image_url><description>Will Taylor Swift get engaged in 2024? Will JD Vance be replaced as veep nominee? Despite its questionable legality, hundreds of millions in crypto are being wagered on events like these on Polymarket.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The last little bit</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/07/the-last-little-bit/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>Important hills usually get much steeper at the top. 99% of the training in competitive athletics is devoted to the last 1% of performance. A tenth of a second. The same is true for squeezing the last bit of performance out of a car, a grape or a semiconductor. And healthcare, luxury goods and science [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 09:14:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Swiss VR Startup Wants To Transform Pilot Training–And It Just Won A Boost From FAA</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jeremybogaisky/2024/07/31/a-swiss-vr-startup-wants-to-transform-pilot-trainingand-it-just-won-a-boost-from-faa/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66a99cd61d33a8dd9d43962f/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>Loft Dynamics' flight simulator–a tenth the size and 20th the cost of the hulking models currently used–is the first VR trainer to win FAA approval. Could it help solve airlines’ pilot shortage?</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What are you thinking about?</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/07/what-are-you-thinking-about/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>A philosopher can spend a month, a year or a career thinking about one knotty problem. Making assertions, testing theories, understanding how others are thinking about it as well. But this exercise shouldn&amp;#8217;t be reserved for academics. What are you working on? When will you change your mind? What can you learn, what can you [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 09:16:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Data Center Cooling: A CFO’s Call To Action</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2024/07/31/data-center-cooling-a-cfos-call-to-action/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66104eb85d449026d07c25bb/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>While CFOs are not usually immersed in the technical intricacies of data center operations, they bring an important perspective to the discussion.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>“It seems…”</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/07/it-seems/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>What a simple verb. A five-letter modifier that opens the door to discussion. If we state something as a fact, we&amp;#8217;re asking for an argument. But seems opens the door to learning and discussion. What are you seeing that I&amp;#8217;m not seeing?</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 08:08:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Record-Breaking $75 Million Ransom Paid To Dark Angels Gang</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/daveywinder/2024/07/31/record-breaking-75-million-ransom-paid-to-dark-angels-gang/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66a8c6beb5769b3c032f9cdb/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>You may not have heard of these ransomware criminals, but according to threat intelligence researchers, they’ve hit a $75 million ransom payday. Meet the Dark Angels.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 11:18:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Zoom stretch</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/07/the-zoom-stretch/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>There are a lot of structural reasons why in-person meetings don&amp;#8217;t involve a break every 12 minutes. It takes too long to stop and start. But those rules don&amp;#8217;t apply to Zoom. Screens off! Stand up. We&amp;#8217;ll be back in 60 seconds. If it&amp;#8217;s not worth coming back, the meeting should have ended already. If [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 09:04:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>