<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 12:43:09 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>‘Fortnite’ Chapter 5, Season 4 Is Coming Sooner Than Expected As Season 3 Ends Early</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2024/08/13/fortnite-chapter-5-season-4-is-coming-sooner-than-expected-as-season-3-ends-early/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66ba915faa2077638a379250/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>Everything you need to know about the new season of Fortnite and its big X-Men crossover.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:36:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Multiple choice</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/multiple-choice/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>“None of the above” is often the best option. We’re regularly confronted with multiple-choice questions. The foundation is already established, the options are already limited, do you want this or that? But the real questions lie in the assumptions that happened before you were even asked. When a developer brings you six website options, they’re […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 09:12:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This 300-Year-Old Winemaker Is Embracing AI</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2024/08/13/this-300-year-old-winemaker-is-embracing-ai/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66bb8b2777e6f566b9b0ca33/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>For 300-year-old Bordeaux winemaker Château Ducru-Beaucaillou, embracing new technology while preserving its heritage is a strategic business imperative.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mediocrity and perfectionism</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/mediocrity-and-perfectionism/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>It’s surprising to realize that they’re the same. They are both places to hide. When we ship average work, it’s not our fault. We’re simply doing what the manual says, and if you don’t like it, blame the culture and the system. And when we hold back on shipping because it isn’t perfect, we’re also […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 09:31:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Major Quantum Safe Milestone Reached As NIST Publishes PQC Standards</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/tiriasresearch/2024/08/13/major-quantum-safe-milestone-reached-as-nist-publishes-pqc-standards/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66bb8add69b41fc6d9c7ab4d/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>Migration to quantum safe, and how quickly it can be achieved, is critical to the future of the global digital economy. Welcome to the PQC Era. The work begins now.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:35:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fire inspectors</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/fire-inspectors/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Running into a burning building is heroic work. Keeping buildings from burning down in the first place is actually just as important. And it scales more reliably.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 09:34:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stephen Curry Asking Team USA Ping Pong Players For Their Autograph Is Pure Olympic Gold</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/johnbbrandon/2024/08/13/stephen-curry-asking-team-usa-ping-pong-players-for-their-autograph-is-pure-olympic-gold/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66bb894c98abf3a9d442825b/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>Recently, at the Olympics in Paris that just concluded, the Golden State Warriors all-time scoring leader approached the US Team for the ping pong competition for an autograph.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:35:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Living in the future</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/living-in-the-future/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>In a bad 1950s science fiction movie, you might see flying jetpacks, invisibility cloaks and ray guns. What we got instead is a device that fits in our pocket. It allows us to connect to more than a billion people. It knows where we are and where we’re going. It has all of our contacts, […]</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 09:10:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From Classical IT To AI Jazz.  Time To Get Some Lessons.</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/steveandriole/2024/08/13/from-classical-it-to-ai-jazz--time-to-get-some-lessons/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66b2546895bfccb9ffdacf36/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>The Internet opened a lane for AI – and then AI opened its own lane. But this one is far wider and impactful than the Internet ever was.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adjacent but not relevant</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/adjacent-but-not-relevant/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>There’s a sale on band saw blades, including a really good deal on one that fits the saw you owned years ago. The folks who live next door to the house you used to live in are having a raucous party. A guy with a name just like yours wins the lottery… These adjacencies can […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>