<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 06:59:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>IFi Audio’s Zen Can 3 Is The Best Budget Analog Headphone Amplifier</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/marksparrow/2024/08/18/ifi-audios-zen-can-3-is-the-best-budget-analog-headphone-amplifier/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66bb1e527c0cabd7838066d6/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>This amazing little headphone amplifier can boost the output of a smartphone or digital audio player. Alternatively, it's the perfect way to upgrade any headphone output.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The landlord and the creative coach</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/the-landlord-and-the-creative-coach/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>The conflict is real. “Jean-Michel [Basquiat] called,” Mr. Warhol wrote in his diary on Sept. 5, 1983. “He’s afraid he’s just going to be a flash in the pan. And I told him not to worry, that he wouldn’t be. But then I got scared because he’s rented our building on Great Jones and what […]</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 09:47:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NASA’s Webb Telescope Finds Evidence For An Ocean World Around Uranus</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jamiecartereurope/2024/08/18/nasas-webb-telescope-finds-evidence-for-an-ocean-world-around-uranus/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66a7902cbb2f9655372c3b9e/0x0.jpg?width=960&amp;precrop=4915%2C2765%2Cx0%2Cy406</image_url><description>NASA's Webb Telescope finds evidence for an underground ocean on Uranus moon Ariel, raising interest in future missions to explore the seventh planet and its moons.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In defense of the hard parts</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/in-defense-of-the-hard-parts/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Yesterday’s post was a little glib. Without a doubt, we add more value when we focus on the emotional labor of important work, leaving others the chance to create commodities. But the repetitive, difficult nature of leaning into commodity production can give us insight, humility and skill. It helps us understand just how hard the […]</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 10:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Final ‘Escape From Tarkov’ Pre Wipe Event Features A Fire Sale</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/mikestubbs/2024/08/18/the-final-escape-from-tarkov-pre-wipe-event-features-a-fire-sale/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66b74001086926426a098709/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>What is likely to be the last pre wipe event in Escape From Tarkov is here as all the traders have reduced their prices to pennies.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 10:48:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The hard parts (and the important parts)</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/the-hard-parts-and-the-important-parts/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>The hard parts of what you do all day can feel fraught. It’s heavy lifting. Emergencies. Dangerous labor. The stakes are high and the work can be difficult. The important parts of what you do all day are valuable to someone else. This is what you’re getting paid for–solving a customer’s problems. A simple example: […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 08:23:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Supreme Court Justice Decries The Human Toll Of Too Much Law So Let’s Put Generative AI To Work And Overrule This Problem For Good</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/lanceeliot/2024/08/18/supreme-court-justice-decries-the-human-toll-of-too-much-law-so-lets-put-generative-ai-to-work-and-overrule-this-problem-for-good/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66c18f6453d3f7dbeddeec46/0x0.jpg?width=960&amp;precrop=1618%2C910%2Cx0%2Cy45</image_url><description>Supreme Court Justice Neil Gorsuch has come out with a new book decrying the human tool of too much law. Here's how generative AI can solve or overrule the dire problem.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 07:08:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The paradox of lottery thinking</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/the-paradox-of-lottery-thinking/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Tim Brownson points us to this recent poll of people in Great Britain. About one out of four people surveyed (of all ages) believe that they could qualify for the Olympics if they trained for the next four years. This is absurd. It’s the very absurdity of it that makes it common. “I could do […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 09:27:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>UFC 305 Results: Bonus Winners, Highlights And Reaction</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/brianmazique/2024/08/18/ufc-305-results-bonus-winners-highlights-and-reaction/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66c1841a1d537ab817c757c1/0x0.jpg?width=960&amp;precrop=1608%2C904%2Cx0%2Cy0</image_url><description>Dricus du Plessis successfully defended his UFC middleweight championship on Saturday night in the main event of UFC 305 in Perth, Australia.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 06:19:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Long-term selfish</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/long-term-selfish/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Everyone is selfish. We do things that increase our chances of survival, help us achieve our goals and give us a story we can tell ourselves about our role in the community. But short-term selfish is something we try to grow out of. Short-term selfish runs a red light because we’re in a hurry. It […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 09:34:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>