<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 07:27:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Eli Lilly Surges On Strong Earnings As Mounjaro And Zepbound Sales Soar</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/roberthart/2024/08/08/eli-lilly-surges-on-strong-earnings-as-mounjaro-and-zepbound-sales-soar/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66b483ac209f487b8001c075/0x0.jpg?width=960&amp;precrop=2301%2C1294%2Cx0%2Cy68</image_url><description>Eli Lilly has struggled to meet overwhelming demand for Zepbound and Mounjaro and is already working to see off competition from giants like Roche and Pfizer racing to bring their own obesity drugs to market.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 12:21:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Silence vs noise</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/silence-vs-noise/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent.png</image_url><description>When a group comes together, noise is easy. Just a few people have to make a commotion for noise to happen. But silence requires everyone to be in sync.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 10:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Updated FTC Safeguards Rule: The What, Why And How</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2024/08/08/updated-ftc-safeguards-rule-the-what-why-and-how/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66b39c647144669545864fc2/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>Here are some recommendations and best practices that can help organizations better comply with the FTC Safeguards mandate.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 12:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Misunderstanding bigness</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/misunderstanding-bigness/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent.png</image_url><description>IBM spent a fortune fighting calls for them to be broken up. So did AT&amp;T and Microsoft. In all three cases, there’s plenty of evidence that they would have been better off if they had simply broken themselves up. Microsoft is still recovering and IBM never will. One computer company, one phone company, one software […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 09:09:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Tale Of Two Trade Shows: IMTS And The Detroit Auto Show</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/billkoenig/2024/08/08/a-tale-of-two-trade-shows-imts-and-the-detroit-auto-show/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66b3ebc1ce04923d5ab88f08/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>IMTS and the Detroit Auto Show are trying to navigate challenges facing trade shows in the 21st century. IMTS is going the traditional route. Detroit is making changes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The challenge of “a risky scheme”</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/the-power-of-a-risky-scheme/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent3.png</image_url><description>New ideas aren’t adopted all at once. A few people go first while the rest of us watch to see how it goes. “Look, Mikey, he likes it!” This is the story of tech innovations, dance crazes and even food. Ideas spread horizontally, and people who prefer the status quo will embrace an idea only […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 09:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Invest Wisely To Reduce Your Company’s Exposure To Breaches</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2024/08/08/invest-wisely-to-reduce-your-companys-exposure-to-breaches/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/64959bb3a9cf3119818f46c2/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>With breaches and exposures in every industry continuing to rise, there is an understandable focus on reducing and eliminating breaches.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Learning in August</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/learning-in-august/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent2.png</image_url><description>What better time? An hour a day for a month and you can learn a skill you’ll have forever. Beach reads are a fine way to chill out, but a month spent to learn a skill is a fine way to take advantage of a quiet time. My brand new course on Strategy is now […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 09:47:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Here’s How AI Can Turn Every Decision Into A Data-Driven One</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2024/08/08/heres-how-ai-can-turn-every-decision-into-a-data-driven-one/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/64df7ff50bca66ac42c712fa/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>AI shouldn’t function as the decision-maker but as an indispensable assistant in the decision-making process. Here are the steps to take to make this happen.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 11:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Reclaiming “fiasco”</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/reclaiming-fiasco/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/transparent2.png</image_url><description>Usually modified with “total,” the failure might not be as bad as we fear. The origin of the word probably comes from Italian, a long time ago. The person who loses a round in a game has to buy the next bottle for the group (from: flask). Which means that there is going to be […]</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 09:24:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>