<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 06:55:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Unique Program Puts Seniors In EVs For Free, Reduce Parking Costs</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/edgarsten/2024/08/13/unique-program-puts-seniors-in-evs-for-free-reduce-parking-costs/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66ba5370835bfb5a12edad92/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>Some residents at a retirement home near Toronto are able to borrow an EV at no cost. But they have to make a commitment that requires a major concession.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:51:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Multiple choice</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/multiple-choice/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>“None of the above” is often the best option. We’re regularly confronted with multiple-choice questions. The foundation is already established, the options are already limited, do you want this or that? But the real questions lie in the assumptions that happened before you were even asked. When a developer brings you six website options, they’re […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 09:12:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why The CPO Is Pivotal In Driving Business Transformation</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/councils/forbestechcouncil/2024/08/13/why-the-cpo-is-pivotal-in-driving-business-transformation/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66ba80593deda0371172dd3c/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>The modern CPO’s responsibilities have transcended beyond creating shareholder value to acting as a strategic business partner and organizational catalyst for change.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mediocrity and perfectionism</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/mediocrity-and-perfectionism/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>It’s surprising to realize that they’re the same. They are both places to hide. When we ship average work, it’s not our fault. We’re simply doing what the manual says, and if you don’t like it, blame the culture and the system. And when we hold back on shipping because it isn’t perfect, we’re also […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 09:31:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Forbes Next Billion-Dollar Startups List Has Accurately Predicted 100+ Unicorns In 10 Years</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/amyfeldman/2024/08/13/forbes-next-billion-dollar-startups-list-has-accurately-predicted-100-unicorns-in-10-years/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66baac6e727fce0b0caa6e0e/0x0.jpg?width=960&amp;precrop=2712%2C1525%2Cx0%2Cy4</image_url><description>Of the Next Billion-Dollar Startups list’s 225 alumni, 131, or 58%, became unicorns, including DoorDash, Figma, Anduril, Benchling and Rippling. This year, the list is dominated by artificial intelligence.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fire inspectors</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/fire-inspectors/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Running into a burning building is heroic work. Keeping buildings from burning down in the first place is actually just as important. And it scales more reliably.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 09:34:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How A Former Palantir Exec Built A Google-Like Surveillance Tool For The Police</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/thomasbrewster/2024/08/13/how-a-former-palantir-exec-built-a-google-like-surveillance-tool-for-the-police/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66b4fd1aedd318f58ce9f710/0x0.jpg?width=960&amp;precrop=4180%2C2350%2Cx0%2Cy0</image_url><description>Founded and backed by former Palantir execs, Peregrine hopes to turbocharge local police's access to surveillance data, while curbing cops’ abuses of their technologies.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Living in the future</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/living-in-the-future/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>In a bad 1950s science fiction movie, you might see flying jetpacks, invisibility cloaks and ray guns. What we got instead is a device that fits in our pocket. It allows us to connect to more than a billion people. It knows where we are and where we’re going. It has all of our contacts, […]</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 09:10:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How We Create The Next Billion-Dollar Startups: The Factors That Determine Who Makes The List</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/truebridge/2024/08/13/how-we-create-the-next-billion-dollar-startups-the-factors-that-determine-who-makes-the-list/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66b2642e8db554c9b02aa36c/0x0.jpg?width=960&amp;precrop=3232%2C1818%2Cx0%2Cy7</image_url><description>With more than 55,000 venture-funded private companies in the market, selecting 25 companies with the best potential to hit unicorn status is a challenging task.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adjacent but not relevant</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/adjacent-but-not-relevant/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>There’s a sale on band saw blades, including a really good deal on one that fits the saw you owned years ago. The folks who live next door to the house you used to live in are having a raucous party. A guy with a name just like yours wins the lottery… These adjacencies can […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>