<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 07:26:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>AI's Practical Evolution In Manufacturing And Supply Chains: From Hype To High Returns</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2024/07/29/ais-practical-evolution-in-manufacturing-and-supply-chains-from-hype-to-high-returns/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/6242fa6e9eceb44afd4ab6ab/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>The convergence of AI's continuous learning capabilities with deep domain expertise promises to drive ongoing innovation and transformation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 12:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What are you thinking about?</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/07/what-are-you-thinking-about/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>A philosopher can spend a month, a year or a career thinking about one knotty problem. Making assertions, testing theories, understanding how others are thinking about it as well. But this exercise shouldn&amp;#8217;t be reserved for academics. What are you working on? When will you change your mind? What can you learn, what can you [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 09:16:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kamala Harris And The Climate Change Fight</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/alanohnsman/2024/07/26/kamala-harris-and-the-climate-change-fight-monarch-tractor-costa-samara/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66a3c37b1ce7f0db892908e7/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>In this week's Current Climate newsletter, Kamala Harris and the climate change fight; a big fundraise for electric robot tractors; and transitioning to a zero-carbon economy</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>“It seems…”</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/07/it-seems/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>What a simple verb. A five-letter modifier that opens the door to discussion. If we state something as a fact, we&amp;#8217;re asking for an argument. But seems opens the door to learning and discussion. What are you seeing that I&amp;#8217;m not seeing?</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 08:08:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eliminating Unfair Power Structures To Foster Workplace Innovation</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2024/07/29/eliminating-unfair-power-structures-to-foster-workplace-innovation/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/627114653e082e5a8fa3642a/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>The workplace mafia is a group that dominates promotions, decision-making and the overall office environment through personal connections rather than merit.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Zoom stretch</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/07/the-zoom-stretch/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>There are a lot of structural reasons why in-person meetings don&amp;#8217;t involve a break every 12 minutes. It takes too long to stop and start. But those rules don&amp;#8217;t apply to Zoom. Screens off! Stand up. We&amp;#8217;ll be back in 60 seconds. If it&amp;#8217;s not worth coming back, the meeting should have ended already. If [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 09:04:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Great AI Myth: These 3 Misconceptions Fuel It</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ericsiegel/2024/07/29/the-great-ai-myth-these-3-misconceptions-fuel-it/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66a76609e000b9d4b6a49145/0x0.jpg?width=960&amp;precrop=3000%2C2002%2Cx0%2Cy123</image_url><description>The impending arrival of artificial general intelligence is a story of wish fulfillment that lacks concrete evidence.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 11:47:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Important change is systems change</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/07/important-change-is-systems-change/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Willpower is overrated. If you want to eat healthier, don&amp;#8217;t work hard to avoid stopping at the cookie jar when you walk into the kitchen. Get rid of the cookie jar. Systems are long-lasting, widespread and resilient. We can push back on them with effort, but over time, the system usually comes out ahead. Once [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 09:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Will The Growing Adoption Of Weight Loss Drugs Mean For Customer Behavior?</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2024/07/29/what-will-the-growing-adoption-of-weight-loss-drugs-mean-for-customer-behavior/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66a3da4795b140160b085c68/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>From menus at restaurants and services at health centers to stock at grocery stores and even the locations of each, I believe we are heading for a period of change.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 11:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A bowl of rice</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/07/a-bowl-of-rice/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>It&amp;#8217;s expensive. Hundreds of people were involved in getting you that simple bowl of rice. It involved countless gallons of water, hours of labor, gallons of fuel. A complex supply chain that ensured you got what you needed, in perfect condition, just as you were ready for it. And it&amp;#8217;s cheap. The amount of time [&amp;#8230;]</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 09:25:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>