<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 07:23:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>3 Ways To Incorporate Supplier Collaboration Into Your Decarbonization Efforts</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/councils/forbestechcouncil/2024/08/20/3-ways-to-incorporate-supplier-collaboration-into-your-decarbonization-efforts/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66c38c04999b5f1ea665bd57/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>There is a growing need for companies to work more closely with suppliers to achieve decarbonization goals and enhance supply chain resiliency.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 12:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Non-professional writers</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/non-professional-writers/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Nobody asks you to design a bridge, write a sonnet or do open heart surgery. We leave these essential tasks to trained professionals. But many job descriptions carry the unstated addendum, “and write.” Write memos, proposals, and even instruction manuals. The local supermarket is reducing its hours for the summer (well deserved). The sign they […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 09:25:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How AI Is Changing Security, Customer Experience And Efficiency</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/councils/forbestechcouncil/2024/08/20/how-ai-is-changing-security-customer-experience-and-efficiency/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66c389d10244fcd9618f5f8e/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>Technologies such as video surveillance, once viewed solely as a security tool, have become critical IT infrastructure components, aided by the power of AI.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The prevailing conditions</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/the-prevailing-conditions/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>It doesn’t matter how hard you try, you’re not going to change the direction of the wind. That doesn’t mean you can’t get good at sailing, though. And yes, if we do try, we can change the conditions in our household, community or workplace. It might feel like wind, but it’s caused by us and […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 09:41:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Harnessing AI, Federated Learning And Blockchain For A Better Future In Medical Use Cases</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/councils/forbestechcouncil/2024/08/20/harnessing-ai-federated-learning-and-blockchain-for-a-better-future-in-medical-use-cases/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66c34a91fa8ebc7e263469a3/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>The integration of AI, federated learning and blockchain creates a powerful synergy that can transform healthcare.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 11:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The landlord and the creative coach</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/the-landlord-and-the-creative-coach/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>The conflict is real. “Jean-Michel [Basquiat] called,” Mr. Warhol wrote in his diary on Sept. 5, 1983. “He’s afraid he’s just going to be a flash in the pan. And I told him not to worry, that he wouldn’t be. But then I got scared because he’s rented our building on Great Jones and what […]</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 09:47:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Software Quality Reaches Tipping Point For Some Automakers</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/stevetengler/2024/08/20/software-quality-reaches-tipping-point-for-some-automakers/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66bf7caf2c0acccd9596942d/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>Software recalls have reached an epidemic proportion. Some CEOs have figured out a short-term and mid-term bandage, but few have figured out the long-term fix.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In defense of the hard parts</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/in-defense-of-the-hard-parts/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Yesterday’s post was a little glib. Without a doubt, we add more value when we focus on the emotional labor of important work, leaving others the chance to create commodities. But the repetitive, difficult nature of leaning into commodity production can give us insight, humility and skill. It helps us understand just how hard the […]</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 10:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Major U.S. Defense Investor Has Links To Sanctioned Russian Oligarchs</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidjeans/2024/08/20/8vc-russian-oligarchs/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66bf929f703c1e59bdbfce5a/0x0.jpg</image_url><description>Led by Palantir cofounder Joe Lonsdale, 8VC employs two children of alleged Kremlin allies on its investment team.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The hard parts (and the important parts)</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/08/the-hard-parts-and-the-important-parts/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>The hard parts of what you do all day can feel fraught. It’s heavy lifting. Emergencies. Dangerous labor. The stakes are high and the work can be difficult. The important parts of what you do all day are valuable to someone else. This is what you’re getting paid for–solving a customer’s problems. A simple example: […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 08:23:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>