<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 06:57:36 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>How Headless Architecture Enhances Marketing Strategy</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/councils/forbestechcouncil/2024/10/01/how-headless-architecture-enhances-marketing-strategy/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66fb111a41017d7e89e445c8/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>Headless architecture allows you to decouple the front end (presentation layer) from the back end (content and business logic).</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 11:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The paradox of brittle</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/10/the-paradox-of-brittle/</link><image_url>https://i0.wp.com/seths.blog/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/image.png?resize=1024%2C447&amp;ssl=1</image_url><description>Optimizing a device or system means squeezing every drop of productivity out of it. In the short-run, optimization works as long as the world stays the same. We can optimize a device to work at capacity. However, something working at capacity blows up if you step on the gas when you need 5% more out […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 09:04:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Breaking Down Elon Musk's Big Beef With The FAA</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/richardnieva/2024/10/01/elon-musk-spacex-faa-feud/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66fb22e5b9de4e8b646b4d7e/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>The billionaire has been publicly warring with the U.S. space regulator over fines and delays with an onslaught of criticism on X, blog posts and letters to Congress.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Find the others: Worldwide Strategy Meetups</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/09/find-the-others-worldwide-strategy-meetups/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>On October 22, around the world, I’m helping to organize hundreds of in-person get togethers. A chance to share your work and have a conversation about your strategy with others. Mutual support and peer connection. All the details are on this page. It’s free. A chance to connect and make an impact. Looking forward, together.</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 20:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Future Of Work: How AI Will Change Our Interaction With Software</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/councils/forbestechcouncil/2024/10/01/the-future-of-work-how-ai-will-change-our-interaction-with-software/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66fb103a2f92a5ca6cef8066/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>From manufacturing lines to logistics operations, AI will play a pivotal role in streamlining processes and enhancing efficiency.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Twenty questions</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/09/twenty-questions/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Your next project might feel like a calling, but it’s a choice. A choice that will have an impact on each day you spend on it. There are no right answers here, but before you fall in love with a business or an organization, it may pay to think about these and other options that […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 09:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Understanding The Challenges Of Data Congestion On Decentralized Blockchain Networks</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/councils/forbestechcouncil/2024/10/01/understanding-the-challenges-of-data-congestion-on-decentralized-blockchain-networks/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66a9573aec30680e32bf14d0/0x0.jpg?width=960</image_url><description>As decentralized blockchain networks evolve, understanding the causes and effects of this congestion becomes crucial.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 11:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Discovery and invention</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/09/discovery-and-invention/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Isaac Newton didn’t invent gravity. It was there all along. He simply named and explained it. The same is true for planets, continents and obscure species. They’re discovered, not invented. Michelangelo talked about removing all the parts of the marble that weren’t the statue on his way to creating great art. Discovery is like that. […]</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 10:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>October’s Night Sky: Meteors, A Bright Comet And A Huge ‘Supermoon’</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jamiecartereurope/2024/10/01/octobers-night-sky-biggest-supermoon-meteors-and-a-bright-comet/</link><image_url>https://imageio.forbes.com/specials-images/imageserve/66b4f926a633e45fcea58554/0x0.jpg?width=960&amp;precrop=2532%2C1424%2Cx1%2Cy266</image_url><description>In October 2024, stargazers may witness a naked-eye comet, an annular solar eclipse, the year's biggest supermoon, and shooting stars from the Orionid meteor shower.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Who do you want to become?</title><link>https://seths.blog/2024/09/who-do-you-want-to-become/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Emotional enrollment is at the heart of performance, learning and connection. A coach can quickly tell when someone is committed to changing their approach in order to change the outcome–it’s easy to tell this person apart from someone who simply wants what they’re already doing to be more effective. “I want to become someone who’s […]</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 09:51:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>