<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 01:24:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Clinical Benefits of Continued Metformin in PCOS</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/clinical-benefits-of-continued-metformin-in-pcos/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>The following is a summary of “Preconception and first trimester metformin on pregnancy outcomes in women with polycystic ovary syndrome: a systematic...</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 00:00:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2020 to 2022 saw nearly 2 million annual emergency room visits for dental issues</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-million-annual-emergency-room-dental.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Tooth disorders accounted for an annual average of 1,944,000 emergency department visits during 2020 to 2022, according to a June data brief published...</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 00:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>US measles count nears 1,200 cases as Ohio officials confirm 3 outbreaks are over</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-measles-nears-cases-ohio-outbreaks.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>The U.S. logged fewer than 30 measles cases this week as Ohio health officials confirmed three outbreaks in two counties were over.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 09:08:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FDA approves pembrolizumab for resectable head and neck cancer with PD-L1 expression</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-fda-pembrolizumab-resectable-neck-cancer.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Pembrolizumab, an immune checkpoint inhibitor, has been approved by the U.S. Food and Drug Administration (FDA) for the treatment of patients with res...</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 09:20:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Clinical Validity of PLASMIC Score in aHUS Identification</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/clinical-validity-of-plasmic-score-in-ahus-identification/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>The following is a summary of “PLASMIC score to aid diagnosis of aHUS: an analysis of C5 inhibitor clinical trials and the PINC AI™ healthcare databas...</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 21:30:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Natural History of Asymptomatic Renal Stones Before RC</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/natural-history-of-asymptomatic-renal-stones-before-rc/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>The following is a summary of “Does having an asymptomatic renal stone increase morbidity after radical cystectomy?,” published in the May 2025 issue ...</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 23:30:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Neighborly help in the brain: Cerebral cortex networks rapidly reorganize to compensate for lost neurons</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-neighborly-brain-cerebral-cortex-networks.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>How the brain largely maintains its function when neurons are lost—this is what researchers at the University Medical Center Mainz, the Frankfurt Inst...</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 15:20:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Altered Cerebellar Network in Dystonia</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/altered-cerebellar-network-in-dystonia/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>The following is a summary of “Structure–function association of the cerebellar motor network is altered in isolated cervical dystonia,” published in ...</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 22:30:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Organ Use and Transplant Access by Center Volume</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/organ-use-and-transplant-access-by-center-volume/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>The following is a summary of “Being Waitlisted is not Enough—Identification of Pseudo-access to Kidney Transplantation in the United States,” publish...</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 22:30:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Evolutionary model for antibiotic resistance reveals dose timing critical to care</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-evolutionary-antibiotic-resistance-reveals-dose.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Cleveland Clinic researchers are working to improve the way we use evolutionary modeling to understand drug resistance. The study, published in Scienc...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 19:10:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Nourishment Table, with Frederic Leroy</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-nourishment-table-with-frederic-leroy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes food scientist and advocate for regenerative agriculture Dr. Frederic Leroy to disc...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Turn ChatGPT Into Your Personal Meal Planner</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/turn-chatgpt-into-your-personal-meal-planner/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Even for someone who lives and breathes nutrition, meal planning can feel like a grind. There are weeks when I... The post Turn ChatGPT Into Your Pers...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:16:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Rediscovering Health, Nature, and Purpose-Driven Business, with Seth Spears</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rediscovering-health-nature-and-purpose-driven-business-with-seth-spears/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes entrepreneur and strategist Seth Spears for a wide-ranging conversation on health, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: How to Sharpen and Protect Your Mind for a Lifetime, with Dale Bredesen</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/how-to-sharpen-and-protect-your-mind-for-a-lifetime-with-dale-bredesen/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes renowned neurologist Dr. Dale Bredesen back to the show for an insightful conversation abou...</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:01:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quality Matters: How to Choose and Use the Best Collagen Supplement</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/quality-matters-how-to-choose-and-use-the-best-collagen-supplement/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Introduction If you’ve been paying attention to health and wellness trends, you’ve likely noticed collagen supplements everywhere—from your local heal...</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:57:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>