<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 16:06:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Bringing AI into the NICU: How algorithms may help infants' eyes, health</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-ai-nicu-algorithms-infants-eyes.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>When ophthalmologist Emily Cole, MD, steps into the neonatal intensive care unit (NICU) at Children's Hospital Colorado to evaluate an infant's eyes f...</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 20:25:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Many men may not need long-term hormone therapy for prostate cancer, study suggests</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-men-term-hormone-therapy-prostate.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>A study co-led by investigators at the UCLA Health Jonsson Comprehensive Cancer Center found that most of the benefits of androgen deprivation therapy...</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 20:32:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Research challenges idea that gene PTPN22 boosts production of interferons</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-idea-gene-ptpn22-boosts-production.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>A new paper from the University of Kansas overturns the idea that a "risk gene" carried by millions of people worldwide influences production of type ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 20:40:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alternative sweetener sorbitol linked to liver disease</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-alternative-sweetener-sorbitol-linked-liver.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Sweeteners such as aspartame, found in Equal packets, sucralose (Splenda), or sugar alcohols are often seen as healthier alternatives to food with ref...</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 20:11:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tattoos could be a risk factor for melanoma</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-tattoos-factor-melanoma.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>An increasing number of Swedes are getting tattoos and Sweden's population is now one of the most tattooed in Europe. At the same time, the incidence ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 20:50:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Link Between Metabolic Health and Mental Well-Being, with Dr. Matt Bernstein</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-link-between-metabolic-health-and-mental-well-being-with-dr-matt-bernstein/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes psychiatrist Dr. Matt Bernstein to explore the emerging field of metabolic psychiatry, the ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: From Wired &amp; Tired to Calm &amp; Clear: My Top Nutrients for Mood, Focus, and Sleep</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/from-wired-tired-to-calm-clear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris explores natural solutions for one of today’s most pressing challenges: chronic stress, anxiety, and...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Science Behind Oral Inflammation, with Dr. William Levine</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-science-behind-oral-inflammation-with-dr-william-levine/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes board-certified periodontist Dr. William Levine to discuss the overlooked role of gum healt...</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hyaluronic Acid: The Deep Hydration Molecule Your Skin Has Been Waiting For</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/hyaluronic-acid-the-deep-hydration-molecule-your-skin-has-been-waiting-for/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>If you’ve spent any time exploring the world of natural skincare, chances are you’ve heard of hyaluronic acid (HA). Once... The post Hyaluronic Acid: ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rice Ceramides: The Unsung Hero of Skin Hydration and Barrier Health</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rice-ceramides-the-unsung-hero-of-skin-hydration-and-barrier-health/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>We often think of radiant skin as the result of what we put on it: moisturizers, serums, masks. But emerging... The post Rice Ceramides: The Unsung He...</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>