<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 16:51:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Gene variant increases brain inflammation in those with repetitive head impacts</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-gene-variant-brain-inflammation-repetitive.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Chronic traumatic encephalopathy (CTE) is a neurodegenerative disease caused by repetitive head impacts (RHI). However, individuals with similar RHI e...</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 20:58:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists use stem cells to model rare genetic blindness in children</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-scientists-stem-cells-rare-genetic.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Researchers at the Eye Genetics Research Unit at Children's Medical Research Institute (CMRI) are the first in the world to use stem cells to study on...</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 21:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cancer cells have backup metabolic pathway to keep building DNA when blocked, study finds</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-cancer-cells-backup-metabolic-pathway.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Northwestern Medicine scientists have uncovered a surprising link between a tiny cellular engine and the way cancer cells build the DNA they need to p...</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 21:20:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Long-term pharmacological treatment shows promise against memory impairments in Down syndrome</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-term-pharmacological-treatment-memory-impairments.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In 2019, a research group led by Andrés Ozaita, of the Department of Medicine and Life Sciences at Pompeu Fabra University, described that mice models...</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 21:31:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Clinical tool helps predict which brain tumors will require treatment</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-clinical-tool-brain-tumors-require.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>A new study has shown that a clinical tool developed by the University of Liverpool and The Walton Center can accurately predict whether the most comm...</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 21:25:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Link Between Metabolic Health and Mental Well-Being, with Dr. Matt Bernstein</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-link-between-metabolic-health-and-mental-well-being-with-dr-matt-bernstein/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes psychiatrist Dr. Matt Bernstein to explore the emerging field of metabolic psychiatry, the ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: From Wired &amp; Tired to Calm &amp; Clear: My Top Nutrients for Mood, Focus, and Sleep</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/from-wired-tired-to-calm-clear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris explores natural solutions for one of today’s most pressing challenges: chronic stress, anxiety, and...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Science Behind Oral Inflammation, with Dr. William Levine</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-science-behind-oral-inflammation-with-dr-william-levine/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes board-certified periodontist Dr. William Levine to discuss the overlooked role of gum healt...</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hyaluronic Acid: The Deep Hydration Molecule Your Skin Has Been Waiting For</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/hyaluronic-acid-the-deep-hydration-molecule-your-skin-has-been-waiting-for/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>If you’ve spent any time exploring the world of natural skincare, chances are you’ve heard of hyaluronic acid (HA). Once... The post Hyaluronic Acid: ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rice Ceramides: The Unsung Hero of Skin Hydration and Barrier Health</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rice-ceramides-the-unsung-hero-of-skin-hydration-and-barrier-health/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>We often think of radiant skin as the result of what we put on it: moisturizers, serums, masks. But emerging... The post Rice Ceramides: The Unsung He...</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>