<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 10:52:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Accreditation process drives surgical quality improvement, study shows</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-accreditation-surgical-quality.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>About 800 U.S. hospitals have earned accreditation from the American College of Surgeons (ACS) between 2017 and 2023 through programs aimed at improvi...</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 15:29:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Even With Statins, Modifi able Risk Factors Drive MACE Risk in HIV</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/even-with-statins-modifi-able-risk-factors-drive-mace-risk-in-hiv/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>“People with human immuno deficiency virus (HIV; PWH) face an approximately 2-fold increased risk of atherosclerotic cardiovascular disease (ASCVD) co...</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 11:38:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maintenance Therapy Combo Bolsters Survival in Extensive-Stage SCLC</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/maintenance-therapy-combo-bolsters-survival-in-extensive-stage-sclc/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Findings suggest that adding lurbinectedin to atezolizumab for first-line maintenance therapy benefits patients with extensive-stage small cell lung c...</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 14:39:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Once-Daily Treatment for Cushing Syndrome May Safely Restore Cortisol Rhythms</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/once-daily-treatment-for-cushing-syndrome-may-safely-restore-cortisol-rhythms/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Once-daily evening osilodrostat improved cortisol rhythms, sleep, and quality of life in Cushing syndrome without compromising disease control or safe...</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 15:01:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Malaria has returned to the Torres Strait: What does this mean for mainland Australia?</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-malaria-torres-strait-mainland-australia.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Malaria is one of the deadliest diseases spread by mosquitoes. Each year, hundreds of millions of people worldwide are infected and half a million peo...</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 14:54:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quiz Challenge – How Can You Minimize the Radiation Dose in Pediatric Imaging?</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/quiz-challenge-how-can-you-minimize-the-radiation-dose-in-pediatric-imaging/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Take this quiz on reducing the radiation dose in pediatric imaging. The post Quiz Challenge – How Can You Minimize the Radiation Dose in Pediatric Ima...</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 14:58:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What allergy remedies really work? Professor debunks myths</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-allergy-remedies-professor-debunks-myths.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>As seasons change, temperatures rise and flowers begin to bloom, many find themselves battling more than just spring fever, the feeling of excitement,...</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 15:08:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Virtual reality could add empathy to dementia care</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-virtual-reality-empathy-dementia.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>At a conference on aging two years ago, Li-Mei Chen slipped on a pair of virtual reality (VR) goggles and found herself inside the mind of a person wi...</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 15:16:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cannabis use disorder may increase risk for certain psychiatric illnesses</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-cannabis-disorder-psychiatric-illnesses.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Pot. Weed. Mary Jane. Dope. Cannabis goes by many names. The drug has had a rocky history in the United States, but today, many states have legalized ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 15:24:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gaps Identified in Hidradenitis Suppurativa Patient Education</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/gaps-identified-in-hidradenitis-suppurativa-patient-education/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Patients with hidradenitis suppurative seek advice online, highlighting unmet needs in clinician-patient education regarding daily self-management str...</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 15:33:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Nourishment Table, with Frederic Leroy</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-nourishment-table-with-frederic-leroy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes food scientist and advocate for regenerative agriculture Dr. Frederic Leroy to disc...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Turn ChatGPT Into Your Personal Meal Planner</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/turn-chatgpt-into-your-personal-meal-planner/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Even for someone who lives and breathes nutrition, meal planning can feel like a grind. There are weeks when I... The post Turn ChatGPT Into Your Pers...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:16:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Rediscovering Health, Nature, and Purpose-Driven Business, with Seth Spears</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rediscovering-health-nature-and-purpose-driven-business-with-seth-spears/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes entrepreneur and strategist Seth Spears for a wide-ranging conversation on health, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: How to Sharpen and Protect Your Mind for a Lifetime, with Dale Bredesen</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/how-to-sharpen-and-protect-your-mind-for-a-lifetime-with-dale-bredesen/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes renowned neurologist Dr. Dale Bredesen back to the show for an insightful conversation abou...</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:01:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quality Matters: How to Choose and Use the Best Collagen Supplement</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/quality-matters-how-to-choose-and-use-the-best-collagen-supplement/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Introduction If you’ve been paying attention to health and wellness trends, you’ve likely noticed collagen supplements everywhere—from your local heal...</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:57:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>