<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 06:10:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Kenya has eliminated sleeping sickness, says WHO</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-kenya-sickness.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Kenya has eliminated sleeping sickness as a public health problem, the World Health Organization announced on Friday, making it the 10th country to do...</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 09:38:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Physicians with more patient complaints also more likely to receive industry payments</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-physicians-patient-complaints-industry-payments.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Johns Hopkins University School of Medicine and Vanderbilt University Medical Center investigators report that physicians who attract more unsolicited...</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 13:30:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Parental workplace chemical exposure linked to autism severity and behavior in children</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-parental-workplace-chemical-exposure-linked.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>A new study in the International Journal of Hygiene and Environmental Health finds parents' workplace chemical exposure may be linked to a range of be...</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 09:50:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Excessive screen time raises heart disease risk: Study</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-excessive-screen-heart-disease.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Children who spend too much time in front of screens, whether phones or TVs, have an increased risk of heart and metabolic disease, according to a Dan...</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 18:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The meditation app revolution is here, and it's backed by science</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-meditation-app-revolution-science.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Do you have a meditation app on your smartphone, computer or wearable device? Well, you're not alone. There are now thousands of meditation apps avail...</description><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 18:20:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Beauty From Within – Why Radiant Skin, Hair, and Nails Start Inside</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/beauty-from-within-why-radiant-skin-hair-and-nails-start-inside/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, we dive deep into the topic of beauty from within, exploring why radiant skin, hair, and nails truly start...</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 08:01:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Mold, Indoor Air Quality, and Clean Breathing, with Michael Rubino</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/mold-indoor-air-quality-and-clean-breathing-with-michael-rubino/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes environmental wellness expert Michael Rubino for an in-depth conversation on the hi...</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 08:01:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Nourishment Table, with Frederic Leroy</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-nourishment-table-with-frederic-leroy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes food scientist and advocate for regenerative agriculture Dr. Frederic Leroy to disc...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Turn ChatGPT Into Your Personal Meal Planner</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/turn-chatgpt-into-your-personal-meal-planner/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Even for someone who lives and breathes nutrition, meal planning can feel like a grind. There are weeks when I... The post Turn ChatGPT Into Your Pers...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:16:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Rediscovering Health, Nature, and Purpose-Driven Business, with Seth Spears</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rediscovering-health-nature-and-purpose-driven-business-with-seth-spears/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes entrepreneur and strategist Seth Spears for a wide-ranging conversation on health, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>