<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 02:23:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>How to Handle Generational Conflicts in the Medical Workplace</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/how-to-handle-generational-conflicts-in-the-medical-workplace/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Generational conflicts in the medical workplace can cause problems, but fostering open dialogue and building inclusivity can improve collaboration and...</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 05:00:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Brain network activity may offer clues to future drinking behaviors of adolescents</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-05-brain-network-clues-future-behaviors.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Measuring the interaction of brain networks could potentially help identify teens at risk for dangerous drinking, according to a novel study that expl...</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 19:06:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Medicaid Patient Had a Heart Attack While Traveling. He Owed Almost $78,000.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/a-medicaid-patient-had-a-heart-attack-while-traveling-he-owed-almost-78000/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>On Christmas Day at the WaTiki indoor water park, Hans Wirt was getting winded from following his son up the stairs to the waterslides. Wirt’s breathi...</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 11:30:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PW Trivia: Targeting IL-6 in Rheumatoid Arthritis</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/pw-trivia-targeting-il-6-in-rheumatoid-arthritis/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Targeting specific cytokines is key in rheumatoid arthritis treatment—see if you know which biologic agent focuses on interleukin-6. The post PW Trivi...</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 16:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Multiple genetic variants could predict who benefits from alcohol addiction drug</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-05-multiple-genetic-variants-benefits-alcohol.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Alcohol-related genetic variants influence the effects of a medication for treating alcohol use disorder (AUD), according to an innovative study. The ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 19:04:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New classification system proposed for infants with nasal deformity in cleft lip and palate</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-05-classification-infants-nasal-deformity-cleft.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>A proposed classification system appears highly accurate in evaluating nasal deformities in infants with cleft lip and/or palate (CLP), reports a stud...</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 19:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Who should be screened for skin cancer?</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-05-screened-skin-cancer.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Skin cancer is the most common cancer in the U.S. More than 6 million adults are treated for it each year, says Dr. Michael Colgan, a Mayo Clinic Heal...</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 23:10:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Language Service Cutbacks Raise Fear of Medical Errors, Misdiagnoses, Deaths</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/language-service-cutbacks-raise-fear-of-medical-errors-misdiagnoses-deaths/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>SAN FRANCISCO — Health nonprofits and medical interpreters warn that federal cuts have eliminated dozens of positions in California for community work...</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 11:30:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Feds Chop Enforcement Staff and Halt Rules Meant To Curb Black Lung in Coal Miners</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/feds-chop-enforcement-staff-and-halt-rules-meant-to-curb-black-lung-in-coal-miners/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>In early April, President Donald Trump gathered dozens of hard-hat-clad coal miners around him in the White House East Room. He joked about arm-wrestl...</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 11:30:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Employment may support recovery from problem drinking</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-05-employment-recovery-problem.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Having a job may give people a better chance at recovery following treatment for alcohol use disorder. Nationwide data from people who received outpat...</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 19:05:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Turn ChatGPT Into Your Personal Meal Planner</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/turn-chatgpt-into-your-personal-meal-planner/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Even for someone who lives and breathes nutrition, meal planning can feel like a grind. There are weeks when I... The post Turn ChatGPT Into Your Pers...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:16:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Rediscovering Health, Nature, and Purpose-Driven Business, with Seth Spears</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rediscovering-health-nature-and-purpose-driven-business-with-seth-spears/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes entrepreneur and strategist Seth Spears for a wide-ranging conversation on health, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: How to Sharpen and Protect Your Mind for a Lifetime, with Dale Bredesen</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/how-to-sharpen-and-protect-your-mind-for-a-lifetime-with-dale-bredesen/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes renowned neurologist Dr. Dale Bredesen back to the show for an insightful conversation abou...</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:01:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quality Matters: How to Choose and Use the Best Collagen Supplement</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/quality-matters-how-to-choose-and-use-the-best-collagen-supplement/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Introduction If you’ve been paying attention to health and wellness trends, you’ve likely noticed collagen supplements everywhere—from your local heal...</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:57:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Collagen: The Essential Building Block for Strong Joints and Bones</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/collagen-the-essential-building-block-for-strong-joints-and-bones/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>The Foundation of Your Musculoskeletal System If you’ve ever winced going down stairs, felt that telltale morning stiffness, or worried... The post Co...</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 13:31:22 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>