<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 11:07:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Shorter Antibiotic Duration Effective for Gram-Negative Bloodstream Infections</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/shorter-antibiotic-duration-effective-for-gram-negative-bloodstream-infections/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Seven days of antibiotics was noninferior to 14 days for treating Gram-negative bloodstream infections, supporting shorter courses in hospitalized pat...</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 15:00:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gender bias holds back female surgeons, study finds</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-gender-bias-female-surgeons.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Women now make up over half of medical students in Canada, but only one-third of practicing surgeons. A new study suggests part of the gap stems from ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 15:39:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FDA study links high consumer CBD doses to liver enzyme elevations</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-fda-links-high-consumer-cbd.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>FDA researchers report that the upper end of reported consumer use (~400mg of daily CBD intake) of cannabidiol (CBD) may elevate liver enzymes in heal...</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 15:59:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>An Arm and a Leg: The Prescription Drug Playbook, Part II</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/an-arm-and-a-leg-the-prescription-drug-playbook-part-ii/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>In response to the high price of prescription drugs, “An Arm and a Leg” asked listeners to share their strategies for getting the medicine they need a...</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 11:30:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Exercise can greatly benefit teenagers' mental health—here's what the evidence says</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-greatly-benefit-teenagers-mental-health.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Adolescence is a crucial stage of human development. During this unstable period, teenagers experience numerous physical, emotional and social changes...</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 15:30:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>World’s Premier Cancer Institute Faces Crippling Cuts and Chaos</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/worlds-premier-cancer-institute-faces-crippling-cuts-and-chaos/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>The Trump administration’s broadsides against scientific research have caused unprecedented upheaval at the National Cancer Institute, the storied fed...</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 11:30:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Childhood Bacterial Bronchitis Tied to Long-Term Lung Risks</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/childhood-bacterial-bronchitis-tied-to-long-term-lung-risks/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Many children continue to experience respiratory symptoms up to 14 years after treatment for protracted bacterial bronchitis, according to a recent st...</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 14:59:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cooling and antioxidants could prevent hair loss during chemotherapy</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-cooling-antioxidants-hair-loss-chemotherapy.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Hair loss is one of the most feared and traumatic side effects of cancer chemotherapy treatment, both for patients themselves and their loved ones, as...</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 15:33:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Virtual maternity care during COVID-19 pandemic linked to higher NHS costs</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-virtual-maternity-covid-pandemic-linked.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>New research reveals that virtual maternity care during the COVID-19 pandemic may have driven increased use of subsequent care, raising overall matern...</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 15:20:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Online DBT Reduces Chronic Pain Emotion Dysregulation</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/online-dbt-reduces-chronic-pain-emotion-dysregulation/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>A remote dialectical behavior therapy program tailored to chronic pain significantly improved emotion regulation, according to a recent study. The pos...</description><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 15:41:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Mold, Indoor Air Quality, and Clean Breathing, with Michael Rubino</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/mold-indoor-air-quality-and-clean-breathing-with-michael-rubino/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes environmental wellness expert Michael Rubino for an in-depth conversation on the hi...</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 08:01:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Nourishment Table, with Frederic Leroy</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-nourishment-table-with-frederic-leroy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes food scientist and advocate for regenerative agriculture Dr. Frederic Leroy to disc...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Turn ChatGPT Into Your Personal Meal Planner</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/turn-chatgpt-into-your-personal-meal-planner/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Even for someone who lives and breathes nutrition, meal planning can feel like a grind. There are weeks when I... The post Turn ChatGPT Into Your Pers...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:16:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Rediscovering Health, Nature, and Purpose-Driven Business, with Seth Spears</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rediscovering-health-nature-and-purpose-driven-business-with-seth-spears/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes entrepreneur and strategist Seth Spears for a wide-ranging conversation on health, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: How to Sharpen and Protect Your Mind for a Lifetime, with Dale Bredesen</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/how-to-sharpen-and-protect-your-mind-for-a-lifetime-with-dale-bredesen/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes renowned neurologist Dr. Dale Bredesen back to the show for an insightful conversation abou...</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:01:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>