<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 11:00:33 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Common bacteria discovered in the eye linked to cognitive decline</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-02-common-bacteria-eye-linked-cognitive.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Chlamydia pneumoniae—a common bacterium that causes pneumonia and sinus infections—can linger in the eye and brain for years and may aggravate Alzheim...</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:18:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Drinking behavior in early adulthood predicts likelihood of alcohol use disorder symptoms at age 35</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-02-behavior-early-adulthood-likelihood-alcohol.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>A person's drinking patterns at age 18 predict the trajectory of their drinking behavior into adulthood, and that trajectory may predict the likelihoo...</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:04:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Your gut remembers every diet</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-02-gut-diet.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>The summer holidays are often a time of excess. Rich food, larger portions and more frequent social eating are part of the season. Once it's over, man...</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:13:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How early pregnancy impacts aging: Implications for breast-cancer risk</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-02-early-pregnancy-impacts-aging-implications.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>A new study by cell biologists at the University of California, Santa Cruz, suggests that an early first pregnancy may protect against breast cancer d...</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:09:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Inadequate nutrition and lower education linked to worse outcomes for children exposed to alcohol in utero</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-02-inadequate-nutrition-linked-worse-outcomes.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>A new study addresses the puzzle of why heavy drinking throughout pregnancy leads to widely varying outcomes for children. Even in the context of heav...</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:02:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Cold Exposure: Why Sustained Beats Extreme</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/cold-exposure-why-sustained-beats-extreme/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Cold plunges and ice baths dominate social media, but do they really deliver the best metabolic benefits? In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 08:03:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Why Your Sleep Schedule Matters As Much As Duration</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/why-your-sleep-schedule-matters-as-much-as-duration/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris challenges the conventional focus on sleep duration and makes the case that sleep timing and circadi...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 08:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Menopause Brain Fog—What’s Really Happening (and How To Fix It)</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rhr-menopause-brain-fog-whats-really-happening-and-how-to-fix-it/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris examines research confirming that menopause-related brain fog is real, measurable, and reversible. H...</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 08:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Seed Oils and Colon Cancer – What the New Research Really Shows</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/seed-oils-and-colon-cancer-what-the-new-research-really-shows/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Seed oils have become one of the most controversial topics in nutrition, especially after a 2024 University of South Florida study linked high omega-6...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 08:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Longevity Trap: Why Chasing Anti-Aging May Be Aging You</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-longevity-trap-why-chasing-anti-aging-may-be-aging-you/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>In this episode, Chris explains why obsession with anti-aging hacks may actually undermine our long-term health. He examines the common longevity trap...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>