<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 06:26:41 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Cats with dementia show brain changes similar to Alzheimer's in humans</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-cats-dementia-brain-similar-alzheimer.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Cats with dementia have brain changes similar to those of people with Alzheimer's disease, offering a valuable model for studying the condition in hum...</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 11:26:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Subspecialization in oncology increasingly utilized</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-subspecialization-oncology.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Subspecialization in oncology is increasing, but varies widely across cancer types and regions, according to a study published online Aug. 12 in the A...</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 08:36:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI could soon detect early voice box cancer from the sound of your voice</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-ai-early-voice-cancer.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Cancer of the voice box or larynx is an important public health burden. In 2021, there were an estimated 1.1 million cases of laryngeal cancer worldwi...</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 05:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>3D-printed kidney tumors show potential for more targeted treatment</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-3d-kidney-tumors-potential-treatment.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Scientists at Tsinghua University have developed a method to grow kidney tumors in the lab using cells from real patients, offering a potential new to...</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 09:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dollar stores' food options may not be hurting American diets overall, analysis shows</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-dollar-food-options-american-diets.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Using dollar stores for food purchases may be a common practice for Americans looking to free up funds for the rest of their grocery list, researchers...</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 01:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Beauty From Within – Why Radiant Skin, Hair, and Nails Start Inside</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/beauty-from-within-why-radiant-skin-hair-and-nails-start-inside/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, we dive deep into the topic of beauty from within, exploring why radiant skin, hair, and nails truly start...</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 08:01:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Mold, Indoor Air Quality, and Clean Breathing, with Michael Rubino</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/mold-indoor-air-quality-and-clean-breathing-with-michael-rubino/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes environmental wellness expert Michael Rubino for an in-depth conversation on the hi...</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 08:01:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Nourishment Table, with Frederic Leroy</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-nourishment-table-with-frederic-leroy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes food scientist and advocate for regenerative agriculture Dr. Frederic Leroy to disc...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Turn ChatGPT Into Your Personal Meal Planner</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/turn-chatgpt-into-your-personal-meal-planner/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Even for someone who lives and breathes nutrition, meal planning can feel like a grind. There are weeks when I... The post Turn ChatGPT Into Your Pers...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:16:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Rediscovering Health, Nature, and Purpose-Driven Business, with Seth Spears</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rediscovering-health-nature-and-purpose-driven-business-with-seth-spears/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes entrepreneur and strategist Seth Spears for a wide-ranging conversation on health, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>