<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 00:13:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>How the auditory cortex syncs with behavior to help the brain become a better listener</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-auditory-cortex-syncs-behavior-brain.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>When we are engaged in a task, our brain's auditory system changes how it works. One of the main auditory centers of the brain, the auditory cortex, i...</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 19:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How immune cells deliver their deadly cargo: An unexpected connection to lipid metabolism</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-immune-cells-deadly-cargo-unexpected.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>When immune cells strike, precision is everything. New research reveals how natural killer and T cells orchestrate the release of toxic granules—micro...</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 19:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How lifestyle and environment reshape the sperm epigenome and why it matters for fertility, embryos and child health</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-lifestyle-environment-reshape-sperm-epigenome.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>A review in Clinical Epigenetics synthesizes growing evidence that paternal lifestyle and environmental exposures such as diet, obesity, smoking, endo...</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 19:10:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Poor sleep in youth linked to early signs of biological stress</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-poor-youth-linked-early-biological.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Late nights, early risings and broken sleep schedules are hallmarks of youth, but those sleepless nights may leave marks deeper than dark circles unde...</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 18:54:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stringent climate policies could offer major health and economic gains by 2030</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-stringent-climate-policies-major-health.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Air pollution is one of the world's leading health risks, contributing to nearly one in eight deaths globally. A new study published in Science Advanc...</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 19:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Science Behind Oral Inflammation, with Dr. William Levine</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-science-behind-oral-inflammation-with-dr-william-levine/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes board-certified periodontist Dr. William Levine to discuss the overlooked role of gum healt...</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hyaluronic Acid: The Deep Hydration Molecule Your Skin Has Been Waiting For</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/hyaluronic-acid-the-deep-hydration-molecule-your-skin-has-been-waiting-for/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>If you’ve spent any time exploring the world of natural skincare, chances are you’ve heard of hyaluronic acid (HA). Once... The post Hyaluronic Acid: ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rice Ceramides: The Unsung Hero of Skin Hydration and Barrier Health</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rice-ceramides-the-unsung-hero-of-skin-hydration-and-barrier-health/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>We often think of radiant skin as the result of what we put on it: moisturizers, serums, masks. But emerging... The post Rice Ceramides: The Unsung He...</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lutein and Zeaxanthin: The Carotenoids That Protect and Perfect Your Skin from Within</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/lutein-and-zeaxanthin-the-carotenoids-that-protect-and-perfect-your-skin-from-within/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>When most people think of lutein and zeaxanthin, they picture eye health supplements or leafy green vegetables. But these vibrant... The post Lutein a...</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:00:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vitamin C: The Collagen-Stimulating, Skin-Brightening Antioxidant Your Skin Can’t Live Without</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/vitamin-c-the-collagen-stimulating-skin-brightening-antioxidant-your-skin-cant-live-without/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>When it comes to supporting skin health from the inside out, few nutrients are as essential—or as well-researched—as vitamin C.... The post Vitamin C:...</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 16:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>