<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 16:27:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Two forms of ketamine therapy can reduce symptom severity in patients with treatment-resistant depression</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-09-ketamine-therapy-symptom-severity-patients.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>A new study led by Mass General Brigham investigators compared the effects of repeated intravenous (IV) ketamine and intranasal (IN) esketamine in pat...</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 21:19:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Childhood stress strongly linked to chronic disease in adulthood, researchers report</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-09-childhood-stress-strongly-linked-chronic.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Research published by Duke University researchers has found a strong link between higher stress in children and adverse health conditions for them lat...</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 20:33:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Flavored marijuana vapes becoming new face of teen drug use, sparking addiction fears</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-09-flavored-marijuana-vapes-teen-drug.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Flavored marijuana vaping is now the most common form of use among American teenagers who vape cannabis, according to new findings from the University...</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 20:52:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Unique pan-cancer immunotherapy destroys tumors without attacking healthy tissue</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-09-unique-pan-cancer-immunotherapy-destroys.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>A new, highly potent class of immunotherapeutics with unique Velcro-like binding properties can kill diverse cancer types without harming normal tissu...</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 20:50:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nasal vaccines and the future of immunization</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-09-nasal-vaccines-future-immunization.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Vaccines are usually administered with a needle poke into the arm. But what if instead of a poke, you could get vaccinated with a huff and a puff?</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 21:14:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hyaluronic Acid: The Deep Hydration Molecule Your Skin Has Been Waiting For</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/hyaluronic-acid-the-deep-hydration-molecule-your-skin-has-been-waiting-for/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>If you’ve spent any time exploring the world of natural skincare, chances are you’ve heard of hyaluronic acid (HA). Once... The post Hyaluronic Acid: ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rice Ceramides: The Unsung Hero of Skin Hydration and Barrier Health</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rice-ceramides-the-unsung-hero-of-skin-hydration-and-barrier-health/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>We often think of radiant skin as the result of what we put on it: moisturizers, serums, masks. But emerging... The post Rice Ceramides: The Unsung He...</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lutein and Zeaxanthin: The Carotenoids That Protect and Perfect Your Skin from Within</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/lutein-and-zeaxanthin-the-carotenoids-that-protect-and-perfect-your-skin-from-within/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>When most people think of lutein and zeaxanthin, they picture eye health supplements or leafy green vegetables. But these vibrant... The post Lutein a...</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:00:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vitamin C: The Collagen-Stimulating, Skin-Brightening Antioxidant Your Skin Can’t Live Without</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/vitamin-c-the-collagen-stimulating-skin-brightening-antioxidant-your-skin-cant-live-without/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>When it comes to supporting skin health from the inside out, few nutrients are as essential—or as well-researched—as vitamin C.... The post Vitamin C:...</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 16:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eggshell Membrane Collagen: A Natural Ally for Skin, Hair, and Nail Vitality</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/eggshell-membrane-collagen-a-natural-ally-for-skin-hair-and-nail-vitality/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>In the growing world of natural beauty and inside-out skincare, few ingredients offer the versatility and clinical backing of eggshell... The post Egg...</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>