<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:34:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>What's the difference between a home birth and a free birth?</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-difference-home-birth-free.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>If you're looking on social media for information and experiences of giving birth at home, you'll find widely varied content.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 16:50:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI-driven system automates fax filing and digital consent, saving 8,500 staff hours</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-ai-driven-automates-digital-consent.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>An emerging artificial intelligence-powered system developed at Penn Medicine has tripled the speed of fax processing and cut a full week off the new ...</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 19:33:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Daily oral GLP-1 pill a promising alternative to injectables for weight loss, clinical trial finds</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-daily-oral-glp-pill-alternative.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>A new oral GLP-1 medication can help adults with obesity and type 2 diabetes lose more weight and improve their blood sugar levels compared to a place...</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Most people are happy to do their own hearing tests at home. Could it relieve pressure on the NHS?</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-people-happy-home-relieve-pressure.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>If the NHS recommended it, would people test their own hearing at home and use self-fitting hearing aids?</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 19:40:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Epigenetic changes regulate gene expression, but what regulates epigenetics?</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-epigenetic-gene-epigenetics.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>All the cells in an organism have the exact same genetic sequence. What differs across cell types is their epigenetics—meticulously placed chemical ta...</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 19:31:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Link Between Metabolic Health and Mental Well-Being, with Dr. Matt Bernstein</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-link-between-metabolic-health-and-mental-well-being-with-dr-matt-bernstein/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes psychiatrist Dr. Matt Bernstein to explore the emerging field of metabolic psychiatry, the ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: From Wired &amp; Tired to Calm &amp; Clear: My Top Nutrients for Mood, Focus, and Sleep</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/from-wired-tired-to-calm-clear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris explores natural solutions for one of today’s most pressing challenges: chronic stress, anxiety, and...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Science Behind Oral Inflammation, with Dr. William Levine</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-science-behind-oral-inflammation-with-dr-william-levine/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes board-certified periodontist Dr. William Levine to discuss the overlooked role of gum healt...</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hyaluronic Acid: The Deep Hydration Molecule Your Skin Has Been Waiting For</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/hyaluronic-acid-the-deep-hydration-molecule-your-skin-has-been-waiting-for/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>If you’ve spent any time exploring the world of natural skincare, chances are you’ve heard of hyaluronic acid (HA). Once... The post Hyaluronic Acid: ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rice Ceramides: The Unsung Hero of Skin Hydration and Barrier Health</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rice-ceramides-the-unsung-hero-of-skin-hydration-and-barrier-health/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>We often think of radiant skin as the result of what we put on it: moisturizers, serums, masks. But emerging... The post Rice Ceramides: The Unsung He...</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>