<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 07:16:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Families explore how a smartwatch can give early warnings of severe tantrums</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-families-explore-smartwatch-early-severe.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Evenings in the Staal household often carried a delicate unpredictability. After a full school day—and as Ethan's medication began to wear off—the shi...</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:27:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>National poll: Less than half of parents say swearing is never OK for kids</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-national-poll-parents-kids.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Today's parents may be growing more relaxed about their children using curse words, according to a national poll.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 05:20:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New method predicts asthma attacks up to five years in advance</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-method-asthma-years-advance.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Researchers at Mass General Brigham and Karolinska Institutet have identified a new method to predict asthma exacerbations with a high degree of accur...</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 10:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Revoice' device gives stroke patients their voice back</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-revoice-device-patients-voice.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Researchers have developed a wearable, comfortable and washable device called Revoice that could help people regain the ability to communicate natural...</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 10:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Can Canada's health systems handle increased demand during FIFA World Cup?</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-canada-health-demand-fifa-world.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Excitement is building for FIFA World Cup soccer games in Toronto and Vancouver in June and July, yet Canada's overburdened health systems may buckle ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 05:10:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Why Your Sleep Schedule Matters As Much As Duration</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/why-your-sleep-schedule-matters-as-much-as-duration/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris challenges the conventional focus on sleep duration and makes the case that sleep timing and circadi...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 08:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Menopause Brain Fog—What’s Really Happening (and How To Fix It)</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rhr-menopause-brain-fog-whats-really-happening-and-how-to-fix-it/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris examines research confirming that menopause-related brain fog is real, measurable, and reversible. H...</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 08:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Seed Oils and Colon Cancer – What the New Research Really Shows</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/seed-oils-and-colon-cancer-what-the-new-research-really-shows/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Seed oils have become one of the most controversial topics in nutrition, especially after a 2024 University of South Florida study linked high omega-6...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 08:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Longevity Trap: Why Chasing Anti-Aging May Be Aging You</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-longevity-trap-why-chasing-anti-aging-may-be-aging-you/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>In this episode, Chris explains why obsession with anti-aging hacks may actually undermine our long-term health. He examines the common longevity trap...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Link Between Metabolic Health and Mental Well-Being, with Dr. Matt Bernstein</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-link-between-metabolic-health-and-mental-well-being-with-dr-matt-bernstein/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes psychiatrist Dr. Matt Bernstein to explore the emerging field of metabolic psychiatry, the ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>