<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:23:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Inflammation-induced metabolic shifts linked to brain disorders</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-inflammation-metabolic-shifts-linked-brain.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Acute systemic inflammation has long been suspected to trigger harmful processes within the brain, contributing to neurodegenerative disorders such as...</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 18:46:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Key protein ACE2 could protect against high blood pressure and diabetes</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-key-protein-ace2-high-blood.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Proteins circulating in the blood can reveal what's happening in the body, from how we process energy to how diseases develop. Unlike genetic testing,...</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 18:46:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prolonged hydrodistention may provide longer symptom relief in interstitial cystitis</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-prolonged-hydrodistention-longer-symptom-relief.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>For patients with interstitial cystitis (IC), longer cystoscopic hydrodistention (HD) times may result in improved efficacy and longer symptom relief,...</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 18:40:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Genomic test helps flag early aggressive prostate cancer in African American patients</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-genomic-flag-early-aggressive-prostate.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>A new Moffitt Cancer Center study suggests a widely used genomic test can more accurately identify which men with early prostate cancer are at high ri...</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 18:50:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>30-year smoking duration-based criteria could increase lung cancer screening</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-year-duration-based-criteria-lung.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Thirty-year smoking duration-based criteria could reduce eligibility gaps for all races relative to whites, while improving six-year lung cancer detec...</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 18:41:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Seed Oils and Colon Cancer – What the New Research Really Shows</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/seed-oils-and-colon-cancer-what-the-new-research-really-shows/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Seed oils have become one of the most controversial topics in nutrition, especially after a 2024 University of South Florida study linked high omega-6...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 08:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Longevity Trap: Why Chasing Anti-Aging May Be Aging You</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-longevity-trap-why-chasing-anti-aging-may-be-aging-you/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>In this episode, Chris explains why obsession with anti-aging hacks may actually undermine our long-term health. He examines the common longevity trap...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Link Between Metabolic Health and Mental Well-Being, with Dr. Matt Bernstein</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-link-between-metabolic-health-and-mental-well-being-with-dr-matt-bernstein/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes psychiatrist Dr. Matt Bernstein to explore the emerging field of metabolic psychiatry, the ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: From Wired &amp; Tired to Calm &amp; Clear: My Top Nutrients for Mood, Focus, and Sleep</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/from-wired-tired-to-calm-clear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris explores natural solutions for one of today’s most pressing challenges: chronic stress, anxiety, and...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Science Behind Oral Inflammation, with Dr. William Levine</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-science-behind-oral-inflammation-with-dr-william-levine/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes board-certified periodontist Dr. William Levine to discuss the overlooked role of gum healt...</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>