<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 11:00:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>New therapy outperforms standard treatment in reducing binge-eating among veterans</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-therapy-outperforms-standard-treatment-binge.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Researchers from the University of California San Diego have found that a novel treatment called regulation of cues combined with behavioral weight lo...</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Less processed diet may be more beneficial for weight loss, clinical trial indicates</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-diet-beneficial-weight-loss-clinical.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>When given nutritionally matched diets, participants lost twice as much weight eating minimally processed foods compared to ultra-processed foods, sug...</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Researchers watched 150 episodes of Bluey—they found it can teach kids about resilience for real life</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-episodes-bluey-kids-resilience-real.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>She's 6 years old, lives in Brisbane and might just be one of the best resilience coaches on television.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 15:36:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fall prevention program developed for older adults with mild cognitive impairment</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-fall-older-adults-mild-cognitive.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Falls pose a significant risk to older adults, often resulting in injuries that lead to other health problems, decreased independence, and a lower qua...</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 15:37:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Psychology research reveals how the brain constructs emotional experiences</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-psychology-reveals-brain-emotional.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Arousal—how alert or excited one feels—is a basic part of emotions, along with whether those emotions are positive or negative. Scientists still don't...</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 15:55:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Mold, Indoor Air Quality, and Clean Breathing, with Michael Rubino</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/mold-indoor-air-quality-and-clean-breathing-with-michael-rubino/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes environmental wellness expert Michael Rubino for an in-depth conversation on the hi...</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 08:01:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Nourishment Table, with Frederic Leroy</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-nourishment-table-with-frederic-leroy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes food scientist and advocate for regenerative agriculture Dr. Frederic Leroy to disc...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Turn ChatGPT Into Your Personal Meal Planner</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/turn-chatgpt-into-your-personal-meal-planner/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Even for someone who lives and breathes nutrition, meal planning can feel like a grind. There are weeks when I... The post Turn ChatGPT Into Your Pers...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:16:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Rediscovering Health, Nature, and Purpose-Driven Business, with Seth Spears</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rediscovering-health-nature-and-purpose-driven-business-with-seth-spears/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes entrepreneur and strategist Seth Spears for a wide-ranging conversation on health, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: How to Sharpen and Protect Your Mind for a Lifetime, with Dale Bredesen</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/how-to-sharpen-and-protect-your-mind-for-a-lifetime-with-dale-bredesen/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes renowned neurologist Dr. Dale Bredesen back to the show for an insightful conversation abou...</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:01:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>