<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 11:37:36 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Periostin Identified as Key Biomarker for Differentiating Sinonasal Lesions</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/periostin-identified-as-key-biomarker-for-differentiating-sinonasal-lesions/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Extracellular matrix proteins show efficacy for distinguishing between sinonasal lesions, including antrochoanal polyps, nasal polyps, and inverted pa...</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 15:54:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FDA Clearance of Blood Test for Alzheimer’s Inspires Cautious Optimism</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/fda-clearance-of-blood-test-for-alzheimers-inspires-cautious-optimism/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Dr. Richard G. Stefanacci explains why the FDA's recent clearance of a diagnostic blood test for Alzheimer's deserves celebration and critical examina...</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 15:49:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Real-World Data Reveal Higher Risk of Serious Infections in Patients With CLL/SLL</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/real-world-data-reveal-higher-risk-of-serious-infections-in-patients-with-cll-sll/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>A real-world study presented at ASCO 2025 found that patients with CLL/SLL experienced a higher risk of serious infections with one treatment regimen ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 16:02:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Recent Research on Nasal Polyps Highlights Disease’s Impact</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/recent-research-on-nasal-polyps-highlights-diseases-impact/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Recent research on nasal polyps includes an evaluation of the Sino-Nasal Outcome Test 22 questionnaire and a look at the mental impact of the conditio...</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 15:53:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Polycystic ovary syndrome: Awareness improves significantly as health professionals and patients support name change</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-05-polycystic-ovary-syndrome-awareness-significantly.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Most experts and those experiencing the potentially debilitating features of polycystic ovary syndrome (PCOS), which affects one in eight women, want ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 16:02:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Personalized cancer model predicts patient-specific gene behavior, potentially improving survival outcomes</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-05-personalized-cancer-patient-specific-gene.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Carnegie Mellon University researchers are using personalized models to decode how cancer behaves in individual patients—revealing hidden subtypes, im...</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 16:10:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mapping the 'brain in the gut' may provide clues to gastrointestinal disorders</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-05-brain-gut-clues-gastrointestinal-disorders.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Researchers at Karolinska Institutet have identified three types of nerve cells connected to the intestinal villi, suggesting that previously unknown ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 16:18:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What are the most common causes of nasal polyps?</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/what-are-the-most-common-causes-of-nasal-polyps/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Test your knowledge on nasal polyps, and how you compare to your peers. The post What are the most common causes of nasal polyps? first appeared on Ph...</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 15:52:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Understanding how Creutzfeldt-Jakob disease hides in neurons for decades</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-05-creutzfeldt-jakob-disease-neurons-decades.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In April 2025, three people in Oregon developed Creutzfeldt-Jakob disease (CJD), a rare, fatal neurological condition that is similar to bovine spongi...</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 16:28:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Potent CDK9 inhibitor shows promise for overcoming drug resistance in hematological malignancies</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-05-potent-cdk9-inhibitor-drug-resistance.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>A research team has developed a new class of compounds that effectively inhibit both wild-type CDK9 and its drug-resistant mutant form, offering a pro...</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 16:27:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Turn ChatGPT Into Your Personal Meal Planner</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/turn-chatgpt-into-your-personal-meal-planner/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Even for someone who lives and breathes nutrition, meal planning can feel like a grind. There are weeks when I... The post Turn ChatGPT Into Your Pers...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:16:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Rediscovering Health, Nature, and Purpose-Driven Business, with Seth Spears</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rediscovering-health-nature-and-purpose-driven-business-with-seth-spears/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes entrepreneur and strategist Seth Spears for a wide-ranging conversation on health, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: How to Sharpen and Protect Your Mind for a Lifetime, with Dale Bredesen</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/how-to-sharpen-and-protect-your-mind-for-a-lifetime-with-dale-bredesen/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes renowned neurologist Dr. Dale Bredesen back to the show for an insightful conversation abou...</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:01:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quality Matters: How to Choose and Use the Best Collagen Supplement</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/quality-matters-how-to-choose-and-use-the-best-collagen-supplement/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Introduction If you’ve been paying attention to health and wellness trends, you’ve likely noticed collagen supplements everywhere—from your local heal...</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:57:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Collagen: The Essential Building Block for Strong Joints and Bones</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/collagen-the-essential-building-block-for-strong-joints-and-bones/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>The Foundation of Your Musculoskeletal System If you’ve ever winced going down stairs, felt that telltale morning stiffness, or worried... The post Co...</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 13:31:22 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>