<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 06:55:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Popular YoCrunch Yogurt Recalled Over Plastic Pieces in Packaging</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/popular-yocrunch-yogurt-recalled-over-plastic-pieces-in-packaging/</link><image_url>https://cdn.physiciansweekly.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/HEALTHDAY_Web_small3.png</image_url><description>WEDNESDAY, July 16, 2025 (HealthDay News) — YoCrunch yogurt products are being pulled from store shelves nationwide due to a safety concern, its manuf...</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 07:31:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Court Allows West Virginia to Restrict Abortion Pill Mifepristone</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/court-allows-west-virginia-to-restrict-abortion-pill-mifepristone/</link><image_url>https://cdn.physiciansweekly.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/HEALTHDAY_Web_small3.png</image_url><description>WEDNESDAY, July 16, 2025 (HealthDay News) — A federal appeals court has ruled that West Virginia can limit access to mifepristone, a medication used t...</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 07:31:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Thousands Laid off From NIH, FDA and CDC After Supreme Court Decision</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/thousands-laid-off-from-nih-fda-and-cdc-after-supreme-court-decision/</link><image_url>https://cdn.physiciansweekly.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/HEALTHDAY_Web_small3.png</image_url><description>WEDNESDAY, July 16, 2025 (HealthDay News) — Thousands of health workers lost their jobs this week after a U.S. Supreme Court ruling cleared the way fo...</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 07:31:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Global study shows longer brain scans lower research costs, provide more accurate predictions</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-global-longer-brain-scans-accurate.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Artificial intelligence (AI) models trained on large datasets are increasingly seen as the key to unlocking personalized treatments for brain disorder...</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 10:10:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Million Veterans Gave DNA To Aid Health Research. Scientists Worry the Data Will Be Wasted.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/a-million-veterans-gave-dna-to-aid-health-research-scientists-worry-the-data-will-be-wasted/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>One of the world’s biggest genetic databases comprises DNA data donated over the years by more than a million retired military service members. It’s p...</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 11:30:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Researchers try new ways of preserving more hearts for transplants</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-ways-hearts-transplants.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Two university hospitals are pioneering new ways to expand lifesaving heart transplants for adults and babies—advances that could help recover would-b...</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 09:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI can accelerate search for more effective Alzheimer's medicines by streamlining clinical trials</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-ai-effective-alzheimer-medicines-clinical.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Scientists have used an AI model to reassess the results of a completed clinical trial for an Alzheimer's disease drug. They found that the drug slowe...</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 10:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Higher copper intake correlates with better cognitive performance in older adults, data suggest</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-higher-copper-intake-cognitive-older.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Cognitive impairment is increasing globally. All stages of dementia are marked by declines in memory and executive function. Previous research has exa...</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 10:01:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Radiation and temozolomide improves hearing in an adult brainstem glioma patient with a rare IDH2 mutation: Case report</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-temozolomide-adult-brainstem-glioma-patient.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>A group led by the Department of Neurosurgery at the Brain Research Institute, Niigata University, has successfully treated a patient with a brainstem...</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 10:04:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lost in Translation: Interpreter Cutbacks Could Put Patient Lives on the Line</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/lost-in-translation-interpreter-cutbacks-could-put-patient-lives-on-the-line/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>LISTEN: Federal law entitles patients to interpreters if they don’t have a strong grasp of English. KFF Health News correspondent Vanessa G. Sánchez a...</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 11:30:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Mold, Indoor Air Quality, and Clean Breathing, with Michael Rubino</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/mold-indoor-air-quality-and-clean-breathing-with-michael-rubino/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes environmental wellness expert Michael Rubino for an in-depth conversation on the hi...</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 08:01:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Nourishment Table, with Frederic Leroy</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-nourishment-table-with-frederic-leroy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes food scientist and advocate for regenerative agriculture Dr. Frederic Leroy to disc...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Turn ChatGPT Into Your Personal Meal Planner</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/turn-chatgpt-into-your-personal-meal-planner/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Even for someone who lives and breathes nutrition, meal planning can feel like a grind. There are weeks when I... The post Turn ChatGPT Into Your Pers...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:16:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Rediscovering Health, Nature, and Purpose-Driven Business, with Seth Spears</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rediscovering-health-nature-and-purpose-driven-business-with-seth-spears/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes entrepreneur and strategist Seth Spears for a wide-ranging conversation on health, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: How to Sharpen and Protect Your Mind for a Lifetime, with Dale Bredesen</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/how-to-sharpen-and-protect-your-mind-for-a-lifetime-with-dale-bredesen/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes renowned neurologist Dr. Dale Bredesen back to the show for an insightful conversation abou...</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:01:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>