<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Declines in driving frequency, complexity seen for drivers with mild cognitive impairment</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-declines-frequency-complexity-drivers-mild.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Drivers with mild cognitive impairment (MCI) have declines in driving frequency, complexity, and spatial range, according to a study published online ...</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>California officials warn against foraging wild mushrooms after deadly poisoning outbreak</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-california-foraging-wild-mushrooms-deadly.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>California officials are warning foragers after an outbreak of poisoning linked to wild mushrooms that has killed one adult and caused severe liver da...</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:42:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nordic people know how to beat the winter blues. Here's how to find light in the darkest months</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-nordic-people-winter-blues-darkest.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>The Nordic countries are no strangers to the long, dark winter.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:36:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>US stillbirth rate falls 2%, but nearly 20,000 losses still reported</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-stillbirth-falls-losses.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>The U.S. stillbirth rate dropped slightly last year, offering some hope after several years of uncertainty, according to new data from the U.S. Center...</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 15:10:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How DNA tricks help tuberculosis fight back against treatment</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-dna-tuberculosis-treatment.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Tuberculosis (TB) is one of the oldest and deadliest infectious diseases we know. It commonly impacts the lungs, but can also affect other areas of th...</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 15:20:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Longevity Trap: Why Chasing Anti-Aging May Be Aging You</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-longevity-trap-why-chasing-anti-aging-may-be-aging-you/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>In this episode, Chris explains why obsession with anti-aging hacks may actually undermine our long-term health. He examines the common longevity trap...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Link Between Metabolic Health and Mental Well-Being, with Dr. Matt Bernstein</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-link-between-metabolic-health-and-mental-well-being-with-dr-matt-bernstein/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes psychiatrist Dr. Matt Bernstein to explore the emerging field of metabolic psychiatry, the ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: From Wired &amp; Tired to Calm &amp; Clear: My Top Nutrients for Mood, Focus, and Sleep</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/from-wired-tired-to-calm-clear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris explores natural solutions for one of today’s most pressing challenges: chronic stress, anxiety, and...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Science Behind Oral Inflammation, with Dr. William Levine</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-science-behind-oral-inflammation-with-dr-william-levine/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes board-certified periodontist Dr. William Levine to discuss the overlooked role of gum healt...</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hyaluronic Acid: The Deep Hydration Molecule Your Skin Has Been Waiting For</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/hyaluronic-acid-the-deep-hydration-molecule-your-skin-has-been-waiting-for/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>If you’ve spent any time exploring the world of natural skincare, chances are you’ve heard of hyaluronic acid (HA). Once... The post Hyaluronic Acid: ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>