<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 05:38:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Timely home repairs are needed for good health in remote Aboriginal communities</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-home-good-health-remote-aboriginal.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>For people living in metro areas, a broken hot water system or washing machine is a nuisance. But it can usually be sorted by a phone call for a same-...</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 02:10:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biovac starts trials on South Africa's first domestically developed cholera vaccine</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-biovac-trials-south-africa-domestically.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Researchers and scientists in South Africa on Tuesday launched clinical trials on the first domestically developed vaccine.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 09:08:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Better treatments buoy multiple-myeloma patients, bound by research cuts and racial disparities</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-treatments-buoy-multiple-myeloma-patients.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>For more than a year, Diane Hunter, now 72, had been experiencing vague symptoms—pain in her spine and hips, nausea, exhaustion, thirst, and frequent ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 01:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ByHeart recalls all baby formula sold nationwide as infant botulism outbreak grows</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-byheart-recalls-baby-formula-sold.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>ByHeart, a manufacturer of organic baby formula, recalled all of its products sold nationwide Tuesday, days after some batches were recalled in an exp...</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 09:10:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Treatment with antibiotics and steroids in adults with pneumonia addressed in latest clinical practice guideline</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-treatment-antibiotics-steroids-adults-pneumonia.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Pneumonia, a largely preventable disease, caused more than two million deaths in 2021, according to the Global Burden of Disease report. Evidence-base...</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 10:12:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: From Wired &amp; Tired to Calm &amp; Clear: My Top Nutrients for Mood, Focus, and Sleep</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/from-wired-tired-to-calm-clear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris explores natural solutions for one of today’s most pressing challenges: chronic stress, anxiety, and...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Science Behind Oral Inflammation, with Dr. William Levine</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-science-behind-oral-inflammation-with-dr-william-levine/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes board-certified periodontist Dr. William Levine to discuss the overlooked role of gum healt...</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hyaluronic Acid: The Deep Hydration Molecule Your Skin Has Been Waiting For</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/hyaluronic-acid-the-deep-hydration-molecule-your-skin-has-been-waiting-for/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>If you’ve spent any time exploring the world of natural skincare, chances are you’ve heard of hyaluronic acid (HA). Once... The post Hyaluronic Acid: ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rice Ceramides: The Unsung Hero of Skin Hydration and Barrier Health</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rice-ceramides-the-unsung-hero-of-skin-hydration-and-barrier-health/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>We often think of radiant skin as the result of what we put on it: moisturizers, serums, masks. But emerging... The post Rice Ceramides: The Unsung He...</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lutein and Zeaxanthin: The Carotenoids That Protect and Perfect Your Skin from Within</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/lutein-and-zeaxanthin-the-carotenoids-that-protect-and-perfect-your-skin-from-within/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>When most people think of lutein and zeaxanthin, they picture eye health supplements or leafy green vegetables. But these vibrant... The post Lutein a...</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:00:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>