<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Costs pose hurdle for promising new hepatitis C lab test</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-pose-hurdle-hepatitis-lab.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>A new rapid test for hepatitis C could help identify many more patients who could be cured of the deadly disease, but its use may be limited unless in...</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:24:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Creating cells that help the brain keep its cool</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-cells-brain-cool.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Researchers at Lund University in Sweden have created a method that makes it possible to transform the brain's support cells into parvalbumin-positive...</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:22:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A mother's circadian rhythm may predict her child's vulnerability to bacterial infection</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-mother-circadian-rhythm-child-vulnerability.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>In laboratory models, researchers at The University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Center discovered that a mother's circadian rhythms, or internal body ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:00:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Australia's red and yellow beach flags can be dangerously confusing. Is it time to change them?</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-australia-red-yellow-beach-flags.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Every summer in Australia, millions of people head to the beach, and every year, thousands are rescued by lifeguards or Surf Life Savers and even surf...</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:58:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>High-dose risankizumab trial tests staying power against psoriasis</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-high-dose-risankizumab-trial-staying.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Oregon Medical Research Center in Portland, Oregon, has led a phase 2 trial in moderate-to-severe plaque psoriasis that paired higher-than-approved do...</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:38:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Menopause Brain Fog—What’s Really Happening (and How To Fix It)</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rhr-menopause-brain-fog-whats-really-happening-and-how-to-fix-it/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris examines research confirming that menopause-related brain fog is real, measurable, and reversible. H...</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 08:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Seed Oils and Colon Cancer – What the New Research Really Shows</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/seed-oils-and-colon-cancer-what-the-new-research-really-shows/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Seed oils have become one of the most controversial topics in nutrition, especially after a 2024 University of South Florida study linked high omega-6...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 08:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Longevity Trap: Why Chasing Anti-Aging May Be Aging You</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-longevity-trap-why-chasing-anti-aging-may-be-aging-you/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>In this episode, Chris explains why obsession with anti-aging hacks may actually undermine our long-term health. He examines the common longevity trap...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Link Between Metabolic Health and Mental Well-Being, with Dr. Matt Bernstein</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-link-between-metabolic-health-and-mental-well-being-with-dr-matt-bernstein/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes psychiatrist Dr. Matt Bernstein to explore the emerging field of metabolic psychiatry, the ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: From Wired &amp; Tired to Calm &amp; Clear: My Top Nutrients for Mood, Focus, and Sleep</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/from-wired-tired-to-calm-clear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris explores natural solutions for one of today’s most pressing challenges: chronic stress, anxiety, and...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>