<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 06:51:24 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>New white paper urges policymakers to modernize practice laws to unlock AI's full potential in health care</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-white-paper-urges-policymakers-modernize.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>As the U.S. confronts a historic health care workforce crisis, a new white paper released today calls on federal and state policymakers to modernize o...</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 11:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Combination therapy could expand treatment options for AML patients and extend survival</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-combination-therapy-treatment-options-aml.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Acute myeloid leukemia (AML), an aggressive and often fatal blood cancer, has long resisted a class of drugs called proteasome inhibitors, which work ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hormone therapy alters body proteins to match gender identity, researchers discover</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-hormone-therapy-body-proteins-gender.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Melbourne researchers have discovered gender-affirming hormone therapy can alter body proteins to match a person's gender identity, potentially affect...</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Experts urge risk-based monitoring as Barrett's esophagus care moves beyond one-size-fits-all</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-experts-urge-based-barrett-esophagus.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>The American Gastroenterological Association (AGA) today released a new clinical practice guideline on the surveillance of Barrett's esophagus, the on...</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eat, explore, rest: Leptin-sensing brain circuit helps overcome anxiety to meet vital needs</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-explore-rest-leptin-brain-circuit.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>How do mammals manage to eat in situations that cause anxiety, step into exposed spaces, or slow down when anxiety drives them to keep moving? A new s...</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Science Behind Oral Inflammation, with Dr. William Levine</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-science-behind-oral-inflammation-with-dr-william-levine/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes board-certified periodontist Dr. William Levine to discuss the overlooked role of gum healt...</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hyaluronic Acid: The Deep Hydration Molecule Your Skin Has Been Waiting For</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/hyaluronic-acid-the-deep-hydration-molecule-your-skin-has-been-waiting-for/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>If you’ve spent any time exploring the world of natural skincare, chances are you’ve heard of hyaluronic acid (HA). Once... The post Hyaluronic Acid: ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rice Ceramides: The Unsung Hero of Skin Hydration and Barrier Health</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rice-ceramides-the-unsung-hero-of-skin-hydration-and-barrier-health/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>We often think of radiant skin as the result of what we put on it: moisturizers, serums, masks. But emerging... The post Rice Ceramides: The Unsung He...</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lutein and Zeaxanthin: The Carotenoids That Protect and Perfect Your Skin from Within</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/lutein-and-zeaxanthin-the-carotenoids-that-protect-and-perfect-your-skin-from-within/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>When most people think of lutein and zeaxanthin, they picture eye health supplements or leafy green vegetables. But these vibrant... The post Lutein a...</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:00:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vitamin C: The Collagen-Stimulating, Skin-Brightening Antioxidant Your Skin Can’t Live Without</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/vitamin-c-the-collagen-stimulating-skin-brightening-antioxidant-your-skin-cant-live-without/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>When it comes to supporting skin health from the inside out, few nutrients are as essential—or as well-researched—as vitamin C.... The post Vitamin C:...</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 16:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>