<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 23:33:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Genetic Findings From Exome Sequencing in Fetal Effusions</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/genetic-findings-from-exome-sequencing-in-fetal-effusions/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>The following is a summary of “Genetic diseases underlying a spectrum of fetal effusions,” published in the May 2025 issue of American Journal of Obst...</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 00:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Perioperative Immunonutrition and Outcomes in Colorectal ERAS</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/perioperative-immunonutrition-and-outcomes-in-colorectal-eras/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>The following is a summary of “Association of perioperative immunonutrition with anastomotic leak among patients undergoing elective colorectal surger...</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 23:00:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New blood test enables the rapid diagnosis of thousands of rare genetic diseases</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-05-blood-enables-rapid-diagnosis-thousands.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>A new, rapid testing method will greatly help the diagnosis of rare diseases in babies and children, according to research presented to the annual con...</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 23:10:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Just three nights of poor sleep might harm your heart: New study</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-05-nights-poor-heart.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>We've long known that a lack of sleep is bad for the heart—but scientists are now starting to understand exactly how it causes harm.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 22:40:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amyloid and Tau Proteins Linked to Postoperative Delirium Risk</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/amyloid-and-tau-proteins-linked-to-postoperative-delirium-risk/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>The following is a summary of “Associations between Aβ40, Aβ42, and tau and postoperative delirium in older adults undergoing cardiac surgery,” publis...</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 23:30:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Depressive Symptoms and Physical Activity in Knee Osteoarthritis</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/depressive-symptoms-and-physical-activity-in-knee-osteoarthritis/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>The following is a summary of “Association Between Depressive Symptoms and Self-Reported Physical Activity in Persons With Knee Osteoarthritis,” publi...</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 22:00:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Clinical Variability in Herpesvirus Infections After Kidney Transplant</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/clinical-variability-in-herpesvirus-infections-after-kidney-transplant/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>The following is a summary of “Transplant centers’ prophylaxis and monitoring strategies: a key determinant of current herpes and polyomavirus inciden...</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 22:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Intravenous tenecteplase beneficial before endovascular thrombectomy</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-05-intravenous-tenecteplase-beneficial-endovascular-thrombectomy.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>For patients with acute ischemic stroke due to large-vessel occlusion who present within 4.5 hours, intravenous tenecteplase before endovascular throm...</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 18:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Genetic investigations reveal reason for severe neuropathy after infection</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-05-genetic-reveal-severe-neuropathy-infection.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Neuropathy, a disorder in which damage to nerves can impair sensation and movement, has many causes, including infection. Now, researchers from the UK...</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 23:10:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How abortion laws focusing on fetal viability miss the mark on women's experiences</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-05-abortion-laws-focusing-fetal-viability.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>During the 2024 presidential campaign, politicians and their surrogates repeatedly raised concerns about abortion later in pregnancy. The topic grabbe...</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 18:40:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Turn ChatGPT Into Your Personal Meal Planner</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/turn-chatgpt-into-your-personal-meal-planner/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Even for someone who lives and breathes nutrition, meal planning can feel like a grind. There are weeks when I... The post Turn ChatGPT Into Your Pers...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:16:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Rediscovering Health, Nature, and Purpose-Driven Business, with Seth Spears</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rediscovering-health-nature-and-purpose-driven-business-with-seth-spears/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes entrepreneur and strategist Seth Spears for a wide-ranging conversation on health, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: How to Sharpen and Protect Your Mind for a Lifetime, with Dale Bredesen</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/how-to-sharpen-and-protect-your-mind-for-a-lifetime-with-dale-bredesen/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes renowned neurologist Dr. Dale Bredesen back to the show for an insightful conversation abou...</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:01:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quality Matters: How to Choose and Use the Best Collagen Supplement</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/quality-matters-how-to-choose-and-use-the-best-collagen-supplement/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Introduction If you’ve been paying attention to health and wellness trends, you’ve likely noticed collagen supplements everywhere—from your local heal...</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:57:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Collagen: The Essential Building Block for Strong Joints and Bones</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/collagen-the-essential-building-block-for-strong-joints-and-bones/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>The Foundation of Your Musculoskeletal System If you’ve ever winced going down stairs, felt that telltale morning stiffness, or worried... The post Co...</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 13:31:22 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>