<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:05:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The first child-specific body scan charts could enable physicians to assess obesity risk</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-child-specific-body-scan-enable.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>A Concordia-led research team has created one of the first reference charts showing how children's adipose (fat) and muscle levels change with age and...</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 21:29:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Experimental targeted therapy shows promise for histiocytosis, a rare blood cancer</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-experimental-therapy-histiocytosis-rare-blood.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>The first time Joey Carlsen Martinez came to Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSK), he was in terrible shape. He had a rare blood cancer called...</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 20:57:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Study reveals epigenetic mechanisms regulating ILC2 memory and asthma recurrence</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-reveals-epigenetic-mechanisms-ilc2-memory.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Researchers have revealed a novel mechanism by which the chromatin remodeler brahma-related gene 1 (Brg1) regulates Group 2 innate lymphoid cells (ILC...</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 21:48:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Testosterone levels decline with age, not menopause, study finds</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-testosterone-decline-age-menopause.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Social media widely promotes testosterone as an essential part of menopausal hormone therapy (MHT, also known as hormone replacement therapy or HRT) t...</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 20:59:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gluten sensitivity linked to gut–brain interaction, not gluten itself, study finds</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-gluten-sensitivity-linked-gutbrain-interaction.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>A study has revealed that gluten sensitivity, which affects approximately 10% of the global population, is not actually about gluten but part of the w...</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 21:04:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Science Behind Oral Inflammation, with Dr. William Levine</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-science-behind-oral-inflammation-with-dr-william-levine/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes board-certified periodontist Dr. William Levine to discuss the overlooked role of gum healt...</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hyaluronic Acid: The Deep Hydration Molecule Your Skin Has Been Waiting For</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/hyaluronic-acid-the-deep-hydration-molecule-your-skin-has-been-waiting-for/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>If you’ve spent any time exploring the world of natural skincare, chances are you’ve heard of hyaluronic acid (HA). Once... The post Hyaluronic Acid: ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rice Ceramides: The Unsung Hero of Skin Hydration and Barrier Health</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rice-ceramides-the-unsung-hero-of-skin-hydration-and-barrier-health/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>We often think of radiant skin as the result of what we put on it: moisturizers, serums, masks. But emerging... The post Rice Ceramides: The Unsung He...</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lutein and Zeaxanthin: The Carotenoids That Protect and Perfect Your Skin from Within</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/lutein-and-zeaxanthin-the-carotenoids-that-protect-and-perfect-your-skin-from-within/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>When most people think of lutein and zeaxanthin, they picture eye health supplements or leafy green vegetables. But these vibrant... The post Lutein a...</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:00:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vitamin C: The Collagen-Stimulating, Skin-Brightening Antioxidant Your Skin Can’t Live Without</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/vitamin-c-the-collagen-stimulating-skin-brightening-antioxidant-your-skin-cant-live-without/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>When it comes to supporting skin health from the inside out, few nutrients are as essential—or as well-researched—as vitamin C.... The post Vitamin C:...</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 16:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>