<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 07:48:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Maxing out your fiber intake can have broad health benefits</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-maxing-fiber-intake-broad-health.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>The amount of fiber you consume can have significant impacts on your body. From healthy digestion, to reducing your risk of developing cancer, eating ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 12:07:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Predicting the risk of heart disease and dementia in older adults: Q&amp;A</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-heart-disease-dementia-older-adults.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>More than 70% of people over 70 years old will one day develop cardiovascular disease, highlighting the need for effective diagnosis, treatment, and c...</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 12:30:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When 'eating for two' is off the menu: Study finds 1 in 10 pregnant women experiences food insecurity in Australia</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-menu-pregnant-women-food-insecurity.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>A nutritious diet is vital to good health in both the mother and the developing baby during pregnancy.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 11:23:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Research shows that improved home ventilation can ease asthma symptoms, advance public health</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-home-ventilation-ease-asthma-symptoms.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>For millions of people living with asthma, even the air inside their homes can make breathing difficult. But researchers at The University of Texas at...</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 12:39:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When death knocks: Study explores life's spookiest question</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-death-explores-life-spookiest.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Death, terror and anxiety might sound like ingredients for the perfect Halloween haunted house, but they are also the focus of a serious study on the ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 11:56:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: From Wired &amp; Tired to Calm &amp; Clear: My Top Nutrients for Mood, Focus, and Sleep</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/from-wired-tired-to-calm-clear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris explores natural solutions for one of today’s most pressing challenges: chronic stress, anxiety, and...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Science Behind Oral Inflammation, with Dr. William Levine</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-science-behind-oral-inflammation-with-dr-william-levine/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes board-certified periodontist Dr. William Levine to discuss the overlooked role of gum healt...</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hyaluronic Acid: The Deep Hydration Molecule Your Skin Has Been Waiting For</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/hyaluronic-acid-the-deep-hydration-molecule-your-skin-has-been-waiting-for/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>If you’ve spent any time exploring the world of natural skincare, chances are you’ve heard of hyaluronic acid (HA). Once... The post Hyaluronic Acid: ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rice Ceramides: The Unsung Hero of Skin Hydration and Barrier Health</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rice-ceramides-the-unsung-hero-of-skin-hydration-and-barrier-health/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>We often think of radiant skin as the result of what we put on it: moisturizers, serums, masks. But emerging... The post Rice Ceramides: The Unsung He...</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lutein and Zeaxanthin: The Carotenoids That Protect and Perfect Your Skin from Within</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/lutein-and-zeaxanthin-the-carotenoids-that-protect-and-perfect-your-skin-from-within/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>When most people think of lutein and zeaxanthin, they picture eye health supplements or leafy green vegetables. But these vibrant... The post Lutein a...</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:00:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>