<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:39:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Social interaction among infants boosts diversity of gut microbial strains, study shows</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-social-interaction-infants-boosts-diversity.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>The microbiome of infants is shaped by social relationships from an early age and not only by family sources, finds a recent study published in the jo...</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:01:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Religion/spirituality may protect against depression among young adult online gamers</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-religionspirituality-depression-young-adult-online.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Internet use is part of daily life for many people in work, social interaction, entertainment, shopping, and many other activities. Many people engage...</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:05:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Brain navigation study reveals function of an unconventional electrical-signaling mode in neurons</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-brain-reveals-function-unconventional-electrical.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Navigating the world is no mean feat, especially when the world pushes back. For instance, airflow hitting a fly on its right side can, after a turn, ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:32:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Treating psoriasis without side effects: Light-activated molecules demonstrate potential</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-psoriasis-side-effects-molecules-potential.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Researchers from the Institute for Advanced Chemistry of Catalonia (IQAC) of the Spanish National Research Council (CSIC) have developed a series of l...</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:39:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Donated blood has a shelf life, and a new test tracks how it ages</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-donated-blood-shelf-life-tracks.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>A new, fast and easy test could revolutionize blood transfusions, giving blood centers and hospitals a reliable way to monitor the quality of red bloo...</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:20:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Why Your Sleep Schedule Matters As Much As Duration</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/why-your-sleep-schedule-matters-as-much-as-duration/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris challenges the conventional focus on sleep duration and makes the case that sleep timing and circadi...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 08:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Menopause Brain Fog—What’s Really Happening (and How To Fix It)</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rhr-menopause-brain-fog-whats-really-happening-and-how-to-fix-it/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris examines research confirming that menopause-related brain fog is real, measurable, and reversible. H...</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 08:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Seed Oils and Colon Cancer – What the New Research Really Shows</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/seed-oils-and-colon-cancer-what-the-new-research-really-shows/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Seed oils have become one of the most controversial topics in nutrition, especially after a 2024 University of South Florida study linked high omega-6...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 08:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Longevity Trap: Why Chasing Anti-Aging May Be Aging You</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-longevity-trap-why-chasing-anti-aging-may-be-aging-you/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>In this episode, Chris explains why obsession with anti-aging hacks may actually undermine our long-term health. He examines the common longevity trap...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Link Between Metabolic Health and Mental Well-Being, with Dr. Matt Bernstein</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-link-between-metabolic-health-and-mental-well-being-with-dr-matt-bernstein/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes psychiatrist Dr. Matt Bernstein to explore the emerging field of metabolic psychiatry, the ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>