<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 12:11:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>One-time gene therapy could end lifelong transfusions for rare blood disease</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-09-gene-therapy-lifelong-transfusions-rare.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Thanks to in-utero blood transfusion technology, what was once a fatal diagnosis in the womb can now result in live births. However, this medical adva...</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:47:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Study urges unified approach to assessing zoonotic and vector-borne disease risks</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-09-urges-approach-zoonotic-vector-borne.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>A study published in the journal One Earth points out that risk assessments for diseases transmitted by infected animals (zoonotic) and by vectors (su...</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 17:09:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>UK dementia patients may be taking antipsychotics for too long</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-09-uk-dementia-patients-antipsychotics.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Thousands of people with dementia are prescribed powerful medications for longer and at higher doses than recommended, raising concerns about safety a...</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:50:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Flu vaccine rates may increase with acknowledging regret, study finds</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-09-flu-vaccine-acknowledging.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Asking people to imagine future regret could be a powerful tool for increasing flu vaccination rates, according to new research from SMU.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 17:04:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Study finds 10% of pediatric blood cancers may stem from medical imaging radiation</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-09-pediatric-blood-cancers-stem-medical.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>A study led by UC San Francisco and UC Davis has concluded that radiation from medical imaging is associated with a higher risk of blood cancers in ch...</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:50:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hyaluronic Acid: The Deep Hydration Molecule Your Skin Has Been Waiting For</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/hyaluronic-acid-the-deep-hydration-molecule-your-skin-has-been-waiting-for/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>If you’ve spent any time exploring the world of natural skincare, chances are you’ve heard of hyaluronic acid (HA). Once... The post Hyaluronic Acid: ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rice Ceramides: The Unsung Hero of Skin Hydration and Barrier Health</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rice-ceramides-the-unsung-hero-of-skin-hydration-and-barrier-health/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>We often think of radiant skin as the result of what we put on it: moisturizers, serums, masks. But emerging... The post Rice Ceramides: The Unsung He...</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lutein and Zeaxanthin: The Carotenoids That Protect and Perfect Your Skin from Within</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/lutein-and-zeaxanthin-the-carotenoids-that-protect-and-perfect-your-skin-from-within/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>When most people think of lutein and zeaxanthin, they picture eye health supplements or leafy green vegetables. But these vibrant... The post Lutein a...</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:00:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vitamin C: The Collagen-Stimulating, Skin-Brightening Antioxidant Your Skin Can’t Live Without</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/vitamin-c-the-collagen-stimulating-skin-brightening-antioxidant-your-skin-cant-live-without/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>When it comes to supporting skin health from the inside out, few nutrients are as essential—or as well-researched—as vitamin C.... The post Vitamin C:...</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 16:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eggshell Membrane Collagen: A Natural Ally for Skin, Hair, and Nail Vitality</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/eggshell-membrane-collagen-a-natural-ally-for-skin-hair-and-nail-vitality/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>In the growing world of natural beauty and inside-out skincare, few ingredients offer the versatility and clinical backing of eggshell... The post Egg...</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>