<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 11:26:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Clinical trial shows efficacy of bacteriophage therapy for Staphylococcus aureus bacteremia</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-clinical-trial-efficacy-bacteriophage-therapy.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>During IDWeek 2025 in Atlanta, Georgia, Loren G. Miller, MD, MPH, investigator at The Lundquist Institute for Biomedical Innovation at Harbor-UCLA Med...</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 16:20:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Four subgroups of polycystic ovary syndrome open doors for individualized treatment</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-subgroups-polycystic-ovary-syndrome-doors.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Four distinct subgroups of polycystic ovary syndrome (PCOS) have been identified in an international study published in Nature Medicine by researchers...</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 16:21:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Legal highs: These new drugs are cheap, dangerous, and just a click away</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-legal-highs-drugs-cheap-dangerous.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Imagine a world where you can buy recreational drugs online and receive them in the mail. Well, this world already exists, and not just with one or tw...</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 16:13:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FDA-approved focused ultrasound treatment for essential tremor now in use as primary treatment for Parkinson's</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-fda-focused-ultrasound-treatment-essential.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Barely an hour after being wheeled into a clinical space at Oregon Health &amp; Science University on Aug. 27, an Arkansas woman emerged with vastly impro...</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 16:20:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Saliva test detects heart failure biomarker for faster, noninvasive diagnosis</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-saliva-heart-failure-biomarker-faster.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Australian scientists have developed a biosensor that can rapidly detect the heart failure biomarker S100A7 in saliva, offering a simple, noninvasive ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 16:17:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: From Wired &amp; Tired to Calm &amp; Clear: My Top Nutrients for Mood, Focus, and Sleep</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/from-wired-tired-to-calm-clear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris explores natural solutions for one of today’s most pressing challenges: chronic stress, anxiety, and...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Science Behind Oral Inflammation, with Dr. William Levine</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-science-behind-oral-inflammation-with-dr-william-levine/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes board-certified periodontist Dr. William Levine to discuss the overlooked role of gum healt...</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hyaluronic Acid: The Deep Hydration Molecule Your Skin Has Been Waiting For</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/hyaluronic-acid-the-deep-hydration-molecule-your-skin-has-been-waiting-for/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>If you’ve spent any time exploring the world of natural skincare, chances are you’ve heard of hyaluronic acid (HA). Once... The post Hyaluronic Acid: ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rice Ceramides: The Unsung Hero of Skin Hydration and Barrier Health</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rice-ceramides-the-unsung-hero-of-skin-hydration-and-barrier-health/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>We often think of radiant skin as the result of what we put on it: moisturizers, serums, masks. But emerging... The post Rice Ceramides: The Unsung He...</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lutein and Zeaxanthin: The Carotenoids That Protect and Perfect Your Skin from Within</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/lutein-and-zeaxanthin-the-carotenoids-that-protect-and-perfect-your-skin-from-within/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>When most people think of lutein and zeaxanthin, they picture eye health supplements or leafy green vegetables. But these vibrant... The post Lutein a...</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:00:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>