<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 11:49:10 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Court Allows West Virginia to Restrict Abortion Pill Mifepristone</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/court-allows-west-virginia-to-restrict-abortion-pill-mifepristone/</link><image_url>https://cdn.physiciansweekly.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/HEALTHDAY_Web_small3.png</image_url><description>WEDNESDAY, July 16, 2025 (HealthDay News) — A federal appeals court has ruled that West Virginia can limit access to mifepristone, a medication used t...</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 07:31:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Popular YoCrunch Yogurt Recalled Over Plastic Pieces in Packaging</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/popular-yocrunch-yogurt-recalled-over-plastic-pieces-in-packaging/</link><image_url>https://cdn.physiciansweekly.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/HEALTHDAY_Web_small3.png</image_url><description>WEDNESDAY, July 16, 2025 (HealthDay News) — YoCrunch yogurt products are being pulled from store shelves nationwide due to a safety concern, its manuf...</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 07:31:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Thousands Laid off From NIH, FDA and CDC After Supreme Court Decision</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/thousands-laid-off-from-nih-fda-and-cdc-after-supreme-court-decision/</link><image_url>https://cdn.physiciansweekly.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/HEALTHDAY_Web_small3.png</image_url><description>WEDNESDAY, July 16, 2025 (HealthDay News) — Thousands of health workers lost their jobs this week after a U.S. Supreme Court ruling cleared the way fo...</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 07:31:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI can identify hidden heart valve defects from a patient's EKG</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-ai-hidden-heart-valve-defects.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>An AI algorithm could help to predict which patients might develop significant heart problems years in advance, just based on EKG readings.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 16:30:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Five things to know about ultra-processed food</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-ultra-food.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Most nutrition scientists agree that occasionally eating ultra-processed food, also called highly processed food, is no big deal. But, statistics show...</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 16:40:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RFK Jr. fires two Trump-appointed senior officials in ongoing HHS restructuring</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-rfk-jr-trump-senior-ongoing.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>U.S. Health and Human Services (HHS) Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. has removed two senior officials who were appointed by President Donald Trump.</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 16:30:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nearly 45% of hospital toilet users fail to wash their hands, study finds</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-hospital-toilet-users.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Almost 1 in 2 people using a hospital toilet did not wash their hands afterwards, according to new research from the University of Surrey—raising seri...</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 16:20:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lost in Translation: Interpreter Cutbacks Could Put Patient Lives on the Line</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/lost-in-translation-interpreter-cutbacks-could-put-patient-lives-on-the-line/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>LISTEN: Federal law entitles patients to interpreters if they don’t have a strong grasp of English. KFF Health News correspondent Vanessa G. Sánchez a...</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 11:30:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New research finds changing your diet could ease persistent headaches after brain injury</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-diet-ease-persistent-headaches-brain.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>A new clinical trial demonstrates that dietary changes significantly reduce persistent post-traumatic headaches (pPTH), a common and debilitating cons...</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 16:40:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Million Veterans Gave DNA To Aid Health Research. Scientists Worry the Data Will Be Wasted.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/a-million-veterans-gave-dna-to-aid-health-research-scientists-worry-the-data-will-be-wasted/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>One of the world’s biggest genetic databases comprises DNA data donated over the years by more than a million retired military service members. It’s p...</description><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 11:30:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Mold, Indoor Air Quality, and Clean Breathing, with Michael Rubino</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/mold-indoor-air-quality-and-clean-breathing-with-michael-rubino/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes environmental wellness expert Michael Rubino for an in-depth conversation on the hi...</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 08:01:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Nourishment Table, with Frederic Leroy</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-nourishment-table-with-frederic-leroy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes food scientist and advocate for regenerative agriculture Dr. Frederic Leroy to disc...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Turn ChatGPT Into Your Personal Meal Planner</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/turn-chatgpt-into-your-personal-meal-planner/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Even for someone who lives and breathes nutrition, meal planning can feel like a grind. There are weeks when I... The post Turn ChatGPT Into Your Pers...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:16:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Rediscovering Health, Nature, and Purpose-Driven Business, with Seth Spears</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rediscovering-health-nature-and-purpose-driven-business-with-seth-spears/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes entrepreneur and strategist Seth Spears for a wide-ranging conversation on health, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: How to Sharpen and Protect Your Mind for a Lifetime, with Dale Bredesen</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/how-to-sharpen-and-protect-your-mind-for-a-lifetime-with-dale-bredesen/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes renowned neurologist Dr. Dale Bredesen back to the show for an insightful conversation abou...</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:01:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>