<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>You finally got a doctor's appointment. Here's how to get the most out of it</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-doctor.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>It's not unusual for a 20-something to text Mom in a panic from the doctor's office, seeking help answering a question. And patients of any age can st...</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 13:14:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Worried about health insurance costs? There may be cheaper options—but with trade-offs</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-health-cheaper-options-offs.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>For the millions of Americans who buy Affordable Care Act insurance, there's still time left to enroll for 2026. But premium increases and the expirat...</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 05:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How a gourmet's palate becomes refined: Taste training mechanisms</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-gourmet-palate-refined-mechanisms.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Why are gourmets seemingly able to detect subtle nuances in taste that others miss? Researchers at Tohoku University have uncovered part of the answer...</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 14:40:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rethinking recurrent brain activity: Core neurons provide an alternative explanation</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-rethinking-recurrent-brain-core-neurons.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Neuroscientists have been trying to understand how the human brain supports numerous advanced capabilities for centuries. The cerebral cortex, the out...</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 15:50:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eczema injectable drug provides quick itch relief, clinical trial results show</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-eczema-drug-quick-relief-clinical.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>A recently approved injectable eczema drug provides quick itch relief to patients with the maddening skin disease, a new study says.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 12:10:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Seed Oils and Colon Cancer – What the New Research Really Shows</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/seed-oils-and-colon-cancer-what-the-new-research-really-shows/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Seed oils have become one of the most controversial topics in nutrition, especially after a 2024 University of South Florida study linked high omega-6...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 08:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Longevity Trap: Why Chasing Anti-Aging May Be Aging You</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-longevity-trap-why-chasing-anti-aging-may-be-aging-you/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>In this episode, Chris explains why obsession with anti-aging hacks may actually undermine our long-term health. He examines the common longevity trap...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Link Between Metabolic Health and Mental Well-Being, with Dr. Matt Bernstein</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-link-between-metabolic-health-and-mental-well-being-with-dr-matt-bernstein/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes psychiatrist Dr. Matt Bernstein to explore the emerging field of metabolic psychiatry, the ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: From Wired &amp; Tired to Calm &amp; Clear: My Top Nutrients for Mood, Focus, and Sleep</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/from-wired-tired-to-calm-clear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris explores natural solutions for one of today’s most pressing challenges: chronic stress, anxiety, and...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Science Behind Oral Inflammation, with Dr. William Levine</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-science-behind-oral-inflammation-with-dr-william-levine/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes board-certified periodontist Dr. William Levine to discuss the overlooked role of gum healt...</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>