<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:51:12 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>When patients report symptoms, clinicians can judge cancer treatment side effects more consistently</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-patients-symptoms-clinicians-cancer-treatment.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>A large multinational clinical trial has found that giving health care providers access to European Organization for Research and Treatment of Cancer ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:28:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists develop first gene-editing treatment for skin conditions</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-scientists-gene-treatment-skin-conditions.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Gene-editing tools like CRISPR have unlocked new treatments for previously uncurable diseases. Now, researchers at the University of British Columbia ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:43:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>An AI model can predict and help contain disease outbreaks in confined spaces</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-ai-disease-outbreaks-confined-spaces.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Researchers have developed a new artificial intelligence-based modeling tool that can accurately predict how infectious diseases spread in confined en...</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:47:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Study cites link between mental health and long COVID in older women</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-cites-link-mental-health-covid.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Older women who have a history of both depression and anxiety had a 78% higher risk of developing long COVID after a SARS-CoV-2 infection, report Univ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 20:59:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Cold Exposure: Why Sustained Beats Extreme</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/cold-exposure-why-sustained-beats-extreme/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Cold plunges and ice baths dominate social media, but do they really deliver the best metabolic benefits? In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 08:03:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New study finds heart attacks involve brain and immune system, not just heart</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-heart-involve-brain-immune.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Arteries become clogged. Blood flow is restricted and oxygen is cut off. The result is a heart attack, the world's leading cause of death.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Why Your Sleep Schedule Matters As Much As Duration</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/why-your-sleep-schedule-matters-as-much-as-duration/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris challenges the conventional focus on sleep duration and makes the case that sleep timing and circadi...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 08:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Menopause Brain Fog—What’s Really Happening (and How To Fix It)</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rhr-menopause-brain-fog-whats-really-happening-and-how-to-fix-it/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris examines research confirming that menopause-related brain fog is real, measurable, and reversible. H...</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 08:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Seed Oils and Colon Cancer – What the New Research Really Shows</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/seed-oils-and-colon-cancer-what-the-new-research-really-shows/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Seed oils have become one of the most controversial topics in nutrition, especially after a 2024 University of South Florida study linked high omega-6...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 08:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Longevity Trap: Why Chasing Anti-Aging May Be Aging You</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-longevity-trap-why-chasing-anti-aging-may-be-aging-you/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>In this episode, Chris explains why obsession with anti-aging hacks may actually undermine our long-term health. He examines the common longevity trap...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>