<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:03:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>'Forever chemicals' may increase liver disease risk in adolescents by as much as 3-fold</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-chemicals-liver-disease-adolescents.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>A new study co-led by the Southern California Superfund Research and Training Program for PFAS Assessment, Remediation and Prevention (ShARP) Center a...</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 19:43:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Research debunks crime spike myth at safe injection sites in Toronto</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-debunks-crime-spike-myth-safe.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Overdose prevention sites and supervised consumption sites in Toronto are not associated with long-term increases in local crime, McGill University re...</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 19:17:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Humans may be predisposed to understanding the complexities of music</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-humans-predisposed-complexities-music.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>There is a long-standing debate in the field of music cognition about the impact of musical training and whether formal training is needed to pick up ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:52:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New clinical standards strengthen antimicrobial stewardship in tuberculosis care</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-clinical-standards-antimicrobial-stewardship-tuberculosis.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Antimicrobial stewardship (AMS) refers to coordinated strategies for the targeted, evidence-based, and safe use of anti-infective agents. The aim is t...</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:14:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mathematics uncovers shifting brain connectivity in autism and aging</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-mathematics-uncovers-shifting-brain-autism.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>It is a central question in neuroscience to understand how different regions of the brain interact, how strongly they "talk" to each other. Researcher...</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 19:53:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Menopause Brain Fog—What’s Really Happening (and How To Fix It)</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rhr-menopause-brain-fog-whats-really-happening-and-how-to-fix-it/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris examines research confirming that menopause-related brain fog is real, measurable, and reversible. H...</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 08:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Seed Oils and Colon Cancer – What the New Research Really Shows</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/seed-oils-and-colon-cancer-what-the-new-research-really-shows/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Seed oils have become one of the most controversial topics in nutrition, especially after a 2024 University of South Florida study linked high omega-6...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 08:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Longevity Trap: Why Chasing Anti-Aging May Be Aging You</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-longevity-trap-why-chasing-anti-aging-may-be-aging-you/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode, Chris explains why obsession with anti-aging hacks may actually undermine our long-term health. He examines the common longevity trap...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Link Between Metabolic Health and Mental Well-Being, with Dr. Matt Bernstein</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-link-between-metabolic-health-and-mental-well-being-with-dr-matt-bernstein/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes psychiatrist Dr. Matt Bernstein to explore the emerging field of metabolic psychiatry, the ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: From Wired &amp; Tired to Calm &amp; Clear: My Top Nutrients for Mood, Focus, and Sleep</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/from-wired-tired-to-calm-clear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris explores natural solutions for one of today’s most pressing challenges: chronic stress, anxiety, and...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>