<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:01:07 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Influence of dog ownership on exercise self-efficacy and physical activity: Differences before and after COVID-19</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-dog-ownership-efficacy-physical-differences.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Researchers at University of Tsukuba examined how dog ownership and exercise self-efficacy affected physical activity among Japanese office workers be...</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:10:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Measles cases jump again in South Carolina, rising to more than 550</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-measles-cases-south-carolina.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Reported measles cases in South Carolina surged by almost 30% in the last few days, state health officials said Friday.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Immune-targeting vaccine shows promise intercepting cancer in patients with Lynch Syndrome</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-immune-vaccine-intercepting-cancer-patients.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>The investigational cancer vaccine, NOUS-209, was found to safely stimulate the immune system to target precancerous and cancerous cells in individual...</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:18:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>US flu activity fell for a second week. But experts worry the season is far from over</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-flu-fell-week-experts-season.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>The U.S. flu season appears to be waning with two straight weeks of decline in measures of flu activity, according to the latest government data relea...</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:20:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alternative RNA splicing tied to schizophrenia-like behaviors in animal models</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-alternative-rna-splicing-schizophrenia-behaviors.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In a new study, Chinese researchers have discovered the previously unrecognized role of alternative splicing of the DOC2A gene in schizophrenia.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Why Your Sleep Schedule Matters As Much As Duration</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/why-your-sleep-schedule-matters-as-much-as-duration/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris challenges the conventional focus on sleep duration and makes the case that sleep timing and circadi...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 08:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Menopause Brain Fog—What’s Really Happening (and How To Fix It)</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rhr-menopause-brain-fog-whats-really-happening-and-how-to-fix-it/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris examines research confirming that menopause-related brain fog is real, measurable, and reversible. H...</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 08:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Seed Oils and Colon Cancer – What the New Research Really Shows</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/seed-oils-and-colon-cancer-what-the-new-research-really-shows/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Seed oils have become one of the most controversial topics in nutrition, especially after a 2024 University of South Florida study linked high omega-6...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 08:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Longevity Trap: Why Chasing Anti-Aging May Be Aging You</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-longevity-trap-why-chasing-anti-aging-may-be-aging-you/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In this episode, Chris explains why obsession with anti-aging hacks may actually undermine our long-term health. He examines the common longevity trap...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Link Between Metabolic Health and Mental Well-Being, with Dr. Matt Bernstein</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-link-between-metabolic-health-and-mental-well-being-with-dr-matt-bernstein/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes psychiatrist Dr. Matt Bernstein to explore the emerging field of metabolic psychiatry, the ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>