<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 02:28:36 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Comparing Surgical Cerclage Routes in Preterm Birth Risk</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/comparing-surgical-cerclage-routes-in-preterm-birth-risk/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Transabdominal cerclage was associated with lower rates of preterm birth and perinatal mortality compared to the transvaginal approach in women at ris...</description><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 00:00:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Continuous glucose monitors are in vogue. But do you really need to track your blood sugar?</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-glucose-vogue-track-blood-sugar.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>A quarter-size device that tracks the rise and fall of sugar in your blood is the latest source of hope—and hype—in the growing buzz around wearable h...</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 20:37:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Weekend warrior' workouts reduce diabetics' risk of death, study indicates</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-weekend-warrior-workouts-diabetics-death.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>A "weekend warrior" exercise schedule can lower diabetics' risk of early death, a new study says.</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 12:50:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Texts about healthier eating may help prevent childhood obesity</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-texts-healthier-childhood-obesity.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>According to recent estimates by the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, nearly one in five children in the United States is affected by obesi...</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 18:10:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Burn Surgery Outcomes Improved With Tranexamic Acid</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/burn-surgery-outcomes-improved-with-tranexamic-acid/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Tranexamic acid lowered blood loss and transfusion needed in burn surgery without affecting hemoglobin. The post Burn Surgery Outcomes Improved With T...</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 22:30:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Brain peptide ODN reduces hunger and boosts glucose regulation in rat study</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-brain-peptide-odn-hunger-boosts.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>University of Pennsylvania and Syracuse University scientists have discovered that a hindbrain-derived peptide, octadecaneuropeptide (ODN), can suppre...</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 13:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Obesity prevalence would shift significantly under proposed new criteria, study finds</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-obesity-prevalence-shift-significantly-criteria.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>In the first multinational study of a proposed change to how obesity is defined—which calls for health factors beyond a person's height and weight to ...</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 20:35:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Expectations and Outcomes of Kidney Care in OAs</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/expectations-and-outcomes-of-kidney-care-in-oas/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Older adults often misjudge kidney treatment outcomes, but most achieve key goals over time. The post Expectations and Outcomes of Kidney Care in OAs ...</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 21:30:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Immunoadsorption and Plasma Exchange in Chronic Neuropathy</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/immunoadsorption-and-plasma-exchange-in-chronic-neuropathy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>PE and IA offered similar clinical benefits in long-standing CIDP, with IA linked to shorter hospital stays. The post Immunoadsorption and Plasma Exch...</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 22:30:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Financial Power of Unicorns Driving Change in Urology</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/financial-power-of-unicorns-driving-change-in-urology/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Billion-dollar unicorns are reshaping urology through innovation and AI-driven drug development, signaling both opportunity and challenge for future p...</description><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 23:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Mold, Indoor Air Quality, and Clean Breathing, with Michael Rubino</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/mold-indoor-air-quality-and-clean-breathing-with-michael-rubino/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes environmental wellness expert Michael Rubino for an in-depth conversation on the hi...</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 08:01:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Nourishment Table, with Frederic Leroy</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-nourishment-table-with-frederic-leroy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes food scientist and advocate for regenerative agriculture Dr. Frederic Leroy to disc...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Turn ChatGPT Into Your Personal Meal Planner</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/turn-chatgpt-into-your-personal-meal-planner/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Even for someone who lives and breathes nutrition, meal planning can feel like a grind. There are weeks when I... The post Turn ChatGPT Into Your Pers...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:16:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Rediscovering Health, Nature, and Purpose-Driven Business, with Seth Spears</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rediscovering-health-nature-and-purpose-driven-business-with-seth-spears/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes entrepreneur and strategist Seth Spears for a wide-ranging conversation on health, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: How to Sharpen and Protect Your Mind for a Lifetime, with Dale Bredesen</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/how-to-sharpen-and-protect-your-mind-for-a-lifetime-with-dale-bredesen/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes renowned neurologist Dr. Dale Bredesen back to the show for an insightful conversation abou...</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:01:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>