<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 10:42:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>More Than 110,000 Rich’s Ice Cream Bars Recalled Due to Listeria Risk</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/more-than-110000-richs-ice-cream-bars-recalled-due-to-listeria-risk/</link><image_url>https://cdn.physiciansweekly.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/HEALTHDAY_Web_small3.png</image_url><description>WEDNESDAY, July 23, 2025 (HealthDay News) — More than 100,000 Rich’s Ice Cream Co. bars have been recalled due to possible listeria contamination. The...</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:31:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tuna Recalled in Seven States Over Listeria Fears</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/tuna-recalled-in-seven-states-over-listeria-fears/</link><image_url>https://cdn.physiciansweekly.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/HEALTHDAY_Web_small3.png</image_url><description>WEDNESDAY, July 23, 2025 (HealthDay News) — Two types of tuna sold in seven states are being recalled due to listeria concerns. The first recall affec...</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:31:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Allogeneic HCT Feasible in Older Patients With Myelodysplastic Syndrome</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/allogeneic-hct-feasible-in-older-patients-with-myelodysplastic-syndrome/</link><image_url>https://cdn.physiciansweekly.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/HEALTHDAY_Web_small3.png</image_url><description>WEDNESDAY, July 23, 2025 (HealthDay News) — Allogeneic hematopoietic cell transplantation (allo-HCT) is feasible in older patients with myelodysplasti...</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 07:31:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Republicans Call Medicaid Rife With Fraudsters. This Man Sees No Choice but To Break the Rules.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/republicans-call-medicaid-rife-with-fraudsters-this-man-sees-no-choice-but-to-break-the-rules/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>MISSOULA, Mont. — As congressional Republicans finalized Medicaid work requirements in President Donald Trump’s budget bill, one man who relies on tha...</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:30:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Research uses AI to find pathologic and genetic basis for worse outcome of endometrial cancer in Black women</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-ai-pathologic-genetic-basis-worse.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Endometrial cancer—in which tumors develop in the inner lining of the uterus—is the most prevalent gynecological cancer in American women, affecting m...</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:29:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Primary care shortage affects 44% of Virginia's neighborhoods, almost 3.8 million residents, study finds</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-primary-shortage-affects-virginia-neighborhoods.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Nearly half of Virginia's neighborhoods don't have enough nearby primary care physicians for their residents, with rural communities being hit hardest...</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:35:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sweet spot for daily steps is lower than often thought, new study finds</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-sweet-daily-thought.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Your fitness tracker might be lying to you. That 10,000-step target flashing on your wrist? It didn't come from decades of careful research. It came f...</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:20:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>States Pass Privacy Laws To Protect Brain Data Collected by Devices</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/states-pass-privacy-laws-to-protect-brain-data-collected-by-devices/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>More states are passing laws to protect information generated by a person’s brain and nervous system as technology improves the ability to unlock the ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:30:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Research links air pollution to an increased risk for bleeding in the brain</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-links-air-pollution-brain.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>University of Utah Health researchers have documented an association between air pollution exposure and a rare type of bleeding within the brain. An a...</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:33:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How B vitamins can affect brain and heart health</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-vitamins-affect-brain-heart-health.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Eight essential nutrients make up the suite of B vitamins also known as the B complex. Research at Tufts and elsewhere has revealed that these B vitam...</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 15:40:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Mold, Indoor Air Quality, and Clean Breathing, with Michael Rubino</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/mold-indoor-air-quality-and-clean-breathing-with-michael-rubino/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes environmental wellness expert Michael Rubino for an in-depth conversation on the hi...</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 08:01:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Nourishment Table, with Frederic Leroy</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-nourishment-table-with-frederic-leroy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes food scientist and advocate for regenerative agriculture Dr. Frederic Leroy to disc...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Turn ChatGPT Into Your Personal Meal Planner</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/turn-chatgpt-into-your-personal-meal-planner/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Even for someone who lives and breathes nutrition, meal planning can feel like a grind. There are weeks when I... The post Turn ChatGPT Into Your Pers...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:16:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Rediscovering Health, Nature, and Purpose-Driven Business, with Seth Spears</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rediscovering-health-nature-and-purpose-driven-business-with-seth-spears/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes entrepreneur and strategist Seth Spears for a wide-ranging conversation on health, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: How to Sharpen and Protect Your Mind for a Lifetime, with Dale Bredesen</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/how-to-sharpen-and-protect-your-mind-for-a-lifetime-with-dale-bredesen/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes renowned neurologist Dr. Dale Bredesen back to the show for an insightful conversation abou...</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:01:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>