<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 01:39:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>'We need to look after our grand-friends': How childcare in aged care can help young and old</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-grand-friends-childcare-aged-young.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>An experimental aged-care model in South Australia, where purpose-built independent retirement living apartments are co-located with an early learning...</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 17:10:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Childhood trauma linked to mental health problems and chronic pain in later life</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-childhood-trauma-linked-mental-health.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>New research from the University of Aberdeen challenges the current view that trauma in childhood increases the risk of all health conditions. The stu...</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 17:20:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Labor Day mission: Build social ties through live events</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-labor-day-mission-social-events.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>If your social life has been lived out in Zoom calls since the height of the pandemic, Labor Day weekend is prime time for a reboot.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 18:20:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why endurance events like marathons should have weight divisions for heavier runners</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-events-marathons-weight-divisions-heavier.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>In sports such as wrestling, boxing, rowing, weight lifting and the martial arts, athletes are grouped by weight to make things fairer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 21:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FDA now providing daily updates on adverse events</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-fda-daily-adverse-events.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>The U.S. Food and Drug Administration is now providing real-time, daily publication updates on adverse event data from its reporting system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 18:10:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rice Ceramides: The Unsung Hero of Skin Hydration and Barrier Health</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rice-ceramides-the-unsung-hero-of-skin-hydration-and-barrier-health/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>We often think of radiant skin as the result of what we put on it: moisturizers, serums, masks. But emerging... The post Rice Ceramides: The Unsung He...</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lutein and Zeaxanthin: The Carotenoids That Protect and Perfect Your Skin from Within</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/lutein-and-zeaxanthin-the-carotenoids-that-protect-and-perfect-your-skin-from-within/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>When most people think of lutein and zeaxanthin, they picture eye health supplements or leafy green vegetables. But these vibrant... The post Lutein a...</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:00:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vitamin C: The Collagen-Stimulating, Skin-Brightening Antioxidant Your Skin Can’t Live Without</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/vitamin-c-the-collagen-stimulating-skin-brightening-antioxidant-your-skin-cant-live-without/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>When it comes to supporting skin health from the inside out, few nutrients are as essential—or as well-researched—as vitamin C.... The post Vitamin C:...</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 16:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eggshell Membrane Collagen: A Natural Ally for Skin, Hair, and Nail Vitality</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/eggshell-membrane-collagen-a-natural-ally-for-skin-hair-and-nail-vitality/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>In the growing world of natural beauty and inside-out skincare, few ingredients offer the versatility and clinical backing of eggshell... The post Egg...</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biotin: The Essential Nutrient for Stronger Hair and Healthier Nails</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/biotin-the-essential-nutrient-for-stronger-hair-and-healthier-nails/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>If you’ve ever scanned the beauty aisle or browsed wellness forums, you’ve probably seen biotin pop up again and again... The post Biotin: The Essenti...</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:37:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>