<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 06:31:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Comprehensive molecular atlas of human hippocampus maps cell subtypes and organization</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-comprehensive-molecular-atlas-human-hippocampus.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>The hippocampus is an important brain region known to support various cognitive (i.e., mental) processes, including the encoding and retrieval of memo...</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 11:30:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Metformin changes blood metal levels in humans, offering further insight into its mechanism of action</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-metformin-blood-metal-humans-insight.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>The widely used diabetes drug metformin changes blood metal levels in humans. The Kobe University study is an important step in understanding the drug...</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 01:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Can I still get a COVID shot? What you need to know after a confounding week</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-09-covid-shot-confounding-week.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>A week of fast-moving developments has left some with questions about access to the COVID-19 vaccine.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 11:26:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fall allergy symptoms are similar to spring and summer—and can hit as hard</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-fall-allergy-symptoms-similar-summer.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>If you're wondering why your spring allergy symptoms never went away, it's possible you are suffering from spring… into summer… into fall allergies.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 23:50:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Can kids overdose on melatonin gummies? Yes, and an online store has suspended sales</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-kids-overdose-melatonin-gummies-online.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>US-based online store iHerb has suspended sales of melatonin gummies to Australia. This comes after a rise in reports of non-fatal overdoses in Wester...</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 22:10:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rice Ceramides: The Unsung Hero of Skin Hydration and Barrier Health</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rice-ceramides-the-unsung-hero-of-skin-hydration-and-barrier-health/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>We often think of radiant skin as the result of what we put on it: moisturizers, serums, masks. But emerging... The post Rice Ceramides: The Unsung He...</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lutein and Zeaxanthin: The Carotenoids That Protect and Perfect Your Skin from Within</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/lutein-and-zeaxanthin-the-carotenoids-that-protect-and-perfect-your-skin-from-within/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>When most people think of lutein and zeaxanthin, they picture eye health supplements or leafy green vegetables. But these vibrant... The post Lutein a...</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:00:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vitamin C: The Collagen-Stimulating, Skin-Brightening Antioxidant Your Skin Can’t Live Without</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/vitamin-c-the-collagen-stimulating-skin-brightening-antioxidant-your-skin-cant-live-without/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>When it comes to supporting skin health from the inside out, few nutrients are as essential—or as well-researched—as vitamin C.... The post Vitamin C:...</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 16:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eggshell Membrane Collagen: A Natural Ally for Skin, Hair, and Nail Vitality</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/eggshell-membrane-collagen-a-natural-ally-for-skin-hair-and-nail-vitality/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>In the growing world of natural beauty and inside-out skincare, few ingredients offer the versatility and clinical backing of eggshell... The post Egg...</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biotin: The Essential Nutrient for Stronger Hair and Healthier Nails</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/biotin-the-essential-nutrient-for-stronger-hair-and-healthier-nails/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>If you’ve ever scanned the beauty aisle or browsed wellness forums, you’ve probably seen biotin pop up again and again... The post Biotin: The Essenti...</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:37:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>