<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 06:26:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>How body mass index affects breast cancer risk in postmenopausal women with and without cardiovascular disease</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-body-mass-index-affects-breast.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>New research reveals that excess weight is linked to an especially high risk of developing breast cancer in postmenopausal women with cardiovascular d...</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 08:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Survey of medical student attitudes regarding uterine transplant for cisgender and transgender women: an observational study.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/survey-of-medical-student-attitudes-regarding-uterine-transplant-for-cisgender-and-transgender-women-an-observational-study/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>This study wishes to survey medical students’ attitudes regarding legality of, funding for, and conscientious objection to uterine transplant (UTx) in...</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 06:31:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI-powered virtual staining of biopsies for transplant diagnostics</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-ai-powered-virtual-biopsies-transplant.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Organ transplantation offers life-saving treatment for patients with end-stage organ failure, restoring function and vastly improving quality of life ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 11:24:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The articularis genu as a surrogate for structural determinants of peri-articular myopenia in osteoarthritis.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/the-articularis-genu-as-a-surrogate-for-structural-determinants-of-peri-articular-myopenia-in-osteoarthritis/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>The functional limitations associated with the painful stiffness of knee osteoarthritis (kOA) can affect the muscles of the knee, such as the quadrice...</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 06:31:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New study maps four key pathways to Alzheimer's disease</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-key-pathways-alzheimer-disease.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>UCLA Health researchers have identified four distinct pathways that lead to Alzheimer's disease by analyzing electronic health records, offering new i...</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 11:26:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Boron Difluoride Formazanate Dye With Donor Planarization Engineering for 1060 nm Laser Activated Photothermal Theranostics.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/boron-difluoride-formazanate-dye-with-donor-planarization-engineering-for-1060-nm-laser-activated-photothermal-theranostics/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Phototheranostics within the second near-infrared (NIR-II, 1000-1700 nm) window offer considerable advantages compared to those operating in the visib...</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 06:31:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Transcriptomic and Neurotransmitter Insights Into Gray Matter Volume Changes From 1 Hz rTMS in Treating Schizophrenia With Auditory Verbal Hallucinations.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/transcriptomic-and-neurotransmitter-insights-into-gray-matter-volume-changes-from-1-hz-rtms-in-treating-schizophrenia-with-auditory-verbal-hallucinations/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Auditory verbal hallucinations (AVH) are prominent positive symptoms of schizophrenia that frequently prove resistant to conventional antipsychotic tr...</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 06:31:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aligned Conductive Magnetic Nanofibers with Directional Magnetic Field Stimulation Promotes Peripheral Nerve Regeneration.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/aligned-conductive-magnetic-nanofibers-with-directional-magnetic-field-stimulation-promotes-peripheral-nerve-regeneration/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Peripheral nerve injury is one of the most common disorders of the nervous system. Alternatives to autologous nerve transplantation have attracted sig...</description><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 06:31:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why the L-carnitine sport supplement is controversial</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-carnitine-sport-supplement-controversial.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Sport supplements are hard to get away from if you like to exercise regularly. Even if you're not interested in them, there's a good chance your gym w...</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 14:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Asthma study shows patient expectations influence the course of the disease</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-asthma-patient-disease.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Individual expectations about one's health can influence future condition and speed of the progression of a disease: in fact, research conducted by re...</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 15:10:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Nourishment Table, with Frederic Leroy</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-nourishment-table-with-frederic-leroy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes food scientist and advocate for regenerative agriculture Dr. Frederic Leroy to disc...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Turn ChatGPT Into Your Personal Meal Planner</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/turn-chatgpt-into-your-personal-meal-planner/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Even for someone who lives and breathes nutrition, meal planning can feel like a grind. There are weeks when I... The post Turn ChatGPT Into Your Pers...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:16:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Rediscovering Health, Nature, and Purpose-Driven Business, with Seth Spears</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rediscovering-health-nature-and-purpose-driven-business-with-seth-spears/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes entrepreneur and strategist Seth Spears for a wide-ranging conversation on health, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: How to Sharpen and Protect Your Mind for a Lifetime, with Dale Bredesen</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/how-to-sharpen-and-protect-your-mind-for-a-lifetime-with-dale-bredesen/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes renowned neurologist Dr. Dale Bredesen back to the show for an insightful conversation abou...</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:01:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quality Matters: How to Choose and Use the Best Collagen Supplement</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/quality-matters-how-to-choose-and-use-the-best-collagen-supplement/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Introduction If you’ve been paying attention to health and wellness trends, you’ve likely noticed collagen supplements everywhere—from your local heal...</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:57:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>