<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 17:42:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Eggshell Membrane Collagen: A Natural Ally for Skin, Hair, and Nail Vitality</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/eggshell-membrane-collagen-a-natural-ally-for-skin-hair-and-nail-vitality/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In the growing world of natural beauty and inside-out skincare, few ingredients offer the versatility and clinical backing of eggshell... The post Egg...</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pilot study provides foundation for understanding how music therapy improves pain after pancreatic surgery</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-foundation-music-therapy-pain-pancreatic.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>A study from University Hospitals Connor Whole Health has found that it was feasible to conduct a live music-assisted relaxation and imagery session a...</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:27:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Study shows marked improvement in survival rates for pediatric heart transplantation within Nordic countries</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-survival-pediatric-heart-transplantation-nordic.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In a new observational study, researchers at Lund University in Sweden looked at all children listed for heart transplants in the Nordic countries bet...</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:08:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A future biomarker may help match melanoma patients with the best therapy for them</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-future-biomarker-melanoma-patients-therapy.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Immune checkpoint blockade medications have revolutionized cancer treatment, giving patients and providers new hope to control and sometimes cure meta...</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:10:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Study shows culture shapes shared mental health decision making</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-culture-mental-health-decision.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>A new study has revealed that cultural background can influence how mental health care staff approach shared decision-making with patients.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:13:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sleeping flies that still manage to escape shed light on inhibitory neuronal networks</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-flies-inhibitory-neuronal-networks.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Flies too need their sleep. In order to be able to react to dangers, however, they must not completely phase out the environment. Researchers at Chari...</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 21:37:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biotin: The Essential Nutrient for Stronger Hair and Healthier Nails</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/biotin-the-essential-nutrient-for-stronger-hair-and-healthier-nails/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>If you’ve ever scanned the beauty aisle or browsed wellness forums, you’ve probably seen biotin pop up again and again... The post Biotin: The Essenti...</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:37:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Beauty From Within – Why Radiant Skin, Hair, and Nails Start Inside</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/beauty-from-within-why-radiant-skin-hair-and-nails-start-inside/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, we dive deep into the topic of beauty from within, exploring why radiant skin, hair, and nails truly start...</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 08:01:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Mold, Indoor Air Quality, and Clean Breathing, with Michael Rubino</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/mold-indoor-air-quality-and-clean-breathing-with-michael-rubino/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes environmental wellness expert Michael Rubino for an in-depth conversation on the hi...</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 08:01:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Nourishment Table, with Frederic Leroy</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-nourishment-table-with-frederic-leroy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes food scientist and advocate for regenerative agriculture Dr. Frederic Leroy to disc...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>