<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 16:40:30 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Q&amp;A: RSV's hidden toll—adults of all ages may struggle with breathlessness, daily activities for months</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-qa-rsv-hidden-toll-adults.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Recovering from respiratory syncytial virus often doesn't end when it's time to leave the hospital, even for younger adults.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 21:08:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI aids in creation of generated music for therapy and mental-health support</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-ai-aids-creation-generated-music.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>The ethical and artistic debates aside, there are good reasons for research into artificial-intelligence systems that can generate music. A new system...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 20:56:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Swapping old sofas and chairs reduces body levels of harmful flame retardants</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-swapping-sofas-chairs-body-flame.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>New research led by the California Department of Public Health and partners has found that replacing foam-containing furniture made before 2014 would ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 20:57:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Does losing weight make an athlete better? Associations between body composition and performance</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-weight-athlete-associations-body-composition.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>According to a recent study, reducing body fat can improve long-distance running and cross-country skiing performance. However, a more effective way f...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 20:55:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Neutron scattering sheds light on lung injuries linked to vaping</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-neutron-lung-injuries-linked-vaping.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Researchers from the University of Windsor are using neutrons at the Department of Energy's Oak Ridge National Laboratory to better understand symptom...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 21:20:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Longevity Trap: Why Chasing Anti-Aging May Be Aging You</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-longevity-trap-why-chasing-anti-aging-may-be-aging-you/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>In this episode, Chris explains why obsession with anti-aging hacks may actually undermine our long-term health. He examines the common longevity trap...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Link Between Metabolic Health and Mental Well-Being, with Dr. Matt Bernstein</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-link-between-metabolic-health-and-mental-well-being-with-dr-matt-bernstein/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes psychiatrist Dr. Matt Bernstein to explore the emerging field of metabolic psychiatry, the ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: From Wired &amp; Tired to Calm &amp; Clear: My Top Nutrients for Mood, Focus, and Sleep</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/from-wired-tired-to-calm-clear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris explores natural solutions for one of today’s most pressing challenges: chronic stress, anxiety, and...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Science Behind Oral Inflammation, with Dr. William Levine</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-science-behind-oral-inflammation-with-dr-william-levine/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes board-certified periodontist Dr. William Levine to discuss the overlooked role of gum healt...</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hyaluronic Acid: The Deep Hydration Molecule Your Skin Has Been Waiting For</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/hyaluronic-acid-the-deep-hydration-molecule-your-skin-has-been-waiting-for/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>If you’ve spent any time exploring the world of natural skincare, chances are you’ve heard of hyaluronic acid (HA). Once... The post Hyaluronic Acid: ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>