<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 11:01:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>‘We Dissent’: NIH Workers Protest Trump Policies That ‘Harm the Health of Americans’</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/we-dissent-nih-workers-protest-trump-policies-that-harm-the-health-of-americans/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Hundreds of workers at the National Institutes of Health on Monday openly protested the Trump administration’s cuts to the agency and consequences for...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 11:30:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Novel Immune Mechanism that Protects Intestine Discovered</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/novel-immune-mechanism-that-protects-intestine-discovered/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Researchers discovered a previously unrecognized type 1 immune mechanism that preserves intestinal integrity in mice harboring tissue-invasive helmint...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 15:25:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Promoting Quality Sleep in the ICU: Part 1</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/promoting-quality-sleep-in-the-icu-part-1/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Dr. Brodkey explains how prolonged disturbances to sleep in the ICU can become a significant issue for patients, leading to psychological or physiolog...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 14:57:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Exploring characteristics of primary care physicians who provide low-value care in Japan</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-exploring-characteristics-primary-physicians-japan.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Researchers at the University of Tsukuba have analyzed the provision of low-value care in primary care settings. The study, published in JAMA Health F...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 15:44:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CT colonography beats stool DNA testing for colon cancer screening</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-ct-colonography-stool-dna-colon.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Compared to stool DNA testing, researchers found that CT colonography is a cost-saving and clinically effective method for colorectal cancer screening...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 15:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>As Cannabis Users Age, Health Risks Appear To Grow</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/as-cannabis-users-age-health-risks-appear-to-grow/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Benjamin Han, a geriatrician and addiction medicine specialist at the University of California-San Diego, tells his students a cautionary tale about a...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 11:30:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hundreds of new N-acyl lipids identified, expanding the dictionary of human metabolism</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-hundreds-acyl-lipids-dictionary-human.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Human metabolism is a complex web of chemical processes and interactions between our cells and the microbes living within us. The more scientists can ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Existing drug class may help patients with skin cancer that resists standard treatments</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-drug-class-patients-skin-cancer.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Increased activity in a specific biological pathway may explain why many patients with a deadly form of skin cancer do not respond to the latest cance...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 15:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>$20K Bonuses Among Latest Moves To Improve California’s Prison Mental Health System</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/20k-bonuses-among-latest-moves-to-improve-californias-prison-mental-health-system/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>SACRAMENTO, Calif. — After decades of unsuccessful efforts to improve California prison conditions ruled unconstitutional and blamed for record-high s...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 11:30:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The virus that won't quit: New research reveals how SARS-CoV-2 evolves</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-virus-wont-reveals-sars-cov.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Researchers have tracked how the COVID-19 virus mutates long term, revealing patterns that could help predict the emergence of future variants.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 15:53:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Nourishment Table, with Frederic Leroy</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-nourishment-table-with-frederic-leroy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes food scientist and advocate for regenerative agriculture Dr. Frederic Leroy to disc...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Turn ChatGPT Into Your Personal Meal Planner</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/turn-chatgpt-into-your-personal-meal-planner/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Even for someone who lives and breathes nutrition, meal planning can feel like a grind. There are weeks when I... The post Turn ChatGPT Into Your Pers...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:16:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Rediscovering Health, Nature, and Purpose-Driven Business, with Seth Spears</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rediscovering-health-nature-and-purpose-driven-business-with-seth-spears/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes entrepreneur and strategist Seth Spears for a wide-ranging conversation on health, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: How to Sharpen and Protect Your Mind for a Lifetime, with Dale Bredesen</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/how-to-sharpen-and-protect-your-mind-for-a-lifetime-with-dale-bredesen/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes renowned neurologist Dr. Dale Bredesen back to the show for an insightful conversation abou...</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:01:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quality Matters: How to Choose and Use the Best Collagen Supplement</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/quality-matters-how-to-choose-and-use-the-best-collagen-supplement/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Introduction If you’ve been paying attention to health and wellness trends, you’ve likely noticed collagen supplements everywhere—from your local heal...</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:57:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>