<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 06:05:22 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Brain's 'pulse generators' grow and shrink as memories are formed, study finds</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-brain-pulse-generators-memories.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Memories and learning processes are based on changes in the brain's neuronal connections, and as a result, in signal transmission between neurons.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 10:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gut bacteria shift early in inflammatory bowel disease, study reveals</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-gut-bacteria-shift-early-inflammatory.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Patients experience significant changes in gut bacteria at the onset of inflammatory bowel disease (IBD), a new international study has found—offering...</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 10:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Novo Nordisk says US approves first GLP-1 pill for weight loss</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-novo-nordisk-glp-pill-weight.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Danish pharmaceutical giant Novo Nordisk announced Monday the US Food and Drug Administration (FDA) had approved its popular GLP-1 anti-obesity drug W...</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 09:36:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ozempic Meals? Restaurants shrink portions to match bite-sized hunger</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-ozempic-meals-restaurants-portions-sized.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>A self-described foodie, social butterfly and New Yorker for 20 years, Lina Axmacher has long loved exploring the city's famed restaurant culture.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 09:37:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Listening in' on the brain's hidden language: Engineered protein detects the faintest incoming signals</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-brain-hidden-language-protein-faintest.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Scientists have engineered a protein able to record the incoming chemical signals of brain cells (as opposed to just their outgoing signals). These wh...</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 10:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Seed Oils and Colon Cancer – What the New Research Really Shows</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/seed-oils-and-colon-cancer-what-the-new-research-really-shows/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Seed oils have become one of the most controversial topics in nutrition, especially after a 2024 University of South Florida study linked high omega-6...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 08:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Longevity Trap: Why Chasing Anti-Aging May Be Aging You</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-longevity-trap-why-chasing-anti-aging-may-be-aging-you/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In this episode, Chris explains why obsession with anti-aging hacks may actually undermine our long-term health. He examines the common longevity trap...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Link Between Metabolic Health and Mental Well-Being, with Dr. Matt Bernstein</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-link-between-metabolic-health-and-mental-well-being-with-dr-matt-bernstein/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes psychiatrist Dr. Matt Bernstein to explore the emerging field of metabolic psychiatry, the ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: From Wired &amp; Tired to Calm &amp; Clear: My Top Nutrients for Mood, Focus, and Sleep</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/from-wired-tired-to-calm-clear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris explores natural solutions for one of today’s most pressing challenges: chronic stress, anxiety, and...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Science Behind Oral Inflammation, with Dr. William Levine</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-science-behind-oral-inflammation-with-dr-william-levine/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes board-certified periodontist Dr. William Levine to discuss the overlooked role of gum healt...</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>