<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 10:52:22 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Growth performance and carcass traits of growing and finishing pigs fed diets with a partial to total replacement of soybean meal with Spirulina powder.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/growth-performance-and-carcass-traits-of-growing-and-finishing-pigs-fed-diets-with-a-partial-to-total-replacement-of-soybean-meal-with-spirulina-powder/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>The protein sources in pig diets strongly rely on soybean meal, but its production has been associated with soil degradation, deforestation and loss o...</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 06:30:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Score a bonus with these video gaming tips: Extra life in the real world</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-score-bonus-video-gaming-extra.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>In video games, all players usually need to do to stay healthy is to drink the occasional healing potion or perhaps grab a floating heart. Avoiding zo...</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 15:27:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Married people may have better colorectal cancer outcomes, study shows</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-people-colorectal-cancer-outcomes.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Marital status significantly impacts survival rates for patients with colorectal cancer, according to a new study co-authored by a Fox Chase Cancer Ce...</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 15:47:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pre-surgical combination therapy boosts survival in patients with rare thyroid cancer</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-pre-surgical-combination-therapy-boosts.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>A pre-surgical combination therapy including pembrolizumab plus dabrafenib and trametinib (DTP) significantly improved survival in patients with rare ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 15:26:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A new network to help improve postpartum contraception care</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-network-postpartum-contraception.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>A collaborative, multi-disciplinary network focusing on postpartum contraception care has been established by Dr. Jessica Botfield, Senior Research Fe...</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 15:48:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blood test detects multiple cancer types through cell-free DNA</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-blood-multiple-cancer-cell-free.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Researchers from Geneseeq and a network of Chinese academic hospitals have validated a blood test that can detect a broad range of cancers with high a...</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 15:30:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Association between preoperative glycaemic control (HbA1c) and early outcomes following primary hip and knee arthroplasty.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/association-between-preoperative-glycaemic-control-hba1c-and-early-outcomes-following-primary-hip-and-knee-arthroplasty/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>This study investigates the relationship between diabetes mellitus (DM), glycated haemoglobin (HbA1c), and postoperative outcomes among patients under...</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 06:00:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Underscoring The Importance of Blood Donation: Tackling Barriers</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/underscoring-the-importance-of-blood-donation-tackling-barriers/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>On a recent episode of Peer POV: The Pulse on Medicine, Amanda Hess, an Advisory Board Member of the Association for Blood Donor Professionals, discus...</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 14:39:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Personalized Diet Plans Promising to Improve MM Outcomes</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/personalized-diet-plans-promising-to-improve-mm-outcomes/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Tailored nutrition and exercise programs appear promising for patients with multiple myeloma (MM), but more research is needed to fully understand the...</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 14:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Effectiveness of a community health advisor colorectal cancer screening educational intervention on stool test completion in an African American primary care patient population: a pragmatic randomized controlled trial.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/effectiveness-of-a-community-health-advisor-colorectal-cancer-screening-educational-intervention-on-stool-test-completion-in-an-african-american-primary-care-patient-population-a-pragmatic-randomized/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Colorectal cancer (CRC) disparities in incidence and mortality for African Americans compared to white Americans are explained by socioeconomic, behav...</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 06:00:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Turn ChatGPT Into Your Personal Meal Planner</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/turn-chatgpt-into-your-personal-meal-planner/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Even for someone who lives and breathes nutrition, meal planning can feel like a grind. There are weeks when I... The post Turn ChatGPT Into Your Pers...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:16:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Rediscovering Health, Nature, and Purpose-Driven Business, with Seth Spears</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rediscovering-health-nature-and-purpose-driven-business-with-seth-spears/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes entrepreneur and strategist Seth Spears for a wide-ranging conversation on health, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: How to Sharpen and Protect Your Mind for a Lifetime, with Dale Bredesen</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/how-to-sharpen-and-protect-your-mind-for-a-lifetime-with-dale-bredesen/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes renowned neurologist Dr. Dale Bredesen back to the show for an insightful conversation abou...</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:01:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quality Matters: How to Choose and Use the Best Collagen Supplement</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/quality-matters-how-to-choose-and-use-the-best-collagen-supplement/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Introduction If you’ve been paying attention to health and wellness trends, you’ve likely noticed collagen supplements everywhere—from your local heal...</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:57:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Collagen: The Essential Building Block for Strong Joints and Bones</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/collagen-the-essential-building-block-for-strong-joints-and-bones/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>The Foundation of Your Musculoskeletal System If you’ve ever winced going down stairs, felt that telltale morning stiffness, or worried... The post Co...</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 13:31:22 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>