<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 16:12:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>New electrical signature of Parkinson's disease identified</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-electrical-signature-parkinson-disease.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>What happens in the brain when a person experiences the characteristic movement symptoms of Parkinson's disease? Researchers around the world are seek...</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 20:33:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Safeguarding fertility: Study investigates key hormone for women with cancer choosing fertility preservation</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-safeguarding-fertility-key-hormone-women.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Newly diagnosed female cancer patients of reproductive age have a very short window for storing their eggs and embryos before starting cancer treatmen...</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 20:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Laser eye treatment shows potential for halting dry macular degeneration progression in animal models</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-laser-eye-treatment-potential-halting.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Around a third of people over the age of 80 suffer from age-related macular degeneration (AMD), with an estimated 20 million Americans aged 40 and old...</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 20:28:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Connection between liver and brain in the context of metabolic liver disease revealed</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-liver-brain-context-metabolic-disease.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>A multidisciplinary research team has discovered that liver alterations associated with metabolic dysfunction–associated fatty liver disease (MASLD) c...</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 20:13:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Molecular profiling of renal medullary carcinoma identifies TROP2 as a promising therapeutic target</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-molecular-profiling-renal-medullary-carcinoma.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Researchers at The University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Center, in collaboration with BostonGene, conducted the largest and most comprehensive molec...</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 20:20:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: From Wired &amp; Tired to Calm &amp; Clear: My Top Nutrients for Mood, Focus, and Sleep</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/from-wired-tired-to-calm-clear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris explores natural solutions for one of today’s most pressing challenges: chronic stress, anxiety, and...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Science Behind Oral Inflammation, with Dr. William Levine</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-science-behind-oral-inflammation-with-dr-william-levine/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes board-certified periodontist Dr. William Levine to discuss the overlooked role of gum healt...</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hyaluronic Acid: The Deep Hydration Molecule Your Skin Has Been Waiting For</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/hyaluronic-acid-the-deep-hydration-molecule-your-skin-has-been-waiting-for/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>If you’ve spent any time exploring the world of natural skincare, chances are you’ve heard of hyaluronic acid (HA). Once... The post Hyaluronic Acid: ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rice Ceramides: The Unsung Hero of Skin Hydration and Barrier Health</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rice-ceramides-the-unsung-hero-of-skin-hydration-and-barrier-health/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>We often think of radiant skin as the result of what we put on it: moisturizers, serums, masks. But emerging... The post Rice Ceramides: The Unsung He...</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lutein and Zeaxanthin: The Carotenoids That Protect and Perfect Your Skin from Within</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/lutein-and-zeaxanthin-the-carotenoids-that-protect-and-perfect-your-skin-from-within/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>When most people think of lutein and zeaxanthin, they picture eye health supplements or leafy green vegetables. But these vibrant... The post Lutein a...</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:00:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>