<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 07:20:41 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Marriage and emotional support may protect against obesity through brain–gut connection</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-marriage-emotional-obesity-braingut.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Strong social relationships, particularly high-quality marriages, may help protect against obesity by influencing a complex communication system betwe...</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 05:10:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Survey reveals nearly all Americans not aware midwives provide care beyond pregnancy and birth</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-survey-reveals-americans-aware-midwives.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>According to the Department of Health and Human Services, the United States is expected to face a significant shortage of OB-GYNs in the next five yea...</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 05:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Air pollution linked to more severe heart disease</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-air-pollution-linked-severe-heart.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Long-term exposure to common air pollutants is associated with more advanced coronary artery disease—with notable differences between women and men—ac...</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 10:00:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New tool can help concussion patients manage fear and improve recovery</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-tool-concussion-patients-recovery.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Researchers from Edith Cowan University (ECU) have developed a new tool to evaluate fear avoidance behavior following a concussion.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 10:00:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>US skips World AIDS day for the first time in 37 years</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-world-aids-day-years.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>For the first time in more than three decades, the United States did not take part in World AIDS Day on December 1, a major change from past years whe...</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 04:50:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Longevity Trap: Why Chasing Anti-Aging May Be Aging You</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-longevity-trap-why-chasing-anti-aging-may-be-aging-you/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>In this episode, Chris explains why obsession with anti-aging hacks may actually undermine our long-term health. He examines the common longevity trap...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Link Between Metabolic Health and Mental Well-Being, with Dr. Matt Bernstein</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-link-between-metabolic-health-and-mental-well-being-with-dr-matt-bernstein/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes psychiatrist Dr. Matt Bernstein to explore the emerging field of metabolic psychiatry, the ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: From Wired &amp; Tired to Calm &amp; Clear: My Top Nutrients for Mood, Focus, and Sleep</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/from-wired-tired-to-calm-clear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris explores natural solutions for one of today’s most pressing challenges: chronic stress, anxiety, and...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Science Behind Oral Inflammation, with Dr. William Levine</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-science-behind-oral-inflammation-with-dr-william-levine/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes board-certified periodontist Dr. William Levine to discuss the overlooked role of gum healt...</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hyaluronic Acid: The Deep Hydration Molecule Your Skin Has Been Waiting For</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/hyaluronic-acid-the-deep-hydration-molecule-your-skin-has-been-waiting-for/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>If you’ve spent any time exploring the world of natural skincare, chances are you’ve heard of hyaluronic acid (HA). Once... The post Hyaluronic Acid: ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>