<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 06:21:22 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Research reveals rare form of neuroinflammatory disease is more common in Old Order Amish than general population</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-reveals-rare-neuroinflammatory-disease-common.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Researchers from Children's Hospital of Philadelphia (CHOP) and the Clinic for Special Children found that complement factor I (CFI) deficiency, an ul...</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 10:20:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Study links persistent fatigue in breast cancer survivors to increased inflammation</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-potential-link-fatigue-breast-cancer.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>For many breast cancer survivors, fatigue may linger long after treatment ends, which can have a significant impact on cognitive function, ability to ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 10:21:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mental health care needs urgent reform to include lifestyle interventions, claims report</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-mental-health-urgent-reform-lifestyle.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Mental health services must urgently increase investment in lifestyle interventions to improve care and help close the 15-year life expectancy gap fac...</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 10:25:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Portable test detects infections from a single drop of blood in 15 minutes</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-lab-required-ultra-sensitive-health.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Researchers at Arizona State University have developed a breakthrough diagnostic tool that could transform how quickly and reliably we detect illnesse...</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 10:26:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How small changes in walking technique may help treat knee osteoarthritis</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-small-technique-knee-osteoarthritis.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Gait analysis and pain measures show that subtly adjusting the angle of the foot during walking may reduce knee pain caused by osteoarthritis. This ap...</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 23:30:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Beauty From Within – Why Radiant Skin, Hair, and Nails Start Inside</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/beauty-from-within-why-radiant-skin-hair-and-nails-start-inside/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, we dive deep into the topic of beauty from within, exploring why radiant skin, hair, and nails truly start...</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 08:01:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Mold, Indoor Air Quality, and Clean Breathing, with Michael Rubino</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/mold-indoor-air-quality-and-clean-breathing-with-michael-rubino/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes environmental wellness expert Michael Rubino for an in-depth conversation on the hi...</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 08:01:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Nourishment Table, with Frederic Leroy</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-nourishment-table-with-frederic-leroy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes food scientist and advocate for regenerative agriculture Dr. Frederic Leroy to disc...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Turn ChatGPT Into Your Personal Meal Planner</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/turn-chatgpt-into-your-personal-meal-planner/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Even for someone who lives and breathes nutrition, meal planning can feel like a grind. There are weeks when I... The post Turn ChatGPT Into Your Pers...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:16:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Rediscovering Health, Nature, and Purpose-Driven Business, with Seth Spears</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rediscovering-health-nature-and-purpose-driven-business-with-seth-spears/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes entrepreneur and strategist Seth Spears for a wide-ranging conversation on health, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>