<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:37:44 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Genomics-guided tool helps guide immunotherapy choices for advanced kidney cancers</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-genomics-tool-immunotherapy-choices-advanced.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>A study led by Roswell Park Comprehensive Cancer Center helps explain why a rare and hyper-aggressive subtype of kidney cancer is susceptible to immun...</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 21:40:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Did you walk or cycle to school as a child? Your children are likely to follow in your footsteps</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-school-child-children-footsteps.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>If you used physically active modes of commuting to school, your children are likely to do the same. A study published in the European Journal of Publ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:47:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Study shows people overestimate hill steepness based on their eye level</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-people-overestimate-hill-steepness-based.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>People's perceptions of the world are easily impacted by the angle at which they view objects in it, suggests a new study.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 20:13:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>User-friendly tool streamlines transcriptomic data analysis for precision medicine applications</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-user-friendly-tool-transcriptomic-analysis.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>The Barcelona Institute for Global Health (ISGlobal) has launched HTGAnalyzer, a new, easy-to-use, fast and reproducible bioinformatics tool for advan...</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:38:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Report ties to child mental health crisis to immigration enforcement</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-child-mental-health-crisis-immigration.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Aggressive immigration practices—such as detention, deportation, and workplace raids—are contributing to widespread emotional trauma among both immigr...</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:33:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Beauty From Within – Why Radiant Skin, Hair, and Nails Start Inside</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/beauty-from-within-why-radiant-skin-hair-and-nails-start-inside/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, we dive deep into the topic of beauty from within, exploring why radiant skin, hair, and nails truly start...</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 08:01:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Mold, Indoor Air Quality, and Clean Breathing, with Michael Rubino</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/mold-indoor-air-quality-and-clean-breathing-with-michael-rubino/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes environmental wellness expert Michael Rubino for an in-depth conversation on the hi...</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 08:01:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Nourishment Table, with Frederic Leroy</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-nourishment-table-with-frederic-leroy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes food scientist and advocate for regenerative agriculture Dr. Frederic Leroy to disc...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Turn ChatGPT Into Your Personal Meal Planner</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/turn-chatgpt-into-your-personal-meal-planner/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Even for someone who lives and breathes nutrition, meal planning can feel like a grind. There are weeks when I... The post Turn ChatGPT Into Your Pers...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:16:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Rediscovering Health, Nature, and Purpose-Driven Business, with Seth Spears</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rediscovering-health-nature-and-purpose-driven-business-with-seth-spears/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes entrepreneur and strategist Seth Spears for a wide-ranging conversation on health, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>