<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 10:46:33 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The robotic revolution in cardiac surgery.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/the-robotic-revolution-in-cardiac-surgery/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Robotic-assisted cardiac surgery (RACS) is revolutionizing the landscape of cardiovascular interventions through technological precision, minimally in...</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:31:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Effectiveness of an online mindfulness based stress reduction intervention on psychological distress among patients with COVID19 after hospital discharge.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/effectiveness-of-an-online-mindfulness-based-stress-reduction-intervention-on-psychological-distress-among-patients-with-covid19-after-hospital-discharge/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Given the high prevalence of psychological complications during pandemics such as COVID-19, it is imperative to identify effective psychological inter...</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:30:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Characteristics of Postural Instability in Idiopathic Normal Pressure Hydrocephalus.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/characteristics-of-postural-instability-in-idiopathic-normal-pressure-hydrocephalus/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>In patients with idiopathic normal pressure hydrocephalus (iNPH), the characteristics of static steady-state balance disturbance are not as well under...</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:30:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Researchers redesign vaginal speculum to ease fear and pain</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-redesign-vaginal-speculum-ease-pain.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>It is cold, hard, metallic and commonly associated with pain. Not a medieval torture instrument, but the vaginal speculum used every day around the wo...</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 14:38:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CXCL14 drives age-related intervertebral disc degeneration via NF-κB pathway activation in a multiomic study.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/cxcl14-drives-age-related-intervertebral-disc-degeneration-via-nf-%ce%bab-pathway-activation-in-a-multiomic-study/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Intervertebral disc degeneration (IDD), a common cause of chronic low back pain, strongly impacts daily life. Although previous studies have identifie...</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:31:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Revealing how senescent cells shape aging at the single-cell level</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-revealing-senescent-cells-aging-cell.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>A research team led by Professor Takuya Yamamoto (Department of Life Science Frontiers) and Professor Yasuhiro Yamada at the University of Tokyo has d...</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 14:40:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Novel open-source diagnostic tool offers affordable, reliable pathogen detection for resource-limited settings</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-source-diagnostic-tool-reliable-pathogen.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>A bottleneck in ensuring access to widespread molecular diagnostics, especially in low- and middle-income countries, has been the high cost and logist...</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 15:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Magnetic Bioadhesive for Tumor Therapy: Synergistic Magnetothermal and Chemodynamic Effects.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/magnetic-bioadhesive-for-tumor-therapy-synergistic-magnetothermal-and-chemodynamic-effects/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Therapeutic bioadhesives with injectability, strong adhesion, magnetothermal responsiveness, sustained efficacy, and biosafety are desired for in situ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 06:31:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New imaging technique monitors protein changes in cancer cells without dyes</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-imaging-technique-protein-cancer-cells.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Researchers from Helmholtz Munich and the Technical University of Munich have developed a novel method to track cancer treatment responses in individu...</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 14:50:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hidden pockets of GHB harm revealed as ambulance attendances surge across Australia</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-hidden-pockets-ghb-revealed-ambulance.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>New research has revealed a substantial increase in GHB-related ambulance attendances across Australia, with Victoria recording the highest rate and G...</description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 14:39:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Mold, Indoor Air Quality, and Clean Breathing, with Michael Rubino</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/mold-indoor-air-quality-and-clean-breathing-with-michael-rubino/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes environmental wellness expert Michael Rubino for an in-depth conversation on the hi...</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 08:01:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Nourishment Table, with Frederic Leroy</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-nourishment-table-with-frederic-leroy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes food scientist and advocate for regenerative agriculture Dr. Frederic Leroy to disc...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Turn ChatGPT Into Your Personal Meal Planner</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/turn-chatgpt-into-your-personal-meal-planner/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Even for someone who lives and breathes nutrition, meal planning can feel like a grind. There are weeks when I... The post Turn ChatGPT Into Your Pers...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:16:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Rediscovering Health, Nature, and Purpose-Driven Business, with Seth Spears</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rediscovering-health-nature-and-purpose-driven-business-with-seth-spears/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes entrepreneur and strategist Seth Spears for a wide-ranging conversation on health, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: How to Sharpen and Protect Your Mind for a Lifetime, with Dale Bredesen</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/how-to-sharpen-and-protect-your-mind-for-a-lifetime-with-dale-bredesen/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes renowned neurologist Dr. Dale Bredesen back to the show for an insightful conversation abou...</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:01:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>