<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:00:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Map of autism mutations shows diverse genes converge on shared brain pathways</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-autism-mutations-diverse-genes-converge.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>UCLA Health researchers have created a comprehensive map showing how eight different genetic mutations associated with autism spectrum disorder affect...</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:00:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Should I take a fish oil supplement for my heart, joints or mood?</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-fish-oil-supplement-heart-joints.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Fish oil, also known as omega-3, is one of the most popular dietary supplements. It's often promoted to protect the heart, boost mood, reduce inflamma...</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:16:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Study finds longer hospital stays and higher readmissions for young adults with complex childhood conditions</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-longer-hospital-stays-higher-readmissions.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>More children with medically complex conditions are surviving into adulthood, but researchers have had limited visibility into how these conditions in...</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A neural basis for dumb decisions: Why paying more or waiting in line for an item increases its value in our minds</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-neural-basis-dumb-decisions-paying.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Ahab hunting down Moby Dick. Wile E. Coyote chasing the Road Runner. Learning Latin. Walking over hot coals. Standing in a long line for boba tea or e...</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:00:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Glowing bacterial sensors detect gut illness in mice before symptoms emerge</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-bacterial-sensors-gut-illness-mice.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>University of British Columbia researchers have engineered gut bacteria that dim their fluorescent glow in the presence of illness. Their findings cou...</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:00:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Cold Exposure: Why Sustained Beats Extreme</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/cold-exposure-why-sustained-beats-extreme/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Cold plunges and ice baths dominate social media, but do they really deliver the best metabolic benefits? In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 08:03:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Why Your Sleep Schedule Matters As Much As Duration</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/why-your-sleep-schedule-matters-as-much-as-duration/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris challenges the conventional focus on sleep duration and makes the case that sleep timing and circadi...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 08:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Menopause Brain Fog—What’s Really Happening (and How To Fix It)</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rhr-menopause-brain-fog-whats-really-happening-and-how-to-fix-it/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris examines research confirming that menopause-related brain fog is real, measurable, and reversible. H...</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 08:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Seed Oils and Colon Cancer – What the New Research Really Shows</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/seed-oils-and-colon-cancer-what-the-new-research-really-shows/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Seed oils have become one of the most controversial topics in nutrition, especially after a 2024 University of South Florida study linked high omega-6...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 08:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Longevity Trap: Why Chasing Anti-Aging May Be Aging You</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-longevity-trap-why-chasing-anti-aging-may-be-aging-you/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>In this episode, Chris explains why obsession with anti-aging hacks may actually undermine our long-term health. He examines the common longevity trap...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>