<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>New guideline expands stroke treatment for adults, offers first pediatric stroke guidance</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-guideline-treatment-adults-pediatric-guidance.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Expanded eligibility for advanced stroke therapies and new recommendations for diagnosing and treating stroke in children and adults are among the maj...</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 15:43:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Behavioral traits in adolescence predict preference for alcohol, AI analysis finds</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-behavioral-traits-adolescence-alcohol-ai.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>A machine learning analysis identified certain behavior profiles that predict a preference for alcohol in adolescent mice, which may provide insights ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 15:37:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fish allergy risk varies by fish size and which part is eaten, research reveals</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-fish-allergy-varies-size-eaten.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>A new study reveals allergy risks from fish depend not just on species but also on the size of the fish and which part you eat. James Cook University ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 15:31:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Certain sex hormones could play important role in understanding long-term heart health</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-sex-hormones-play-important-role.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>People with type 2 diabetes face a higher risk of heart attacks, strokes and other cardiovascular problems, according to the National Institutes of He...</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 15:32:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gout medication may reduce the risk of heart attack and stroke</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-gout-medication-heart.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>A new study, led by experts at the University of Nottingham, has found that medicines used to treat gout can also reduce the risk of heart attack and ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Why Your Sleep Schedule Matters As Much As Duration</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/why-your-sleep-schedule-matters-as-much-as-duration/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris challenges the conventional focus on sleep duration and makes the case that sleep timing and circadi...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 08:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Menopause Brain Fog—What’s Really Happening (and How To Fix It)</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rhr-menopause-brain-fog-whats-really-happening-and-how-to-fix-it/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris examines research confirming that menopause-related brain fog is real, measurable, and reversible. H...</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 08:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Seed Oils and Colon Cancer – What the New Research Really Shows</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/seed-oils-and-colon-cancer-what-the-new-research-really-shows/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Seed oils have become one of the most controversial topics in nutrition, especially after a 2024 University of South Florida study linked high omega-6...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 08:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Longevity Trap: Why Chasing Anti-Aging May Be Aging You</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-longevity-trap-why-chasing-anti-aging-may-be-aging-you/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>In this episode, Chris explains why obsession with anti-aging hacks may actually undermine our long-term health. He examines the common longevity trap...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Link Between Metabolic Health and Mental Well-Being, with Dr. Matt Bernstein</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-link-between-metabolic-health-and-mental-well-being-with-dr-matt-bernstein/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes psychiatrist Dr. Matt Bernstein to explore the emerging field of metabolic psychiatry, the ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>