<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 08:00:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>New possible treatment pathway for Shank3-related autism discovered</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-treatment-pathway-shank3-autism.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Autism spectrum disorder (ASD) is a neurodevelopmental condition characterized by differences in communication, behavior and the processing of sensory...</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 12:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI learns from the tree of life to support rare disease diagnosis</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-ai-tree-life-rare-disease.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Researchers have created an artificial intelligence model that can identify which mutations in human proteins are most likely to cause disease, even w...</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 10:00:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How a cheap, century-old drug can improve life with type 1 diabetes</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-cheap-century-drug-life-diabetes.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>A Garvan-led clinical trial has found that using a common and inexpensive type 2 diabetes drug reduces insulin needs in type 1 diabetes, opening doors...</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 10:00:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rejuvenating the blood: New pharmacological strategy targets RhoA in hematopoietic stem cells</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-rejuvenating-blood-pharmacological-strategy-rhoa.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Aging is defined as the deterioration of function over time, and it is one of the main risk factors for numerous chronic diseases. Although aging is a...</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 10:00:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Human brains are preconfigured with instructions for understanding the world, evidence suggests</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-human-brains-preconfigured-world-evidence.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Humans have long wondered when and how we begin to form thoughts. Are we born with a pre-configured brain, or do thought patterns only begin to emerge...</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 10:00:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Link Between Metabolic Health and Mental Well-Being, with Dr. Matt Bernstein</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-link-between-metabolic-health-and-mental-well-being-with-dr-matt-bernstein/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes psychiatrist Dr. Matt Bernstein to explore the emerging field of metabolic psychiatry, the ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: From Wired &amp; Tired to Calm &amp; Clear: My Top Nutrients for Mood, Focus, and Sleep</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/from-wired-tired-to-calm-clear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris explores natural solutions for one of today’s most pressing challenges: chronic stress, anxiety, and...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Science Behind Oral Inflammation, with Dr. William Levine</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-science-behind-oral-inflammation-with-dr-william-levine/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes board-certified periodontist Dr. William Levine to discuss the overlooked role of gum healt...</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hyaluronic Acid: The Deep Hydration Molecule Your Skin Has Been Waiting For</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/hyaluronic-acid-the-deep-hydration-molecule-your-skin-has-been-waiting-for/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>If you’ve spent any time exploring the world of natural skincare, chances are you’ve heard of hyaluronic acid (HA). Once... The post Hyaluronic Acid: ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rice Ceramides: The Unsung Hero of Skin Hydration and Barrier Health</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rice-ceramides-the-unsung-hero-of-skin-hydration-and-barrier-health/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>We often think of radiant skin as the result of what we put on it: moisturizers, serums, masks. But emerging... The post Rice Ceramides: The Unsung He...</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>