<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 07:17:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Review finds that future vaccine trials must include care home residents</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-future-vaccine-trials-home-residents.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>The first review of vaccine trials conducted in care homes concludes that it is "crucial" that future vaccine trials include care home residents.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 11:37:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Whole-food diet adherence means you really can eat much more and be well-nourished but still consume far fewer calories</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-food-diet-adherence-nourished-consume.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Research led by scientists at the University of Bristol and co-authored by top US nutritional experts reveals that people following a completely unpro...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 10:53:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hidden mpox exposure detected in healthy Nigerian adults, revealing under-recognized transmission</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-hidden-mpox-exposure-healthy-nigerian.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>The mpox virus appears to be circulating silently in parts of Nigeria, in many cases without the symptoms typically associated with the disease, accor...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 10:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The flu is everywhere: So why aren't Canadians getting vaccinated for viral illnesses?</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-flu-canadians-vaccinated-viral-illnesses.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>The death of Prashant Sreekumar made headlines across Canada when the 43-year-old father of three died in the emergency room of Edmonton's Grey Nuns h...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 11:54:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fracture prevention for Aboriginal and Torres Strait Islander people: Research uncovers perspectives on bone health</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-fracture-aboriginal-torres-strait-islander.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Despite Aboriginal and Torres Strait Islander people experiencing a higher rate of fragility fractures from low-impact injuries, such as a fall from s...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 09:53:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Why Your Sleep Schedule Matters As Much As Duration</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/why-your-sleep-schedule-matters-as-much-as-duration/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris challenges the conventional focus on sleep duration and makes the case that sleep timing and circadi...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 08:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Menopause Brain Fog—What’s Really Happening (and How To Fix It)</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rhr-menopause-brain-fog-whats-really-happening-and-how-to-fix-it/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris examines research confirming that menopause-related brain fog is real, measurable, and reversible. H...</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 08:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Seed Oils and Colon Cancer – What the New Research Really Shows</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/seed-oils-and-colon-cancer-what-the-new-research-really-shows/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Seed oils have become one of the most controversial topics in nutrition, especially after a 2024 University of South Florida study linked high omega-6...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 08:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Longevity Trap: Why Chasing Anti-Aging May Be Aging You</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-longevity-trap-why-chasing-anti-aging-may-be-aging-you/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>In this episode, Chris explains why obsession with anti-aging hacks may actually undermine our long-term health. He examines the common longevity trap...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Link Between Metabolic Health and Mental Well-Being, with Dr. Matt Bernstein</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-link-between-metabolic-health-and-mental-well-being-with-dr-matt-bernstein/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes psychiatrist Dr. Matt Bernstein to explore the emerging field of metabolic psychiatry, the ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>