<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 14:08:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Paternal Mental Distress Linked to Poorer Offspring Development</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/paternal-mental-distress-linked-to-poorer-offspring-development/</link><image_url>https://cdn.physiciansweekly.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/HEALTHDAY_Web_small3.png</image_url><description>WEDNESDAY, June 25, 2025 (HealthDay News) — Paternal mental distress is associated with poorer child development, according to a study published onlin...</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 07:31:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gene Therapy Effective in Patients With Recessive Dystrophic Epidermolysis Bullosa</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/gene-therapy-effective-in-patients-with-recessive-dystrophic-epidermolysis-bullosa/</link><image_url>https://cdn.physiciansweekly.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/HEALTHDAY_Web_small3.png</image_url><description>WEDNESDAY, June 25, 2025 (HealthDay News) — For patients with recessive dystrophic epidermolysis bullosa (RDEB), a one-time surgical application of pr...</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 07:31:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Common bacteria in mouth can help predict progression of head and neck cancer</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-common-bacteria-mouth-neck-cancer.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>For decades, oral health care has mainly focused on preventing cavities and gum disease. However, scientific research has increasingly highlighted the...</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 18:40:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>There is no loneliness epidemic, so why do we keep talking as if there is?</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-loneliness-epidemic.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Most people experience periods of loneliness, isolation or solitude in their lives. But these are different things, and the proportion of people feeli...</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 18:30:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>COVID-19 pandemic significantly eroded American public's trust in US public health institutions, assessment shows</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-covid-pandemic-significantly-eroded-american.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Four discrete cross-sectional surveys of US adults from 2020–2024 reveal US adults reporting high confidence in the Centers for Disease Control and Pr...</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 19:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Empowerment Self-Defense Arms ED Staff Against Rising Workplace Violence</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/empowerment-self-defense-arms-ed-staff-against-rising-workplace-violence/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Empowerment self-defense training protects emergency department staff, boosts confidence, enhances communication, and fosters a safer work environment...</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 15:06:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>California’s Much-Touted IVF Law May Be Delayed Until 2026, Leaving Many in the Lurch</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/californias-much-touted-ivf-law-may-be-delayed-until-2026-leaving-many-in-the-lurch/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>California lawmakers are poised to delay the state’s much-ballyhooed new law mandating in vitro fertilization insurance coverage for millions, set to ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 11:30:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What RFK Jr. Isn’t Talking About: How To Make Vaccines Safer</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/what-rfk-jr-isnt-talking-about-how-to-make-vaccines-safer/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Within an hour of receiving a covid vaccination in November 2020, Utah preschool teacher Brianne Dressen felt pins and needles through her arms and le...</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 11:30:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Study finds no added benefit of surfactant treatment for babies with severe bronchiolitis</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-added-benefit-surfactant-treatment-babies.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>A major UK-led clinical trial has found that a treatment commonly used to help premature babies breathe offers no benefit for infants on life support ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 18:20:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deeper sleep is more likely to lead to eureka moments, study indicates</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-deeper-eureka-moments.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>"Sleeping on it," especially dropping deeper than a doze, might help people gain insight into certain kinds of tasks, according to a study published i...</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 19:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Nourishment Table, with Frederic Leroy</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-nourishment-table-with-frederic-leroy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes food scientist and advocate for regenerative agriculture Dr. Frederic Leroy to disc...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Turn ChatGPT Into Your Personal Meal Planner</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/turn-chatgpt-into-your-personal-meal-planner/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Even for someone who lives and breathes nutrition, meal planning can feel like a grind. There are weeks when I... The post Turn ChatGPT Into Your Pers...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:16:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Rediscovering Health, Nature, and Purpose-Driven Business, with Seth Spears</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rediscovering-health-nature-and-purpose-driven-business-with-seth-spears/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes entrepreneur and strategist Seth Spears for a wide-ranging conversation on health, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: How to Sharpen and Protect Your Mind for a Lifetime, with Dale Bredesen</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/how-to-sharpen-and-protect-your-mind-for-a-lifetime-with-dale-bredesen/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes renowned neurologist Dr. Dale Bredesen back to the show for an insightful conversation abou...</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:01:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quality Matters: How to Choose and Use the Best Collagen Supplement</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/quality-matters-how-to-choose-and-use-the-best-collagen-supplement/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Introduction If you’ve been paying attention to health and wellness trends, you’ve likely noticed collagen supplements everywhere—from your local heal...</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:57:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>