<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 00:49:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Your daily orange juice could be helping your heart</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-daily-orange-juice-heart.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Most of us think of orange juice as a simple breakfast habit, something you pour without much thought. Yet scientists are discovering that this everyd...</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 01:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Autonomy and intrinsic sense of control linked to drinking behaviors and alcohol consequences</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-autonomy-intrinsic-linked-behaviors-alcohol.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Individuals' autonomy and sense of control are associated with the quantity and frequency of their alcohol consumption and its consequences, according...</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 19:02:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Patients are more than participants: What meaningful engagement really looks like—and why it improves health research</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-patients-meaningful-engagement-health.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>When we talk about "patient engagement" in research, it can sound like a slogan on a grant application rather than something that changes people's liv...</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 20:40:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why metabolism matters in Fanconi anemia: How a rare genetic disorder disrupts energy pathways</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-metabolism-fanconi-anemia-rare-genetic.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Experts at Cincinnati Children's have uncovered striking metabolic differences in people with Fanconi anemia (FA), a rare genetic disorder that causes...</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 19:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New research shows no increase in proportion of adults in England with autism or psychotic disorders</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-proportion-adults-england-autism-psychotic.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>The Adult Psychiatric Morbidity Survey provides the official statistics on trends over time in autism, psychotic disorder, bipolar disorder, drug and ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 23:40:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Link Between Metabolic Health and Mental Well-Being, with Dr. Matt Bernstein</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-link-between-metabolic-health-and-mental-well-being-with-dr-matt-bernstein/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes psychiatrist Dr. Matt Bernstein to explore the emerging field of metabolic psychiatry, the ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: From Wired &amp; Tired to Calm &amp; Clear: My Top Nutrients for Mood, Focus, and Sleep</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/from-wired-tired-to-calm-clear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris explores natural solutions for one of today’s most pressing challenges: chronic stress, anxiety, and...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Science Behind Oral Inflammation, with Dr. William Levine</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-science-behind-oral-inflammation-with-dr-william-levine/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes board-certified periodontist Dr. William Levine to discuss the overlooked role of gum healt...</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hyaluronic Acid: The Deep Hydration Molecule Your Skin Has Been Waiting For</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/hyaluronic-acid-the-deep-hydration-molecule-your-skin-has-been-waiting-for/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>If you’ve spent any time exploring the world of natural skincare, chances are you’ve heard of hyaluronic acid (HA). Once... The post Hyaluronic Acid: ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rice Ceramides: The Unsung Hero of Skin Hydration and Barrier Health</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rice-ceramides-the-unsung-hero-of-skin-hydration-and-barrier-health/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>We often think of radiant skin as the result of what we put on it: moisturizers, serums, masks. But emerging... The post Rice Ceramides: The Unsung He...</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>