<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:55:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>How digital health tools strengthen care when patients are the core focus</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-digital-health-tools-patients-core.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>From patient portals and text messages to wearable devices and artificial intelligence, digital health technologies are becoming a significant part of...</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 16:30:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Study recommends better continuity of care with GPs for people with dementia to save NHS money</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-gps-people-dementia-nhs-money.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Better continuity of care with GPs for people with dementia who are in their final year of life can save the NHS money, according to new research from...</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 18:40:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anticipating aging-related mental decline using saliva samples and AI</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-aging-mental-decline-saliva-samples.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>As humans age beyond early adulthood, their physical and mental functions tend to slowly worsen over time. One of the most common sources of severe me...</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 17:40:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New federal plan aims to use more donor organs, improve transplant safety</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-federal-aims-donor-transplant-safety.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>U.S. health officials unveiled proposed changes to the nation's transplant system, hoping to help more patients get lifesaving organs, even when donat...</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 17:10:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Your sense of self is deeply tied to your memory—here's how</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-deeply-memory.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>You might say you have a "bad memory" because you don't remember what cake you had at your last birthday party or the plot of a movie you watched last...</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 17:40:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Cold Exposure: Why Sustained Beats Extreme</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/cold-exposure-why-sustained-beats-extreme/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Cold plunges and ice baths dominate social media, but do they really deliver the best metabolic benefits? In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 08:03:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Why Your Sleep Schedule Matters As Much As Duration</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/why-your-sleep-schedule-matters-as-much-as-duration/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris challenges the conventional focus on sleep duration and makes the case that sleep timing and circadi...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 08:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Menopause Brain Fog—What’s Really Happening (and How To Fix It)</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rhr-menopause-brain-fog-whats-really-happening-and-how-to-fix-it/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris examines research confirming that menopause-related brain fog is real, measurable, and reversible. H...</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 08:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Seed Oils and Colon Cancer – What the New Research Really Shows</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/seed-oils-and-colon-cancer-what-the-new-research-really-shows/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Seed oils have become one of the most controversial topics in nutrition, especially after a 2024 University of South Florida study linked high omega-6...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 08:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Longevity Trap: Why Chasing Anti-Aging May Be Aging You</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-longevity-trap-why-chasing-anti-aging-may-be-aging-you/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>In this episode, Chris explains why obsession with anti-aging hacks may actually undermine our long-term health. He examines the common longevity trap...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>