<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 16:07:52 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Discovery of breast cancer treatment resistance mechanism could lead to new hope for some</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-discovery-breast-cancer-treatment-resistance.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Mayo Clinic researchers have discovered a key reason why certain breast cancers might not respond to an important new class of therapeutics called ant...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 20:24:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: From Wired &amp; Tired to Calm &amp; Clear: My Top Nutrients for Mood, Focus, and Sleep</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/from-wired-tired-to-calm-clear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris explores natural solutions for one of today’s most pressing challenges: chronic stress, anxiety, and...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Whole tablets may be safer than crushed ones for patients with poststroke swallowing disorders</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-tablets-safer-patients-poststroke-swallowing.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>For decades, stroke patients with swallowing difficulties have routinely received crushed tablets to reduce the risk of aspiration. New clinical data ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 20:02:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Previously unknown genetic cause of microcephaly identified</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-previously-unknown-genetic-microcephaly.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Microcephaly is a congenital malformation that leads to a significantly reduced brain size and is often accompanied by developmental delay. An interna...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 19:56:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Texas sues Tylenol makers over alleged autism link</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-texas-sues-tylenol-makers-alleged.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>The Texas attorney general announced a lawsuit Tuesday against the pharmaceutical companies behind Tylenol that echoes the Trump administration's alle...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 20:23:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why you can salvage moldy cheese but never spoiled meat: A toxicologist advises on what to watch out for</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-salvage-moldy-cheese-meat-toxicologist.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>When you open the refrigerator and find a wedge of cheese flecked with green mold, or a package of chicken that smells faintly sour, it can be temptin...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 19:58:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Science Behind Oral Inflammation, with Dr. William Levine</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-science-behind-oral-inflammation-with-dr-william-levine/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes board-certified periodontist Dr. William Levine to discuss the overlooked role of gum healt...</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hyaluronic Acid: The Deep Hydration Molecule Your Skin Has Been Waiting For</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/hyaluronic-acid-the-deep-hydration-molecule-your-skin-has-been-waiting-for/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>If you’ve spent any time exploring the world of natural skincare, chances are you’ve heard of hyaluronic acid (HA). Once... The post Hyaluronic Acid: ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rice Ceramides: The Unsung Hero of Skin Hydration and Barrier Health</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rice-ceramides-the-unsung-hero-of-skin-hydration-and-barrier-health/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>We often think of radiant skin as the result of what we put on it: moisturizers, serums, masks. But emerging... The post Rice Ceramides: The Unsung He...</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lutein and Zeaxanthin: The Carotenoids That Protect and Perfect Your Skin from Within</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/lutein-and-zeaxanthin-the-carotenoids-that-protect-and-perfect-your-skin-from-within/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>When most people think of lutein and zeaxanthin, they picture eye health supplements or leafy green vegetables. But these vibrant... The post Lutein a...</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:00:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>