<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 06:33:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>FDA Approves Gardenia-Based Blue Dye for Use in Foods and Drinks</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/fda-approves-gardenia-based-blue-dye-for-use-in-foods-and-drinks/</link><image_url>https://cdn.physiciansweekly.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/HEALTHDAY_Web_small3.png</image_url><description>TUESDAY, July 15, 2025 (HealthDay News) — A natural blue food coloring made from gardenia fruit has been approved by the U.S. Food and Drug Administra...</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 07:31:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Most Major Ice Cream Brands Will Remove Synthetic Dyes by 2028</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/most-major-ice-cream-brands-will-remove-synthetic-dyes-by-2028/</link><image_url>https://cdn.physiciansweekly.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/HEALTHDAY_Web_small3.png</image_url><description>TUESDAY, July 15, 2025 (HealthDay News) — About 90% of the ice cream sold in the U.S. will no longer contain artificial dyes by 2028, federal health o...</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 07:31:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Unraveling respiratory illnesses with iPSCs on microfluidic chips</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-unraveling-respiratory-illnesses-ipscs-microfluidic.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Respiratory infections such as COVID-19 have been responsible for numerous pandemics and have placed a substantial burden on health care systems. Such...</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 10:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Find the Right Medical Rehab Services</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/how-to-find-the-right-medical-rehab-services/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Rehabilitation therapy can be a godsend after hospitalization for a stroke, a fall, an accident, a joint replacement, a severe burn, or a spinal cord ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 11:30:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Comprehensive genomic profiling linked to higher targeted therapy use, with Medicare patients lagging behind</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-comprehensive-genomic-profiling-linked-higher.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Optum and Illumina Inc. researchers documented that less than half of patients with newly diagnosed advanced cancers received any biomarker testing be...</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 11:14:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Guide to Nociplastic Pain Management in Primary Care</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/a-guide-to-nociplastic-pain-management-in-primary-care/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Researchers recently created a guide to help primary care clinicians navigate the complexities of chronic, nociplastic pain in their practices. The po...</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 11:00:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Discovery of low power cellular housekeeping in human oocytes could boost IVF success</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-discovery-power-cellular-housekeeping-human.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Human eggs are some of the most patient cells in the body, lying dormant for decades until needed. A study published in The EMBO Journal shows that th...</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 10:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Even Grave Errors at Rehab Hospitals Go Unpenalized and Undisclosed</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/even-grave-errors-at-rehab-hospitals-go-unpenalized-and-undisclosed/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Rehab hospitals that help people recover from major surgeries and injuries have become a highly lucrative slice of the health care business. But feder...</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 11:30:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Optimal heart health in children cuts risk of chronic diseases in adulthood, review indicates</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-optimal-heart-health-children-chronic.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Optimal heart health from birth through adolescence, as measured by a combination of metrics, leads to long-lasting cardiovascular and overall physica...</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 10:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trove of genetic data to spur cancer research released</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-trove-genetic-spur-cancer.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>In an effort to foster progress in cancer research, the National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) is releasing detailed and comprehensive ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 10:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Mold, Indoor Air Quality, and Clean Breathing, with Michael Rubino</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/mold-indoor-air-quality-and-clean-breathing-with-michael-rubino/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes environmental wellness expert Michael Rubino for an in-depth conversation on the hi...</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 08:01:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Nourishment Table, with Frederic Leroy</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-nourishment-table-with-frederic-leroy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes food scientist and advocate for regenerative agriculture Dr. Frederic Leroy to disc...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Turn ChatGPT Into Your Personal Meal Planner</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/turn-chatgpt-into-your-personal-meal-planner/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Even for someone who lives and breathes nutrition, meal planning can feel like a grind. There are weeks when I... The post Turn ChatGPT Into Your Pers...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:16:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Rediscovering Health, Nature, and Purpose-Driven Business, with Seth Spears</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rediscovering-health-nature-and-purpose-driven-business-with-seth-spears/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes entrepreneur and strategist Seth Spears for a wide-ranging conversation on health, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: How to Sharpen and Protect Your Mind for a Lifetime, with Dale Bredesen</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/how-to-sharpen-and-protect-your-mind-for-a-lifetime-with-dale-bredesen/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes renowned neurologist Dr. Dale Bredesen back to the show for an insightful conversation abou...</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:01:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>