<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:53:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Fecal microbiota transplantation in pigs: current status and future perspective.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/fecal-microbiota-transplantation-in-pigs-current-status-and-future-perspective/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Fecal microbiota transplantation (FMT) is gaining attention as a method to modulate the gut microbiome in pigs, with the goal of enhancing health and ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:31:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cannabis use disorder may up risk of benign salivary gland tumors</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-cannabis-disorder-benign-salivary-gland.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Cannabis use disorder (CUD) is associated with increased risk of benign salivary gland tumors, according to a research letter published online July 17...</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 18:30:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Exploring the link between muscle quality and erectile dysfunction: assessing the impact of mass and strength.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/exploring-the-link-between-muscle-quality-and-erectile-dysfunction-assessing-the-impact-of-mass-and-strength/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Sexual dysfunction is a prevalent issue affecting quality of life. Skeletal muscle mass and strength are emerging biomarkers for overall health. Consi...</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:31:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How social media can help abuse survivors heal</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-social-media-abuse-survivors.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>New research from The University of Texas at Arlington reveals that social media platforms can play a potentially life-saving role for young people na...</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 18:40:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Large-scale neuroimaging data collection proves feasible in low-income communities</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-large-scale-neuroimaging-feasible-income.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>People are diverse, and the environments they live in may influence them differently. This broad diversity increases the need for neuroimaging studies...</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 18:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Peyronie’s disease and risk of depression. A nationwide 25-year cohort study.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/peyronies-disease-and-risk-of-depression-a-nationwide-25-year-cohort-study/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Peyronie’s disease leads to penile deformities and can cause physical symptoms, for example, penile pain, and erectile dysfunction, along with psychol...</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:31:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Application of protein A immunoadsorption in thyroid-associated ophthalmopathy (TAO): study protocol for a non-randomised controlled clinical trial.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/application-of-protein-a-immunoadsorption-in-thyroid-associated-ophthalmopathy-tao-study-protocol-for-a-non-randomised-controlled-clinical-trial/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Thyroid-associated antibodies are crucial in the occurrence and development of thyroid-associated ophthalmopathy (TAO). Protein A immunoadsorption is ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:31:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The neurofucntional abnormalities of temporal gyrus underly impaired sensory attenuation in schizophrenia during action-outcome contingent paradigm.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/the-neurofucntional-abnormalities-of-temporal-gyrus-underly-impaired-sensory-attenuation-in-schizophrenia-during-action-outcome-contingent-paradigm/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Previous research suggests that individuals with schizophrenia may exhibit impairments in sensory attenuation. This neurocognitive process is defined ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 06:31:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rural hospital closures led to higher prices at nearby hospitals</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-rural-hospital-closures-higher-prices.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Rural hospital closures directly impact the health of rural Americans by reducing access to care. New research from the University of Minnesota School...</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 18:20:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How mothers supporting mothers can help fill the health care worker shortage gap and other barriers to care</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-mothers-health-worker-shortage-gap.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>For generations, women have relied on informal networks of friends, family and neighbors to navigate the complexities of birth and motherhood. Today, ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 18:10:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Mold, Indoor Air Quality, and Clean Breathing, with Michael Rubino</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/mold-indoor-air-quality-and-clean-breathing-with-michael-rubino/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes environmental wellness expert Michael Rubino for an in-depth conversation on the hi...</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 08:01:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Nourishment Table, with Frederic Leroy</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-nourishment-table-with-frederic-leroy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes food scientist and advocate for regenerative agriculture Dr. Frederic Leroy to disc...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Turn ChatGPT Into Your Personal Meal Planner</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/turn-chatgpt-into-your-personal-meal-planner/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Even for someone who lives and breathes nutrition, meal planning can feel like a grind. There are weeks when I... The post Turn ChatGPT Into Your Pers...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:16:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Rediscovering Health, Nature, and Purpose-Driven Business, with Seth Spears</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rediscovering-health-nature-and-purpose-driven-business-with-seth-spears/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes entrepreneur and strategist Seth Spears for a wide-ranging conversation on health, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: How to Sharpen and Protect Your Mind for a Lifetime, with Dale Bredesen</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/how-to-sharpen-and-protect-your-mind-for-a-lifetime-with-dale-bredesen/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes renowned neurologist Dr. Dale Bredesen back to the show for an insightful conversation abou...</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:01:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>