<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 07:03:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Next-gen CAR-T cell therapy shows early promise in patients with refractory B-cell acute lymphoblastic leukemia</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-gen-car-cell-therapy-early.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Safety and efficacy data from a phase 1 multicenter study evaluating rapcabtagene autoleucel, an investigational next-generation CD19-directed CAR-T c...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 11:09:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Home-based monitoring could transform care for patients receiving T-cell redirecting therapies</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-home-based-patients-cell-redirecting.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Patients who receive T-cell redirecting therapies are typically hospitalized for several days after treatment to watch for side effects. Now new resea...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 10:30:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Researchers identify CD40 as potential biomarker for a type of nodal T cell lymphoma</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-cd40-potential-biomarker-nodal-cell.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Researchers at The University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Center have characterized the complex microenvironment in angioimmunoblastic T cell lymphoma...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 10:51:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Among psychologists, AI use is up, but so are concerns</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-psychologists-ai.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>More than half of psychologists experimented with artificial intelligence tools in their practices in the past year, but almost all cite concerns abou...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 10:43:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>While scientists race to study spread of measles in US, Kennedy unravels hard-won gains</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-scientists-measles-kennedy-unravels-hard.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>The United States is poised to lose its measles-free status next year. If that happens, the country will enter an era in which outbreaks are common ag...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 11:50:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Longevity Trap: Why Chasing Anti-Aging May Be Aging You</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-longevity-trap-why-chasing-anti-aging-may-be-aging-you/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>In this episode, Chris explains why obsession with anti-aging hacks may actually undermine our long-term health. He examines the common longevity trap...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Link Between Metabolic Health and Mental Well-Being, with Dr. Matt Bernstein</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-link-between-metabolic-health-and-mental-well-being-with-dr-matt-bernstein/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes psychiatrist Dr. Matt Bernstein to explore the emerging field of metabolic psychiatry, the ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: From Wired &amp; Tired to Calm &amp; Clear: My Top Nutrients for Mood, Focus, and Sleep</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/from-wired-tired-to-calm-clear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris explores natural solutions for one of today’s most pressing challenges: chronic stress, anxiety, and...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Science Behind Oral Inflammation, with Dr. William Levine</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-science-behind-oral-inflammation-with-dr-william-levine/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes board-certified periodontist Dr. William Levine to discuss the overlooked role of gum healt...</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hyaluronic Acid: The Deep Hydration Molecule Your Skin Has Been Waiting For</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/hyaluronic-acid-the-deep-hydration-molecule-your-skin-has-been-waiting-for/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>If you’ve spent any time exploring the world of natural skincare, chances are you’ve heard of hyaluronic acid (HA). Once... The post Hyaluronic Acid: ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>