<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 06:05:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Rising food prices linked to childhood stunting and obesity</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-food-prices-linked-childhood-stunting.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>When food prices skyrocket during an economic crisis, it is primarily urban populations and people with low levels of education who are affected. This...</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 20:30:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI model predicts B cell reactivity to neoantigens for improved cancer vaccines</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-ai-cell-reactivity-neoantigens-cancer.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Neoantigens are unique markers that distinguish only cancer cells. By adding B cell reactivity, cancer vaccines can move beyond one-time attacks and s...</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:24:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Combination therapy for Burkitt's lymphoma dramatically improves cure rates in mice</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-combination-therapy-burkitt-lymphoma-mice.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Burkitt's lymphoma is a rare and aggressive blood cancer characterized by a translocation of the MYC gene. It occurs most often in children and young ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 21:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Potential biomarker linked to multiple sclerosis progression and brain inflammation</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-potential-biomarker-linked-multiple-sclerosis.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>A new University of Toronto-led study has discovered a possible biomarker linked to multiple sclerosis (MS) disease progression that could help identi...</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:12:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI detects stomach cancer risk in remote communities from upper endoscopic images</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-ai-stomach-cancer-remote-communities.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>In many regions, doctors practice in settings with limited medical resources. Advanced tests, specialist support, and expert guidance for complex deci...</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 17:13:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Menopause Brain Fog—What’s Really Happening (and How To Fix It)</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rhr-menopause-brain-fog-whats-really-happening-and-how-to-fix-it/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris examines research confirming that menopause-related brain fog is real, measurable, and reversible. H...</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 08:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Seed Oils and Colon Cancer – What the New Research Really Shows</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/seed-oils-and-colon-cancer-what-the-new-research-really-shows/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Seed oils have become one of the most controversial topics in nutrition, especially after a 2024 University of South Florida study linked high omega-6...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 08:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Longevity Trap: Why Chasing Anti-Aging May Be Aging You</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-longevity-trap-why-chasing-anti-aging-may-be-aging-you/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In this episode, Chris explains why obsession with anti-aging hacks may actually undermine our long-term health. He examines the common longevity trap...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Link Between Metabolic Health and Mental Well-Being, with Dr. Matt Bernstein</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-link-between-metabolic-health-and-mental-well-being-with-dr-matt-bernstein/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes psychiatrist Dr. Matt Bernstein to explore the emerging field of metabolic psychiatry, the ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: From Wired &amp; Tired to Calm &amp; Clear: My Top Nutrients for Mood, Focus, and Sleep</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/from-wired-tired-to-calm-clear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris explores natural solutions for one of today’s most pressing challenges: chronic stress, anxiety, and...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>