<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:00:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Q&amp;A: Why weight stigma hits hard in a diet-focused culture</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-qa-weight-stigma-hard-diet.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Every January, it can seem like the pressure to lose weight enters full swing. Ads for diet supplements and weight loss drugs abound. Gyms are full of...</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 20:24:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Q&amp;A: How tumor support cells help lung cancer evade targeted therapy</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-qa-tumor-cells-lung-cancer.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>A study led by researchers at Moffitt Cancer Center found that normal cells surrounding a tumor, known as cancer-associated fibroblasts, can help lung...</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 20:16:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Noninvasive prenatal screening could prevent permanent hearing loss in newborns</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-noninvasive-prenatal-screening-permanent-loss.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>A new study indicates that noninvasive prenatal screening (NIPS) performed using a low-cost form of whole genome sequencing can detect the risk in pre...</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 20:25:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cracking prostate cancer's code: An enzyme's central role in controlling subtypes and improving therapeutic response</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-prostate-cancer-code-enzyme-central.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>A large team of researchers led by Wouter Karthaus, head of the Endocrine Therapy Resistance and Molecular Genetics Lab at EPFL, and Eneda Toska at Jo...</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 20:30:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Community asthma program on Navajo Nation increases care-seeking for children with asthma</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-community-asthma-navajo-nation-children.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>A multiyear community asthma program on the Navajo Nation increased asthma-related care and awareness among families, even as the COVID-19 pandemic dr...</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 20:10:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Menopause Brain Fog—What’s Really Happening (and How To Fix It)</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rhr-menopause-brain-fog-whats-really-happening-and-how-to-fix-it/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris examines research confirming that menopause-related brain fog is real, measurable, and reversible. H...</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 08:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Seed Oils and Colon Cancer – What the New Research Really Shows</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/seed-oils-and-colon-cancer-what-the-new-research-really-shows/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Seed oils have become one of the most controversial topics in nutrition, especially after a 2024 University of South Florida study linked high omega-6...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 08:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Longevity Trap: Why Chasing Anti-Aging May Be Aging You</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-longevity-trap-why-chasing-anti-aging-may-be-aging-you/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>In this episode, Chris explains why obsession with anti-aging hacks may actually undermine our long-term health. He examines the common longevity trap...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Link Between Metabolic Health and Mental Well-Being, with Dr. Matt Bernstein</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-link-between-metabolic-health-and-mental-well-being-with-dr-matt-bernstein/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes psychiatrist Dr. Matt Bernstein to explore the emerging field of metabolic psychiatry, the ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: From Wired &amp; Tired to Calm &amp; Clear: My Top Nutrients for Mood, Focus, and Sleep</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/from-wired-tired-to-calm-clear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris explores natural solutions for one of today’s most pressing challenges: chronic stress, anxiety, and...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>