<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 06:50:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>California braces for early, sharper flu season as virus mutation outpaces vaccine, experts say</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-california-braces-early-sharper-flu.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>California could see an early start to the annual flu season, as a combination of low vaccination rates and late mutations to the virus may leave the ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:50:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is AI making some people delusional? Families and experts are worried</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-ai-people-delusional-families-experts.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Generative artificial intelligence has quickly permeated much of what we do online, proving helpful for many. But for a small minority of the hundreds...</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:39:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A retail approach nudges healthier choices in food relief</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-retail-approach-nudges-healthier-choices.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>A University of Adelaide study, conducted in collaboration with Foodbank SA &amp; NT, has demonstrated that strategies supermarkets commonly use to influe...</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:04:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New study shows why some minds can't switch off at night</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-minds-night.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Australian researchers have found compelling evidence that insomnia may be linked to disruptions in the brain's natural 24-hour rhythm of mental activ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:03:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Nature prescriptions' deliver mental health benefits worth more than four times their cost</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-nature-prescriptions-mental-health-benefits.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Young Australians are struggling. Almost three in 10 are experiencing high psychological distress, nearly a quarter feel lonely most of the time, and ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:41:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Link Between Metabolic Health and Mental Well-Being, with Dr. Matt Bernstein</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-link-between-metabolic-health-and-mental-well-being-with-dr-matt-bernstein/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes psychiatrist Dr. Matt Bernstein to explore the emerging field of metabolic psychiatry, the ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: From Wired &amp; Tired to Calm &amp; Clear: My Top Nutrients for Mood, Focus, and Sleep</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/from-wired-tired-to-calm-clear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris explores natural solutions for one of today’s most pressing challenges: chronic stress, anxiety, and...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Science Behind Oral Inflammation, with Dr. William Levine</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-science-behind-oral-inflammation-with-dr-william-levine/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes board-certified periodontist Dr. William Levine to discuss the overlooked role of gum healt...</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hyaluronic Acid: The Deep Hydration Molecule Your Skin Has Been Waiting For</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/hyaluronic-acid-the-deep-hydration-molecule-your-skin-has-been-waiting-for/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>If you’ve spent any time exploring the world of natural skincare, chances are you’ve heard of hyaluronic acid (HA). Once... The post Hyaluronic Acid: ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rice Ceramides: The Unsung Hero of Skin Hydration and Barrier Health</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rice-ceramides-the-unsung-hero-of-skin-hydration-and-barrier-health/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>We often think of radiant skin as the result of what we put on it: moisturizers, serums, masks. But emerging... The post Rice Ceramides: The Unsung He...</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>