<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 06:54:41 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Who is more likely to get long COVID? New study uncovers genetic drivers behind the disease</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-covid-uncovers-genetic-drivers-disease.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Australian scientists have identified the key genetic drivers behind long COVID, revealing why some people continue to experience debilitating symptom...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 11:41:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Seed Oils and Colon Cancer – What the New Research Really Shows</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/seed-oils-and-colon-cancer-what-the-new-research-really-shows/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Seed oils have become one of the most controversial topics in nutrition, especially after a 2024 University of South Florida study linked high omega-6...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 08:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>COVID-19 leaves a lasting mark on the human brain, MRI techniques reveal</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-covid-human-brain-mri-techniques.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>COVID-19 does not just affect the respiratory system, but also significantly alters the brain in people who have fully recovered from the infectious d...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 11:18:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Digital tools can improve dementia care—for people with dementia aging in place and their caregivers</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-digital-tools-dementia-people-aging.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Digital technology is ever-present in how we operate in daily life, particularly to connect with others. While touted as a suitable alternative in pla...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 11:07:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Experimental microneedle painkiller patch for pigs shows proof of concept</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-experimental-microneedle-painkiller-patch-pigs.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>An experimental pain-relieving drug delivery method for farm animals using microneedle patches may not have delivered an effective dose, but it took a...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 10:53:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Colorectal cancer's immune puzzle cracked: Two Treg cell types shape survival odds</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-colorectal-cancer-immune-puzzle-treg.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In most solid tumors, high numbers of regulatory T (Treg) cells are associated with poorer outcomes because they dampen the immune system's ability to...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 11:46:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Longevity Trap: Why Chasing Anti-Aging May Be Aging You</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-longevity-trap-why-chasing-anti-aging-may-be-aging-you/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode, Chris explains why obsession with anti-aging hacks may actually undermine our long-term health. He examines the common longevity trap...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Link Between Metabolic Health and Mental Well-Being, with Dr. Matt Bernstein</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-link-between-metabolic-health-and-mental-well-being-with-dr-matt-bernstein/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes psychiatrist Dr. Matt Bernstein to explore the emerging field of metabolic psychiatry, the ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: From Wired &amp; Tired to Calm &amp; Clear: My Top Nutrients for Mood, Focus, and Sleep</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/from-wired-tired-to-calm-clear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris explores natural solutions for one of today’s most pressing challenges: chronic stress, anxiety, and...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Science Behind Oral Inflammation, with Dr. William Levine</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-science-behind-oral-inflammation-with-dr-william-levine/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes board-certified periodontist Dr. William Levine to discuss the overlooked role of gum healt...</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>