<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 14:14:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Compound produced by gut bacteria may slow Alzheimer's progression</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-compound-gut-bacteria-alzheimer.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>A compound found in the gut may reduce some of the manifestations of Alzheimer's disease, according to a Northwestern Medicine study published in the ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 18:59:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Surgical outcomes of robotic surgery for kidney stones: a systematic review and meta-analysis from section of YAU and EAU endourology.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/surgical-outcomes-of-robotic-surgery-for-kidney-stones-a-systematic-review-and-meta-analysis-from-section-of-yau-and-eau-endourology/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Urinary tract stone disease is quite common in the population, and treatment modalities are constantly evolving. Technological advancements in endouro...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:31:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Comparison between semi-automatic and manual left atrial strain analysis in patients undergoing CABG: feasibility, reproducibility, and clinical implications.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/comparison-between-semi-automatic-and-manual-left-atrial-strain-analysis-in-patients-undergoing-cabg-feasibility-reproducibility-and-clinical-implications/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Left atrial (LA) strain, a powerful parameter for assessing LA function, is underused in routine clinical practice because it requires expertise and t...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:31:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Minimally invasive surgical techniques (MISTs) for benign prostatic hyperplasia: results from a Delphi consensus project to shed light on controversial topics.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/minimally-invasive-surgical-techniques-mists-for-benign-prostatic-hyperplasia-results-from-a-delphi-consensus-project-to-shed-light-on-controversial-topics/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>To conduct a Delphi consensus in order to address key uncertainties and provide expert insights to bridge the gap between guidelines and real-world pr...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:31:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dorsal- vs ventral-onlay buccal mucosal graft urethroplasty for urethral strictures: a meta-analysis.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/dorsal-vs-ventral-onlay-buccal-mucosal-graft-urethroplasty-for-urethral-strictures-a-meta-analysis/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>To compare ventral- and dorsal-onlay buccal mucosal graft (BMG) urethroplasty in patients with urethral stricture, as the optimal placement of BMG in ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:31:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Study delves into the complexity of the most aggressive form of prostate cancer</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-delves-complexity-aggressive-prostate-cancer.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Cancer cannot be understood as a single, uniform disease. The more we delve into studying each type of tumor, the more we recognize the need to subcla...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 19:13:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stress genes clear dead cells, offering new disease insights</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-stress-genes-dead-cells-disease.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>A new study from The University of Texas at Arlington details a novel strategy for how the body clears out dead cells during stress, revealing unexpec...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 19:11:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Creatine is safe, effective and important for everyone, researcher says</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-creatine-safe-effective-important.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Creatine, the supplement popular with athletes for its ability to help build strength and power, is increasingly being recognized for its broad health...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 18:25:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mouth and gut bacteria linked to brain changes in Parkinson's disease</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-mouth-gut-bacteria-linked-brain.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Scientists have discovered a link between bacteria in the mouth and gut and the progression of cognitive decline in Parkinson's disease. Specific chan...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 19:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Role of MicroRNAs in the Pathogenesis and as Biomarkers for Pediatric Epilepsy: A Systematic Review.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/the-role-of-micrornas-in-the-pathogenesis-and-as-biomarkers-for-pediatric-epilepsy-a-systematic-review/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Epilepsy is highly prevalent among children, making it one of the most common neurological diseases in the pediatric population. Its diagnosis is prob...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 06:31:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Nourishment Table, with Frederic Leroy</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-nourishment-table-with-frederic-leroy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes food scientist and advocate for regenerative agriculture Dr. Frederic Leroy to disc...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Turn ChatGPT Into Your Personal Meal Planner</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/turn-chatgpt-into-your-personal-meal-planner/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Even for someone who lives and breathes nutrition, meal planning can feel like a grind. There are weeks when I... The post Turn ChatGPT Into Your Pers...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:16:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Rediscovering Health, Nature, and Purpose-Driven Business, with Seth Spears</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rediscovering-health-nature-and-purpose-driven-business-with-seth-spears/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes entrepreneur and strategist Seth Spears for a wide-ranging conversation on health, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: How to Sharpen and Protect Your Mind for a Lifetime, with Dale Bredesen</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/how-to-sharpen-and-protect-your-mind-for-a-lifetime-with-dale-bredesen/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes renowned neurologist Dr. Dale Bredesen back to the show for an insightful conversation abou...</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:01:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quality Matters: How to Choose and Use the Best Collagen Supplement</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/quality-matters-how-to-choose-and-use-the-best-collagen-supplement/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Introduction If you’ve been paying attention to health and wellness trends, you’ve likely noticed collagen supplements everywhere—from your local heal...</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:57:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>