<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 11:00:32 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Ultrasensitive liquid biopsy method detects low-frequency cancer mutations</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-ultrasensitive-liquid-biopsy-method-frequency.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Liquid biopsy is increasingly recognized as a promising tool for cancer detection and treatment monitoring, yet its effectiveness is often limited by ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:27:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Holiday season sees spike in impaired driving—alcohol isn't the only culprit, expert says</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-holiday-season-spike-impaired-alcohol.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>December is one of the deadliest months for impaired driving; and according to data from the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration in 2022, D...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:29:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Making waves: Innovative tool transforming beach safety education for migrants</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-tool-beach-safety-migrants.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Despite around 9,000 people being rescued by lifesavers each year, drowning deaths in Australia continue to rise, with 1 in 3 drowning victims born ov...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:18:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Study maps out sleep challenges and solutions in China</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-solutions-china.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>A research team led by Professor Lu Lin from the Peking University (PKU) Sixth Hospital has recently provided a comprehensive overview of sleep health...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:14:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Debates about bullying need to look beyond online safety, say researchers</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-debates-bullying-online-safety.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>New research from the Institute of Psychiatry, Psychology &amp; Neuroscience (IoPPN) at King's College London has found that only 2% of young people who e...</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:17:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Longevity Trap: Why Chasing Anti-Aging May Be Aging You</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-longevity-trap-why-chasing-anti-aging-may-be-aging-you/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>In this episode, Chris explains why obsession with anti-aging hacks may actually undermine our long-term health. He examines the common longevity trap...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Link Between Metabolic Health and Mental Well-Being, with Dr. Matt Bernstein</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-link-between-metabolic-health-and-mental-well-being-with-dr-matt-bernstein/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes psychiatrist Dr. Matt Bernstein to explore the emerging field of metabolic psychiatry, the ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: From Wired &amp; Tired to Calm &amp; Clear: My Top Nutrients for Mood, Focus, and Sleep</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/from-wired-tired-to-calm-clear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris explores natural solutions for one of today’s most pressing challenges: chronic stress, anxiety, and...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Science Behind Oral Inflammation, with Dr. William Levine</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-science-behind-oral-inflammation-with-dr-william-levine/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes board-certified periodontist Dr. William Levine to discuss the overlooked role of gum healt...</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hyaluronic Acid: The Deep Hydration Molecule Your Skin Has Been Waiting For</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/hyaluronic-acid-the-deep-hydration-molecule-your-skin-has-been-waiting-for/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>If you’ve spent any time exploring the world of natural skincare, chances are you’ve heard of hyaluronic acid (HA). Once... The post Hyaluronic Acid: ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>