<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 00:32:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>A media–public disconnect exists on wild meat narratives in central Africa during COVID-19</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-mediapublic-disconnect-wild-meat-narratives.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>A new study published by researchers from the University of Oxford, the Wildlife Conservation Society (WCS), CIFOR-ICRAF, and institutional partners r...</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 05:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Primary Care Semen Analysis May Flag Future Health Risks</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/primary-care-semen-analysis-may-flag-future-health-risks/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Semen analysis may serve as an indicator of overall male health, with abnormal results tied to increased risks for chronic disease, mortality, and can...</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 02:30:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Estrogen May Protect Female Hearts From Hypertension</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/estrogen-may-protect-female-hearts-from-hypertension/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Estrogen increases the levels of the protein annexin-A1 in female mice, suggesting a protective effect against hypertension, according to recent resea...</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 05:00:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Intense, persistent grief linked to nearly double mortality risk over 10 years</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-intense-persistent-grief-linked-mortality.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Grief after the loss of a loved one is a natural response—an inevitable part of living and loving. But in a minority of the bereaved, grief is so over...</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 05:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Models Identify Neurologic Deterioration Risk in Critically Ill Children</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/models-identify-neurologic-deterioration-risk-in-critically-ill-children/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>A machine learning model trained to predict neurologic morbidity in critically ill children outperformed current measures and aided in early intervent...</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:34:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Persistent Corneal Sensitivity May Signal Neuropathic Pain After LASIK</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/persistent-corneal-sensitivity-may-signal-neuropathic-pain-after-lasik/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Following LASIK, patients with dry eye and neuropathic pain experience worse outcomes and distinct nerve changes, which may serve as clues for improvi...</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:44:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Air Pollution Drives Allergic-Type Immune Imbalance &amp; Lung Damage</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/air-pollution-drives-allergic-type-immune-imbalance-lung-damage/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Air pollution may promote asthma and worsen lung diseases by altering immune regulation and increasing oxidative stress, according to recent research ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 03:12:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Research findings could improve outcomes for critically ill patients on ventilators, study finds</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-outcomes-critically-ill-patients-ventilators.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>A seven-year international, multi-center clinical trial led by London Health Sciences Centre Research Institute (LHSCRI) and St. Michael's Hospital, a...</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 21:30:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Long-term exposure to outdoor air pollution linked to increased risk of dementia</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-term-exposure-outdoor-air-pollution.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>An analysis of studies incorporating data from almost 30 million people has highlighted the role that air pollution—including that coming from car exh...</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 23:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FDA approves first cream for treating chronic hand eczema</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-fda-cream-chronic-eczema.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>The U.S. Food and Drug Administration (FDA) has signed off on the first-ever cream specifically approved for treating chronic hand eczema (CHE).</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 21:50:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Mold, Indoor Air Quality, and Clean Breathing, with Michael Rubino</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/mold-indoor-air-quality-and-clean-breathing-with-michael-rubino/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes environmental wellness expert Michael Rubino for an in-depth conversation on the hi...</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 08:01:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Nourishment Table, with Frederic Leroy</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-nourishment-table-with-frederic-leroy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes food scientist and advocate for regenerative agriculture Dr. Frederic Leroy to disc...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Turn ChatGPT Into Your Personal Meal Planner</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/turn-chatgpt-into-your-personal-meal-planner/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Even for someone who lives and breathes nutrition, meal planning can feel like a grind. There are weeks when I... The post Turn ChatGPT Into Your Pers...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:16:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Rediscovering Health, Nature, and Purpose-Driven Business, with Seth Spears</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rediscovering-health-nature-and-purpose-driven-business-with-seth-spears/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes entrepreneur and strategist Seth Spears for a wide-ranging conversation on health, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: How to Sharpen and Protect Your Mind for a Lifetime, with Dale Bredesen</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/how-to-sharpen-and-protect-your-mind-for-a-lifetime-with-dale-bredesen/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes renowned neurologist Dr. Dale Bredesen back to the show for an insightful conversation abou...</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:01:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>