<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 07:05:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>How weight loss benefits the health of your fat tissue</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-weight-loss-benefits-health-fat.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>It is well known that obesity typically leads to inflammation and dysfunction of fat tissue that increases the risk of developing metabolic diseases s...</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 10:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DNA testing of colorectal polyps improves insight into hereditary risks</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-dna-colorectal-polyps-insight-hereditary.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>For 10% of colorectal cancer patients, hereditary factors play a role, with higher percentages among younger patients. Research from Radboud Universit...</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Expanded school-based program linked to lower youth tobacco use rates in California</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-school-based-linked-youth-tobacco.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Researchers from University of California San Diego report that an expanded, school-based tobacco prevention program in California was associated with...</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 10:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TV depictions of Hands-Only CPR are often misleading, research suggests</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-tv-depictions-cpr.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>TV depictions of out-of-hospital cardiac arrest may mislead viewers about who is most likely to need cardiopulmonary resuscitation (CPR) and where it'...</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 10:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ADRIATIC clinical trial results suggest durvalumab may offer a new path in small cell lung cancer care</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-adriatic-clinical-trial-results-durvalumab.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>A new study suggests that the immune checkpoint inhibitor, durvalumab, may offer new treatment options for patients living with small cell lung cancer...</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:33:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Menopause Brain Fog—What’s Really Happening (and How To Fix It)</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rhr-menopause-brain-fog-whats-really-happening-and-how-to-fix-it/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris examines research confirming that menopause-related brain fog is real, measurable, and reversible. H...</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 08:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Seed Oils and Colon Cancer – What the New Research Really Shows</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/seed-oils-and-colon-cancer-what-the-new-research-really-shows/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Seed oils have become one of the most controversial topics in nutrition, especially after a 2024 University of South Florida study linked high omega-6...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 08:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Longevity Trap: Why Chasing Anti-Aging May Be Aging You</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-longevity-trap-why-chasing-anti-aging-may-be-aging-you/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>In this episode, Chris explains why obsession with anti-aging hacks may actually undermine our long-term health. He examines the common longevity trap...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Link Between Metabolic Health and Mental Well-Being, with Dr. Matt Bernstein</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-link-between-metabolic-health-and-mental-well-being-with-dr-matt-bernstein/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes psychiatrist Dr. Matt Bernstein to explore the emerging field of metabolic psychiatry, the ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: From Wired &amp; Tired to Calm &amp; Clear: My Top Nutrients for Mood, Focus, and Sleep</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/from-wired-tired-to-calm-clear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris explores natural solutions for one of today’s most pressing challenges: chronic stress, anxiety, and...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>