<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 07:15:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Digital therapy shows promise as a treatment for female sexual dysfunction</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-02-digital-therapy-treatment-female-sexual.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Sexual dysfunction is a reality for many women, but the subject remains taboo. A large percentage of women remain untreated, a problem that is exacerb...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 10:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Celtic curse' genetic disease hotspots revealed in UK and Ireland</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-02-celtic-curse-genetic-disease-hotspots.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>People from the Outer Hebrides and north-west Ireland have the highest risk of developing a genetic disease that causes a dangerous build-up of iron i...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 10:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Faced with common heart failure symptoms, most young adults wouldn't seek care</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-02-common-heart-failure-symptoms-young.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Alex Balmes' symptoms were uncommon for a 32-year-old—irregular heartbeat, fatigue, shortness of breath, bloating, unexpected weight gain.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:09:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A new way to communicate with neurons using focused ultrasound stimulation</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-02-communicate-neurons-focused-ultrasound.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>I still vividly remember the first time we observed neurons responding not to audible sound, but to concentrated, precisely calibrated ultrasonic puls...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Single-shot HIV vaccine candidate induces neutralizing antibodies for the first time</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-02-shot-hiv-vaccine-candidate-neutralizing.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Scientists at The Wistar Institute have developed an HIV vaccine candidate that achieves something never before observed in the field: inducing neutra...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:36:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Cold Exposure: Why Sustained Beats Extreme</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/cold-exposure-why-sustained-beats-extreme/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Cold plunges and ice baths dominate social media, but do they really deliver the best metabolic benefits? In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 08:03:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Why Your Sleep Schedule Matters As Much As Duration</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/why-your-sleep-schedule-matters-as-much-as-duration/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris challenges the conventional focus on sleep duration and makes the case that sleep timing and circadi...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 08:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Menopause Brain Fog—What’s Really Happening (and How To Fix It)</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rhr-menopause-brain-fog-whats-really-happening-and-how-to-fix-it/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris examines research confirming that menopause-related brain fog is real, measurable, and reversible. H...</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 08:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Seed Oils and Colon Cancer – What the New Research Really Shows</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/seed-oils-and-colon-cancer-what-the-new-research-really-shows/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Seed oils have become one of the most controversial topics in nutrition, especially after a 2024 University of South Florida study linked high omega-6...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 08:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Longevity Trap: Why Chasing Anti-Aging May Be Aging You</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-longevity-trap-why-chasing-anti-aging-may-be-aging-you/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In this episode, Chris explains why obsession with anti-aging hacks may actually undermine our long-term health. He examines the common longevity trap...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>