<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:03:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Strategies to keep drug discovery research alive in the US despite funding cuts</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-strategies-drug-discovery-alive-funding.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In the face of US federal funding cuts, biomedical researchers propose strategies for continued progress in drug discovery. Publishing in Trends in Ph...</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 16:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New federal loan caps could disrupt the medical field</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-federal-loan-caps-disrupt-medical.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Researchers from the Harvard Pilgrim Health Care Institute have produced the first national estimate of how many medical students would be affected by...</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 16:00:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Cognitive Legos' help the brain build complex behaviors</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-cognitive-legos-brain-complex-behaviors.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Artificial intelligence may write award-winning essays and diagnose disease with remarkable accuracy, but biological brains still hold the upper hand ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 16:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why watching someone get hurt on screen makes you wince: How the brain triggers echoes of touch sensation</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-screen-wince-brain-triggers-echoes.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>If watching Robert De Niro ordering hammer-based retribution on a cheat's hand in "Casino" instinctively made you wince, you are not alone. Many peopl...</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 16:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How the brain decides what to remember: Study reveals sequentially operating molecular 'timers'</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-brain-reveals-sequentially-molecular-timers.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Every day, our brains transform quick impressions, flashes of inspiration, and painful moments into enduring memories that underpin our sense of self ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 16:00:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Link Between Metabolic Health and Mental Well-Being, with Dr. Matt Bernstein</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-link-between-metabolic-health-and-mental-well-being-with-dr-matt-bernstein/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes psychiatrist Dr. Matt Bernstein to explore the emerging field of metabolic psychiatry, the ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: From Wired &amp; Tired to Calm &amp; Clear: My Top Nutrients for Mood, Focus, and Sleep</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/from-wired-tired-to-calm-clear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris explores natural solutions for one of today’s most pressing challenges: chronic stress, anxiety, and...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Science Behind Oral Inflammation, with Dr. William Levine</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-science-behind-oral-inflammation-with-dr-william-levine/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes board-certified periodontist Dr. William Levine to discuss the overlooked role of gum healt...</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hyaluronic Acid: The Deep Hydration Molecule Your Skin Has Been Waiting For</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/hyaluronic-acid-the-deep-hydration-molecule-your-skin-has-been-waiting-for/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>If you’ve spent any time exploring the world of natural skincare, chances are you’ve heard of hyaluronic acid (HA). Once... The post Hyaluronic Acid: ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rice Ceramides: The Unsung Hero of Skin Hydration and Barrier Health</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rice-ceramides-the-unsung-hero-of-skin-hydration-and-barrier-health/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>We often think of radiant skin as the result of what we put on it: moisturizers, serums, masks. But emerging... The post Rice Ceramides: The Unsung He...</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>