<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:40:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Q&amp;A: Medical negligence in Nigeria—what's known, and what needs to be done</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-qa-medical-negligence-nigeria.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Medical negligence in Nigeria came to the fore when author Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie accused a Lagos hospital of negligence after the death of one of h...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:13:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Memory training technique may help lower stress by shifting recall patterns</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-memory-technique-stress-shifting-recall.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Our minds have a tendency to latch onto negative experiences more strongly than positive ones. While occasional negative thoughts are a common human e...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:04:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Physical therapy research highlights the toll of arthritis on the workforce, as well as the path forward</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-physical-therapy-highlights-toll-arthritis.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>According to new research from the University of Delaware, nearly 40% of American adults ages 18 to 64 with arthritis—almost 10 million people—say the...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:56:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Q&amp;A: Vicious cycle? How gum disease and rheumatoid arthritis feed off one another</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-qa-vicious-gum-disease-rheumatoid.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>It's well established that gum disease and rheumatoid arthritis (RA) are strongly linked. But what wasn't known, until a recent study, was that the tw...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:06:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Exposure to wildfire smoke late in pregnancy may raise autism risk in children</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-exposure-wildfire-late-pregnancy-autism.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Exposure to wildfire smoke during the final months of pregnancy may raise the risk that a child is later diagnosed with autism, according to a new stu...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Why Your Sleep Schedule Matters As Much As Duration</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/why-your-sleep-schedule-matters-as-much-as-duration/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris challenges the conventional focus on sleep duration and makes the case that sleep timing and circadi...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 08:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Menopause Brain Fog—What’s Really Happening (and How To Fix It)</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rhr-menopause-brain-fog-whats-really-happening-and-how-to-fix-it/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris examines research confirming that menopause-related brain fog is real, measurable, and reversible. H...</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 08:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Seed Oils and Colon Cancer – What the New Research Really Shows</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/seed-oils-and-colon-cancer-what-the-new-research-really-shows/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Seed oils have become one of the most controversial topics in nutrition, especially after a 2024 University of South Florida study linked high omega-6...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 08:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Longevity Trap: Why Chasing Anti-Aging May Be Aging You</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-longevity-trap-why-chasing-anti-aging-may-be-aging-you/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>In this episode, Chris explains why obsession with anti-aging hacks may actually undermine our long-term health. He examines the common longevity trap...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Link Between Metabolic Health and Mental Well-Being, with Dr. Matt Bernstein</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-link-between-metabolic-health-and-mental-well-being-with-dr-matt-bernstein/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes psychiatrist Dr. Matt Bernstein to explore the emerging field of metabolic psychiatry, the ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>