<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 06:37:03 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Pancreatic insulin disruption triggers bipolar disorder-like behaviors in mice, study shows</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-pancreatic-insulin-disruption-triggers-bipolar.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Bipolar disorder is a psychiatric disorder characterized by alternating episodes of depression (i.e., low mood and a loss of interest in everyday acti...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 11:30:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Evaluating chatbot accuracy in the fast-changing blood cancer field</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-09-chatbot-accuracy-fast-blood-cancer.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Patients are increasingly turning to AI for medical information and even advice, but how should they approach using AI-powered services? A new study p...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 11:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Customizable protein helps body remove harmful cells, offering hope for cancer and autoimmune diseases</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-09-customizable-protein-body-cells-cancer.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>A team of scientists at Kyoto University's Institute for Integrated Cell-Material Sciences (iCeMS) has created a protein-based therapeutic tool that c...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gaming to socialize or escape? Research scopes out problematic gaming habits</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-09-gaming-socialize-scopes-problematic-habits.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>People who have autistic-like traits, but who fall short of a clinical diagnosis, are at risk of problematic gaming, according to a new Charles Darwin...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 11:05:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hysterectomy with bilateral oophorectomy may increase risk of stroke</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-09-hysterectomy-bilateral-oophorectomy.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Given the seriousness and increased frequency of strokes, many studies have been conducted to assess the relationship between hysterectomy and/or bila...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:02:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rice Ceramides: The Unsung Hero of Skin Hydration and Barrier Health</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rice-ceramides-the-unsung-hero-of-skin-hydration-and-barrier-health/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>We often think of radiant skin as the result of what we put on it: moisturizers, serums, masks. But emerging... The post Rice Ceramides: The Unsung He...</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lutein and Zeaxanthin: The Carotenoids That Protect and Perfect Your Skin from Within</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/lutein-and-zeaxanthin-the-carotenoids-that-protect-and-perfect-your-skin-from-within/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>When most people think of lutein and zeaxanthin, they picture eye health supplements or leafy green vegetables. But these vibrant... The post Lutein a...</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:00:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vitamin C: The Collagen-Stimulating, Skin-Brightening Antioxidant Your Skin Can’t Live Without</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/vitamin-c-the-collagen-stimulating-skin-brightening-antioxidant-your-skin-cant-live-without/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>When it comes to supporting skin health from the inside out, few nutrients are as essential—or as well-researched—as vitamin C.... The post Vitamin C:...</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 16:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eggshell Membrane Collagen: A Natural Ally for Skin, Hair, and Nail Vitality</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/eggshell-membrane-collagen-a-natural-ally-for-skin-hair-and-nail-vitality/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>In the growing world of natural beauty and inside-out skincare, few ingredients offer the versatility and clinical backing of eggshell... The post Egg...</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biotin: The Essential Nutrient for Stronger Hair and Healthier Nails</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/biotin-the-essential-nutrient-for-stronger-hair-and-healthier-nails/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>If you’ve ever scanned the beauty aisle or browsed wellness forums, you’ve probably seen biotin pop up again and again... The post Biotin: The Essenti...</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:37:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>