<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 06:42:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Quick CPR from lay rescuers can nearly double survival for children after cardiac arrest</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-quick-cpr-lay-rescuers-survival.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Cardiopulmonary resuscitation (CPR) performed within five minutes of a child's heart stopping nearly doubled their chances of survival, according to p...</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 10:00:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Low-dose aspirin linked to lower cardiovascular event risk for adults with type 2 diabetes</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-dose-aspirin-linked-cardiovascular-event.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>People with type 2 diabetes (T2D) and an elevated risk for cardiovascular disease (CVD) who took low-dose aspirin were less likely to experience a maj...</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 10:00:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Long-term use of melatonin supplements to support sleep may have negative heart health effects</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-term-melatonin-supplements-negative-heart.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Long-term use of melatonin supplements, often used to promote sleep and address insomnia, is associated with a higher risk of heart failure diagnosis,...</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 10:00:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Optimal cardiovascular health among people with type 2 diabetes may offset dementia risk</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-optimal-cardiovascular-health-people-diabetes.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Having optimal cardiovascular health may offset the risk of developing mild cognitive impairment and dementia for people with type 2 diabetes (T2D), e...</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 10:00:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Assessing heart-pumping glitch may reduce stroke risk in adults with heart muscle disease</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-heart-glitch-adults-muscle-disease.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>A hidden atrial dysfunction may raise stroke risk in people with transthyretin amyloid cardiomyopathy (ATTR-CM); however, a noninvasive assessment too...</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 10:00:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: From Wired &amp; Tired to Calm &amp; Clear: My Top Nutrients for Mood, Focus, and Sleep</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/from-wired-tired-to-calm-clear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris explores natural solutions for one of today’s most pressing challenges: chronic stress, anxiety, and...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Science Behind Oral Inflammation, with Dr. William Levine</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-science-behind-oral-inflammation-with-dr-william-levine/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes board-certified periodontist Dr. William Levine to discuss the overlooked role of gum healt...</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hyaluronic Acid: The Deep Hydration Molecule Your Skin Has Been Waiting For</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/hyaluronic-acid-the-deep-hydration-molecule-your-skin-has-been-waiting-for/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>If you’ve spent any time exploring the world of natural skincare, chances are you’ve heard of hyaluronic acid (HA). Once... The post Hyaluronic Acid: ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rice Ceramides: The Unsung Hero of Skin Hydration and Barrier Health</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rice-ceramides-the-unsung-hero-of-skin-hydration-and-barrier-health/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>We often think of radiant skin as the result of what we put on it: moisturizers, serums, masks. But emerging... The post Rice Ceramides: The Unsung He...</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lutein and Zeaxanthin: The Carotenoids That Protect and Perfect Your Skin from Within</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/lutein-and-zeaxanthin-the-carotenoids-that-protect-and-perfect-your-skin-from-within/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>When most people think of lutein and zeaxanthin, they picture eye health supplements or leafy green vegetables. But these vibrant... The post Lutein a...</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:00:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>