<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 17:52:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Food insecurity linked to tumor growth in pediatric neuroblastoma</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-food-insecurity-linked-tumor-growth.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Neuroblastoma remains one of the deadliest childhood malignancies, accounting for a disproportionate number of pediatric cancer deaths worldwide.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 22:22:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quantifying the intensity of emotional response to sound, images and touch through skin conductance</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-quantifying-intensity-emotional-response-images.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>When we listen to a moving piece of music or feel the gentle pulse of a haptic vibration, our bodies react before we consciously register the feeling....</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 21:55:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FDA approves Caplyta for major depressive disorder in adults</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-fda-caplyta-major-depressive-disorder.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>The U.S. Food and Drug Administration has approved Caplyta (lumateperone) as an adjunctive therapy with antidepressants for the treatment of major dep...</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 22:11:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Could psychotherapy work by changing how we navigate our own minds?</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-psychotherapy-minds.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>The stereotypical image of psychotherapy shows a patient lying on a couch, exploring their deepest traumas. This leads to awareness of unconscious hab...</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 22:18:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FDA approves Darzalex Faspro for high-risk smoldering multiple myeloma</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-fda-darzalex-faspro-high-smoldering.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>The U.S. Food and Drug Administration has approved Darzalex Faspro (daratumumab and hyaluronidase-fihj) as a single-agent treatment for adult patients...</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 22:12:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: From Wired &amp; Tired to Calm &amp; Clear: My Top Nutrients for Mood, Focus, and Sleep</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/from-wired-tired-to-calm-clear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris explores natural solutions for one of today’s most pressing challenges: chronic stress, anxiety, and...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Science Behind Oral Inflammation, with Dr. William Levine</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-science-behind-oral-inflammation-with-dr-william-levine/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes board-certified periodontist Dr. William Levine to discuss the overlooked role of gum healt...</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hyaluronic Acid: The Deep Hydration Molecule Your Skin Has Been Waiting For</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/hyaluronic-acid-the-deep-hydration-molecule-your-skin-has-been-waiting-for/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>If you’ve spent any time exploring the world of natural skincare, chances are you’ve heard of hyaluronic acid (HA). Once... The post Hyaluronic Acid: ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rice Ceramides: The Unsung Hero of Skin Hydration and Barrier Health</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rice-ceramides-the-unsung-hero-of-skin-hydration-and-barrier-health/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>We often think of radiant skin as the result of what we put on it: moisturizers, serums, masks. But emerging... The post Rice Ceramides: The Unsung He...</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lutein and Zeaxanthin: The Carotenoids That Protect and Perfect Your Skin from Within</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/lutein-and-zeaxanthin-the-carotenoids-that-protect-and-perfect-your-skin-from-within/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>When most people think of lutein and zeaxanthin, they picture eye health supplements or leafy green vegetables. But these vibrant... The post Lutein a...</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:00:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>