<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 01:19:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Suzetrigine for Acute Pain Shows Promise Amid Data Gaps: ICER</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/suzetrigine-for-acute-pain-shows-promise-amid-data-gaps-icer/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Suzetrigine offers a “promising but inconclusive” net health benefit for acute pain treatment versus nonsystemic therapy, opioids, and NSAIDs. The pos...</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:29:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Calprotectin Tied to 90-Day Mortality in ED Patients With Acute Dyspnea</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/calprotectin-tied-to-90-day-mortality-in-ed-patients-with-acute-dyspnea/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Research shows that in patients presenting to the emergency department with acute dyspnea, increased calprotectin was associated with 90-day mortality...</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 03:52:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mixed Clinician Feedback Highlights Gains, Gaps in AI Scribe Technology</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/mixed-clinician-feedback-highlights-gains-gaps-in-ai-scribe-technology/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Physician feedback indicates that AI scribes ease workload and burnout, but respondents cited concerns with accuracy and the need for more inclusive f...</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:46:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Modified Thoracoplasty Enables Successful Oversized Heart Transplant in Toddler</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/modified-thoracoplasty-enables-successful-oversized-heart-transplant-in-toddler/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Surgeons performed chest reconstruction to enable an oversized heart transplant in a toddler, and 25-year follow-up shows the patient is healthy and a...</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 00:54:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Recharging the Healer: Why Physicians Must Unplug</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/recharging-the-healer-why-physicians-must-unplug/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Dr. Alex McDonald discusses the importance of self-care in addressing physician burnout and shares evidence-based physician wellness strategies. The p...</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 04:47:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Annual UK cost of PTSD likely tops £40 billion, cost analysis reveals</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-annual-uk-ptsd-tops-billion.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>The annual UK cost of the mental health disorder PTSD is likely to top £40 billion, but the figures are based on 2020–1 prevalence rates—the most rece...</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 23:30:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Novel analysis identifies differences between benign and cancerous breast calcifications</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-analysis-differences-benign-cancerous-breast.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Benign and cancerous calcium phosphate deposits that may look identical on a mammogram have distinct differences in their structures and formation pro...</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 20:30:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Study identifies social steps to mitigate mental illness</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-social-mitigate-mental-illness.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Mental illnesses are thought to be caused by both biological and environmental factors in complex interaction. Among the environmental contributors ar...</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 20:31:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Risk for dementia, ischemic stroke, mortality lower with GLP-1 receptor agonists in type 2 diabetes, obesity</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-dementia-ischemic-mortality-glp-receptor.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>For adults with type 2 diabetes and obesity, glucagon-like peptide 1 receptor agonists (GLP-1 RAs) are associated with a lower risk for dementia, stro...</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 21:20:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GLP-1 diabetes drugs likely trump metformin for curbing dementia risk in type 2 diabetes, study finds</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-glp-diabetes-drugs-trump-metformin.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>GLP-1 receptor agonists, a class of drug used to treat type 2 diabetes, likely trump the widely prescribed metformin for curbing dementia risk in peop...</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 23:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Mold, Indoor Air Quality, and Clean Breathing, with Michael Rubino</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/mold-indoor-air-quality-and-clean-breathing-with-michael-rubino/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes environmental wellness expert Michael Rubino for an in-depth conversation on the hi...</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 08:01:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Nourishment Table, with Frederic Leroy</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-nourishment-table-with-frederic-leroy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes food scientist and advocate for regenerative agriculture Dr. Frederic Leroy to disc...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Turn ChatGPT Into Your Personal Meal Planner</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/turn-chatgpt-into-your-personal-meal-planner/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Even for someone who lives and breathes nutrition, meal planning can feel like a grind. There are weeks when I... The post Turn ChatGPT Into Your Pers...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:16:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Rediscovering Health, Nature, and Purpose-Driven Business, with Seth Spears</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rediscovering-health-nature-and-purpose-driven-business-with-seth-spears/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes entrepreneur and strategist Seth Spears for a wide-ranging conversation on health, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: How to Sharpen and Protect Your Mind for a Lifetime, with Dale Bredesen</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/how-to-sharpen-and-protect-your-mind-for-a-lifetime-with-dale-bredesen/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes renowned neurologist Dr. Dale Bredesen back to the show for an insightful conversation abou...</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:01:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>