<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 11:00:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Quitting smoking is associated with recovery from other addictions</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-recovery-addictions.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Adults who smoke cigarettes and are addicted to alcohol or other drugs were more likely to achieve sustained remission of their substance use disorder...</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 16:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Counties with low rates of cervical cancer screening see higher rates of incidence and death</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-counties-cervical-cancer-screening-higher.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Women in counties with repeatedly lower cervical cancer screening rates suffer nearly double the rate of cervical cancer diagnoses, particularly of la...</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 16:00:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Running is a substance-free pleasure that supports addiction recovery</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-substance-free-pleasure-addiction-recovery.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Addiction is a widespread health issue that will affect about 1 in 5 Canadians over their lifetimes. For example, addiction to opioids has led to opio...</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 15:54:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Two-dose therapy for S. aureus bloodstream infections on par with standard treatment</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-dose-therapy-aureus-bloodstream-infections.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>A National Institutes of Health (NIH)-supported clinical trial has found that the outcome of treating complicated Staphylococcus aureus bloodstream in...</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 16:00:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blood-based diagnostic biosensor developed to detect PTSD</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-blood-based-diagnostic-biosensor-ptsd.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Researchers at the University of Tennessee, Knoxville's Tickle College of Engineering and UT Institute of Agriculture are partnering with technology d...</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 15:59:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Beauty From Within – Why Radiant Skin, Hair, and Nails Start Inside</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/beauty-from-within-why-radiant-skin-hair-and-nails-start-inside/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, we dive deep into the topic of beauty from within, exploring why radiant skin, hair, and nails truly start...</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 08:01:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Mold, Indoor Air Quality, and Clean Breathing, with Michael Rubino</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/mold-indoor-air-quality-and-clean-breathing-with-michael-rubino/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes environmental wellness expert Michael Rubino for an in-depth conversation on the hi...</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 08:01:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Nourishment Table, with Frederic Leroy</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-nourishment-table-with-frederic-leroy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes food scientist and advocate for regenerative agriculture Dr. Frederic Leroy to disc...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Turn ChatGPT Into Your Personal Meal Planner</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/turn-chatgpt-into-your-personal-meal-planner/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Even for someone who lives and breathes nutrition, meal planning can feel like a grind. There are weeks when I... The post Turn ChatGPT Into Your Pers...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:16:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Rediscovering Health, Nature, and Purpose-Driven Business, with Seth Spears</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rediscovering-health-nature-and-purpose-driven-business-with-seth-spears/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes entrepreneur and strategist Seth Spears for a wide-ranging conversation on health, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>