<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:33 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Pain med side effects may be masquerading as heart failure</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-pain-med-side-effects-masquerading.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Clinicians may fail to recognize common side effects of drugs like gabapentin—which are frequently prescribed for nerve pain—leading them to prescribe...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Taking a drug like Ozempic? What you need to know about risks of suicidal thoughts and contraception failure</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-drug-ozempic-suicidal-thoughts-contraception.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>The rise of GLP-1 drugs such as Ozempic and Mounjaro has been nothing short of meteoric. Originally developed to treat diabetes, these drugs are now w...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 15:57:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>For those living with dementia, new study suggests shingles vaccine could slow the disease</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-dementia-shingles-vaccine-disease.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>An unusual public health policy in Wales may have produced the strongest evidence yet that a vaccine can reduce the risk of dementia. In a new study l...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:00:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Contraceptive pills may affect women's mental health</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-contraceptive-pills-affect-women-mental.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>The contraceptive pill has been hailed as one of the most revolutionary health technologies of the 20th century—a tool that gave women control over th...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 15:56:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Longevity Trap: Why Chasing Anti-Aging May Be Aging You</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-longevity-trap-why-chasing-anti-aging-may-be-aging-you/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In this episode, Chris explains why obsession with anti-aging hacks may actually undermine our long-term health. He examines the common longevity trap...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rising complexity in pediatric patients is reshaping hospital care</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-complexity-pediatric-patients-reshaping-hospital.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>A new national analysis shows that over the past two decades, inpatient care for children with complex chronic conditions (CCCs) has become far more i...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Link Between Metabolic Health and Mental Well-Being, with Dr. Matt Bernstein</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-link-between-metabolic-health-and-mental-well-being-with-dr-matt-bernstein/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes psychiatrist Dr. Matt Bernstein to explore the emerging field of metabolic psychiatry, the ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: From Wired &amp; Tired to Calm &amp; Clear: My Top Nutrients for Mood, Focus, and Sleep</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/from-wired-tired-to-calm-clear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris explores natural solutions for one of today’s most pressing challenges: chronic stress, anxiety, and...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Science Behind Oral Inflammation, with Dr. William Levine</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-science-behind-oral-inflammation-with-dr-william-levine/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes board-certified periodontist Dr. William Levine to discuss the overlooked role of gum healt...</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hyaluronic Acid: The Deep Hydration Molecule Your Skin Has Been Waiting For</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/hyaluronic-acid-the-deep-hydration-molecule-your-skin-has-been-waiting-for/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>If you’ve spent any time exploring the world of natural skincare, chances are you’ve heard of hyaluronic acid (HA). Once... The post Hyaluronic Acid: ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>