<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:59:01 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Two in five cancers worldwide are likely preventable, says new research</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-02-cancers-worldwide.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Nearly 40% of new cancer cases worldwide in 2022 may be associated with modifiable risk factors, according to an analysis of 36 cancer types from 185 ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 22:20:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When suicidal calls come in, who answers? Georgia crisis line response rates reveal gaps</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-02-suicidal-georgia-crisis-line-response.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Kaitlin Cooke of Cartersville, Georgia, was contemplating suicide when she started calling a statewide mental health crisis line in 2018. She said she...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 22:40:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Four out of every 10 cancer cases are preventable: WHO</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-02-cancer-cases.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Nearly four out of every 10 cancer cases could be prevented if people avoided a range of risk factors including smoking, drinking, air pollution and c...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 22:40:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pregnancy, breastfeeding associated with higher levels of cognitive function for postmenopausal women</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-02-pregnancy-breastfeeding-higher-cognitive-function.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Female brains have historically evolved to adapt to pregnancy, undergoing structural and functional changes. But the cognitive health implications of ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:42:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Q&amp;A: Cannabis usage in middle-aged, older adults linked to larger brain volume, better cognitive function</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-02-qa-cannabis-usage-middle-aged.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Research studying the effects of cannabis on the brain has often focused on adolescents, but a new study from CU Anschutz researchers looks at populat...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:38:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Cold Exposure: Why Sustained Beats Extreme</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/cold-exposure-why-sustained-beats-extreme/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Cold plunges and ice baths dominate social media, but do they really deliver the best metabolic benefits? In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 08:03:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Why Your Sleep Schedule Matters As Much As Duration</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/why-your-sleep-schedule-matters-as-much-as-duration/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris challenges the conventional focus on sleep duration and makes the case that sleep timing and circadi...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 08:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Menopause Brain Fog—What’s Really Happening (and How To Fix It)</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rhr-menopause-brain-fog-whats-really-happening-and-how-to-fix-it/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris examines research confirming that menopause-related brain fog is real, measurable, and reversible. H...</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 08:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Seed Oils and Colon Cancer – What the New Research Really Shows</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/seed-oils-and-colon-cancer-what-the-new-research-really-shows/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Seed oils have become one of the most controversial topics in nutrition, especially after a 2024 University of South Florida study linked high omega-6...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 08:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Longevity Trap: Why Chasing Anti-Aging May Be Aging You</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-longevity-trap-why-chasing-anti-aging-may-be-aging-you/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>In this episode, Chris explains why obsession with anti-aging hacks may actually undermine our long-term health. He examines the common longevity trap...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>