<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:35:22 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>A machine learning tool can help with diagnosing, monitoring colorectal cancer</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-05-machine-tool-colorectal-cancer.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Scientists aiming to advance cancer diagnostics have developed a machine learning tool that is able to identify metabolism-related molecular profile d...</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 19:24:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Silent Myocardial Ischemia Found in More Than 37% of Patients With Diabetes</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/silent-myocardial-ischemia-found-in-more-than-37-of-patients-with-diabetes/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Research found that 37.65% of adults with diabetes had silent myocardial ischemia, with poor glycemic control, smoking, and long disease duration as k...</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:43:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Exercise and eat your veggies: Experts warn against privileged heart disease prevention strategies</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-05-veggies-experts-privileged-heart-disease.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>A leading cardiovascular disease researcher from Simon Fraser University is ringing the alarm on universal recommendations intended to improve heart h...</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:41:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Q&amp;A: Gene Therapy for Neurologic Disorders</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/qa-gene-therapy-for-neurologic-disorders/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Deepa Soundara Rajan, MD, and Jennifer L. Gannon, MD, discuss the current state of gene therapy for treating neurologic disorders. The post Q&amp;A: Gene ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:26:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Migraine Preventative Therapy Shows Real-World Rapid Relief, Safety</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/migraine-preventative-therapy-shows-real-world-rapid-relief-safety/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Atogepant proved effective, safe, and well-tolerated in refractory high-frequency episodic migraine and chronic migraine, according to a recent study....</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:06:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Got knee pain? Stimulating the vagus nerve through the ear may help</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-05-knee-pain-vagus-nerve-ear.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Tying shoelaces, getting into a car, picking things up off the floor and walking down stairs all involve flexing that most difficult of joints: the kn...</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 19:33:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Race-Neutral VBAC Tool Doesn’t Eliminate Outcome Disparities</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/race-neutral-vbac-tool-doesnt-eliminate-outcome-disparities/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>The removal of race and ethnicity from a vaginal birth after cesarean calculator did not impact labor or VBAC rates among certain racial and ethnic gr...</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:37:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RSV infections in children requiring primary care lead to significant economic impact</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-05-rsv-infections-children-requiring-primary.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Infections from respiratory syncytial virus (RSV) in children requiring primary care led to significant societal economic costs from outpatient treatm...</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:50:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Annual Flu Vaccine Cuts Severe Outcomes in Children by Over 50%</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/annual-flu-vaccine-cuts-severe-outcomes-in-children-by-over-50/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>The overall efficacy of the influenza vaccine is 55.7% for preventing influenza-related emergency visits or hospitalizations among children of all age...</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:53:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Viral mechanism uses mitochondrial remodeling to block immune response, presenting a new drug target</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-05-viral-mechanism-mitochondrial-remodeling-block.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Researchers at The Wistar Institute have identified a previously unknown mechanism by which viruses can reprogram mitochondrial structure to silence i...</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 19:25:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Turn ChatGPT Into Your Personal Meal Planner</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/turn-chatgpt-into-your-personal-meal-planner/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Even for someone who lives and breathes nutrition, meal planning can feel like a grind. There are weeks when I... The post Turn ChatGPT Into Your Pers...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:16:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Rediscovering Health, Nature, and Purpose-Driven Business, with Seth Spears</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rediscovering-health-nature-and-purpose-driven-business-with-seth-spears/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes entrepreneur and strategist Seth Spears for a wide-ranging conversation on health, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: How to Sharpen and Protect Your Mind for a Lifetime, with Dale Bredesen</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/how-to-sharpen-and-protect-your-mind-for-a-lifetime-with-dale-bredesen/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes renowned neurologist Dr. Dale Bredesen back to the show for an insightful conversation abou...</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:01:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quality Matters: How to Choose and Use the Best Collagen Supplement</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/quality-matters-how-to-choose-and-use-the-best-collagen-supplement/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Introduction If you’ve been paying attention to health and wellness trends, you’ve likely noticed collagen supplements everywhere—from your local heal...</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:57:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Collagen: The Essential Building Block for Strong Joints and Bones</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/collagen-the-essential-building-block-for-strong-joints-and-bones/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>The Foundation of Your Musculoskeletal System If you’ve ever winced going down stairs, felt that telltale morning stiffness, or worried... The post Co...</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 13:31:22 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>