<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 07:15:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Before the party starts: Parental attitudes linked to college binge drinking</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-party-parental-attitudes-linked-college.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>College students who binge drink may be acting on influences they brought from home, a new Washington State University-led study suggests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 11:54:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trying to move more? Expert explains the benefits of counting steps</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-expert-benefits.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Mackenzie Long, a personal trainer in physical therapy and sports medicine at the Mayo Clinic Health System in La Crosse and Onalaska, Wisconsin, expl...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 10:04:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Brainquake' phenomenon links psychotic states to chaotic information flow</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-brainquake-phenomenon-links-psychotic-states.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Some psychiatric disorders, particularly schizophrenia and bipolar disorder (BP), can prompt the emergence of so-called psychotic states, mental state...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 12:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Short and irregular weekday sleep disrupts glucose regulation even after weekend sleep recovery, study reveals</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-short-irregular-weekday-disrupts-glucose.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Researchers at the Yong Loo Lin School of Medicine, National University of Singapore (NUS Medicine), have found that insufficient weekday sleep signif...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 10:27:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ultrasound pinpoints vascular complications from cosmetic fillers</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-ultrasound-vascular-complications-cosmetic-fillers.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Ultrasound can aid in treating complications from cosmetic filler injections, according to research being presented at the annual meeting of the Radio...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 10:35:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Longevity Trap: Why Chasing Anti-Aging May Be Aging You</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-longevity-trap-why-chasing-anti-aging-may-be-aging-you/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>In this episode, Chris explains why obsession with anti-aging hacks may actually undermine our long-term health. He examines the common longevity trap...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Link Between Metabolic Health and Mental Well-Being, with Dr. Matt Bernstein</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-link-between-metabolic-health-and-mental-well-being-with-dr-matt-bernstein/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes psychiatrist Dr. Matt Bernstein to explore the emerging field of metabolic psychiatry, the ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: From Wired &amp; Tired to Calm &amp; Clear: My Top Nutrients for Mood, Focus, and Sleep</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/from-wired-tired-to-calm-clear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris explores natural solutions for one of today’s most pressing challenges: chronic stress, anxiety, and...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Science Behind Oral Inflammation, with Dr. William Levine</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-science-behind-oral-inflammation-with-dr-william-levine/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes board-certified periodontist Dr. William Levine to discuss the overlooked role of gum healt...</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hyaluronic Acid: The Deep Hydration Molecule Your Skin Has Been Waiting For</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/hyaluronic-acid-the-deep-hydration-molecule-your-skin-has-been-waiting-for/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>If you’ve spent any time exploring the world of natural skincare, chances are you’ve heard of hyaluronic acid (HA). Once... The post Hyaluronic Acid: ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>