<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 17:22:44 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>RISE-IBD Offers Insight Into Patient Coping Skills</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/rise-ibd-offers-insight-into-patient-coping-skills/</link><image_url>https://cdn.physiciansweekly.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/RISE-IBD-Graphic.jpg</image_url><description>The novel Resilience Scale for IBD, or RISE-IBD, aims to provide clinicians and patients with a tool for assessing resilience in inflammatory bowel di...</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 18:59:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Clinical Trial Referral Habits: A Deeper Look at What Your Peers Are Doing in Oncology</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/clinical-trial-referral-habits-a-deeper-look-at-what-your-peers-are-doing-in-oncology/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>A Physician’s Weekly survey of oncologists recently found that while most discuss clinical trial options in 11-50% of patient visits, major barriers t...</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 19:58:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The importance of psychological resilience in aging and widowhood</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-importance-psychological-resilience-aging-widowhood.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>A new study from Florida State University's Claude Pepper Center and Pepper Institute on Aging &amp; Public Policy has shed new light on the importance of...</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 21:47:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tardive Dyskinesia in Focus</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/tardive-dyskinesia-in-focus/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>In this slideshow, we explore ICD-TD diagnosis rates, metabolites among patients with tardive dyskinesia, and more. The post Tardive Dyskinesia in Foc...</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 21:19:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WHO, UNICEF say more than 14 million infants worldwide remain unvaccinated</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-unicef-million-infants-worldwide-unvaccinated.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Data released this week by the World Health Organization and UNICEF indicate modest gains in childhood vaccination rates, but globally, more than 14 m...</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 21:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Study suggests some maternal HIV infections may be missed during pregnancy</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-maternal-hiv-infections-pregnancy.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Newborns exposed to HIV during pregnancy or birth should receive preventive antiretroviral medication immediately after delivery to reduce the risk of...</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 21:24:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eight babies born after mitochondrial donation treatment to reduce transmission of mitochondrial DNA disease</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-babies-born-mitochondrial-donation-treatment.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>The UK's pioneering licensed IVF technique to reduce the risk of mitochondrial diseases carried out in Newcastle has seen eight babies born, research ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 22:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Music therapy may ease distress for dementia patients in hospital wards</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-music-therapy-ease-distress-dementia.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>A new treatment that uses music therapy on dementia wards could improve care and support for some of the NHS's most vulnerable patients.</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 22:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>VICTORION-INCEPTION Trial Reframes Lipid-Lowering Strategy in Difficult-to-Treat Patients</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/victorion-trial-reframes-lipid-lowering-strategy-in-difficult-to-treat-patients/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Rachel H. Giles, PhD, and Kirk Knowlton, MD, discuss the results from the VictORIAN Inception Trial presented at the National Lipid Association. The p...</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 15:23:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Addressing Gait Deficits in Multiple Sclerosis With Neuromodulation &amp; Neuroplasticity</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/addressing-gait-deficits-in-multiple-sclerosis-with-neuromodulation-neuroplasticity/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Antonella Favit-Van Pelt, MD, PhD, discusses the use of neuromodulation and neuroplasticity for addressing gait deficits in patients with multiple scl...</description><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 15:21:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Mold, Indoor Air Quality, and Clean Breathing, with Michael Rubino</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/mold-indoor-air-quality-and-clean-breathing-with-michael-rubino/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes environmental wellness expert Michael Rubino for an in-depth conversation on the hi...</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 08:01:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Nourishment Table, with Frederic Leroy</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-nourishment-table-with-frederic-leroy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes food scientist and advocate for regenerative agriculture Dr. Frederic Leroy to disc...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Turn ChatGPT Into Your Personal Meal Planner</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/turn-chatgpt-into-your-personal-meal-planner/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Even for someone who lives and breathes nutrition, meal planning can feel like a grind. There are weeks when I... The post Turn ChatGPT Into Your Pers...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:16:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Rediscovering Health, Nature, and Purpose-Driven Business, with Seth Spears</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rediscovering-health-nature-and-purpose-driven-business-with-seth-spears/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes entrepreneur and strategist Seth Spears for a wide-ranging conversation on health, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: How to Sharpen and Protect Your Mind for a Lifetime, with Dale Bredesen</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/how-to-sharpen-and-protect-your-mind-for-a-lifetime-with-dale-bredesen/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes renowned neurologist Dr. Dale Bredesen back to the show for an insightful conversation abou...</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:01:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>