<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 07:48:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Drinking less could prevent cancer deaths, study suggests</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-cancer-deaths.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Reducing annual alcohol consumption in Australia by one liter a person could significantly lower deaths from several major cancers, particularly among...</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:39:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Researchers link obesity, estrogen use, and increased blood-clotting risk</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-link-obesity-estrogen-blood-clotting.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>A research team led by Dr. Rinku Majumder from LSU Health New Orleans has published a groundbreaking study in the Journal of Clinical Investigation sh...</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:33:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How lung cancer's return pattern predicts survival after first treatment fails</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-smarter-lung-cancer.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>When lung cancer treatment stops working, what happens next? New research reveals the answer may depend on how the cancer grows.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:37:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Imaging technique can reduce benign breast biopsies by 25%</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-imaging-technique-benign-breast-biopsies.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>In breast cancer, a biopsy is the only diagnostic procedure that can determine if a suspicious lump or area is cancerous. However, in the U.S., betwee...</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:34:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Researcher identifies biomarkers that could improve early detection of pancreatic cancer</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-biomarkers-early-pancreatic-cancer.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>A researcher at the IU Indianapolis Fairbanks School of Public Health has identified a set of novel biomarkers that could significantly improve early ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:35:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Why Your Sleep Schedule Matters As Much As Duration</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/why-your-sleep-schedule-matters-as-much-as-duration/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris challenges the conventional focus on sleep duration and makes the case that sleep timing and circadi...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 08:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Menopause Brain Fog—What’s Really Happening (and How To Fix It)</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rhr-menopause-brain-fog-whats-really-happening-and-how-to-fix-it/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris examines research confirming that menopause-related brain fog is real, measurable, and reversible. H...</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 08:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Seed Oils and Colon Cancer – What the New Research Really Shows</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/seed-oils-and-colon-cancer-what-the-new-research-really-shows/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Seed oils have become one of the most controversial topics in nutrition, especially after a 2024 University of South Florida study linked high omega-6...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 08:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Longevity Trap: Why Chasing Anti-Aging May Be Aging You</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-longevity-trap-why-chasing-anti-aging-may-be-aging-you/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>In this episode, Chris explains why obsession with anti-aging hacks may actually undermine our long-term health. He examines the common longevity trap...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Link Between Metabolic Health and Mental Well-Being, with Dr. Matt Bernstein</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-link-between-metabolic-health-and-mental-well-being-with-dr-matt-bernstein/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes psychiatrist Dr. Matt Bernstein to explore the emerging field of metabolic psychiatry, the ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>