<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 06:41:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Children born to mothers over 45 face higher risk of premature birth and complications, study finds</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-children-born-mothers-higher-premature.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Giving birth to a child after 40 is becoming more and more common—but it can entail an increased risk to the child. A new study based on data from ove...</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 06:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Influence of Probiotics on Vaginal Flora and GBS in Pregnant Women</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/influence-of-probiotics-on-vaginal-flora-and-gbs-in-pregnant-women/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Probiotics in late pregnancy may not reduce GBS colonization but can beneficially shift vaginal microbiota composition. The post Influence of Probioti...</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 00:00:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cardiac intermediary metabolism in heart failure: substrate use, signalling roles and therapeutic targets.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/cardiac-intermediary-metabolism-in-heart-failure-substrate-use-signalling-roles-and-therapeutic-targets/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>The number of patients with heart failure is expected to rise sharply owing to ageing populations, poor dietary habits, unhealthy lifestyles and impro...</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 06:00:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Antibiotics and energy inhibitors effectively kill aggressive melanoma cells by blocking mitochondrial pathways</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-antibiotics-energy-inhibitors-effectively-aggressive.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Researchers have discovered that the most aggressive melanomas, the deadliest form of skin cancer, overactivate two key processes in mitochondria, the...</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 08:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Closed loop' learning barriers prevent doctors from using life-saving bedside ultrasound</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-loop-barriers-doctors-life-bedside.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Many doctors abandon a potentially life-saving medical scanning technology soon after training, because systemic barriers prevent it from becoming par...</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 06:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Safety of Stent Placement by Non-Urologic Surgeons</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/safety-of-stent-placement-by-non-urologic-surgeons/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Prophylactic ureteral stent placement by non-urologic surgeons demonstrated high technical success and an acceptable safety profile. The post Safety o...</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 23:00:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Simple insulin resistance test may also predict cognitive decline in Alzheimer's patients</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-simple-insulin-resistance-cognitive-decline.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Insulin resistance detected by routine triglyceride-glucose (TyG) index can flag people with early Alzheimer's who are four times more likely to prese...</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 23:10:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ozone Injection Into Intervertebral Foramen for Chronic Postherpetic Neuralgia Treatment</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/ozone-injection-into-intervertebral-foramen-for-chronic-postherpetic-neuralgia-treatment/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>A targeted ozone injection technique guided by CT imaging effectively eased drug-resistant postherpetic neuralgia, reducing pain, hypersensitivity, an...</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 23:30:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Structural Retinal Changes Mirror Disability in MS</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/structural-retinal-changes-mirror-disability-in-ms/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>OCT-detected retinal layer loss reflects underlying progression in MS, even without relapse or MRI evidence. The post Structural Retinal Changes Mirro...</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 23:00:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tinnitus linked to impaired cognitive function</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-tinnitus-linked-impaired-cognitive-function.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Individuals with versus those without tinnitus have significantly lower scores on cognitive function tests, according to a study published online May ...</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 20:10:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Nourishment Table, with Frederic Leroy</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-nourishment-table-with-frederic-leroy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes food scientist and advocate for regenerative agriculture Dr. Frederic Leroy to disc...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Turn ChatGPT Into Your Personal Meal Planner</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/turn-chatgpt-into-your-personal-meal-planner/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Even for someone who lives and breathes nutrition, meal planning can feel like a grind. There are weeks when I... The post Turn ChatGPT Into Your Pers...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:16:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Rediscovering Health, Nature, and Purpose-Driven Business, with Seth Spears</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rediscovering-health-nature-and-purpose-driven-business-with-seth-spears/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes entrepreneur and strategist Seth Spears for a wide-ranging conversation on health, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: How to Sharpen and Protect Your Mind for a Lifetime, with Dale Bredesen</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/how-to-sharpen-and-protect-your-mind-for-a-lifetime-with-dale-bredesen/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes renowned neurologist Dr. Dale Bredesen back to the show for an insightful conversation abou...</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:01:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quality Matters: How to Choose and Use the Best Collagen Supplement</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/quality-matters-how-to-choose-and-use-the-best-collagen-supplement/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Introduction If you’ve been paying attention to health and wellness trends, you’ve likely noticed collagen supplements everywhere—from your local heal...</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:57:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>