<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 06:33:24 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Growth performance and carcass traits of growing and finishing pigs fed diets with a partial to total replacement of soybean meal with Spirulina powder.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/growth-performance-and-carcass-traits-of-growing-and-finishing-pigs-fed-diets-with-a-partial-to-total-replacement-of-soybean-meal-with-spirulina-powder/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>The protein sources in pig diets strongly rely on soybean meal, but its production has been associated with soil degradation, deforestation and loss o...</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 06:30:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Effects of passive blood-flow-restriction and electromyostimulation on ICU-acquired weakness (ICUAW): a study protocol for a randomized-controlled, parallel-group clinical trial.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/effects-of-passive-blood-flow-restriction-and-electromyostimulation-on-icu-acquired-weakness-icuaw-a-study-protocol-for-a-randomized-controlled-parallel-group-clinical-trial/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Intensive care unit-acquired weakness (ICUAW) is a prevalent secondary disorder in critically ill patients, characterized by significant loss of muscl...</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 06:00:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Effectiveness of a community health advisor colorectal cancer screening educational intervention on stool test completion in an African American primary care patient population: a pragmatic randomized controlled trial.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/effectiveness-of-a-community-health-advisor-colorectal-cancer-screening-educational-intervention-on-stool-test-completion-in-an-african-american-primary-care-patient-population-a-pragmatic-randomized/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Colorectal cancer (CRC) disparities in incidence and mortality for African Americans compared to white Americans are explained by socioeconomic, behav...</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 06:00:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Perioperative sildenafil citrate administration in hepatectomy: a study protocol of randomized controlled trial.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/perioperative-sildenafil-citrate-administration-in-hepatectomy-a-study-protocol-of-randomized-controlled-trial/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Intraoperative blood loss (IBL) is the major concern in hepatectomy, which was closely relating to the central venous pressure (CVP). The controlled l...</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 06:00:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Association between preoperative glycaemic control (HbA1c) and early outcomes following primary hip and knee arthroplasty.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/association-between-preoperative-glycaemic-control-hba1c-and-early-outcomes-following-primary-hip-and-knee-arthroplasty/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>This study investigates the relationship between diabetes mellitus (DM), glycated haemoglobin (HbA1c), and postoperative outcomes among patients under...</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 06:00:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Does a culturally tailored quality of life intervention benefit Latina breast cancer survivors and caregivers?</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-05-culturally-tailored-quality-life-intervention.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>A randomized controlled trial assessed the benefits of a group-based intervention that fosters communication and coping skills in a culturally tailore...</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 08:10:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sea change in cancer care requires urgent action to strengthen oncology workforce and care delivery, say researchers</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-05-sea-cancer-requires-urgent-action.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Rapid advances in cancer treatment have benefited many people, but urgent change is needed in Canada's cancer care workforce to ensure patient care, a...</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 05:10:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The hearts of female elite athletes adapt differently than those of male elite athletes, research reveals</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-05-hearts-female-elite-athletes-differently.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Intensive exercise and sport changes the heart of an athlete. Research led by Amsterdam UMC shows that the hearts of female athletes have different ch...</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 08:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Study shows that an anti-inflammatory diet could extend overall survival after treatment for stage III colon cancer</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-anti-inflammatory-diet-survival-treatment.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Patients with colon cancer who consumed an anti-inflammatory diet during a Phase III clinical trial showed longer overall survival post-treatment comp...</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 11:05:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Plastic particles found in food could harm the body</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-05-plastic-particles-food-body.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Results from a new animal study suggest that microscopic plastic particles found in food and beverages may affect glucose metabolism and harm organs s...</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 21:50:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Turn ChatGPT Into Your Personal Meal Planner</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/turn-chatgpt-into-your-personal-meal-planner/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Even for someone who lives and breathes nutrition, meal planning can feel like a grind. There are weeks when I... The post Turn ChatGPT Into Your Pers...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:16:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Rediscovering Health, Nature, and Purpose-Driven Business, with Seth Spears</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rediscovering-health-nature-and-purpose-driven-business-with-seth-spears/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes entrepreneur and strategist Seth Spears for a wide-ranging conversation on health, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: How to Sharpen and Protect Your Mind for a Lifetime, with Dale Bredesen</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/how-to-sharpen-and-protect-your-mind-for-a-lifetime-with-dale-bredesen/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes renowned neurologist Dr. Dale Bredesen back to the show for an insightful conversation abou...</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:01:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quality Matters: How to Choose and Use the Best Collagen Supplement</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/quality-matters-how-to-choose-and-use-the-best-collagen-supplement/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Introduction If you’ve been paying attention to health and wellness trends, you’ve likely noticed collagen supplements everywhere—from your local heal...</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:57:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Collagen: The Essential Building Block for Strong Joints and Bones</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/collagen-the-essential-building-block-for-strong-joints-and-bones/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>The Foundation of Your Musculoskeletal System If you’ve ever winced going down stairs, felt that telltale morning stiffness, or worried... The post Co...</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 13:31:22 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>