<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:38:43 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Q&amp;A: What you need to know about new dietary guidelines</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-qa-dietary-guidelines.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Earlier this month, the federal government issued new dietary guidelines that place an emphasis on protein, including red meat; recommend full-fat dai...</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:29:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Q&amp;A: At-home HPV tests may usher in a new era for cervical cancer screening</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-qa-home-hpv-usher-era.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Regular cervical cancer screening using HPV testing and/or Pap tests can prevent up to 90% or more of cervical cancers by detecting and treating preca...</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:22:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Carbon-ion therapy offers nonsurgical option for early breast cancer treatment</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-carbon-ion-therapy-nonsurgical-option.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>For many women with early breast cancer, surgery is effective but life-altering. New five-year data from the National Institutes for Quantum Science a...</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:26:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A new atlas could help guide researchers studying neurological disease</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-atlas-neurological-disease.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Functioning brain cells need a functioning system for picking up the trash and sorting the recycling. But when the cellular sanitation machines respon...</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:25:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dietary supplement may protect against inflammation-related injury and death by enhancing kidney function</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-dietary-supplement-inflammation-injury-death.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>As soon as you are wounded—whether from grabbing a hot pan or contracting the flu—you begin a unique journey through variable symptoms toward either r...</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:13:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Why Your Sleep Schedule Matters As Much As Duration</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/why-your-sleep-schedule-matters-as-much-as-duration/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris challenges the conventional focus on sleep duration and makes the case that sleep timing and circadi...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 08:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Menopause Brain Fog—What’s Really Happening (and How To Fix It)</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rhr-menopause-brain-fog-whats-really-happening-and-how-to-fix-it/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris examines research confirming that menopause-related brain fog is real, measurable, and reversible. H...</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 08:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Seed Oils and Colon Cancer – What the New Research Really Shows</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/seed-oils-and-colon-cancer-what-the-new-research-really-shows/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Seed oils have become one of the most controversial topics in nutrition, especially after a 2024 University of South Florida study linked high omega-6...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 08:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Longevity Trap: Why Chasing Anti-Aging May Be Aging You</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-longevity-trap-why-chasing-anti-aging-may-be-aging-you/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>In this episode, Chris explains why obsession with anti-aging hacks may actually undermine our long-term health. He examines the common longevity trap...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Link Between Metabolic Health and Mental Well-Being, with Dr. Matt Bernstein</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-link-between-metabolic-health-and-mental-well-being-with-dr-matt-bernstein/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes psychiatrist Dr. Matt Bernstein to explore the emerging field of metabolic psychiatry, the ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>