<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 06:36:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>FTO (fat-mass and obesity-associated protein) deficiency aggravates age-dependent depression-like behaviors and cognitive impairment.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/fto-fat-mass-and-obesity-associated-protein-deficiency-aggravates-age-dependent-depression-like-behaviors-and-cognitive-impairment/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>The demethylase fat mass and obesity-related associated protein (FTO) is strongly associated with depression. Aging is a risk factor for synaptic plas...</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 06:30:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>National Poll shows many parents struggle letting teens have independence on family vacations</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-national-poll-parents-struggle-teens.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Parents' visions of family vacation time may not always match what their teens have in mind.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 10:54:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Psilocybin provides benefit for people with cancer and major depression, clinical trial reveals</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-psilocybin-benefit-people-cancer-major.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>New results from a clinical trial reveal that a single dose of psilocybin—a naturally occurring psychedelic compound found in mushrooms—can provide su...</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 08:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mechanism of Fatty Acid Metabolism and Regulation by Lactate During Exercise in White Adipose and Skeletal Muscle Tissue: A Review.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/mechanism-of-fatty-acid-metabolism-and-regulation-by-lactate-during-exercise-in-white-adipose-and-skeletal-muscle-tissue-a-review/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Lactate plays a central role in controlling the utilization of energy substrates and the selection of metabolic pathways. This review aims to determin...</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 06:30:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Study indicates racial differences in tumor collagen structure may impact cancer prognosis</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-racial-differences-tumor-collagen-impact.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In cancer care, accurate tools for predicting whether a tumor will spread (metastasize) can help patients receive the most appropriate treatments. But...</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 10:25:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sounding the alarm: Survey shows men are unaware of 'young man's disease'</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-alarm-survey-men-unaware-young.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>A survey commissioned by The Ohio State University Comprehensive Cancer Center—Arthur G. James Cancer Hospital and Richard J. Solove Research Institut...</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 11:02:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Research challenges link between loneliness and mortality for older adults receiving home care</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-link-loneliness-mortality-older-adults.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Various reports have linked loneliness to premature death, with some—including the U.S. Surgeon General—suggesting that loneliness is as harmful to on...</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 10:59:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Association between obstructive sleep apnea and quality of life in Korean middle-aged people: a cross-sectional study.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/association-between-obstructive-sleep-apnea-and-quality-of-life-in-korean-middle-aged-people-a-cross-sectional-study/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Obstructive sleep apnea (OSA), a serious sleep disorder, can lead to comorbidities and decreased quality of life if untreated. Poor sleep quality from...</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 06:30:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The dysregulation and regulatory mechanism of long non-coding RNA LBX2-AS1 in children with epilepsy.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/the-dysregulation-and-regulatory-mechanism-of-long-non-coding-rna-lbx2-as1-in-children-with-epilepsy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Epilepsy is a long-lasting neurological condition distinguished by recurring seizures, and related to oxidative stress and inflammation. This study in...</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 06:30:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Modifiable lifestyle factors, genetic susceptibility, and incident ankylosing spondylitis.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/modifiable-lifestyle-factors-genetic-susceptibility-and-incident-ankylosing-spondylitis/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>To evaluate modifiable lifestyle-genetic susceptibility interaction with the risk of ankylosing spondylitis (AS).This study included 382,035 individua...</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 06:30:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Nourishment Table, with Frederic Leroy</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-nourishment-table-with-frederic-leroy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes food scientist and advocate for regenerative agriculture Dr. Frederic Leroy to disc...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Turn ChatGPT Into Your Personal Meal Planner</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/turn-chatgpt-into-your-personal-meal-planner/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Even for someone who lives and breathes nutrition, meal planning can feel like a grind. There are weeks when I... The post Turn ChatGPT Into Your Pers...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:16:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Rediscovering Health, Nature, and Purpose-Driven Business, with Seth Spears</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rediscovering-health-nature-and-purpose-driven-business-with-seth-spears/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes entrepreneur and strategist Seth Spears for a wide-ranging conversation on health, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: How to Sharpen and Protect Your Mind for a Lifetime, with Dale Bredesen</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/how-to-sharpen-and-protect-your-mind-for-a-lifetime-with-dale-bredesen/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes renowned neurologist Dr. Dale Bredesen back to the show for an insightful conversation abou...</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:01:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quality Matters: How to Choose and Use the Best Collagen Supplement</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/quality-matters-how-to-choose-and-use-the-best-collagen-supplement/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Introduction If you’ve been paying attention to health and wellness trends, you’ve likely noticed collagen supplements everywhere—from your local heal...</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:57:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>