<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 17:09:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Pneumocystis pneumonia is striking unexpected patient groups, study shows</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-pneumocystis-pneumonia-unexpected-patient-groups.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>A seven-year study of 470 patients revealed that a severe fungal lung infection once mainly seen in specific high-risk groups is increasingly affectin...</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:08:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Menstruation topic still stigmatized by younger generation in Spain, study finds</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-menstruation-topic-stigmatized-younger-generation.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>The menstrual taboo persists. This is the main conclusion of a pioneering macro-study in Spain involving more than 4,000 participants and led by the I...</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:31:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Study investigates how having a pet in early childhood can influence emotional development</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-pet-early-childhood-emotional.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>A research team from the INMA Project (Childhood and Environment) has analyzed how pet ownership during early childhood may be related to emotional an...</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:36:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How the gut builds long-lasting immunity after viral infections</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-gut-immunity-viral-infections.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>A new study led by University of Toronto researchers has shown that immune cells in the gut follow an atypical pathway to produce antibodies that prov...</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:10:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scientists document rise in temperature-related deaths in the US</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-scientists-document-temperature-deaths.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Researchers led by investigators at Mass General Brigham have discovered that over the last 25 years, heat and cold-related deaths have caused more th...</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 22:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: From Wired &amp; Tired to Calm &amp; Clear: My Top Nutrients for Mood, Focus, and Sleep</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/from-wired-tired-to-calm-clear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris explores natural solutions for one of today’s most pressing challenges: chronic stress, anxiety, and...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Science Behind Oral Inflammation, with Dr. William Levine</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-science-behind-oral-inflammation-with-dr-william-levine/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes board-certified periodontist Dr. William Levine to discuss the overlooked role of gum healt...</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hyaluronic Acid: The Deep Hydration Molecule Your Skin Has Been Waiting For</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/hyaluronic-acid-the-deep-hydration-molecule-your-skin-has-been-waiting-for/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>If you’ve spent any time exploring the world of natural skincare, chances are you’ve heard of hyaluronic acid (HA). Once... The post Hyaluronic Acid: ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rice Ceramides: The Unsung Hero of Skin Hydration and Barrier Health</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rice-ceramides-the-unsung-hero-of-skin-hydration-and-barrier-health/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>We often think of radiant skin as the result of what we put on it: moisturizers, serums, masks. But emerging... The post Rice Ceramides: The Unsung He...</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lutein and Zeaxanthin: The Carotenoids That Protect and Perfect Your Skin from Within</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/lutein-and-zeaxanthin-the-carotenoids-that-protect-and-perfect-your-skin-from-within/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>When most people think of lutein and zeaxanthin, they picture eye health supplements or leafy green vegetables. But these vibrant... The post Lutein a...</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:00:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>