<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 11:03:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Genetically identical, but not the same: How gut microbiota composition shapes the immune system in mice</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-genetically-identical-gut-microbiota-composition.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Laboratory mice are often considered the scientific equivalent of identical twins—genetically identical and expected to look and behave the same. But ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 14:56:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Genetic study shows that common blood cancer includes subtypes</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-genetic-common-blood-cancer-subtypes.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>A new study from Karolinska Institutet, published in Cell Reports Medicine, shows that follicular lymphoma (FL), a common type of blood cancer, is not...</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 15:28:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Work-family conflict a major contributor to poor mental health in farmers, study finds</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-family-conflict-major-contributor-poor.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>A new study has revealed that work-family conflict (WFC) is a common contributor to psychological distress among farmers in Ireland, with researchers ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 14:45:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Morning coffee boosts mood significantly, study finds</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-morning-coffee-boosts-mood-significantly.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>People who regularly consume caffeine are usually in a better mood after a cup of coffee or another caffeinated drink—an effect that is much more pron...</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 14:51:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How does marijuana affect our bodies?</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-marijuana-affect-bodies.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Marijuana has been a hot topic for years, but one often clouded by misperceptions. Many turn to it as a perceived panacea, hoping it will address heal...</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 14:58:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Beauty From Within – Why Radiant Skin, Hair, and Nails Start Inside</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/beauty-from-within-why-radiant-skin-hair-and-nails-start-inside/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, we dive deep into the topic of beauty from within, exploring why radiant skin, hair, and nails truly start...</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 08:01:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Mold, Indoor Air Quality, and Clean Breathing, with Michael Rubino</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/mold-indoor-air-quality-and-clean-breathing-with-michael-rubino/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes environmental wellness expert Michael Rubino for an in-depth conversation on the hi...</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 08:01:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Nourishment Table, with Frederic Leroy</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-nourishment-table-with-frederic-leroy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes food scientist and advocate for regenerative agriculture Dr. Frederic Leroy to disc...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Turn ChatGPT Into Your Personal Meal Planner</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/turn-chatgpt-into-your-personal-meal-planner/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Even for someone who lives and breathes nutrition, meal planning can feel like a grind. There are weeks when I... The post Turn ChatGPT Into Your Pers...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:16:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Rediscovering Health, Nature, and Purpose-Driven Business, with Seth Spears</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rediscovering-health-nature-and-purpose-driven-business-with-seth-spears/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes entrepreneur and strategist Seth Spears for a wide-ranging conversation on health, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>