<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 10:57:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Tiny Baby’s Life-Threatening Wound Healed With Fish Skin</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/tiny-babys-life-threatening-wound-healed-with-fish-skin/</link><image_url>https://cdn.physiciansweekly.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/HEALTHDAY_Web_small3.png</image_url><description>TUESDAY, June 3, 2025 (HealthDay News) — When Eliana DeVos plays with her Ariel doll, her mom can’t help but get emotional. “I call her my little merm...</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 07:31:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Understanding COPD as a Multisystem Disease Guides Better Care</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/understanding-copd-as-a-multisystem-disease-guides-better-care/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In a recent paper, researchers recommended prompt screening methods and management strategies for comorbidities that occur commonly in patients with C...</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 14:35:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Acupuncture may alleviate nocturia in men treated for prostate cancer</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-acupuncture-alleviate-nocturia-men-prostate.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Acupuncture may reduce nocturia in patients treated for prostate cancer, according to a research letter published online in JAMA Oncology.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 15:50:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Study shows that parents aren't following public health guidelines despite allergy risk</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-parents-health-guidelines-allergy.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>A new study, published in the European Journal of Clinical Nutrition, has found that several parents are delaying the introduction of highly allergeni...</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 15:55:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ballad Health’s Hospital Monopoly Underperformed. Then Tennessee Lowered the Bar.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/ballad-healths-hospital-monopoly-underperformed-then-tennessee-lowered-the-bar/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Despite years of patient complaints and quality-of-care concerns, Ballad Health — the nation’s largest state-sanctioned hospital monopoly — will now b...</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 11:30:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Diagnostic pen converts handwriting into electrical signals to detect Parkinson's</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-diagnostic-pen-electrical-parkinson.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>A team at the University of California, Los Angeles has developed a low-cost diagnostic pen that converts handwriting into electrical signals for earl...</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 15:50:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump’s ‘One Big Beautiful Bill’ Continues Assault on Obamacare</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/trumps-one-big-beautiful-bill-continues-assault-on-obamacare/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Millions would lose Medicaid coverage. Millions would be left without health insurance. Signing up for health plans on the Affordable Care Act marketp...</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 11:30:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Native Americans Hurt by Federal Health Cuts, Despite RFK Jr.’s Promises of Protection</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/native-americans-hurt-by-federal-health-cuts-despite-rfk-jr-s-promises-of-protection/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>WINDOW ROCK, Ariz. — Navajo Nation leaders took turns talking with the U.S. government’s top health official as they hiked along a sandstone ridge ove...</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 11:30:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Researchers call for an inflammatory subtype of major depression, paving the way for precision psychiatry</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-inflammatory-subtype-major-depression-paving.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Researchers at Emory University have provided compelling evidence supporting the existence of an inflammatory subtype of major depression, a breakthro...</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 15:30:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pepto Bismol may not prevent traveler's diarrhea, new study finds</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-pepto-bismol-diarrhea.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Pepto Bismol is a go-to stomach remedy, but a new study suggests it might not help prevent diarrhea during international travel.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 15:40:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Nourishment Table, with Frederic Leroy</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-nourishment-table-with-frederic-leroy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes food scientist and advocate for regenerative agriculture Dr. Frederic Leroy to disc...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Turn ChatGPT Into Your Personal Meal Planner</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/turn-chatgpt-into-your-personal-meal-planner/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Even for someone who lives and breathes nutrition, meal planning can feel like a grind. There are weeks when I... The post Turn ChatGPT Into Your Pers...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:16:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Rediscovering Health, Nature, and Purpose-Driven Business, with Seth Spears</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rediscovering-health-nature-and-purpose-driven-business-with-seth-spears/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes entrepreneur and strategist Seth Spears for a wide-ranging conversation on health, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: How to Sharpen and Protect Your Mind for a Lifetime, with Dale Bredesen</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/how-to-sharpen-and-protect-your-mind-for-a-lifetime-with-dale-bredesen/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes renowned neurologist Dr. Dale Bredesen back to the show for an insightful conversation abou...</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:01:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quality Matters: How to Choose and Use the Best Collagen Supplement</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/quality-matters-how-to-choose-and-use-the-best-collagen-supplement/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Introduction If you’ve been paying attention to health and wellness trends, you’ve likely noticed collagen supplements everywhere—from your local heal...</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:57:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>