<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 22:12:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Investigating lithium's potential role in slowing cognitive decline in Alzheimer's disease</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-lithium-potential-role-cognitive-decline.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Alzheimer's disease (AD) is a progressive neurodegenerative disorder characterized by cognitive decline such as memory loss and behavioral disturbance...</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 02:30:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Psychiatric treatment is no guarantee of a return to work, says study</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-psychiatric-treatment.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Mental health problems are keeping an increasing number of Norwegians out of the employment market. Treatment alone is often not enough to get people ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 01:20:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Researchers diagnose disease with a drop of blood, a microscope and AI</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-disease-blood-microscope-ai.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Not long ago, the idea of diagnosing a disease with a droplet of blood was considered a pipe dream. Today, this technology could soon become a reality...</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 02:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Young donor age emerges as key factor in stem cell transplant success</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-young-donor-age-emerges-key.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>HLA compatibility is considered the key criterion for selecting donors for allo-HSCT. DKMS study data presented at the DGHO Annual Meeting 2025 in Col...</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 02:40:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The future of insulin delivery for diabetes could be through a patch</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-future-insulin-delivery-diabetes-patch.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>A compound that enables the delivery of insulin through the skin has been demonstrated in mice and minipigs. The findings, reported in a paper publish...</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 03:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Link Between Metabolic Health and Mental Well-Being, with Dr. Matt Bernstein</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-link-between-metabolic-health-and-mental-well-being-with-dr-matt-bernstein/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes psychiatrist Dr. Matt Bernstein to explore the emerging field of metabolic psychiatry, the ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: From Wired &amp; Tired to Calm &amp; Clear: My Top Nutrients for Mood, Focus, and Sleep</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/from-wired-tired-to-calm-clear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris explores natural solutions for one of today’s most pressing challenges: chronic stress, anxiety, and...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Science Behind Oral Inflammation, with Dr. William Levine</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-science-behind-oral-inflammation-with-dr-william-levine/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes board-certified periodontist Dr. William Levine to discuss the overlooked role of gum healt...</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hyaluronic Acid: The Deep Hydration Molecule Your Skin Has Been Waiting For</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/hyaluronic-acid-the-deep-hydration-molecule-your-skin-has-been-waiting-for/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>If you’ve spent any time exploring the world of natural skincare, chances are you’ve heard of hyaluronic acid (HA). Once... The post Hyaluronic Acid: ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rice Ceramides: The Unsung Hero of Skin Hydration and Barrier Health</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rice-ceramides-the-unsung-hero-of-skin-hydration-and-barrier-health/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>We often think of radiant skin as the result of what we put on it: moisturizers, serums, masks. But emerging... The post Rice Ceramides: The Unsung He...</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>