<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 11:00:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Astrocytes found to aid spinal cord repair by signaling immune response</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-astrocytes-aid-spinal-cord-immune.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Cedars-Sinai investigators have discovered a healing mechanism that could one day be harnessed to help treat patients with spinal cord injuries, strok...</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:00:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New risk score helps predict pancreatic cancer recurrence</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-score-pancreatic-cancer-recurrence.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Cedars-Sinai investigators, leading a multi-institutional team, have developed and validated a tool to predict which patients with pancreatic neuroend...</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:00:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Confused by the doctor's questionnaire? Study suggests it's common</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-doctor-questionnaire-common.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Imagine sitting down for an appointment with a therapist—or any care provider. Perhaps it's the first time you've seen this provider, or the first tim...</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Liver cell reprogramming boosts T cell function in aging immune systems</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-liver-cell-reprogramming-boosts-function.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>As people age, their immune system function declines. T cell populations become smaller and can't react to pathogens as quickly, making people more su...</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:00:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How do brains stay stable, and when might a dose of flexibility be helpful?</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-brains-stay-stable-dose-flexibility.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Young minds are easily molded. Each new experience rewires a child's brain circuitry, adding and removing synaptic connections between neurons. These ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:00:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Seed Oils and Colon Cancer – What the New Research Really Shows</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/seed-oils-and-colon-cancer-what-the-new-research-really-shows/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Seed oils have become one of the most controversial topics in nutrition, especially after a 2024 University of South Florida study linked high omega-6...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 08:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Longevity Trap: Why Chasing Anti-Aging May Be Aging You</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-longevity-trap-why-chasing-anti-aging-may-be-aging-you/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>In this episode, Chris explains why obsession with anti-aging hacks may actually undermine our long-term health. He examines the common longevity trap...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Link Between Metabolic Health and Mental Well-Being, with Dr. Matt Bernstein</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-link-between-metabolic-health-and-mental-well-being-with-dr-matt-bernstein/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes psychiatrist Dr. Matt Bernstein to explore the emerging field of metabolic psychiatry, the ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: From Wired &amp; Tired to Calm &amp; Clear: My Top Nutrients for Mood, Focus, and Sleep</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/from-wired-tired-to-calm-clear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris explores natural solutions for one of today’s most pressing challenges: chronic stress, anxiety, and...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Science Behind Oral Inflammation, with Dr. William Levine</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-science-behind-oral-inflammation-with-dr-william-levine/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes board-certified periodontist Dr. William Levine to discuss the overlooked role of gum healt...</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>