<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 11:00:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Signature neural patterns may help predict recovery from traumatic brain injury</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-signature-neural-patterns-recovery-traumatic.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>After traumatic brain injury (TBI), some patients may recover completely, while others retain severe disabilities. Accurately evaluating prognosis is ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>System replicates womb lining to 'listen in' to embryo-mother interactions during implantation</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-replicates-womb-lining-embryo-mother.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>By engineering a system replicating the womb lining with high biological accuracy, researchers at the Babraham Institute and Stanford University have ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:00:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Iron deficiency without anemia common with moderate-to-severe atopic dermatitis</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-iron-deficiency-anemia-common-moderate.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Iron deficiency without anemia is a common feature of moderate-to-severe atopic dermatitis (AD), according to a study published in Nutrients.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:58:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Protein MCL1 links cancer cell survival and energy metabolism</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-protein-mcl1-links-cancer-cell.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>A study by the Mildred Scheel Early Career Center group led by Dr. Mohamed Elgendy at the TUD Faculty of Medicine provides fundamental insights into c...</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:36:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Study finds that where a patient lives affects recovery after a hip fracture</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-patient-affects-recovery-hip-fracture.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Older adults who live in economically disadvantaged neighborhoods spend significantly fewer days at home in the year after a fall-related hip fracture...</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Seed Oils and Colon Cancer – What the New Research Really Shows</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/seed-oils-and-colon-cancer-what-the-new-research-really-shows/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Seed oils have become one of the most controversial topics in nutrition, especially after a 2024 University of South Florida study linked high omega-6...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 08:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Longevity Trap: Why Chasing Anti-Aging May Be Aging You</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-longevity-trap-why-chasing-anti-aging-may-be-aging-you/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>In this episode, Chris explains why obsession with anti-aging hacks may actually undermine our long-term health. He examines the common longevity trap...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Link Between Metabolic Health and Mental Well-Being, with Dr. Matt Bernstein</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-link-between-metabolic-health-and-mental-well-being-with-dr-matt-bernstein/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes psychiatrist Dr. Matt Bernstein to explore the emerging field of metabolic psychiatry, the ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: From Wired &amp; Tired to Calm &amp; Clear: My Top Nutrients for Mood, Focus, and Sleep</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/from-wired-tired-to-calm-clear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris explores natural solutions for one of today’s most pressing challenges: chronic stress, anxiety, and...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Science Behind Oral Inflammation, with Dr. William Levine</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-science-behind-oral-inflammation-with-dr-william-levine/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes board-certified periodontist Dr. William Levine to discuss the overlooked role of gum healt...</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>