<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 06:50:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Neurons burn sugar differently: Discovery offers new hope for fighting neurodegeneration</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-neurons-sugar-differently-discovery-neurodegeneration.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>A new study from scientists at the Buck Institute for Research on Aging has revealed a surprising player in the battle against Alzheimer's disease and...</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 10:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cardiometabolic Index and Incontinence in Women</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/cardiometabolic-index-and-incontinence-in-women/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Higher cardiometabolic index levels were strongly linked to all types of urinary incontinence in women. The post Cardiometabolic Index and Incontinenc...</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 00:00:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Survey identifies top factors Americans blame for declining focus and attention</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-survey-factors-americans-blame-declining.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Studies show that the average attention span is now only eight seconds. That's about as much time as it takes to read a few sentences before being dis...</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 05:10:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How a common herpes virus evades the immune system: Study tackles a leading cause of birth defects</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-common-herpes-virus-evades-immune.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>New research from the University of Pittsburgh School of Medicine and La Jolla Institute for Immunology, published today in Nature Microbiology, revea...</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 10:00:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI matches doctors in mapping lung tumors for radiation therapy</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-ai-doctors-lung-tumors-therapy.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>In radiation therapy, precision can save lives. Oncologists must carefully map the size and location of a tumor before delivering high-dose radiation ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 10:00:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Complement Levels Vary in irAE-n and Controls</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/complement-levels-vary-in-irae-n-and-controls/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Complement activation was common but non-specific in immune-related neuropathy and myositis, questioning the utility of complement inhibitors. The pos...</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 23:00:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Effect of Decision Support on Dialysis Choice and Outcomes</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/effect-of-decision-support-on-dialysis-choice-and-outcomes/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Helping individuals through shared decision making led to prior dialysis planning, good treatment alignment, and improved outcomes shaped by age, frai...</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 22:00:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Human immune response to pig kidney transplants mapped, identifying early rejection markers</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-06-human-immune-response-pig-kidney.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>A pioneering study has provided unprecedented insights into the immune response following pig-to-human kidney xenotransplantation. The findings, prese...</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 23:10:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seeding Kinetics of α-Synuclein Linked to PD Prognosis</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/seeding-kinetics-of-%ce%b1-synuclein-linked-to-pd-prognosis/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Faster α-synuclein seeding in cerebrospinal fluid signaled a higher risk of cognitive decline in Parkinson’s disease. The post Seeding Kinetics of α-S...</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 23:30:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Racial Differences Affect Breast Surgery Timing</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/racial-differences-affect-breast-surgery-timing/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Women from racial minority groups experienced delayed breast cancer surgery regardless of distance traveled, revealing persistent care disparities. Th...</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 23:00:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Nourishment Table, with Frederic Leroy</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-nourishment-table-with-frederic-leroy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes food scientist and advocate for regenerative agriculture Dr. Frederic Leroy to disc...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Turn ChatGPT Into Your Personal Meal Planner</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/turn-chatgpt-into-your-personal-meal-planner/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Even for someone who lives and breathes nutrition, meal planning can feel like a grind. There are weeks when I... The post Turn ChatGPT Into Your Pers...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:16:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Rediscovering Health, Nature, and Purpose-Driven Business, with Seth Spears</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rediscovering-health-nature-and-purpose-driven-business-with-seth-spears/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes entrepreneur and strategist Seth Spears for a wide-ranging conversation on health, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: How to Sharpen and Protect Your Mind for a Lifetime, with Dale Bredesen</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/how-to-sharpen-and-protect-your-mind-for-a-lifetime-with-dale-bredesen/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes renowned neurologist Dr. Dale Bredesen back to the show for an insightful conversation abou...</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:01:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quality Matters: How to Choose and Use the Best Collagen Supplement</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/quality-matters-how-to-choose-and-use-the-best-collagen-supplement/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Introduction If you’ve been paying attention to health and wellness trends, you’ve likely noticed collagen supplements everywhere—from your local heal...</description><pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:57:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>