<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 11:00:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>France tightens infant formula rules after toxin scare</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-france-tightens-infant-formula-toxin.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>France has said it will impose stricter limits on the acceptable level of a toxin called cereulide in infant formula after potentially contaminated pr...</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:28:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Study suggests young adults' memories of childhood adversity shift with parental support</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-young-adults-memories-childhood-adversity.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>New research from Michigan State University finds that how young adults recall adverse childhood experiences fluctuates based on the current quality o...</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:40:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Perceiving nature in daily life and exercise linked to better mental health</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-nature-daily-life-linked-mental.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Is living in a leafy neighborhood enough to improve your mental health? Not necessarily. What matters most is frequent exposure to nature across diffe...</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:50:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Study maps 30 rheumatoid arthritis biopsies, linking joint scarring to treatment resistance</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-rheumatoid-arthritis-biopsies-linking-joint.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Rheumatoid arthritis (RA) is a common autoimmune disease where the body's immune system mistakenly attacks the lining of its own joints, causing chron...</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:30:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Small improvements in sleep, physical activity and diet are linked with a longer life</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-small-physical-diet-linked-longer.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>We may not need to completely overhaul our lives to live healthier for longer, according to a large UK-based study. This is welcome news, particularly...</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:50:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Cold Exposure: Why Sustained Beats Extreme</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/cold-exposure-why-sustained-beats-extreme/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Cold plunges and ice baths dominate social media, but do they really deliver the best metabolic benefits? In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 08:03:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Why Your Sleep Schedule Matters As Much As Duration</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/why-your-sleep-schedule-matters-as-much-as-duration/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris challenges the conventional focus on sleep duration and makes the case that sleep timing and circadi...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 08:05:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Menopause Brain Fog—What’s Really Happening (and How To Fix It)</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rhr-menopause-brain-fog-whats-really-happening-and-how-to-fix-it/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris examines research confirming that menopause-related brain fog is real, measurable, and reversible. H...</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 08:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Seed Oils and Colon Cancer – What the New Research Really Shows</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/seed-oils-and-colon-cancer-what-the-new-research-really-shows/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Seed oils have become one of the most controversial topics in nutrition, especially after a 2024 University of South Florida study linked high omega-6...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 08:05:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Longevity Trap: Why Chasing Anti-Aging May Be Aging You</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-longevity-trap-why-chasing-anti-aging-may-be-aging-you/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode, Chris explains why obsession with anti-aging hacks may actually undermine our long-term health. He examines the common longevity trap...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>