<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 06:40:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Association Found Between Home Mold, Hypersensitivity Pneumonitis</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/association-found-between-home-mold-hypersensitivity-pneumonitis/</link><image_url>https://cdn.physiciansweekly.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/HEALTHDAY_Web_small3.png</image_url><description>THURSDAY, July 17, 2025 (HealthDay News) — Home mold, often attributed to chronic and/or recurring water intrusion, is associated with hypersensitivit...</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 07:31:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Less pain, more gain: Phenol-groups drive a new recipe for safer, stronger mRNA vaccines</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-pain-gain-phenol-groups-recipe.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>As millions of people know firsthand, the most common side effect of mRNA vaccines like the COVID-19 shot is inflammation: soreness, redness and a day...</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 10:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In rural Canadian town, new risk of measles deepens vaccine tensions</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-rural-canadian-town-measles-deepens.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>In the Canadian town of Aylmer, where Mennonites in traditional dress walk down the main street alongside secular locals, bitter divisions over vaccin...</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 09:34:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>KFF Health News’ ‘What the Health?’: The Senate Saves PEPFAR Funding — For Now</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/kff-health-news-what-the-health-the-senate-saves-pepfar-funding-for-now/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>The Host Julie Rovner KFF Health News @jrovner @julierovner.bsky.social Read Julie’s stories. Julie Rovner is chief Washington correspondent and host ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 11:30:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maybe It’s Not Just Aging. Maybe It’s Anemia.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/maybe-its-not-just-aging-maybe-its-anemia/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Gary Sergott felt weary all the time. “I’d get tired, short of breath, a sort of malaise,” he said. He was cold even on warm days and looked pale with...</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 11:30:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gene essential for vitamin D absorption could help unlock treatments for cancer and autoimmune diseases</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-gene-essential-vitamin-d-absorption.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Vitamin D is not only an essential nutrient, but also the precursor of the hormone calcitriol, indispensable for health. It regulates the uptake of ph...</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 05:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Surprising finding could pave way for universal cancer vaccine</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-pave-universal-cancer-vaccine.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>An experimental mRNA vaccine has boosted the tumor-fighting effects of immunotherapy in a mouse-model study, bringing researchers one step closer to t...</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 10:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prioritizing Weight Loss Quality Over Quantity, Thanks to New Treatments</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/prioritizing-weight-loss-quality-over-quantity-thanks-to-new-treatments/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Better health, not just fewer pounds—weight loss quality is the new priority in modern obesity management. The post Prioritizing Weight Loss Quality O...</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 11:00:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scar tissue in athletes' hearts tied to higher risk of dangerous cardiac rhythms</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-07-scar-tissue-athletes-hearts-higher.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Scar tissue in the heart was associated with abnormal heart rhythms among healthy, long-time male endurance athletes aged 50 or older, potentially inc...</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 00:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Los Angeles Weighs a Disaster Registry. Disability Advocates Warn Against False Assurances.</title><link>https://www.physiciansweekly.com/los-angeles-weighs-a-disaster-registry-disability-advocates-warn-against-false-assurances/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>In the wake of January’s deadly wildfires, Los Angeles County leaders are weighing a disaster registry intended to help disabled and senior residents ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 11:30:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Mold, Indoor Air Quality, and Clean Breathing, with Michael Rubino</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/mold-indoor-air-quality-and-clean-breathing-with-michael-rubino/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes environmental wellness expert Michael Rubino for an in-depth conversation on the hi...</description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 08:01:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Nourishment Table, with Frederic Leroy</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-nourishment-table-with-frederic-leroy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes food scientist and advocate for regenerative agriculture Dr. Frederic Leroy to disc...</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Turn ChatGPT Into Your Personal Meal Planner</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/turn-chatgpt-into-your-personal-meal-planner/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Even for someone who lives and breathes nutrition, meal planning can feel like a grind. There are weeks when I... The post Turn ChatGPT Into Your Pers...</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 20:16:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: Rediscovering Health, Nature, and Purpose-Driven Business, with Seth Spears</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/rediscovering-health-nature-and-purpose-driven-business-with-seth-spears/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris Kresser welcomes entrepreneur and strategist Seth Spears for a wide-ranging conversation on health, ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: How to Sharpen and Protect Your Mind for a Lifetime, with Dale Bredesen</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/how-to-sharpen-and-protect-your-mind-for-a-lifetime-with-dale-bredesen/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes renowned neurologist Dr. Dale Bredesen back to the show for an insightful conversation abou...</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 08:01:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>