<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is a randomly ordered feed of the most recent entries from theBalancedBriefNLhealthAndWellness, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 11:00:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>FDA looks into reports of deaths after COVID vaccination</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-fda-deaths-covid-vaccination.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Federal officials say the U.S. Food and Drug Administration (FDA) is reviewing reports of possible deaths in adults and children following COVID-19 va...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 15:50:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>EU to reward antibiotic innovation with new pharma rules</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-eu-reward-antibiotic-pharma.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Drugmakers that develop new antibiotics are set to benefit from longer market protection in Europe after the EU agreed Thursday to a wide-ranging refo...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 15:46:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Novel 'body-swap' robot provides insights into how the brain keeps us upright</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-body-swap-robot-insights-brain.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Imagine driving a car with a steering that doesn't respond instantly and a GPS that always reflects where you were a second ago. To stay on course, yo...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 15:38:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Balanced neural inhibition in the hippocampus is crucial for recognition memory</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-neural-inhibition-hippocampus-crucial-recognition.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>A new study has revealed that neural inhibition and balanced neural activity in a specific area of the brain is required for recognition memory. The f...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 15:49:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Octopus-inspired 3D micro-LEDs pave the way for selective pancreatic cancer therapy</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-octopus-3d-micro-pave-pancreatic.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Conventional pancreatic cancer treatments face a critical hurdle due to the dense tumor microenvironment (TME). This biological barrier surrounds the ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 15:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Longevity Trap: Why Chasing Anti-Aging May Be Aging You</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-longevity-trap-why-chasing-anti-aging-may-be-aging-you/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In this episode, Chris explains why obsession with anti-aging hacks may actually undermine our long-term health. He examines the common longevity trap...</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Link Between Metabolic Health and Mental Well-Being, with Dr. Matt Bernstein</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-link-between-metabolic-health-and-mental-well-being-with-dr-matt-bernstein/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes psychiatrist Dr. Matt Bernstein to explore the emerging field of metabolic psychiatry, the ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: From Wired &amp; Tired to Calm &amp; Clear: My Top Nutrients for Mood, Focus, and Sleep</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/from-wired-tired-to-calm-clear/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris explores natural solutions for one of today’s most pressing challenges: chronic stress, anxiety, and...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RHR: The Science Behind Oral Inflammation, with Dr. William Levine</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/the-science-behind-oral-inflammation-with-dr-william-levine/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>In this episode of Revolution Health Radio, Chris welcomes board-certified periodontist Dr. William Levine to discuss the overlooked role of gum healt...</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 08:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hyaluronic Acid: The Deep Hydration Molecule Your Skin Has Been Waiting For</title><link>https://chriskresser.com/hyaluronic-acid-the-deep-hydration-molecule-your-skin-has-been-waiting-for/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>If you’ve spent any time exploring the world of natural skincare, chances are you’ve heard of hyaluronic acid (HA). Once... The post Hyaluronic Acid: ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>