<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 00:44:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>We’re in a Home Construction Golden Age—Here’s How Investors Would Benefit From Building</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/why-investors-should-be-flocking-to-new-construction</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>This may be the best time ever to invest in new construction.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 16:01:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OpenAI and Google lay out their competing AI visions</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/18/openai-and-google-lay-out-their-competing-ai-visions/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Welcome back to TechCrunch’s Week in Review. This week had two major events from OpenAI and Google. OpenAI’s spring update event saw the reveal of its new model, GPT-4o, which has voice and vision capabilities that can turn ChatGPT into a virtual assistant seemingly aspiring to be “Her.” Hot off OpenAI’s tail, Google’s I/O conference […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 21:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Police Tactics at Some Pro-Palestine Protests Ignore Past Lessons</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/18/police-israel-palestine-campus-protests</link><description>While some universities have sought peaceful approaches, others have used aggressive policing that bucks research from the protests following George Floyd’s murder.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Federal Experts Talk Bird Flu ‘What Ifs’ in WebMD Live Event</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/cold-and-flu/news/20240516/federal-experts-talk-bird-flu-what-ifs?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>WebMD brought together experts from four federal agencies to talk prevention, monitoring, and what the “what ifs” of bird flu might look like.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:50:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>5 Ways to Capitalize on Public Investments in Tax Increment Financing (TIF) Districts</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/ways-to-capitalize-on-public-investments-in-tax-increment-financing-districts</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>These smart strategies make the most of community investments while increasing your profitability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Expedia says two execs dismissed after ‘violation of company policy’</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/18/expedia-says-two-execs-dismissed-after-violation-of-company-policy/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Expedia says Rathi Murthy and Sreenivas Rachamadugu, respectively its CTO and senior vice president of core services product &amp; engineering, are no longer employed at the travel booking company. In a statement shared with Bloomberg and elsewhere, Expedia said Murthy and Rachamadugu are “no longer employed at Expedia Group” due to an unspecified “violation of […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 19:05:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Susan Chira to Step Down as The Marshall Project’s Editor-in-Chief in January</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/16/susan-chira-eic-step-down</link><description>Under her stewardship, the news nonprofit more than doubled in size, opened local newsrooms and won its second Pulitzer Prize.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What’s Next in Health Care for Older Adults: Questions and Answers With John Whyte, MD</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/blog-aging-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>As WebMD’s chief medical officer, John Whyte, MD, is in a unique position to see both the current state of medical care for America’s older adults and the way things are trending for the future. We asked him to share his insight on a few topics, along with a bit of advice.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:29:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adventures in Property Management: 5 Lessons Learned from My Years of Self-Managing Single Family Rentals</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/lessons-learned-from-years-of-self-managing-single-family-rentals</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Use my tips to be a better self-managing landlord.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>With AI startups booming, nap pods and Silicon Valley hustle culture are back</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/18/ai-startups-nap-pods-silicon-valley-hustle-culture/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>When Jeffrey Wang posted to X asking if anyone wanted to go in on an order of fancy-but-affordable office nap pods, he didn’t expect the post to go viral. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When Bad Cops Become Private Security Guards</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/11/police-private-guard-florida-chicago</link><description>There’s growing evidence that former officers with troubling histories of abuse can easily find second careers in private security.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Get the Care You Need in a COVID-19 World</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/covid-senior-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>What to expect at the doctor’s office, hospitals, and long-term care facilities, the future of telemedicine, and how to get the best care during COVID-19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 19:50:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A New South Carolina Law Would Severely Crack Down on Wholesaling</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/new-south-carolina-law-would-severely-crack-down-on-wholesaling</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>The bill could be a precursor of what's to come across the country.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OpenAI created a team to control ‘superintelligent’ AI — then let it wither, source says</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/18/openai-created-a-team-to-control-superintelligent-ai-then-let-it-wither-source-says/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>OpenAI’s Superalignment team, responsible for developing ways to govern and steer “superintelligent” AI systems, was promised 20% of the company’s compute resources, according to a person from that team. But requests for a fraction of that compute were often denied, blocking the team from doing their work. That issue, among others, pushed several team members […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 17:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Rare Bright Spot for a Canine Lover Doing Time: Raising Puppies to Become Service Dogs</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/10/service-dogs-training-prison-essay</link><description>Adam Roberts reflects on the highs and occasional lows of training Labrador retrievers for the Puppies Behind Bars program.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Personal Shopper: A Savvy Black Entrepreneur Guides You to Eczema-Friendly Clothes, Creams, Cosmetics, and More</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/savvy-black-entrepreneur-guides-eczema-friendly-clothes-creams-cosmetics?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>A savvy black entrepreneur guides you on an eczema-friendly shopping spree.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:54:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Only One Major Market is Seeing Housing Prices Decline Right Now</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/home-prices-declining-in-only-one-major-metro-area</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Supply is up and demand is down, so why aren't more cities seeing price decreases?</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 13:56:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>VCs and the military are fueling self-driving startups that don’t need roads</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/18/vcs-and-the-military-are-fueling-self-driving-startups-that-dont-need-roads/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>A new crop of early-stage startups — along with some recent VC investments — illustrates a niche emerging in the autonomous vehicle technology sector. Unlike the companies bringing robotaxis to city streets, these startups are taking their tech off-road. Two recent entrants — Seattle-based Overland AI and New Brunswick-based Potential — are poised to get […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Marshall Project Wins the Dart Award for “The Mercy Workers”</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/06/the-marshall-project-wins-the-dart-award-for-the-mercy-workers</link><description>Our feature on mitigation specialists who help save people from the death penalty was recognized for making “significant contributions to public understanding of trauma-related issues.”</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Behind the Spike in Colorectal Cancer Among Young Americans</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/colorectal-cancer/news/20240515/behind-the-spike-in-colorectal-cancer-cases?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Colorectal cancer cases increased a whopping 333% among 15- to 19-year-olds and 185% among 20- to 24-year-olds from 1999 to 2020.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:59:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>