<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 02:18:33 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>With Slow Spring Homebuying, Zillow Predicts Price Drops in 2025</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-231</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Zillow’s latest housing market forecast shows a decline in home prices over the next year after a very slow spring homebuying season. While spring is traditionally the hottest time of […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 07:02:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spain’s exposure to climate change helps Madrid-based VC Seaya close €300M climate tech fund</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/04/spains-exposure-to-climate-change-helps-madrid-based-vc-seaya-close-e300m-climate-tech-fund/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>According to a recent Dealroom report on the Spanish tech ecosystem, the combined enterprise value of Spanish startups surpassed €100 billion in 2023. In the latest confirmation of this upward trend, Madrid-based VC fund Seaya has closed Seaya Andromeda, an “Article 9” €300 million climate tech fund based out of Madrid. Article 9 refers to the EU’s Sustainable […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 16:50:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Crime Rates and the 2024 Election: What You Need to Know</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/27/trump-and-biden-spar-over-crime-rates-ahead-of-their-debate-what-do-we-really-know</link><description>As crime data again becomes a flashpoint in the presidential campaign, experts push for better national statistics.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Federal Experts Talk Bird Flu ‘What Ifs’ in WebMD Live Event</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/cold-and-flu/news/20240516/federal-experts-talk-bird-flu-what-ifs?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>WebMD brought together experts from four federal agencies to talk prevention, monitoring, and what the “what ifs” of bird flu might look like.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:50:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>9 Surprisingly Hot Markets Where Investors Can Still Find Affordable Short-Term Rental Properties</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/surprisingly-hot-short-term-rental-markets</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>These under-the-radar markets still have plenty of affordable inventory and could be potential goldmines for short-term rental investors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:54:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Forestay, Europe’s newest $220M growth-stage VC fund, will focus on AI</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/04/forestay-europes-newest-220m-growth-stage-vc-fund-will-focus-on-ai/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Forestay, an emerging VC based out of Geneva, Switzerland, has been busy. This week it closed its second fund, Forestay Capital II, at a hard cap of $220 million. The VC wasn’t well known in Europe until it started to lead rounds in enterprise startups a couple of years ago, notably scanning software startup Scandit […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 15:29:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Death Row Prisoner’s Parting Interview</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/24/texas-death-row-prisoner-final-interview</link><description>Days before his scheduled execution in Texas, Ramiro Gonzales speaks on faith, legacy — and apologizing to the family of his victim, Bridget Townsend.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What’s Next in Health Care for Older Adults: Questions and Answers With John Whyte, MD</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/blog-aging-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>As WebMD’s chief medical officer, John Whyte, MD, is in a unique position to see both the current state of medical care for America’s older adults and the way things are trending for the future. We asked him to share his insight on a few topics, along with a bit of advice.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:29:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Yes, Earning Financial Independence Has Downsides</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/earning-financial-independence-has-downsides</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Earning financial independence requires making sacrifices that not many talk about.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A year later, what Threads could learn from other social networks</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/04/a-year-later-what-threads-could-learn-from-other-social-networks/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Threads, Meta’s alternative to Twitter, just celebrated its first birthday. After launching on July 5 last year, the social network has reached 175 million monthly active users — that’s a notable achievement. But, after a year, Threads is trying to find its own voice by not being as newsy as Twitter/X and not being as […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 13:36:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The New Battle Over an Old Institution: Forced Prison Labor</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/22/prison-slavery-forced-labor-lawsuits-bills</link><description>Inside the latest legal and legislative efforts to close state constitutional loopholes that allow slavery as punishment for a crime.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Get the Care You Need in a COVID-19 World</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/covid-senior-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>What to expect at the doctor’s office, hospitals, and long-term care facilities, the future of telemedicine, and how to get the best care during COVID-19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 19:50:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>My 1031 Exchange Property Is Listed. Here’s How I’m Managing the Clock.</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/1031-investor-journal-six</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>After six months, Liz's personal property is on the market and the 1031 exchange process is almost set.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>J2 Ventures, focused on military healthcare, grabs $150M for its second fund</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/04/j2-ventures-focused-on-military-healthcare-grabs-150m-for-its-second-fund/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>J2 Ventures, a firm led mostly by U.S. military veterans, announced on Thursday that it has raised a $150 million second fund. The Boston-based firm invests in startups whose products are purchased by civilians and the U.S. Department of Defense. While many emerging VCs are struggling to raise second funds, J2’s latest vehicle is more […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mississippi Wants to Allow Some Votes From Jails and Prisons. Red Tape May Stop It.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/20/mississippi-voting-from-prison-and-jails</link><description>A new state law will allow more people in jails and prisons to cast absentee ballots, but many obstacles remain.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Personal Shopper: A Savvy Black Entrepreneur Guides You to Eczema-Friendly Clothes, Creams, Cosmetics, and More</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/savvy-black-entrepreneur-guides-eczema-friendly-clothes-creams-cosmetics?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>A savvy black entrepreneur guides you on an eczema-friendly shopping spree.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:54:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is Rent-to-Own the Easiest and Most “Passive” Way to Scale Your Portfolio?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-427</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Do you have a cash flow problem? Maybe property management fees are setting you back, or you’re spending too much on repairs and maintenance. Today, we’re bringing you a powerful […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 07:02:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HealthEquity says data breach is an ‘isolated incident’</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/03/healthequity-says-data-breach-is-an-isolated-incident/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>HealthEquity said in an 8-K filing with the SEC that it detected “anomalous behavior by a personal use device belonging to a business partner.” © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 22:21:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Minneapolis Cop Who Beat Him Pleaded Guilty. He Still Fears the Department Won’t Change.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/16/police-minneapolis-beating-jaleel-stallings</link><description>Jaleel Stallings was swept up in the chaos of protests over George Floyd’s murder. The outcome changed his life.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Behind the Spike in Colorectal Cancer Among Young Americans</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/colorectal-cancer/news/20240515/behind-the-spike-in-colorectal-cancer-cases?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Colorectal cancer cases increased a whopping 333% among 15- to 19-year-olds and 185% among 20- to 24-year-olds from 1999 to 2020.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:59:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>