<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:05:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Utah Hockey Club Unveils Logos, Uniforms, Colours, and Name for 2024-25</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/13/utah-hockey-club-unveils-logos-uniforms-colours-and-name-for-2024-25/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>It’s officially official: Utah has an NHL team… and a name, logo, colours, and uniform (even if those last four are just temporary). Today, the National Hockey League made it official by announcing the Utah Hockey Club would join the league in time for the 2024-25 season, absorbing the roster,</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 01:30:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Teyana Taylor's Income Almost Twice Iman Shumpert's, So He Claims in Divorce</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/13/teyana-taylor-makes-almost-double-iman-shumpert-money-child-support/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Teyana Taylor is earning nearly double what Iman Shumpert makes every month ... at least that's what he's telling the judge overseeing their divorce. In new court documents, obtained by TMZ, Iman breaks down the estranged couple's finances ... and…</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:05:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rising Tides: Halifax NSL Club Unveils Name, Crest</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/13/rising-tides-halifax-nsl-club-unveils-name-crest/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Nova Scotia-based club is third of Northern Super League's six teams for inaugural season in 2025 to unveil their visual identity system</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 00:28:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Supreme Court Blocks 'Trump Too Small' Trademark Attempt</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/13/trump-too-small-trademark-rejected-supreme-court/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>A California man seeking to lock up the rights to a Donald Trump dig just took a legal L in the highest court in the land ... but he can still sell his shirts with the suggestive phrase. The Supreme Court just unanimously rejected Steve Elster's…</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:05:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MLB Releases Fourth of July Caps for 2024</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/13/mlb-releases-fourth-of-july-caps-for-2024/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Major League Baseball and New Era have unveiled the stars-and-stripes-themed caps that players, managers, coaches, and umpires will wear on-field for Independence Day in the United States on Thursday, July 4, 2024. This year, all 30 clubs will wear a cream-coloured crown, with teams again having the option of a</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 20:03:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Britney Spears Vacations in Mexico with Brother, Says She's Hitting the Bar</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/13/britney-spears-vacation-brother-bryan-mexico-bar/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Britney Spears isn't estranged from all of her relatives these days -- she's still got her brother, Bryan Spears, in her corner ... who's actually with her in Mexico as she parties it up. The pop star shared a brief sneak peek at a recent getaway…</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:05:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cardinals &amp; Giants Pay Tribute to Negro Leagues with Throwback Uniforms at Rickwood Field Next Week</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/12/cardinals-giants-pay-tribute-to-negro-leagues-with-throwback-uniforms-at-rickwood-field-next-week/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The special throwback uniforms for the Major League Baseball and Minor League Baseball games at Rickwood Field next week have been unveiled. The Major League game, officially known as “MLB at Rickwood Field,” will be played on June 20th. The San Francisco Giants and St. Louis Cardinals will wear uniforms</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 17:47:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gypsy Rose Blanchard Says She Experimented with Women in Prison</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/13/gypsy-rose-blanchard-experimented-women-prison-sexuality/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Gypsy Rose Blanchard says she never had a chance to properly explore her sexuality -- including potentially being attracted to women -- but when she was locked up ... she did. In the latest episode of Lifetime's "Gypsy Rose: Life After Lock Up,"…</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:05:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Baltimore Orioles Add Blue T. Rowe Price Patch to Jerseys</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/12/baltimore-orioles-add-blue-t-rowe-price-goat-patch-to-jerseys/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Baltimore Orioles have announced a new partnership with T. Rowe Price, a global investment management firm headquartered in Baltimore. The partnership will include adding their corporate logo to the sleeves of the Orioles jerseys. This patch made its debut last night during their game against the Atlanta Braves at</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 15:28:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shakira Says She Isn't Thinking About Dating Post-Piqué, But Open to Flings</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/13/shakira-not-thinking-about-dating-after-messy-split-pique/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Shakira isn't looking to lock down a new man -- but what's interesting is that she seems open to banging casually ... this after being linked to a ton of famous dudes of late. The singer talked about her dating life in her new cover story for…</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 02:05:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>