<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:39:30 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>CFL’s Edmonton Elks Introduce New Third Jersey Ahead of 75th Anniversary Season</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/05/cfls-edmonton-elks-introduce-new-third-jersey-ahead-of-75th-anniversary-season/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Tonal triangle pattern on shoulders represents evergreen forests in Northern Alberta and North Saskatchewan River valley; new logo based on team's original logo adorns sleeves</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 03:54:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gypsy Rose Blanchard's Lawsuit Against Blogger Dismissed, Wrong Venue</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/05/gypsy-rose-blanchard-lawsuit-blogger-dismissed-wrong-venue-jurisdiction/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Gypsy Rose Blanchard was trying to take a blogger to court for allegedly trashing her -- but a judge just told her to take her grievances elsewhere ... 'cause the case got thrown out. According to court records, GRB's lawsuit against April Johns --…</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:39:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Utah Jazz Unveil New Uniforms With Two-Season Rollout</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/05/utah-jazz-unveil-new-uniforms-with-two-season-rollout/basketball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Utah Jazz have unveiled four new uniforms as part of a two-season transition that will once again put mountains and the color purple at the forefront of their branding.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 20:47:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adam Levine Returning To 'The Voice' As a Judge, Joining Next Season</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/05/adam-levine-returning-the-voice-singing-coach/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Adam Levine is making a reality TV comeback ... returning to "The Voice" after several seasons away from the singing competition show. The Maroon 5 frontman just announced his upcoming return as a coach on the NBC show ... he'll be back for Season…</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:39:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MLB 2024 All-Star Game Workout Day Caps Leaked</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/05/mlb-2024-all-star-game-workout-day-caps-leaked/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>There’s a Major League Baseball All-Star Game leak; it must be Summer! Thanks to a recent series of Tweets, we’ve gotten a first glimpse at one of this year’s MLB All-Star Game uniforms, which will be worn during the All-Star festivities in Arlington, Texas, next month. Just so everyone’s clear,</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 19:50:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hunter Biden's Ex-GF Claims He'd Smoke Crack As Soon As He'd Wake Up</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/05/hunter-biden-trial-ex-girlfried-claims-would-smoke-crack-wake-up/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Different kind of wake-and-bake for Hunter Biden ... at least that's what his ex-girlfriend claimed on the stand, alleging he'd light up a crack pipe upon waking up in his drug days. Hunter's ex, Zoe Kestan, testified in court out in Delaware…</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:39:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Boston Marathon Marks Global Running Day With New Race Logo</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/05/boston-marathon-marks-global-running-day-with-new-race-logo/other/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>To mark Global Running Day on Wednesday, June 5, perhaps the world’s most famous foot race unveiled a new logo. The Boston Athletic Association unveiled the new logo for the Boston Marathon on Wednesday, along with the announcement of a commitment of $500 million over the next 10 years to</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 16:26:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Robert F. Kennedy Jr. Says Biden Fears Debating Him More Than Trump Does</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/05/robert-f-kennedy-jr-rfk-fec-complaint-biden-trump-presidential-debate/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>It doesn't look like Robert F. Kennedy Jr. is going to have a chance to join President Biden and former prez Donald Trump on the debate stage this month -- and he thinks it's mostly Biden blocking him. We spoke to the independent presidential…</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:39:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Real Madrid Keep it Simple With 2024-25 Home Kits</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/05/real-madrid-keep-it-simple-with-2024-25-home-kits/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Traditional predominantly white kits include subtle houndstooth pattern with R and M shapes on front and back, along with black accents</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 15:44:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Halyna Hutchins' Family's Attorney Slams Alec Baldwin Reality TV Show</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/05/halyna-hutchins-family-attorney-gloria-allred-slam-alec-baldwin-reality-tv-show/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Halyna Hutchins' family's attorney is pissed about Alec Baldwin's new reality show ... side-eyeing the timing of the announcement and referring to it as a public relations stunt. Gloria Allred -- who's repping members of the late cinematographer's…</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:39:30 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>