<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from multiple RSS sources, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:50:24 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Sunbelt Surge: 15 Cities Dominating the Growth Charts</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/best-sunbelt-markets-for-growth</link><description>Simply investing in any metro Sunbelt market is not a recipe for success. To catch a cresting wave of appreciation and cash flow, you’ll need to dive deep into the metrics […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:48:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JioCinema launches 35-cent premium tier, stepping up rivalry with Netflix and Prime Video</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/24/jiocinema-launches-35-cent-premium-tier-stepping-up-rivalry-with-netflix-and-prime-video/</link><description>JioCinema introduced a new monthly subscription plan on Thursday, with the lowest tier costing just 35 cents. The revamp in the pricing strategy comes as the market-leading service seeks to exert greater pressure on rivals including Netflix and Prime Video. The service — backed by Asia’s richest man, Mukesh Ambani — introduced two monthly tiers: […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:39:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Enduring Use of Solitary, and New Proposed Limits That Will Likely Fail (Again)</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/20/solitary-confinement-reform-oklahoma-washington-florida</link><description>Isolation’s damaging effects are widely known. But many facilities confine people — even youth — virtually all day, sometimes in shower stalls.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Getting Cancer Care in Rural America</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/cancer/features/cancer-care-rural-america?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>With fewer oncologists in rural areas than in cities, there are challenges in getting cancer care. Find out what may help bridge that gap.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:48:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Warning: These States and Cities Are Becoming Uninvestable Due to Politics</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/how-politics-is-making-these-states-and-cities-uninvestable</link><description>Taxes and regulations impact your bottom line as an investor—and not always in direct or obvious ways. Unfortunately, as soon as you start talking about either one, the average person closes their […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:27:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eric Schmidt-backed Augment, a GitHub Copilot rival, launches out of stealth with $252M</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/24/eric-schmidt-backed-augment-a-github-copilot-rival-launches-out-of-stealth-with-252m/</link><description>AI is supercharging coding — and developers are embracing it. In a recent StackOverflow poll, 44% of software engineers said that they use AI tools as part of their development processes now and 26% plan to soon. Gartner estimates that over half of organizations are currently piloting or have already deployed AI-driven coding assistants, and […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:36:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Officials Failed to Act When COVID Hit Prisons. A New Study Shows the Deadly Cost.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/18/covid-prison-deaths-data</link><description>People in prison died at 3.4 times the rate of the free population, with the oldest hit hardest. New data holds lessons for preventing future deaths.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Common Chemicals: Breast Cancer Link?</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/breast-cancer/features/common-chemicals-breast-cancer-link?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Experts discuss whether chemicals in our environment have a connection to the risk of breast cancer.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:35:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The BEST Ways to Protect Your Rental Property and Keep Your Tenants Safe</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-397</link><description>If you own a rental property, it’s YOUR responsibility to provide a safe environment for tenants. This starts with things like tenant screening, security upgrades, and most importantly, acting swiftly […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:02:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Radical thinks the time has come for solar-powered, high-altitude autonomous aircraft</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/24/radical-thinks-the-time-has-come-for-solar-powered-high-altitude-autonomous-aircraft/</link><description>Though many eyes are on space as orbit develops into a thriving business ecosystem, Radical is keeping things a little closer to the ground — but not too close. Its high-altitude, solar-powered aircraft aim to succeed where Facebook’s infamous Aquila failed by refining the tech and embracing more markets. It’s hard to believe that Facebook’s […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:52:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Parents Paying for Their Children’s Crimes</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/13/michigan-school-shooting-parents</link><description>Experts warn about a wave of legal consequences for parents like the Crumbleys, while some states consider prosecutions for kids as young as 10.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Transgender People at Risk of Breast Cancer?</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/breast-cancer/features/breast-cancer-risk-transgender-people?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Breast cancer can happen in people of any gender. Learn about what factors affect breast cancer risk in transgender people.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:24:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Building Wealth with OLD Homes and How to Keep Tenants for Longer</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-942</link><description>How do you find investment properties nobody else is looking for—the ones with cash flow potential, equity upside, and wealth-building qualities all the other investors overlook? Simple: buy what nobody […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:02:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stripe, doubling down on embedded finance, de-couples payments from the rest of its stack</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/24/stripe-doubling-down-on-embedded-finance-de-couples-payments-from-the-rest-of-its-stack/</link><description>Stripe continues to hold the title of being the biggest financial technology business still in private hands, with a current valuation of about $65 billion and a whopping $1 trillion in total processed payment volume last year alone. But fintech is fragmented and a fast-moving target, and with competitors chipping away at its place, Stripe is […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:32:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I Had a Tough Job at My Brooklyn Jail: Keeping Men From Taking Their Own Lives</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/12/brooklyn-jail-suicide-prevention-aide</link><description>As a suicide prevention aide, I had to make sure my fellow detainees didn’t harm themselves. It was surprisingly easy to get such a complex job.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Breast Cancer Mammography vs. Thermography</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/breast-cancer/features/mammography-vs-thermography?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Mammography is still the tried-and-true, go-to tool doctors and the FDA recommend for screening for breast cancer. Thermography isn’t recommended.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:21:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Investor’s Guide to a Single-Family Rental Emergency Fund</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/the-investors-guide-to-a-single-family-rental-emergency-fund</link><description>This article is presented by REI Nation. Read our editorial guidelines for more information. As real estate investors, your emergency funds are a critical line of defense against unexpected costs. It prevents you from dipping into […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 19:23:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why code-testing startup Nova AI uses open source LLMs more than OpenAI</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/24/why-code-testing-startup-nova-ai-uses-open-source-llms-more-than-openai/</link><description>Enterprises still don't trust OpenAI, while open source AI models are cheaper and more than sufficient for targeted specific tasks, Nova AI founder says.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:08:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Supreme Court Case on Homelessness May Limit Prisoner Rights and Expand Executions</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/10/supreme-court-homeless-grants-pass-originalism</link><description>In Grants Pass v. Johnson, a town in Oregon asks the court to reconsider what constitutes “cruel and unusual punishments.”</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Breast Cancer Pathology Report: What It Means</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/breast-cancer/features/breast-cancer-pathology-report?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>When you find out that you have breast cancer, your pathology report is an important part of your medical record. Get to know what it means.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:17:15 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>