<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 06:58:39 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>West Virginia Mountaineers Unveil New Football Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/29/west-virginia-mountaineers-unveil-new-football-uniforms/college/</link><description>West Virginia unveiled new uniforms over the weekend that pay homage to different eras of Mountaineer football while maintaining a few modern touches.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 19:39:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Weeknd's Manager Security Guard Shot In Attempted Home Invasion</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/29/the-weeknd-manager-cash-xo-attempted-home-invasion-security-shot/</link><description>The Weeknd's manager Amir "Cash XO" Esmailian is currently dealing with the aftermath of a scary situation -- this after one of his security guards was shot multiple times. Law enforcement sources tell TMZ ... the shooting occurred early Monday…</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 06:58:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Grit and Glow: Tampa Bay Rays Unveil Skateboard-Inspired City Connect Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/29/grit-and-glow-tampa-bay-rays-unveil-skateboard-inspired-city-connect-uniforms/baseball/</link><description>The Tampa Bay Rays unveiled their new Nike MLB City Connect Series uniform today, taking inspiration from the region’s skateboarding culture while also mixing in a few fun little nods to the team’s history. These uniforms are set to make their on-field debut during a special weekend series from May</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 16:42:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kim Zolciak &amp; Kroy Biermann's Home to Be Foreclosed in Days Unless They Act</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/29/kim-zolciak-kroy-biermann-georgia-home-foreclosure-date-set/</link><description>Kim Zolciak and Kroy Biermann could be out on their ass soon -- their lender is letting them know loud and clear that they plan to foreclose on their house ... unless they make some moves in court. According to new legal docs, obtained by TMZ,…</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 06:58:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jacksonville Jaguars Reveal 30th Season Logo Following Fan Vote</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/28/jacksonville-jaguars-reveal-30th-season-logo-following-fan-vote/football/</link><description>After asking fans to vote among four unique designs, the Jacksonville Jaguars officially unveiled their new 30th season logo during their 2024 NFL Draft party on Thursday evening.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 15:43:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Selena Quintanilla's Brother A.B. Apologizes After Chastising Festival Crowd</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/29/selena-quintanilla-brother-ab-apologizes-festival-music-outburst/</link><description>Selena Quintanilla's brother, A.B., III is offering up an apology after losing it on fans this weekend during a music festival in Texas ... and he's blaming the fact he was off his meds. In a since-deleted video shared to Instagram, the musician --…</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 06:58:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NFL Will Allow Players To Wear Guardian Caps In Games</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/28/nfl-will-allow-players-to-wear-guardian-caps-in-games/football/</link><description>The NFL announced it will now allow players to wear Guardian Caps, a 12-ounce soft shell that fits over their helmets, during regular-season games in an effort to reduce head injuries.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 15:25:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Travis Kelce Gets New Contract, Highest Paid Tight End In NFL</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/29/travis-kelce-tight-end-contract-extension-taylor-swift-chiefs-nfl/</link><description>Travis Kelce was already having an amazing 2024 ... he won Super Bowl LVIII, he's dating the biggest star in the world, and now he's getting a new, fat contract extension -- making him the richest tight end in the NFL! The 34-year-old perennial Pro…</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 06:58:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Report: CFL’s Saskatchewan Roughriders to Add Fourth Uniform in 2024</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/27/report-cfls-saskatchewan-roughriders-to-add-fourth-uniform-in-2024/football/</link><description>Riders reportedly adding uniform that's predominantly a darker shade of green than usual; helmet to feature logo filed with Canadian trademark office in 2022</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 18:13:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Los Angeles Comedian Rudy Moreno Hospitalized in ICU, Wife Can't Find Him</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/29/rudy-moreno-los-angeles-comedian-hospital-icu-wife-cant-find-him/</link><description>Rudy Moreno -- a veteran L.A. comedian who's huge in the Latin comedy scene -- is currently hospitalized in the ICU ... but his spouse tells us she can't even locate him. The stand-up's wife, Arlene, tells TMZ ... Rudy's been in the intensive care…</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 06:58:39 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>