<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 15:17:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Nats, Orioles to Play in MLB’s First-Ever All-City Connect Uniform Game</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/03/nats-orioles-to-play-in-mlbs-first-ever-all-city-connect-uniform-game/baseball/</link><description>For the first time in Major League Baseball history, two teams will wear their Nike MLB City Connect uniforms in the same game. This morning, the Washington Nationals announced they will don their cherry blossom-themed City Connect uniforms when they host the Baltimore Orioles on Tuesday, May 7 for the</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 15:40:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cop Shoots at Pack of Dogs Attacking Man in the Street in Harrowing Video</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/02/philadelphia-police-cop-shoot-pit-bulls-cane-corso-dogs-attack-man-video/</link><description>An unsettling scene unfolded in Philadelphia -- where a police officer had to shoot a canine after a pack of dogs started to maul a poor man in the street, in broad daylight. This disturbing footage is making the rounds online -- and it shows the…</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 15:17:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cincinnati Bengals Reveal Updated Turf Design</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/02/cincinnati-bengals-reveal-updated-turf-design/football/</link><description>The Cincinnati Bengals are in the process of installing new FieldTurf at Paycor Stadium and will have an updated design as a result.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 22:33:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Man Claims to Have Caught 'Time Traveler' Using His Shed in Wild Video</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/02/time-traveler-hides-shed-viral-video-tiktok/</link><description>One guy claims to have captured a real-life Marty McFly on camera at his Florida Airbnb -- posting a video that certainly seems to suggest time travel is real ... if you buy this, that is. A dude named Alec Schaal posted a series of videos this…</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 15:17:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Liverpool FC Pays Homage to Treble-Winning 1984 Squad With 2024-25 Home Kit</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/02/liverpool-fc-pays-homage-to-treble-winning-1984-squad-with-2024-25-home-kit/soccer/</link><description>Front and back of shirt feature yellow pinstripe pattern that spells out "YWNA" for club motto, "You'll Never Walk Alone"</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:19:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Britney Spears in Huge Fight With Boyfriend, Hotel Guests Fear Mental Breakdown</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/02/britney-spears-fight-injured-boyfriend-paul-soliz-chateau-marmont-mental-breakdown/</link><description>Britney Spears got into a huge fight with her boyfriend Wednesday night, and she ended up out of control, crying, possibly cut, and almost driven away in an ambulance ... TMZ has learned. Britney got to the Chateau Marmont late Wednesday night with…</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 15:17:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ope! Madison Mallards unveil another alternate</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/02/ope-madison-mallards-unveil-another-alternate/baseball/</link><description>There are a lot of theories about the origins of the quirky exclamation “Ope!”—none of which stand up to any real scrutiny. More onomatopoeia than actual word, the term has been likened to “oops” or “oh” plus the letter P, and associated with most anywhere human beings have made inadvertent</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 12:07:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ryan Reynolds' Dive Into Sports Apparel Inspired by Wrexham, 'Deadpool'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/03/ryan-reynolds-dive-into-sports-apparel-inspired-by-wrexham-deadpool/</link><description>Ryan Reynolds is doubling down on his investment in the sports world, and it's in large part due to fans of his 2 biggest franchises ... TMZ has learned. The actor's investment firm, Maximum Effort, announced Thursday it's spending big to become…</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 15:17:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tri-City Chili Peppers to play “Cosmic Baseball” under black lights</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/01/tri-city-chili-peppers-to-play-cosmic-baseball-under-black-lights/baseball/</link><description>Nearly a century after the Negro Leagues’ Kansas City Monarchs became the first professional baseball team to host a baseball game under artificial lights, the Coastal Plain League’s Tri-City Chili Peppers are putting their own spin on that innovation. The team will play “Cosmic Baseball” under powerful black lights that</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 02:45:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>President Biden's L.A. Visit Cost LAPD Millions in Staffing</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/03/president-joe-biden-los-angeles-visit-cops-cost-millions/</link><description>President Biden's got a nice chunk o' change for his campaign war chest after visiting Los Angeles, but it did the opposite for the city ... draining millions from the budget. According to documents, obtained by TMZ, additional LAPD staffing costs…</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 15:17:48 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>