<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 12:07:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Babe Ruth ‘Called Shot’ Jersey Could Fetch $30M at Auction</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/16/babe-ruth-called-shot-jersey-could-fetch-30-million-at-auction/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The jersey Babe Ruth was wearing during one of the most iconic moments of his career is going up for auction, and it could sell for a record-breaking amount of money. Ruth’s road grey New York Yankees jersey with the number 3 on the back will be put up for</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 17:01:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Matthew Perry Death, Charges Against 2 Doctors, 'Ketamine Queen' and Personal Assistant</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/15/matthew-perry-case-us-attorney/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>5:57 PM PT -- Jasveen Sangha, AKA "The Ketamine Queen," and Dr. Salvador Plasencia appeared in court Thursday and pleaded not guilty. Sangha was jailed without bond and the judge set Dr. Plasencia's bond at $100,000. Her trial is set for October 8,…</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 12:07:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Numbers on Caps, Colourful Equipment this Weekend in MLB</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/16/numbers-on-caps-colourful-equipment-this-weekend-in-mlb/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Why are baseball players wearing numbers on their hats this weekend? Because Players’ Weekend is back! Major League Baseball Players’ Weekend is meant to be a platform for players to celebrate the people, places, and causes that have influenced their lives (while, naturally, sneaking in some new merch out there</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 16:42:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Doctors In Matthew Perry Case Investigated By Medical Board, Still Have Licenses</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/15/doctors-matthew-perry-case-investigation-medical-licenses-active/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>The two doctors charged in connection with Matthew Perry's death are being investigated by the Medical Board of California, but they haven't had their licenses suspended ... at least not yet. Dr. Mark Chavez and Dr. Salvador Plasencia are the two…</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 12:07:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2024-25 European Football Kit Preview: Premier League</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/16/2024-25-european-football-kit-preview-premier-league/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>33rd season of Premier League and 126th season of English top flight soccer kicks off on Friday, August 16, with match between Manchester United and Fulham</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Guess Who This Charming Kiddo Turned Into!</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/16/guess-who-charming-kiddo-turned-into/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Before this cool lil guy giving major side-eye and a smise turned into a broadcaster, he was just playing with his pet snake, Sam, and growing up with quite a famous mama (a Vanderbilt) and runnin' around the concrete jungle! From a young age, this…</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 12:07:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>West Virginia Mountaineers To Honor Jerry West With Commemorative Logo, Throwback Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/15/west-virginia-mountaineers-to-honor-jerry-west-with-commemorative-logo-throwback-uniforms/basketball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>West Virginia will honor late NBA great Jerry West with a commemorative logo, which will be worn by all 18 varsity sports teams on their jerseys, warm-ups or helmets throughout the 2024-25 season, as well as throwback basketball uniforms.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 03:00:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TMZ TV Hot Takes: Arrests In Matthew Perry Death Case, North West, Tom Brady</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/16/tmz-tv-hot-takes-matthew-perry-case-north-west-tom-brady/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>There was a big break in the Matthew Perry death case, North West is twinning with her dog, and Tom Brady is showing off his arm ... all this on today's TMZ Hot Takes. First up on "TMZ Live," Harvey and Charles break down all the arrests and…</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 12:07:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Think Fast: Ottawa NSL Franchise Rolls Out ‘Rapid FC’ Name, Logo</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/15/think-fast-ottawa-nsl-franchise-rolls-out-rapid-fc-name-logo/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Crest shows a peregrine falcon streaking into the middle of an O with a tulip at the top; club also releases French-language primary and secondary logos</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 23:40:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Olympian Alysha Newman Says OnlyFans Page Has Exploded Since Viral Twerk</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/16/alysha-newman-twerking-onlyfans-olympics/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Canadian pole vaulter Alysha Newman's twerking celebration in France has been great for her wallet ... she tells TMZ Sports the impromptu dance has led to an explosion of followers on her OnlyFans page. The Olympian broke it all down for us this…</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 12:07:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>