<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 07:26:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Implementation Shortfalls Hamstring Factor Strategies</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/01/implementation-shortfalls-hamstring-factor-strategies/</link><description>Smart rebalancing rules help portfolio managers capture more of the return that is inherent in their factor strategies. Concentrating on “priority best” trading improves factor portfolio performance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 11:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Californians are sick of the 'malaise that's plagued' the state, says CEO who plans to build new city in the Bay Area—and he's submitted 20,000 signatures to prove it</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/01/california-forever-signatures-submitted-bay-area-green-city/</link><description>The Silicon Valley-backed campaign to build a green city in the San Francisco Bay Area has submitted what it says are enough signatures to qualify for the November election.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 12:12:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IFRS Accounting Standard Will Support Better Investment Decisions</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/30/ifrs-accounting-standard-will-support-better-investment-decisions/</link><description>IFRS 18 responds to investors' concerns about challenges in comparing companies' financial performance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 11:34:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deliveroo driver bit off customer's thumb—now U.K. government cracks down on account sharing</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/01/deliveroo-rider-surrey-customers-thumbnow-uk-government-delivery-platforms-account-sharing/</link><description>Delivery platforms will carry out enhanced checks on riders, as substitute rider Jennifer Roche faces a prison sentence for attacking a customer.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 11:23:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meir Statman: Your State of Mind Influences Your Investing Success</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/29/meir-statman-your-state-of-mind-influences-your-investing-success/</link><description>Meir Statman shares his insights on the broader aspects of financial well-being and its interconnection with life satisfaction.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 12:58:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aston Martin's first quarter earnings drop 34% as it awaits fourth CEO in four years</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/01/aston-martin-q1-earnings-drop-34-percent-new-ceo-adrian-hallmark/</link><description>The luxury carmaker shipped 945 vehicles in the period, a 26% decline from the prior year, while revenue dropped 10% to $334 million.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 10:42:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: Trailblazers, Heroes, and Crooks</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/26/book-review-trailblazers-heroes-and-crooks/</link><description>Stephen Foerster, CFA, extracts lessons from exceptional episodes in financial history that ordinary investors and seasoned professionals alike can put to profitable use. The bonus is that you'll be entertained from start to finish.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Novo Nordisk's market value of $570 billion is now bigger than the entire Danish economy—creating a 'Nokia risk' for Denmark</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/01/novo-nordisk-market-value-570-billion-bigger-than-danish-denmark-economy/</link><description>“When you have superpowers, you have super responsibility," says CEO Lars Fruergaard Jorgensen.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 10:40:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Price Risk? Unpacking the Equity Risk Premium</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/24/what-price-risk-unpacking-the-equity-risk-premium/</link><description>Stocks are a good wager over the long term, on favorable odds. But stocks remain a bet, and investors must grasp how much returns can vary over long time horizons.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Geely-backed Polestar pushes back results for second time in a year, as the Swedish carmaker battles accounting errors</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/01/swedish-ev-maker-polestar-accounting-error-second-time-in-year-sluggish-auto-sales-cash-burn/</link><description>The EV maker is relying on new models such as the Polestar 4 coupe to bolster sales.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 10:02:33 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>