<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:41:37 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The Best BIPOC New Releases + Beach Reads</title><link>https://bookriot.com/best-bipoc-new-releases-beach-reads/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Untitled-design-2024-05-14T141619.580.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>Which new books out today are you adding to the TBR?</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:19:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Used car prices held flat in April 2024 while payments increased</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/article/used-car-prices-held-flat-in-april-2024-while-payments-increased/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/14112855/shutterstock_2172554281.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Car Buying , Used Car Buying Continue reading Used car prices held flat in April 2024 while payments increased Used car prices held flat in April 2024 while payments increased originally appeared on Autoblog on Tue, 14 May 2024 13:02:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 18:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GameStop, AMC attracting a fraction of retail trader interest seen during 2021's meme mania</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/14/gamestop-amc-attracting-a-fraction-of-retail-trader-interest-seen-during-2021s-meme-mania.html</link><description>Mom-and-pop traders snapped up shares after the man credited with starting the meme stock mania resurfaced online, though at a lesser extent than seen in 2021.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:24:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 553</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-553/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-553</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Tools and technology change rapidly. Yet as wonderful as technology can be, it doesn’t replace the need for human connection through interactions. Keep this in mind as you are searching for a new job. It’s your human connections that often open doors! In this week’s collection of news and tips for job seekers, you’ll find: […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 553 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 12:19:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A case for public preschool: New study reveals preschool benefits to be longer-lasting and substantial</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/benefits-of-public-preschool/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=benefits-of-public-preschool</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Preschool lays a foundation for elementary school students to succeed. In the United States, as children approach kindergarten entry, it is increasingly common for 4-year-olds to be in non-parental group care and education, often in a center- or school-based setting where they can learn alongside peers. For children from low-income communities, […] The post A case for public preschool: New study reveals preschool benefits to be longer-lasting and substantial appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 08:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wood-Fired Pizza Dough</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/wood-fired-pizza-dough/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>This is the perfect beginner’s guide for making wood-fired pizza dough! Pizza expert, Chef Brandon Price, taught me how to…</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Easy Low-Light Indoor Plants</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/easy-low-light-indoor-plants/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>I used to think every houseplant needed a sunny corner or bright windowsill to thrive. But it turns out many of our favorite go-to houseplants do just fine in shady corners and low-light locations. So before you write off your house as too dark to sustain plant life, check out this list of the best indoor plants for low light. You might be surprised at how many good options there are! Our upstairs family room is the brightest room we’ve ever owned thanks to big unobstructed windows on all 4 sides. But most of our indoor plants live downstairs, where we get far less natural light. Luckily, that hasn’t stopped us from growing our collection of happy healthy houseplants. 9 Houseplants That Don’t Need A Lot Of Light Here are our favorite low-light indoor plants. We list a lot more info on them below, but here’s a quick list to bring on your next trip to the plant store: Snake Plant ZZ Plant Pothos Heartleaf Philodendron English Ivy Aglaonema Cast Iron Plant Monstera Parlor Palm Perhaps our favorite part of this list is that these aren’t ugly “consolation plants” that people begrudgingly buy for dark homes. Continue reading Easy Low-Light Indoor Plants at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 14:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>My Saks May Array</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/my-saks-may-array/</link><description>Outfit Details: Sandro Top, Erdem Skirt, Prada Bag, Sherman Fields Necklace Thank you to Saks Fifth Avenue for sponsoring this… The post My Saks May Array appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 05:00:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nobel Prize-Winning Author Alice Munro has Died at 92</title><link>https://bookriot.com/alice-munro-has-died/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/off-center-collage-1.png</image_url><description>She won the Nobel Prize for Literature in 2013, with the Academy saying she could "accommodate the entire epic complexity of the novel in just a few short pages."</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:57:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jackery Explorer 2000 Pro portable power station is now at its lowest price ever</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/article/jackery-explorer-2000-pro-portable-power-station-is-now-at-its-lowest-price-ever/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/13164327/Jackery-2000-PRO-copy.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Commerce Continue reading Jackery Explorer 2000 Pro portable power station is now at its lowest price ever Jackery Explorer 2000 Pro portable power station is now at its lowest price ever originally appeared on Autoblog on Tue, 14 May 2024 12:20:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:20:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Top bond fund manager Ford O'Neil of Fidelity reveals his 'secret sauce' to generate outperformance</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/14/top-bond-fund-manager-ford-oneil-reveals-his-secret-sauce-to-outperform.html</link><description>O'Neil was recently nominated for Morningstar's 2024 outstanding portfolio manager award for investing excellence.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 552</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-552/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-552</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>When you are searching for a job, you will inevitably run into unexpected scenarios. You will have questions, experience self-doubt and even feel discouraged. You’ll also experience great wins, meet wonderful people and discover new things about yourself. That’s the roller-coaster of job search. Consider Summary Sunday your resource for getting questions answered and showing […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 552 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 11:37:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fathers’ views on family and work after COVID-19 lockdowns</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/fathers-views-on-family-and-work-after-covid-19-lockdowns/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fathers-views-on-family-and-work-after-covid-19-lockdowns</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Fathers often want to be present for their children and contribute to household tasks, but they can lack opportunities and confidence; they may see themselves as “helpers” instead of parents. Australian fathers in our small study reported that they spent more time with their children during the COVID-19 lockdowns, and they […] The post Fathers’ views on family and work after COVID-19 lockdowns appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blueberry Lemon Upside-Down Cake</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/blueberry-lemon-upside-cake/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Be prepared to fall in love with this blueberry lemon upside-down cake! A delicious and moist lemon sponge cake bursting…</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/how-to-remove-wallpaper/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Wallpaper has made a big comeback as a trendy home design choice. But despite its resurgence, there are still plenty of us dealing with dingy, dated, or downright ugly old wallpaper we don’t want. In our old home, we had to remove wallpaper in so many rooms: the kitchen, the dining room, the foyer, and two different bathrooms! As we traveled from room to room removing wallpaper, we tested 4 different methods, and today we’ll share what we learned. Removing wallpaper doesn’t require special tools or lots of money. It’s a totally doable project for any homeowner. However, it can be a tedious process that can take elbow grease and patience, depending on the size of your room and the stubbornness of your wallpaper. But having removed several rooms worth of decades-old wallpaper, we can confidently say it’s worth the effort! You can also check out more before and afters of our once-wallpapered rooms. Continue reading How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:21:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Our Latest Favorites From Amazon</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/our-latest-favorites-from-amazon/</link><description>Outfit Details: Beaded Handmade Bag Welcome to our latest favorites from Amazon that I’m especially excited to share! This week… The post Our Latest Favorites From Amazon appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 05:00:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Enid Public Library Board Bans Pride Display, Entering Third Year of Pride Display Battles</title><link>https://bookriot.com/enid-public-library-bans-pride-display/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Untitled-design-55.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>A Pride display at Enid Public Library has once again been banned by the board, despite having been approved the prior two years. A history of this board's LGBTQ+ display bans.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 16:55:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2025 Genesis GV80 First Drive: It's what's inside that counts</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/14/2025-genesis-gv80-first-drive-review/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/13145058/GenesisGV80400-copy.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Genesis , First Drives , SUV , Luxury Continue reading 2025 Genesis GV80 First Drive: It's what's inside that counts 2025 Genesis GV80 First Drive: It's what's inside that counts originally appeared on Autoblog on Tue, 14 May 2024 12:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Walmart is laying off, relocating hundreds of corporate workers across the country. Read the memo</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/14/walmart-to-lay-off-relocate-hundreds-of-corporate-workers.html</link><description>The move follows the closures of the company's health clinics and comes ahead of its earnings report on Thursday.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 18:53:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>While a little competition in the workplace might help bring out the best in everyone involved, an atmosphere rooted in envy, fear, or jealousy can do the exact opposite. This post will help you recognize signs that your coworker is threatened by you, and help you navigate the situation. 1. They Don’t Want You Involved […] The post 10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:07:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Strong Latine Identity Supports U.S. Latine Children’s Well-Being</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/a-strong-latine-identity-supports-u-s-latine-childrens-well-being/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=a-strong-latine-identity-supports-u-s-latine-childrens-well-being</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key Takeaways for caregivers Children tend to have better health and well-being when they have a strong ethnic identity (affinity and adoption of ethnicity-based self-concept). A traditional Latine cultural value (familismo) that emphasizes family bonds is also associated with better developmental outcomes. Caregivers can support the development of U.S. Latine children (and possibly other children […] The post A Strong Latine Identity Supports U.S. Latine Children’s Well-Being appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 03:03:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cinnamon Roll Casserole</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/cinnamon-roll-casserole/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Get ready for a tasty treat with this easy cinnamon roll casserole! Using canned cinnamon rolls, this casserole is so…</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aglaonema Plant – Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/aglaonema-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Aglaonema, also called the Chinese Evergreen Plant, is an easy-care houseplant that lives happily in many lighting conditions – even a dark corner of our daughter’s room. There are dozens of different Aglaonema varieties, most with large tropical foliage and colors ranging from silvery-green, red, and even vibrant pink. They’re also tough to kill, so they’re a great option for forgetful plant owners or anyone looking for an easy win in the plant department. These truly have been very low maintenance for us. We purchased our two Aglaonemas (pronounced ag-lee-oh-neem-ah ) to put atop our daughter’s closet. It’s sometimes hard to distinguish different varieties, but we believe that’s an Aglaonema Silver (right) and either a Candy Cane or Princess Silver Queen (left). Aglaonema Quick Facts Here’s what you need to know about your Aglaonema at a glance: Latin name : Aglaonema is the genus under which there are 21 recognized species . Continue reading Aglaonema Plant – Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:47:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amazon Home Refresh Tips</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/amazon-home-refresh-tips/</link><description>Embrace the mid-spring refresh with Amazon and give your home a vibrant makeover for the season. Amazon makes it easy… The post Amazon Home Refresh Tips appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 05:00:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Trailer for The Lord of The Rings: The Rings of Power Season 2</title><link>https://bookriot.com/new-trailer-for-the-lord-of-the-rings-the-rings-of-power-season-2/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Rings-of-Power-season-two-trailer.jpeg.optimal.jpeg</image_url><description>Will be watching season two?</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 16:54:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Well-built little Chinese EV called the Seagull poses big threat to U.S. auto industry</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/14/well-built-little-chinese-ev-called-the-seagull-poses-big-threat-to-u-s-auto-industry/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/14115403/visitors_inspect_a_byd_seagull_car_during_the_45th_bangkok___.jpeg</image_url><description>Filed under: Green , Electric Continue reading Well-built little Chinese EV called the Seagull poses big threat to U.S. auto industry Well-built little Chinese EV called the Seagull poses big threat to U.S. auto industry originally appeared on Autoblog on Tue, 14 May 2024 11:57:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 16:57:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Education Dept. announces highest interest rate on federal student loans in more than a decade</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/14/education-dept-announces-2024-25-interest-rates-on-student-loans.html</link><description>The U.S. Department of Education announced on Tuesday the interest rates on federal student loans for the 2024-2025 academic year.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 18:49:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 551</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-551/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-551</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Job search requires writing and marketing skills. It also requires strong verbal communication. If these skills are not part of your normal work function, you’ll want some help. That’s what this week’s Summary Sunday is all about. There’s no doubt that LinkedIn is one of THE most powerful tools in your career toolbox. It contains […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 551 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 11:37:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Children caught between highly conflicted divorced parents at greater risk of mental health problems</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/children-caught-between-conflicted-divorced-parents/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=children-caught-between-conflicted-divorced-parents</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Interparental conflict after divorce escalates the risk of mental health problems in children and adolescents. Elevated levels of conflict between parents can also induce fear and worry in children about their future and whether they will be adequately taken care of. In turn, a greater fear of abandonment puts children at […] The post Children caught between highly conflicted divorced parents at greater risk of mental health problems appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 08:59:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Thai Chicken Salad</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/thai-chicken-salad/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Crunchy and bright, this Thai Chicken Salad with creamy peanut dressing is bursting with flavor, texture and deliciousness! Prep it in…</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Corn Plant – Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/corn-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Corn plants ( Dracaena fragrans ) are popular low-maintenance houseplants you’ve probably seen at the nursery, home improvement store, or doctor’s office. I even had one in my college dorm room! You can recognize them by their spear-shaped leaves and woody, cane-line trunks that can grow up to 6 feet tall indoors. But did you know there are several varieties of corn plants? We didn’t! Heck, we didn’t even realize some of our smaller houseplants were in the same corn plant family! Currently, we own two smaller varieties of corn plants, pictured above. The one on the left is a Dracaena Limelight ( Dracaena fragrans ‘Limelight’ ) and the taller plant is a Draecanea Dorado ( Dracaena fragrans ‘Dorado’ ). We actually have several limelights around because we love their vibrant color on shelves, tabletops, and windowsills. Corn Plant Quick Facts Latin name : Dracaena fragrans Common names : Corn plant, cornstalk plant, false palms Light : Bright, indirect light but can tolerate lower-light conditions Watering : Keep soil moist, but not soggy. Continue reading Corn Plant – Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 17:37:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shell Season</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/shell-season/</link><description>Spring welcomes the captivating allure of shell season. As nature awakens and warmth spreads, ocean treasures inspire wardrobe choices. This… The post Shell Season appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:58:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Riot’s Deals of the Day for May 14, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/book-riots-deals-of-the-day-for-may-14-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/deals-051424.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>A land of gods and monsters, a *very* special book, a mysterious alien biodome, and more of today's best book deals.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 16:24:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Warm weather's back — and with it, reminders to prevent hot car deaths</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/article/warm-weathers-back-and-with-it-reminders-to-prevent-hot-car-deaths/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/14110953/female_driver_and_cheerful_young_boy_on_back_seat_.jpeg</image_url><description>Filed under: Government/Legal , Safety , Technology , Emerging Technologies Continue reading Warm weather's back — and with it, reminders to prevent hot car deaths Warm weather's back — and with it, reminders to prevent hot car deaths originally appeared on Autoblog on Tue, 14 May 2024 11:26:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 16:26:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Google rolls out its most powerful AI models as competition from OpenAI heats up</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/14/google-announces-lightweight-ai-model-gemini-flash-1point5-at-google-i/o.html</link><description>Google on Tuesday announced new additions to its AI model following a flashy rollout a day earlier from OpenAI.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 18:46:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>15 Ways to Own Digital Terrain</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/15-ways-to-own-digital-terrain/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=15-ways-to-own-digital-terrain</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>It is now no longer optional…you must have an online presence! Your career stability and your job search demand it. Here are some tips to help you begin claiming digital terrain and brand it with your unique messaging! Why Should You Own Digital Terrain? You need to stake a claim by owning turf on the […] The post 15 Ways to Own Digital Terrain appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 15:56:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>“Why do they feel sad?” Shared book reading reveals how children learn about others’ emotions</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/shared-book-reading/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=shared-book-reading</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers: It is good for children to identify the emotions of others in conversations with caregivers because it scaffolds their ability to identify others’ emotions on their own. Children who use more emotion talk in parent-child conversations about emotions are more likely to have higher emotion knowledge one year later. Parents can […] The post “Why do they feel sad?” Shared book reading reveals how children learn about others’ emotions appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 08:19:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Meal Plan #4</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/weekly-menu-plan-4/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Take advantage of this weekly meal plan that has all the favorite recipes that families love! It is so easy…</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Using Solid Stain In Our Outdoor Shower</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/solid-deck-stain-outdoor-shower/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>In all of our years of DIYing, I don’t think we’ve ever used a solid stain before. But we recently had a project that was *perfectly* suited for it and, well, solid stain quickly won us over. It was recommended by a professional house painter to us, specifically because he thought it would be great for our outdoor shower. And we found it easy to apply, it gave us great coverage, and we got an even-better-than-we-expected result (which is always the best kind!). So here’s a post that covers all the pros &amp; cons and hows &amp; whys of solid stain. As you can see, the “canvas” for this staining project was our outdoor shower. We gave it a mini-makeover right after moving in, but we knew it may need more attention and care down the line. Honestly, we dreaded the task of stripping and restaining it – so many nooks &amp; crannies! Continue reading Using Solid Stain In Our Outdoor Shower at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 17:46:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Discovering My Avaline Favorites</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/discovering-my-avaline-favorites/</link><description>Thank you to Avaline for sponsoring this post. Spring symbolizes fresh starts and cleaner living. In my quest to align… The post Discovering My Avaline Favorites appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:50:47 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>