<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 06:57:43 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>When the Dallas Stars Shifted to Green and Silver in 2013</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/04/when-the-dallas-stars-shifted-to-green-and-silver-in-2013/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Eleven years ago today, the Dallas Stars unveiled their current logo and uniform, marking the most significant shift in the franchise’s visual identity in over two decades. The Dallas Stars revealed their new logo and uniforms at a press event in Dallas on June 4, 2013, just two weeks after</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 19:00:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kanye West Accuses Ex-Yeezy Employee Who's Suing Him of Extortion</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/04/kanye-west-accuses-former-yeezy-chief-of-staff-suing-lawsuit-extortion/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Kanye West was accused of a lot of wrongdoing by a former Yeezy employee, but he's hitting back -- claiming it's actually her who's in the wrong ... alleging she's trying to extort him. A legal rep for Ye tells TMZ ... "In response to these…</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 06:57:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Back in Black: CFL’s Ottawa REDBLACKS Launch New Home Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/04/back-in-black-cfls-ottawa-redblacks-launch-new-home-uniforms/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Team's new home uniforms feature striping on helmets and shoulders that borrows heavily from old Ottawa Rough Riders franchise</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 17:55:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Simon Cowell Looking for Stars for New UK Boy Band</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/04/simon-cowell-boy-band-holding-auditions-uk/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Simon Cowell is ready to get back into the boy band game ... and is already on the hunt for his next One Direction-esque success story. Almost 15 years after making magic by bringing together Niall Horan, Liam Payne, Harry Styles, Louis Tomlinson…</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 06:57:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tottenham Hotspur Ready to Rise in New Home Kits — Plus Other Launches From Around Europe</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/04/tottenham-hotspur-ready-to-rise-in-new-home-kits-plus-other-launches-from-around-europe/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>FC St. Pauli returns to Bundesliga with Puma home kits; Celta Vigo switches manufacturers; Nantes celebrates 94-95 title team; Rangers mark 125th anniversary of Ibrox</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 17:20:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Edmonton Oilers Fan Gets Porn Site Offer After Flashing Boobs In Arena</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/04/viral-oilers-fan-flashing-boobs-porn-dude-only-fans-nhl/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>If the Edmonton Oilers fan who flashed her boobs on camera wants another crack at the experience -- a super popular porn site tells TMZ Sports it'd be more than happy to give her the avenue!! A rep for The Porn Dude -- an adult website that snares…</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 06:57:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Twins Announce City Connect Unveil Plans, Water-Themed Uniform?</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/03/twins-announce-city-connect-unveil-plans-water-themed-uniform/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Minnesota Twins have announced some of the details surrounding the upcoming release of their 2024 Nike MLB City Connect uniform. The new uniform will be unveiled on Monday, June 10, during a special event at Target Plaza outside Target Field. The unveiling kicks off the Twins’ “City Connect Launch</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 21:38:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Giant Venomous Flying Spiders Invading New York, Spreading Up East Coast</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/04/giant-venomous-flying-spiders-invading-new-york-joro/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Peter Parker's got company ... an invasive species of spider is preparing to invade New York, and these arachnids can fly through the air like Spider-Man! 😬 Folks in New York and New Jersey are bracing for the imminent arrival of the Joro…</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 06:57:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSL’s AFC Toronto Unveils Name and Crest</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/03/nsls-afc-toronto-unveils-name-and-crest/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Northern Super League club will take to the pitch in 2025 inaugural season with maroon and vermillion color scheme and crest that aims to represent different parts of their city</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 16:44:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MDMA Treatment for PTSD Gets Voted Against by FDA Advisers</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/04/mdma-treatment-ptsd-considered-fda-advisers-ecstasy/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>4:22 PM PT -- And just like that, the FDA advisers who were mulling over using ecstasy to treat people with PTSD just suggested it ain't happening ... voting against it. In a 10-1 vote -- with the one person voting for MDMA's use -- the…</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 06:57:43 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>