<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:50:24 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Update on Utah’s NHL Team Name, Uniform Info, Tournament Coming?</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/24/update-on-utahs-nhl-team-name-uniform-info-tournament-coming/hockey-2/</link><description>Utah’s new National Hockey League team is starting to assemble their list of possible team names ahead of their inaugural (but not expansion) season this fall. DetroitHockey.Net’s Clark Rasmussen, the king of the trademark search, found two more names possibly trademarked by the group, bringing the total to nine that</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:51:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Glen Powell Says Sydney Sweeney Was Brains Behind Movie Marketing Ploy</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/24/glen-powell-sydney-sweeney-brains-movie-marketing-campaign-anyone-but-you/</link><description>Glen Powell is finally saying the quiet part out loud when it comes to his rom-com with Sydney Sweeney -- namely, that their off-screen chemistry was 100% staged and fake. The actor spilled the tea once and for all in a new interview with NYT --…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:50:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Liverpool FC Reportedly Ready to Return to Adidas in 2025</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/24/liverpool-fc-reportedly-ready-to-return-to-adidas-in-2025/soccer/</link><description>New deal with Liverpool reportedly part of an "aggressive push" by Adidas to win high-profile contracts after losing German national team deal</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 17:56:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kim Kardashian Posts Photo with Taylor Swift's Frenemy Karlie Kloss</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/24/kim-kardashian-posts-picture-karlie-kloss-taylor-swift-album/</link><description>Kim Kardashian posted a photo with one of Taylor Swift's famous frenemies -- none other than Karlie Kloss, who stopped being good pals with the Swiftster years ago ... interesting. The reality star posted a selfie from 2022 that featured herself,…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:50:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Houston Texans Unveil Four New Uniforms, Two New Helmets</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/23/houston-texans-unveil-four-new-uniforms-two-new-helmets/football/</link><description>The Houston Texans unveiled their new uniforms on Tuesday morning, including four distinctly different designs intended to satisfy every corner of the fanbase.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 16:17:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jimmie Allen Cries About Contemplating Suicide Amid Sexual Assault Lawsuit</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/24/jimmie-allen-cry-contemplate-suicide-sexual-assault-lawsuit/</link><description>Jimmie Allen is breaking down in tears, thinking about the day he contemplated suicide after he was accused of sexual assault. In a new interview with Kathie Lee Gifford, the country singer got emotional while discussing the toll the sexual assault…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:50:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Madison Mallards unveil alternates IN A VAN DOWN BY THE RIVER</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/22/madison-mallards-unveil-alternates-in-a-van-down-by-the-river/baseball/</link><description>The collegiate summer level Madison Mallards unveiled an alternate identity today based on a classic Saturday Night Live sketch that featured the late, great Madison native Chris Farley over three decades ago in 1993. The logo and uniforms evoke Farley’s character Matt Foley, a down-on-his-luck motivational speaker who famously lives</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 01:21:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Reggie Bush Getting Heisman Trophy Back After Forfeiting Award In 2010</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/24/reggie-bush-getting-heisman-trophy-back-usc-trojans/</link><description>7:37 AM PT -- It's official -- Reggie Bush was welcomed back to the Heisman family on Wednesday ... with the Trust sharing a picture of Bush posing with his trophy. 7:02 AM PT -- Reggie just took to his Instagram page to celebrate the news --…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:50:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Minnesota Vikings Alternate, New York Giants Throwback Jerseys Leak</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/22/minnesota-vikings-alternate-new-york-giants-throwback-jerseys-leak/football/</link><description>Former NFL wide receiver Antonio Brown's social media network leaked two more jerseys that will be worn this season, including a Minnesota Vikings alternate and New York Giants throwback design.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 21:24:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anne Heche's Estate Struggling to Pay Off $6 Million in Debts, Son Says</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/24/anne-heche-estate-struggle-pay-debt-son/</link><description>Anne Heche's estate is having difficulty paying off its outstanding debts -- this according to court docs filed by the late actress' son. Homer Laffoon is the administrator of his late mom's estate, and he filed docs with the court saying the…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:50:24 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>