<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 06:52:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>2025 MLB All-Star Game Logo Revealed; Hosted by Atlanta Braves</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/22/2025-mlb-all-star-game-logo-revealed-hosted-by-atlanta-braves/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Atlanta… You’re on the clock. Four years after they lost the game with just months to go, the Atlanta Braves are back and ready to host. Major League Baseball, along with the team, today unveiled the logo for the 2025 MLB All-Star Game, to be played at Truist Field on</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 00:18:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jessie James Decker Plans To Reduce Breast Implants After 4th Child</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/22/jessie-james-decker-breast-implant-reduction-plans/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Jessie James Decker is getting something off her chest ... revealing she plans to swap out her breast implants with a smaller size after giving birth to her fourth child with ex-NFL star Eric Decker earlier this year. The country singer shared the…</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 06:52:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are The Kansas City Chiefs Considering Alternate Uniforms?</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/22/are-the-kansas-city-chiefs-considering-alternate-uniforms/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Don't expect the Kansas City Chiefs to get an alternate uniform anytime soon, though their owner appears to be warming up to the idea.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 22:23:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chris Brown, Yella Beezy Sued For Alleged Assault Backstage on '11:11' Tour</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/22/chris-brown-yella-beezy-sued-alleged-assault-11-11-tour-lawsuit/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Chris Brown's "11:11" tour has been marred by some serious thuggery ... according to a new lawsuit accusing the singer of orchestrating the assault of several men. According to legal docs, obtained by TMZ Hip Hop, Brown, Yella Beezy, CB's entourage…</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 06:52:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New York Jets Unveil “The Classic” Throwback Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/22/new-york-jets-unveil-the-classic-throwback-uniforms/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Although it’s only been five years since they moved away from the design, the New York Jets unveiled a familiar throwback uniform that will be worn against the Buffalo Bills on Monday Night Football on Oct. 14.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 20:04:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Karen Read's Retrial Date Set Just Weeks After Judge Declared Mistrial</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/22/karen-read-murder-case-retrial-date-set-mistrial-john-okeefe/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Karen Read is heading back to court for round two -- a judge just greenlit a second murder trial in the death of her BF, John O'Keefe ... weeks after declaring it a mistrial following a hung jury. Massachusetts Judge Beverly Cannone has penciled in…</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 06:52:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AFC Bournemouth Launch Michael B. Jordan-Designed Kits for Preseason U.S. Tour</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/21/afc-bournemouth-launch-michael-b-jordan-designed-kits-for-preseason-u-s-tour/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>English Premier League club AFC Bournemouth have enlisted some Hollywood help for the kits for their preseason tour of the United States. Bournemouth launched the kits on Saturday, July 21, the same day as their first preseason friendly against Wrexham AFC in Santa Barbara, California. They’re designed by actor-director Michael</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 16:54:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'16 &amp; Pregnant' Star Autumn Crittendon Dead at 27, Recent Health Issues</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/22/16-and-pregnant-autumn-crittendon-dead-dies-health-issues/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Autumn Crittendon of "16 &amp; Pregnant" fame has died -- and it sounds like there were some health problems her family was aware of ... TMZ has learned. The MTV star's sister broke the news on Facebook Sunday -- penning a heartfelt message to her…</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 06:52:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Notre Dame Fighting Irish Unveil Updated Home Football Jerseys</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/19/notre-dame-fighting-irish-unveil-updated-home-football-jerseys/college/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Although they leaked in the very first screenshot of EA Sports' College Football 25 back in May, Notre Dame revealed several small changes to its standard home jerseys on Friday morning.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 22:17:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ana Navarro Says George Clooney Owes Democrats a 'Big Check' Over Biden Exit</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/22/ana-navarro-george-clooney-owes-democrats-big-check-president-joe-biden-exit/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Ana Navarro is putting George Clooney on blast after he called on President Biden to exit the election ... demanding the actor now show up for the Democratic Party in a big way. Check it out, the political strategist sounded off on the A-lister…</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 06:52:54 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>