<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 01:24:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>With So Much Uncertainty, Can You Reliably Build Generational Wealth From Passive Real Estate Investments?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/can-you-build-generational-wealth-through-passive-real-estate</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>From proposals to cap rent increases, all the way down to rent control, is the uncertainty in today's market enough to make investors leave it altogether?</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 18:22:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Asus ROG Ally X turns PC gaming into a portable console</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/21/the-asus-rog-ally-x-turns-pc-gaming-into-a-portable-console/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>A little more than a year after launching the ROG Ally, Asus is releasing a refined version of its portable device, the ROG Ally X. This Windows-based machine starts shipping on July 22 for $800. I’ve been playing with the portable console for a few days, and there’s already a lot to like — especially […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Five Things to Know About Kamala Harris’ Criminal Justice Record</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/21/kamala-harris-criminal-justice-record</link><description>Here’s where Vice President Kamala Harris, a former prosecutor, stands on important criminal justice issues.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 19:09:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Real Estate Investors Are Making These 6 Costly Mistakes. Don’t Be One of Them.</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/top-6-mistakes-real-estate-investors-are-making-in-2024</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Investors in both stocks and real estate are making the same mistakes right now. Here's what you need to be aware of.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 18:05:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CIA AI director Lakshmi Raman claims the agency is taking a ‘thoughtful approach’ to AI</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/21/cia-ai-director-lakshmi-raman-claims-the-agency-is-taking-a-thoughtful-approach-to-ai/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>As a part of TechCrunch’s ongoing Women in AI series, which seeks to give AI-focused women academics and others their well-deserved — and overdue — time in the spotlight, TechCrunch interviewed Lakshmi Raman, the director of AI at the CIA. We talked about her path to director as well as the CIA’s use of AI, and the […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Project 2025 Plans for Trump to Have Unprecedented Power Over the Justice Department</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/20/trump-project-2025-crime-prosecutors</link><description>The policy plan for a second Trump term would turn the department against progressive local prosecutors.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Home Construction Is Undergoing a Revolution. Here’s How Investors Will Benefit.</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/are-3d-homes-the-future-of-home-construction</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Will we be able to hit "print" and generate housing one day? It could be sooner than you think.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 17:49:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Kamala Harris has said about AI, tech regulation, and more</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/21/what-kamala-harris-has-said-about-ai-tech-regulation-and-more/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>With President Joe Biden dropping out of the race, Vice President Kamala Harris may become the Democrats’ new nominee. In announcing his plans, Biden offered his “full support and endorsement for Kamala to be the nominee of our party this year,” while Harris said her “intention is to win and earn this nomination.” That said, […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 22:47:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Love Beyond Bars: Jules and Samantha</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/19/photo-essay-werkheisers-wrongful-conviction</link><description>Jules and Samantha Werkheiser fought their wrongful convictions for over a decade. Here’s their journey of survival — and motherhood — in pictures.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Don’t Risk Your Money: Check These Stats Before Selecting Your Investment Market</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/check-these-stats-before-selecting-your-investment-market</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Choosing the right market to invest in is your most important investment decision.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 14:38:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Joe Biden drops out of presidential race</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/21/joe-biden-drops-out-of-presidential-race/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>U.S. President Joe Biden has announced he no longer plans to seek reelection, a decision that follows weeks of growing pressure from some Democratic Party supporters, including high-profile tech investors and executives. “It has been the greatest honor of my life to serve as your President,” Biden said in a statement. “And while it has […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meet the New Generation of Unarmed First Responders in This New Podcast Series</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/18/police-north-carolina-podcast-mental-health</link><description>“The Fifth Branch,” a podcast from The Marshall Project and Tradeoffs, examines new, alternative ways to respond to 911 crisis calls.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A World Without Airbnb &amp; Why “Sinking” Could Cause Your Insurance to Skyrocket</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-991</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Airbnb bans escalate, a “tsunami” could be coming for this real estate niche, and “sinking” cities lead to skyrocketing insurance prices. The housing market changes every week, so we’re here […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 07:02:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Made by Google 2024: Pixel 9, Gemini, a new foldable and other things to expect from the event</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/21/made-by-google-2024-pixel-9-gemini-a-new-foldable-and-other-things-to-expect-from-the-event/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Google is expected to announce four Pixel devices: the Pixel 9, Pixel 9 Pro, Pixel 9 Pro XL and Pixel 9 Pro Premium, running Android 15. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What We Know About J.D. Vance’s Legislative Action on Criminal Justice</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/17/what-we-know-from-sen-j-d-vance-s-legislative-action-on-criminal-justice-issues</link><description>On immigration and more, Vance has defended and legislated former President Donald Trump’s policy goals.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 23:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>