<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 06:50:33 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>ECHL’s Indy Fuel Rev Up For Move to New Arena With Refreshed Logos</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/29/echls-indy-fuel-rev-up-for-move-to-new-arena-with-refreshed-logos/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Indiana-based ECHL team will play first 15 games of 2024-25 season on the road while construction wraps up on the new Fisher Events Center</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 20:29:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NBC's Colin Jost Shows Off Wrapped Toes After Injury During Olympic Coverage</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/29/nbc-colin-jost-toe-injury-olympic-surfing-coverage/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>NBC's Colin Jost is only seven toes down in his Olympic coverage in Tahiti -- the "Saturday Night Live" star has been dealing with a nagging injury after a nasty run-in with a reef. The "Weekend Update" anchor -- who's notably ditched his shoes…</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 06:50:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Looking Back: Atlanta Hawks   1970 Switch to “Mod” Green and Blue Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/29/looking-back-atlanta-hawks-1970-switch-to-mod-green-and-blue-uniforms/basketball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Just two years after they relocated from St. Louis, the Atlanta Hawks made a splash in the NBA with a radical new look that marked a significant shift in their identity and left their old recycled St. Louis Hawks uniforms far in the rear-view mirror. The team introduced a bright,</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 18:04:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Foolio Murder Investigation, Tampa Cops Arrest 3 Suspects</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/29/julio-foolio-murder-arrests-yungeen-ace-atk-kta/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Tampa police feel like they're on the right track to solving rapper Julio Foolio's murder ... 3 people were arrested in connection with the deadly shooting and cops say they're closing in on 2 more!!! On Monday, Tampa PD held a press conference…</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 06:50:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Manchester Clubs’ Kit Launches Highlight Busy Few Days in European Unveilings</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/26/manchester-clubs-kit-launches-highlight-busy-few-days-in-european-unveilings/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Other clubs unveilings 2024-25 kits include Leicester City, Brentford, Atalanta, Werder Bremen, Eintracht Frankfurt, Augsburg, Real Valladolid</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 17:03:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Scary Movie' Actress Erica Ash Dead at 46 After Cancer Battle</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/29/scary-movie-actress-erica-ash-dead-dies-cancer-survivors-remorse/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Actress Erica Ash -- famous from one of the 'Scary Movie' films and "Survivor's Remorse" -- has died ... this according to her family. Her mother, Diann Ash, tells TMZ ... "We are deeply saddened to announce the passing of our beloved daughter,…</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 06:50:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Paris 2024 Summer Olympics Logo Explained</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/26/the-paris-2024-summer-olympics-logo-explained/other/olympics/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Now that the games are finally here, you may ask yourself, “What’s the meaning of the 2024 Paris Summer Olympics logo?” The 2024 Summer Olympics logo combines three main elements—the gold medal, the Olympic flame, and “Marianne”—into one cohesive design. So who or what is Marianne, the mysterious female figure</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 15:58:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Big Brother' Star Angela's Real Estate Company Stands By Her Despite Profile Scrub</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/29/big-brother-angela-murray-real-estate-company-stands-by-her-profile-scrub/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Angela Murray is not losing her job because of some abrasive behavior inside the "Big Brother" house ... despite some fans' attempts to hit her where it hurts. Here's the deal ... Angela's under fire for calling housemate Matt "Crazy Eyes" during…</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 06:50:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NLL’s Ottawa Black Bears Ready to Roar in Inaugural Season Jerseys</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/25/nlls-ottawa-black-bears-ready-to-roar-in-inaugural-season-jerseys/other/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Franchise announced relocation to Canadian capital from Long Island in February; striping around waist and sleeves features Indigenous pattern of peace and friendship</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 01:18:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Orioles' James McCann Drilled In Face By 95 MPH Fastball</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/29/james-mcann-face-95-mph-fastball-baltimore-orioles-blue-jays-mlb/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Baltimore Orioles catcher James McCann was drilled in the nose by a 95 MPH fastball on Monday ... but incredibly, the guy shook it off and stayed in the game!! The scary scene went down just minutes ago in the Orioles' tilt with the Blue Jays at…</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 06:50:33 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>