<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 07:46:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Colourful Player Numbers on Caps for MLB’s 2024 Players’ Weekend</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/08/colourful-player-numbers-on-caps-for-mlbs-2024-players-weekend/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Next weekend is Players’ Weekend across Major League Baseball. The series of games played from August 16-18 will be the first time MLB will host a Players’ Weekend since 2019. As part of this year’s celebration, each player’s uniform number will be worn on the right side of their cap</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 03:07:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Marc Anthony's Dominican Republic House Catches Fire, Caught on Video</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/08/marc-anthony-house-fire/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Marc Anthony's house in the Dominican Republic went up in flames Thursday ... burning up part of the building -- and a local TV crew caught it all on camera. The singer-songwriter's villa burst into flames ... and check out the clip, because this…</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 07:46:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Toronto WNBA Team Asks Fans for Assist in Branding</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/08/toronto-wnba-team-asks-fans-for-assist-in-branding/basketball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Team asks for "ideas, names, stories, photos, videos, voice memos, colour preferences and more" from across Canada to help develop name and identity</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 21:07:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Donations Pour In For Lazar Dukic After CrossFit Games Drowning</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/08/drowning-crossfit-lazar-dukic-gofundme/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>The CrossFit community is coming together to support Serbian athlete Lazar Dukic's family after he drowned at the 2024 CrossFit Games ... with hundreds of people donating tens of thousands of dollars in wake of the tragedy. FITAID -- a drink…</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 07:46:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Several Australian Football League Clubs Considering New Looks for 2025</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/08/several-australian-football-league-clubs-considering-new-looks-for-2025/other/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>St. Kilda Football Club, Adelaide Crows and Gold Coast Suns all reportedly considering new logos that are likely to debut next season</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 16:57:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chrisean Rock Mug Shot Surfaces In Oklahoma Drug Case</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/08/chrisean-rock-mug-shot-surfaces/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Chrisean Rock's newest mug shot shows her giant persona after the reality star's buzz was iced after her June arrest. According to her Craig County Sheriff's Office inmate file, Chrisean was finally transferred to Oklahoma on Wednesday evening,…</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 07:46:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Illinois Unveils 1924 Throwback Uniforms For Memorial Stadium Rededication</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/08/illinois-unveils-1924-throwback-uniforms-for-memorial-stadium-rededication/college/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Illinois football program announced on Wednesday that it will wear 1924 throwback uniforms against Michigan on Oct. 19 to mark the 100th anniversary of Memorial Stadium’s dedication and rededication that afternoon. The uniforms were designed to mirror what the Fighting Illini wore against the Wolverines on Oct. 18, 1924,</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 14:29:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>College Students Hospitalized, Shocking Pic Shows Them Passed Out on Cancun Bar</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/08/college-students-hospitalized-cancun-bar/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>College student Zara Hull is speaking out after she and her friend were apparently drugged at a swim-up bar in Cancun, Mexico ... sharing the harrowing details that landed them in the hospital. Hull, who spoke with CBS News after the incident,…</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 07:46:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cleveland Browns Once Again Soliciting Fan Input For Field Design</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/07/cleveland-browns-once-again-soliciting-fan-input-for-field-design/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>For the third year in a row, the Cleveland Browns are asking fans to choose the field design that will be used at Cleveland Browns Stadium this season. First among the three options is the design that has graced the field for the last two seasons, with Brownie the Elf</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 22:23:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ariana Grande Details Conflicted Feelings About Music Leaks</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/08/ariana-grande-leaked-music-comments/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Ariana Grande is laying it all out about the "dehumanizing" impact of hackers leaking her music -- she says she’s got mixed feelings about the whole mess. The singer spilled her thoughts while digging into spicy wings on "Hot Ones" ... she says…</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 07:46:42 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>