<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from multiple RSS sources, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 07:54:24 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The Easiest Way to Invest in Real Estate in 2024</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-950</link><description>There’s one way to invest in real estate that’s cheaper, easier, and more efficient than almost any other strategy. It allows you to get the best mortgage rates with the […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 07:02:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>EU grills Elon Musk’s X about content moderation and deepfake risks</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/08/eu-dsa-x-rfi-genai/</link><description>The European Union has deepened the investigation of Elon Musk-owned social network X it opened back in December, under the bloc’s online governance and content moderation rulebook: the Digital Services Act (DSA). Confirmed breaches of the regime could be expensive for Musk as enforcers are empowered to issue fines of up to 6% of global […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:34:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Marshall Project Wins the Dart Award for “The Mercy Workers”</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/06/the-marshall-project-wins-the-dart-award-for-the-mercy-workers</link><description>Our feature on mitigation specialists who help save people from the death penalty was recognized for making “significant contributions to public understanding of trauma-related issues.”</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anorexia: The Body Neglected</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/mental-health/eating-disorders/anorexia-nervosa/features/anorexia-body-neglected?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>What, exactly, does anorexia nervosa do inside the human body? The heart and bones suffer the most.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>House Hacking Blunder to $2.7 Million in Small Multifamily by Doing THIS</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-403</link><description>Buying small multifamily properties is an easy way to build a portfolio, and with a little creativity, you don’t even need a ton of money! Despite a rocky start to […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 07:02:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Atlan scores $105M for its data control plane, as LLMs boost importance of data</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/08/atlan-scores-105m-for-data-control-plane-just-as-llms-increase-importance-of-data/</link><description>For the founders of Atlan, a data governance startup, data has always been at the heart of what they do, even before they launched the company. In fact, co-founders Prukalpa Sankar and Varun Banka got their start building India’s national data platform called SocialCops. So it probably shouldn’t come as a surprise that they have […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:30:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weinstein Ruling Poses Quandary: Can #MeToo Coexist With Protections for Defendants?</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/04/sex-crimes-weinstein-me-too</link><description>Proving sex crimes often requires evidence that is generally excluded to protect the rights of the accused.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Postpartum PTSD: Right Diagnosis Can Help Mothers and Babies</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/mental-health/news/20240506/postpartum-ptsd-right-diagnosis-can-help-mothers-and-babies?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Many new mothers aren’t aware that postpartum PTSD even exists, but it’s far from rare. Here's what to know.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:19:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seeing Greene: Is Losing $800/Month in Cash Flow Worth $200K+ Equity?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-949</link><description>Would you buy a rental property that loses money every month? What if, in a few years, that one property could make you hundreds of thousands of dollars? Would the […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 07:02:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Axmed raises $2M from Founderful to streamline drug supply chains in underserved markets</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/08/axmed-gets-founderful-backing/</link><description>The seed funding follows a $5M grant the startup got from the Gates Foundation to make maternal and child healthcare available in high-priority countries.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:12:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mississippi Lawmakers Considered Modest Public Defense Reforms. They Rejected All of Them.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/02/mississippi-public-defense-legislative-reforms</link><description>With its refusal to impose oversight or consistent standards in local defense, Mississippi risks falling further behind rest of the U.S., critics say.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Living With Major Depressive Disorder</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/depression/features/live-with-mdd?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>See how one person manages the ups and downs of major depressive disorder -- and how her depression inspired her career as a therapist.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:45:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Personal Finance for Beginners: Bank Accounts, Real Estate, and Retirement</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-526</link><description>Personal finance doesn’t have to be complicated. Saving, investing, and retiring early shouldn’t be a stumbling path to wealth, but many Americans feel this way. So, to clear up some […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 07:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Xona Space Systems closes $19M Series A to build out ultra-accurate GPS alternative</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/08/xona-space-systems-closes-19m-series-a-to-build-out-ultra-accurate-gps-alternative/</link><description>For decades, the Global Positioning System (GPS) has maintained a de facto monopoly on positioning, navigation and timing, because it’s cheap and already integrated into billions of devices around the world. But Xona Space Systems thinks a more accurate system will be necessary to scale autonomous vehicles (AVs), advanced robotics and other technologies for the […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:00:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In This Police Youth Program, a Trail of Sexual Abuse Across the U.S.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/01/police-explorer-sexual-abuse-boy-scouts</link><description>Explorer posts, overseen by the Boy Scouts, are supposed to foster an interest in policing. They have faced nearly 200 allegations of misconduct.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 18:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Therapist’s Perspective</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/depression/features/mdd-therapists-perspective?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>A therapist talks about managing major depressive disorder (MDD): what to expect, strategies for dealing with setbacks, and when to talk to your therapist.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:45:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The American Dream Trap: Maneuvering Major Expenses in Your Financial Adventure</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/avoid-wealth-detours-by-managing-big-ticket-expenses</link><description>From the moment we take our first steps, we’re handed a blueprint for the American dream: It’s the classic tale of success, promising a life of stability, security, and financial […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 21:50:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FTX crypto fraud victims to get their money back — plus interest</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/08/ftx-crypto-fraud-victims-to-get-their-money-back-plus-interest/</link><description>Bankruptcy lawyers representing customers impacted by the dramatic crash of cryptocurrency exchange FTX 17 months ago say that the vast majority of victims will receive their money back — plus interest. The news comes six months after FTX co-founder and former CEO Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF) was found guilty on seven counts related to fraud, conspiracy, and […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 10:53:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Campus Protests Could Shape the 2024 Elections — And Not Just the Presidency</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/30/campus-protests-gaza-arrests-prosecutors-elections</link><description>With hundreds of arrests and more campus standoffs looming, local law enforcement officials could face consequences at the ballot box.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 21:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Handling the Stigma</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/depression/features/mdd-stigma?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Learn from a mental health advocate how the stigma of depression is changing and how acceptance is the first step to managing major depressive disorder.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:44:47 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>