<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 05:18:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Did Inflation Kill the CAPM?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/06/25/did-inflation-kill-the-capm/</link><description>While the immediate future may not be promising for the equity premium, it looks bright for factor premiums.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 13:51:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NTSB chair says Norfolk Southern tried to interfere with derailment probe after botching decision to blow open 5 tank cars and burn the chemicals inside</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/06/26/ntsb-chair-norfolk-southern-interfere-derailment-probe-botching-decision-burn-chemicals/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/AP24177613237817-e1719392817671.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The NTSB also confirmed that the February 2023 derailment was caused by a wheel bearing that video showed was on fire for more than 20 miles beforehand but wasn't caught in time by inaccurate trackside detectors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 10:14:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Behavior of Crowds not Wisdom of Crowds</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/06/21/behavior-of-crowds-not-wisdom-of-crowds/</link><description>When behavioral crowds are roiling the markets, as they are now, best idea active equity has an excellent chance of outperforming.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 17:54:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Novo Nordisk’s Wegovy may just have two years to take over China’s market for weight loss drugs</title><link>https://fortune.com/asia/2024/06/26/novo-nordisk-wegovy-may-have-just-two-years-to-take-over-china-weight-loss-drug-market/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/GettyImages-2061709452-e1719375930298.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Novo Nordisk's China patent on Wegovy's active ingredient expires in 2026, much earlier than its patents in the U.S., Japan and Europe.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 10:08:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is the Outright Ban on a US Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC) a Mistake?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/06/20/is-the-outright-ban-on-a-us-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc-a-mistake/</link><description>Instead of outright banning a US CBDC, wouldn’t it be preferrable to establish clear and enforceable legislative guardrails?</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 17:00:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tornado warnings, flash flooding and large hail add insult to injury in the Midwest: ‘Nature doesn’t care whether you believe in climate change or not’</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/06/26/tornado-warnings-flash-flooding-large-hail-midwest/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/AP24177620671955-e1719392319586.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>A vast swath of land from eastern Nebraska and South Dakota to Iowa and Minnesota has been under siege from flooding from torrential rains since last week, while also being hit with a scorching heat wave.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 10:00:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Concerned About Market Concentration and Lofty Valuations? Consider Small Caps</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/06/19/concerned-about-market-concentration-and-lofty-valuations-consider-small-caps/</link><description>Investors are showing increased concern about large-cap stocks due to high market concentration and lofty stock valuations. Other factors combine to make a compelling case for small caps.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 17:16:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GM brings in Xbox engineer as CEO to steer beleaguered Cruise robotaxi service</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/06/26/gm-cruise-ceo-marc-whitten/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/GettyImages-1462815301-e1719391591102.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Marc Whitten, one of the key engineers behind the Xbox video game console, will take over as Cruise's chief executive.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 09:47:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Is Systems Thinking? A Primer with Applications for Sustainable Investing</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/06/18/what-is-systems-thinking-a-primer-with-applications-for-sustainable-investing/</link><description>Systems thinking is gaining in popularity in many fields including economics, finance, and investment management. Learn what it means and how it's being applied to sustainable investing.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 16:33:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FDA warns Sara Lee and Entenmann’s maker to stop using labels that say their foods contain potentially dangerous allergens when they don’t</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/06/26/fda-sara-lee-entenmanns-bimbo-labels-allergens/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/AP24177785376325.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Bimbo Bakeries USA listed ingredients such as sesame or tree nuts on labels even when they weren't in the foods.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 09:44:16 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>