<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 06:53:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Colorado Buffaloes’ New Football Jerseys Leaked By CTESPN</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/06/colorado-buffaloes-new-football-jerseys-leaked-by-ctespn/college/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Colorado is set to unveil new football uniforms ahead of the 2024 season, and former NFL wide receiver Antonio Brown gave us a sneak peek at the jersey design over the weekend.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 06:35:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>West Virginia Cop Threatens To Shoot Woman During Traffic Stop, Video Shows</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/05/cop-threatens-shoot-woman-traffic-stop-body-slam-video-west-virginia/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>A cop in West Virginia allegedly threatened to shoot a woman during a traffic stop ... then he smashed her car window and body-slammed her to the ground ... and it's all on video. The intense police interaction went down Thursday in Marion County,…</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 06:53:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Premier League Away Kits Dominate Recent Unveilings From Around Europe</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/02/premier-league-away-kits-dominate-recent-unveilings-from-around-europe/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Clubs launching kits include Liverpool, Brighton, Fulham, Bournemouth, Nottingham Forest, Wolves, Le Havre, Stade de Reims, Montepellier, Roma, Parma, RB Leipzig, VFB Stuttgart, Girona</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 21:41:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kylie Jenner &amp; Travis Scott Drop Another $2 Million Off Beverly Hills Home</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/05/kylie-jenner-travis-scott-drop-another-2-million-beverly-hills-home/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Kylie Jenner and Travis Scott appear eager to offload their Beverly Hills home ... as the former flames have slashed the listing price once again. The ex-couple's first home together -- which they nabbed for a notable $13.4 million back in 2018 --…</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 06:53:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Carolina Panthers Add 30th Season Logo To Jerseys</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/02/carolina-panthers-add-30th-season-logo-to-jerseys/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Carolina Panthers will celebrate their 30th season this fall with a commemorative logo, which they quietly unveiled back in May and added to their jerseys ahead of Thursday's Fan Fest at Clemson's Memorial Stadium.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 17:02:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Racist 'Hanging Tree' Viral Video Sparks Police Investigation in Nevada</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/05/racist-maga-hanging-tree-viral-video-nevada-investigation/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Cops in Nevada are investigating after a Black man shared a video where he claims a white man called him racial slurs and told him about a "hanging tree." The viral footage picks up with the white man smiling and flipping off the Black man, who has…</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 06:53:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Macon Some Changes: SPHL’s Mayhem Unveil New Suite of Logos</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/01/macon-some-changes-sphls-mayhem-unveil-new-suite-of-logos/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Primary logo once again depicts a Viking, only this time just the head with a red beard and eyebrows and wearing a shiny silver horned helmet</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 23:36:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Serena Williams Calls Out Paris Hotel For Denying Access To Rooftop Restaurant</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/05/serena-williams-peninsula-hotel-rooftop-problems-paris-olympics/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Serena Williams is putting a Paris hotel on blast ... calling out the establishment for denying her family access to a rooftop restaurant -- despite it being completely "empty." The 42-year-old tennis legend went to X to publicly send a message to…</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 06:53:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Olympic Rings: Their Origin, History, and Meaning</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/01/the-olympic-rings-their-origin-history-and-meaning/other/olympics/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Olympic rings are synonymous with the peak of international sports achievement. Those five interlaced circles of equal size, each a different colour, absolutely dominate the sporting landscape around the globe for two straight weeks before vanishing as quickly as they appeared, hiding away until the next games, usually around</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 20:10:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Billy Ray Cyrus and Firerose Divorce Finalized</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/05/billy-ray-cyrus-fireroses-divorce-finalized/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Billy Ray Cyrus is closing the book on his marriage to Firerose ... because he finalized his divorce from his now-ex-wife ... and it didn't take long at all. Billy Ray's divorce case just settled and is signed, sealed and delivered in the Tennessee…</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 06:53:17 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>