<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 13:15:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Liverpool FC Pays Homage to Treble-Winning 1984 Squad With 2024-25 Home Kit</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/02/liverpool-fc-pays-homage-to-treble-winning-1984-squad-with-2024-25-home-kit/soccer/</link><description>Front and back of shirt feature yellow pinstripe pattern that spells out "YWNA" for club motto, "You'll Never Walk Alone"</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:19:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kim Kardashian &amp; Odell Beckham Jr. Split, Better Off as Friends</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/01/kim-kardashian-odell-beckham-jr-split-better-off-as-friends/</link><description>Kim Kardashian's moving on from Odell Beckham Jr. -- as the two have decided to go their separate ways, and it's all because there's simply no more love in the air ... just friendship. Sources with direct knowledge confirm to TMZ ... the reality…</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 13:15:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ope! Madison Mallards unveil another alternate</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/02/ope-madison-mallards-unveil-another-alternate/baseball/</link><description>There are a lot of theories about the origins of the quirky exclamation “Ope!”—none of which stand up to any real scrutiny. More onomatopoeia than actual word, the term has been likened to “oops” or “oh” plus the letter P, and associated with most anywhere human beings have made inadvertent</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 12:07:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ryan Garcia Tested Positive For PED Before Haney Fight, Boxer Denies Cheating</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/01/ryan-garcia-tested-positive-ped-performance-enhancing-drug-ostarine-devin-haney-fight/</link><description>5/2 -- 6:00 AM PT -- Devin Haney addressed the reports of Ryan Garcia's test results ... saying it's "unfortunate Ryan cheated and disrespected both the fans and the sport of boxing by fighting dirty and breaking positive not once, but twice."…</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 13:15:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tri-City Chili Peppers to play “Cosmic Baseball” under black lights</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/01/tri-city-chili-peppers-to-play-cosmic-baseball-under-black-lights/baseball/</link><description>Nearly a century after the Negro Leagues’ Kansas City Monarchs became the first professional baseball team to host a baseball game under artificial lights, the Coastal Plain League’s Tri-City Chili Peppers are putting their own spin on that innovation. The team will play “Cosmic Baseball” under powerful black lights that</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 02:45:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ginny Weasley in 'Harry Potter' 'Memba Her?!</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/02/ginny-weasley-in-harry-potter-memba-her/</link><description>Hey all you Muggles ... It's frickin' Harry Potter Day! And, in honor of more than 20 years of wands, brooms and golden snitches, it's time to dust off your broomstick and travel back to the Wizarding World with the mythical cast of 'Harry Potter!'…</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 13:15:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rockford Rivets to rebrand as Screw City Sock Monkeys</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/01/rockford-rivets-to-rebrand-as-screw-city-sock-monkeys/baseball/</link><description>The collegiate summer level Rockford Rivets will pay tribute to their hometown’s textile and manufacturing heritage when they take to the field as the Screw City Sock Monkeys for two games this season. The Sock Monkeys nickname derives from Rockford, Illinois’s claim to “Home of the Sock Monkey”—a term the</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 02:03:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TMZ TV Hot Takes: Britney &amp; Jamie Lynn Spears, George Santos, Travis Kelce</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/02/tmz-tv-hot-takes-britney-jamie-lynn-spears-george-santos-travis-kelce/</link><description>It's the middle of the week, and TMZ's got a whole bunch of clips to get you over the hump (day). TMZ Live On "TMZ Live" ... Harvey and Charles analyze Britney Spears calling her sister Jamie Lynn a "bitch" in a rambling, somewhat incoherent video.…</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 13:15:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>First Look at the 2024 World Series and MLB Postseason Logos</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/01/first-look-at-the-2024-world-series-and-mlb-postseason-logos/baseball/</link><description>It might still be the beginning of May, but today, we’re looking forward all the way to October with the release of Major League Baseball’s 2024 Postseason Logos. First, let’s take a look at the whole package: Yes, they do feel awfully similar to last season. However, there are some</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 23:43:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nets' Dorian Finney-Smith Opens Up On Dad's Release After 29 Years In Prison</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/02/dorian-finney-smith-elbert-prison-basketball-reunited-brooklyn-nets-nba-prison/</link><description>Brooklyn Nets hooper Dorian Finney-Smith is opening up about his father's return home after a lengthy, near three-decade prison bid ... telling TMZ Sports pops is making up for lost time by spending time with his family! Elbert Smith was reunited…</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 13:15:18 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>