<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 06:59:10 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>BiggerNews: Multifamily Market Update + Where to Find Deals NOW</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-995</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Multifamily real estate is still offering some significant opportunities to investors—you just need to know where to look! Although the past two years have been rough for multifamily, with falling […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 07:02:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple cuts iPhone price in India amid China slowdown</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/26/apple-cuts-iphone-price-in-india-amid-china-slowdown/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Apple has reduced prices of its iPhone models in India by 3-4% following a cut in import duties in the South Asian market. The price cuts range from 300 rupees ($3.63) for models like the iPhone 13, 14 and 15, and to up to 6,000 rupees ($72.54) for the iPhone 15 Pro and Pro Max […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 11:58:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Love Beyond Bars: Raymond and Cassanda</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/26/photo-essay-raymond-flanks-wrongful-conviction</link><description>Raymond Flanks spent nearly 39 years in Louisiana lockups for a murder he didn’t commit. Luckily, he found love with an old friend, Cassandra Delpit.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 11:00:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rookie Reply: What EVERY Rookie Must Learn Before Investing in Real Estate</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-437</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Not quite ready to invest in real estate? Maybe you’re still getting your finances in check or saving for a bigger down payment. In any case, don’t sit on your […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 07:02:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Egypt’s MNT-Halan banks $157.5M, gobbles up a fintech in Turkey to expand</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/26/egypts-mnt-halan-banks-157-5m-gobbles-up-a-fintech-in-turkey-to-expand/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>MNT-Halan, a fintech unicorn out of Egypt, is on a consolidation march. The microfinance and payments startup has raised $157.5 million in funding and is using the money in part to fund the acquisition of another fintech, Tam Finans, to expand into Turkey. Tam Finans provides financing to micro-enterprises and SMEs. It currently operates 39 […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 08:31:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Problem With Labeling Trump a ‘Felon’</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/25/donald-trump-felon-election24</link><description>Here’s why language used to describe any person convicted of crimes matters, and affects more than the former president.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 23:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is FIRE Dead? No, But Here’s Why Most WON’T Achieve It</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-549</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Is the FIRE movement dead? In 2024, more people are catching on to the huge downsides of pursuing financial independence, retire early. Strict frugality, massive sacrifice, working harder than ever…is […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 07:01:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Energy tech startup Greenely grabs €8M to reach more households and support Europe’s energy transition</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/26/energy-tech-startup-greenely-grabs-e8m-to-reach-more-households-and-support-europes-energy-transition/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The energy transition is a marathon, not a sprint. But opportunities for acceleration are growing. Swedish startup Greenely* has just spotted one. It’s closing an €8 million Series A funding round to expand its energy management platform into neighbouring Nordic countries (so around $8.7M at current exchange rates). The energy tech startup is serving around […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Photos: Three Years of a Family’s Grief and Healing After a Fatal Police Shooting</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/25/family-photos-cleveland-police-shooting-belmonte</link><description>Photographer Michael Indriolo documents an East Cleveland family’s search for peace after the 2021 police shooting of their 19-year-old brother.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 11:00:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>6 Ways to Raise Rent While Respecting Your Residents</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/6-ways-to-raise-rent-while-respecting-your-residents</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Raising rental rates is part of the industry. It can’t be avoided. Whether you’re a solo investor or looking for compassionate, effective property management, this is how to raise rent with respect and keep your properties occupied and producing revenue.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 21:38:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Luxury fashion startup The Floorr empowers personal stylists with tools to grow their businesses</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/25/luxury-fashion-startup-the-floorr-app-personal-stylists/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The Floorr offers tools for conducting sales, hosting tailored styling sessions, creating mood boards, and engaging in text or voice chats with clients, all in one place. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 21:16:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sending Unarmed Responders Instead of Police: What We’ve Learned</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/25/police-mental-health-alternative-911</link><description>There are more than 100 response teams nationwide, but experts say more research on their impact is needed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 11:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>National Rent Control, Falling Mortgage Rates, and Fleeing Homebuyers</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-237</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>A new nationwide rent control proposal could cap rent increases for any landlord with a certain amount of properties. But will it actually pass? How would landlords survive when rents […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 07:02:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Here’s why David Sacks, Paul Graham and other big Silicon Valley names had a brawl on X over VC behavior</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/25/david-sacks-paul-graham-silicon-valley-names-brawl-on-x-over-vc-behavior/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>A decade-old drama involving VC David Sacks and Rippling founder Parker Conrad has blown up on X with many among the Silicon Valley elite taking sides. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 20:59:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Marshall Project Launches Investigate This!</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/25/the-marshall-project-launches-investigate-this</link><description>Our toolkits will offer data, storytelling and engagement resources to empower more criminal justice reporting in local communities</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>