<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from multiple RSS sources, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 11:55:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>5 Things I Always Look For—and You Should Too—in a Flip</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/things-i-always-look-for-in-a-flip</link><description>These five factors will help increase the ROI on your next fix and flip project.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:23:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Police resurrect Lockbit’s site and troll the ransomware gang</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/06/police-resurrect-lockbits-site-and-troll-the-ransomware-gang/</link><description>An international coalition of police agencies have resurrected the dark web site of the notorious LockBit ransomware gang, which they had seized earlier this year, teasing new revelations about the group. On Sunday, what was once LockBit’s official darknet site reappeared online with new posts that suggest the authorities are planning to release new information […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:39:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weinstein Ruling Poses Quandary: Can #MeToo Coexist With Protections for Defendants?</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/04/sex-crimes-weinstein-me-too</link><description>Proving sex crimes often requires evidence that is generally excluded to protect the rights of the accused.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>7 Most Effective Exercises</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/fitness-exercise/features/7-most-effective-exercises?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Not all exercises are created equal. Some are simply more efficient than others, whether they target multiple muscle groups, are suitable for a wide variety of fitness levels, or help you burn calories more effectively.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:55:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What to Know About “Capital Calls” As Multifamily Syndications Get “Squeezed” w/Brian Burke and Mauricio Rauld</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-214</link><description>Multifamily syndications are getting squeezed. With short-term financing coming due and mortgage rates at multi-decade highs, syndicators are calling on their original investors to raise more money so they don’t […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 07:02:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to choose a deep tech startup program</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/06/how-to-choose-a-deep-tech-startup-program/</link><description>Deep tech founders often had to go it alone. But today, there are a wealth of options from incubators to accelerators. Here's how to pick one.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:30:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mississippi Lawmakers Considered Modest Public Defense Reforms. They Rejected All of Them.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/02/mississippi-public-defense-legislative-reforms</link><description>With its refusal to impose oversight or consistent standards in local defense, Mississippi risks falling further behind rest of the U.S., critics say.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>To Fast or to Feast?</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/ibd-crohns-disease/ulcerative-colitis/features/fast-feast-uc?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>These tips will help you enjoy the foods at social events when you have ulcerative colitis and still steer clear of a flare.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:52:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The “Domino Effect”: How to Build an Entire Portfolio from ONE Property</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-402</link><description>The hardest part of real estate investing is, of course, getting started. Once you have your first rental property, it’s much easier to scale your real estate portfolio than you […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 07:02:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dorsey leaves Bluesky, tech giants do more with less, and the next IPO</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/06/dorsey-leaves-bluesky-tech-giants-do-more-with-less-and-the-next-ipo/</link><description>News that Jack Dorsey is out at Bluesky caused a stir this weekend. After all, Dorsey is a former Twitter co-founder and CEO, so his investment of time into the rival social network carried weight. The decentralized social networking service said that it is looking for a new board member. But while we had to […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:16:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In This Police Youth Program, a Trail of Sexual Abuse Across the U.S.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/01/police-explorer-sexual-abuse-boy-scouts</link><description>Explorer posts, overseen by the Boy Scouts, are supposed to foster an interest in policing. They have faced nearly 200 allegations of misconduct.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 18:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Can You Really Know What to Expect in the Long Haul?</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/ibd-crohns-disease/ulcerative-colitis/features/long-haul-expectations-uc?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Ulcerative colitis is a relapsing-remitting disease, so it’s hard to predict symptoms over time. Here’s what to expect and how to recognize remission.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 15:53:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10 Rentals in 5 Years by Buying in Overlooked Short-Term Rental Markets</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-948</link><description>When you think about short-term rental and Airbnb markets, what comes to mind? Joshua Tree, the Smoky Mountains, maybe Destin? We all know about the famous short-term rental markets, but […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 07:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alphabet-owned Intrinsic incorporates Nvidia tech into robotics platform</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/06/alphabet-owned-intrinsic-incorporates-nvidia-tech-into-robotics-platform/</link><description>The first bit of news out of the Automate conference this year arrives by way of Alphabet X spinout Intrinsic. The firm announced at the Chicago event on Monday that it is incorporating a number of Nvidia offerings into its Flowstate robotic app platform. That includes Isaac Manipulator, a collection of foundational models designed to create […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Campus Protests Could Shape the 2024 Elections — And Not Just the Presidency</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/30/campus-protests-gaza-arrests-prosecutors-elections</link><description>With hundreds of arrests and more campus standoffs looming, local law enforcement officials could face consequences at the ballot box.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 21:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ulcerative Colitis: Social Relationships and Dating</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/ibd-crohns-disease/ulcerative-colitis/features/uc-relationships?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Friendship can be a good medicine when you have ulcerative colitis. Learn how to keep your social life going when you don’t always feel like going out.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 15:45:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I Would Have Lost Our Investors $5.5 Million—What Would You Have Done In This Situation?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/i-nearly-lost-our-investors-5-million</link><description>What were you doing on the morning of Jan. 17, 2020? While the world was learning about a strange new virus approaching our shores, my business partner, Ben, and I […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 22:58:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stack Overflow signs deal with OpenAI to supply data to its models</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/06/stack-overflow-signs-deal-with-openai-to-supply-data-to-its-models/</link><description>OpenAI is collaborating with Stack Overflow, the Q&amp;A forum for software developers, to improve its generative AI models’ performance on programming-related tasks. As a result of the partnership, announced Monday, OpenAI’s models, including models served through its ChatGPT chatbot platform, should get better over time at answering programming-related questions, the two companies say. At the […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 15:55:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>They Killed Their Abusive Partners. Now Their Sentences Could Be Reconsidered.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/27/oklahoma-oregon-minnesota-domestic-violence</link><description>Oklahoma could re-examine how it punishes people whose crimes came after years of domestic abuse. Other states may follow.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Normal Aging Process: Changes, Memory, Eyesight, Hearing, and More</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/normal-aging-changes-and-symptoms?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Curious if your body’s aging is normal? WebMD discusses healthy and normal signs of aging.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 14:30:36 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>