<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:41:32 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Could This Derail the Recovery? (What to Do About It)</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/could-this-derail-the-recovery-what-to-do-about-it/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, it's Ross Givens here with the Chart of the Day. Diving into one of my top charts, the Equal-Weight S&amp;P 500 Index (RSP) paints a clearer picture of the market's health by eliminating the dominance of mega-cap tech stocks. Currently, RSP sits a mere 1.5% shy of its all-time highs, signaling a robust recovery from the April pullback. However, with the looming CPI report's potential impact, the market's trajectory remains uncertain. Stay ahead of the curve with my insight. The post Could This Derail the Recovery? (What to Do About It) appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Used car prices held flat in April 2024 while payments increased</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/article/used-car-prices-held-flat-in-april-2024-while-payments-increased/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/14112855/shutterstock_2172554281.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Car Buying , Used Car Buying Continue reading Used car prices held flat in April 2024 while payments increased Used car prices held flat in April 2024 while payments increased originally appeared on Autoblog on Tue, 14 May 2024 13:02:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 18:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is the 1% Rule Dead? + Why Building (NOT Buying) Could Make You More</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-953</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Could building houses make you more money than buying existing ones? When should someone use the 1% rule in real estate, and when does this metric point to a cash […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 07:02:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best BIPOC New Releases + Beach Reads</title><link>https://bookriot.com/best-bipoc-new-releases-beach-reads/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Untitled-design-2024-05-14T141619.580.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>Which new books out today are you adding to the TBR?</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:19:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 553</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-553/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-553</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Tools and technology change rapidly. Yet as wonderful as technology can be, it doesn’t replace the need for human connection through interactions. Keep this in mind as you are searching for a new job. It’s your human connections that often open doors! In this week’s collection of news and tips for job seekers, you’ll find: […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 553 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 12:19:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A case for public preschool: New study reveals preschool benefits to be longer-lasting and substantial</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/benefits-of-public-preschool/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=benefits-of-public-preschool</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Preschool lays a foundation for elementary school students to succeed. In the United States, as children approach kindergarten entry, it is increasingly common for 4-year-olds to be in non-parental group care and education, often in a center- or school-based setting where they can learn alongside peers. For children from low-income communities, […] The post A case for public preschool: New study reveals preschool benefits to be longer-lasting and substantial appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 08:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GameStop, AMC attracting a fraction of retail trader interest seen during 2021's meme mania</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/14/gamestop-amc-attracting-a-fraction-of-retail-trader-interest-seen-during-2021s-meme-mania.html</link><description>Mom-and-pop traders snapped up shares after the man credited with starting the meme stock mania resurfaced online, though at a lesser extent than seen in 2021.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:24:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meet Real Housewives of Atlanta's Newly Revamped Season 16 Cast</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1401574/meet-the-real-housewives-of-atlantas-newly-revamped-season-16-cast?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>Attention, Bravoholics: Get ready to meet your newly revamped group of Georgia peaches. The Real Housewives of Atlanta's season 16 costars have finally been revealed amid a recent cast...</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why the New T+1 Settlement Cycle Matters: A Global Index Provider’s Perspective</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/14/why-the-new-t1-settlement-cycle-matters-a-global-index-providers-perspective/</link><description>Shorter settlement periods are meant to protect market participants. But the new T+1 settlement cycle for US equities may have undesirable knock-on effects for financial market participants around the world, including index fund managers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 16:54:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jerome Powell says it’s ‘different this time’—and Americans and their mortgage rates are a key reason why</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/14/jerome-powell-economy-different-this-time-housing-mortgage-rates-inflation/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/AP24135552031795-e1715711718108.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>But the Fed chair "wouldn't call it hot," saying the wholesale inflation report was "sort of mixed."</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:38:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>My Saks May Array</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/my-saks-may-array/</link><description>Outfit Details: Sandro Top, Erdem Skirt, Prada Bag, Sherman Fields Necklace Thank you to Saks Fifth Avenue for sponsoring this… The post My Saks May Array appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 05:00:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This is Poland. What do you notice?</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/a9yMW2o</link><description>Tags: funny 11115 points, 1548 comments.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:40:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Minor League Baseball teams, local indie bands team up on brands</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/14/minor-league-baseball-teams-local-indie-bands-team-up-on-brands/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Three affiliated Minor League Baseball teams will partner with local independent musicians to create the “Capsule Collection.” This collaboration is intended to do what minor league baseball branding specializes in: highlight connections between teams and their local community. In its just-announced initial stages, the Capsule Collection will combine design elements</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 18:30:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Google I/O 2024: Everything announced so far</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/14/google-i-o-2024-everything-announced-so-far/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Here are quick hits of the biggest news from the keynote as they are announced. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:13:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When Bad Cops Become Private Security Guards</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/11/police-private-guard-florida-chicago</link><description>There’s growing evidence that former officers with troubling histories of abuse can easily find second careers in private security.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wood-Fired Pizza Dough</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/wood-fired-pizza-dough/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>This is the perfect beginner’s guide for making wood-fired pizza dough! Pizza expert, Chef Brandon Price, taught me how to…</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TMZ TV Hot Takes: Taylor Swift, Zendaya's Stylist, Tyson Fury's Dad</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/14/tmz-tv-hot-takes-taylor-swift-zendayas-stylist-tyson-fury-s-dad/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Another Monday has come and gone ... so be sure to end your day with some TMZ TV hot takes. First up, we have "TMZ Live," where Mike and Charles discuss the surprising events from Taylor Swift's updated Eras tour ... including a guest who probably…</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:41:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Experts Watching Bird Flu Carefully in Case It Takes Off</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/cold-and-flu/news/20240514/experts-watching-bird-flu-in-case-it-takes-off?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>The virus variant that is circulating among cattle is not an efficient cause of disease in humans. There may be more concern if H5N1 passes to pigs, because their viral receptors are closer to those in humans.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 20:17:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Easy Low-Light Indoor Plants</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/easy-low-light-indoor-plants/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>I used to think every houseplant needed a sunny corner or bright windowsill to thrive. But it turns out many of our favorite go-to houseplants do just fine in shady corners and low-light locations. So before you write off your house as too dark to sustain plant life, check out this list of the best indoor plants for low light. You might be surprised at how many good options there are! Our upstairs family room is the brightest room we’ve ever owned thanks to big unobstructed windows on all 4 sides. But most of our indoor plants live downstairs, where we get far less natural light. Luckily, that hasn’t stopped us from growing our collection of happy healthy houseplants. 9 Houseplants That Don’t Need A Lot Of Light Here are our favorite low-light indoor plants. We list a lot more info on them below, but here’s a quick list to bring on your next trip to the plant store: Snake Plant ZZ Plant Pothos Heartleaf Philodendron English Ivy Aglaonema Cast Iron Plant Monstera Parlor Palm Perhaps our favorite part of this list is that these aren’t ugly “consolation plants” that people begrudgingly buy for dark homes. Continue reading Easy Low-Light Indoor Plants at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 14:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bulls Back in Control (Do This Now)</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/bulls-back-in-control-do-this-now/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, it's Ross Givens here with the Chart of the Day. In a remarkable shift, my market health model swiftly transitioned from bearish to bullish within a week. This robust buying spree following the recent dip signifies significant strength and resilience in the market. The much-needed correction allowed for the consolidation of previous gains and the shedding of weak-handed sellers. While the overall market gears up for further upward movement, the dynamics for individual stocks present a nuanced scenario, as I delve into in today's Insight. The post Bulls Back in Control (Do This Now) appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jackery Explorer 2000 Pro portable power station is now at its lowest price ever</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/article/jackery-explorer-2000-pro-portable-power-station-is-now-at-its-lowest-price-ever/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/13164327/Jackery-2000-PRO-copy.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Commerce Continue reading Jackery Explorer 2000 Pro portable power station is now at its lowest price ever Jackery Explorer 2000 Pro portable power station is now at its lowest price ever originally appeared on Autoblog on Tue, 14 May 2024 12:20:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:20:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Small Business Owner’s Guide to Taxes, LLCs, Deductions, &amp; Audit Risks</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-528</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Starting your first or next business? This episode is for you. Today, we’re bringing you everything you need to know about small business taxes for beginners. Whether you’re a solo […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 07:01:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nobel Prize-Winning Author Alice Munro has Died at 92</title><link>https://bookriot.com/alice-munro-has-died/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/off-center-collage-1.png</image_url><description>She won the Nobel Prize for Literature in 2013, with the Academy saying she could "accommodate the entire epic complexity of the novel in just a few short pages."</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:57:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 552</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-552/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-552</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>When you are searching for a job, you will inevitably run into unexpected scenarios. You will have questions, experience self-doubt and even feel discouraged. You’ll also experience great wins, meet wonderful people and discover new things about yourself. That’s the roller-coaster of job search. Consider Summary Sunday your resource for getting questions answered and showing […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 552 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 11:37:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fathers’ views on family and work after COVID-19 lockdowns</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/fathers-views-on-family-and-work-after-covid-19-lockdowns/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fathers-views-on-family-and-work-after-covid-19-lockdowns</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Fathers often want to be present for their children and contribute to household tasks, but they can lack opportunities and confidence; they may see themselves as “helpers” instead of parents. Australian fathers in our small study reported that they spent more time with their children during the COVID-19 lockdowns, and they […] The post Fathers’ views on family and work after COVID-19 lockdowns appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Top bond fund manager Ford O'Neil of Fidelity reveals his 'secret sauce' to generate outperformance</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/14/top-bond-fund-manager-ford-oneil-reveals-his-secret-sauce-to-outperform.html</link><description>O'Neil was recently nominated for Morningstar's 2024 outstanding portfolio manager award for investing excellence.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>5 Best Coffee &amp; Espresso Machines To Make Café-Worthy Drinks</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1401485/the-5-best-coffee-espresso-machines-to-make-cafe-worthy-drinks-at-home?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>The products featured in this article are from brands that are available in the NBCUniversal Checkout Marketplace. If you purchase something through our links, we get a commission. The only thing...</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Leveraging AI to Identify and Predict Financial Crises</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/13/leveraging-ai-to-identify-and-predict-financial-crises/</link><description>Despite some current limitations, AI stands to offer significant advantages versus traditional approaches to identifying and predicting financial crises.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 14:39:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Florida’s migrant farming community jolted by bus crash that kills 8, injures dozens more</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/14/florida-bus-crash-migrant-farmers-8-dead/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/AP24135586923586.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Florida farms employ more H-2A workers than any other state, about 50,000 a year, according to the Florida Fruit &amp; Vegetable Association.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:29:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Our Latest Favorites From Amazon</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/our-latest-favorites-from-amazon/</link><description>Outfit Details: Beaded Handmade Bag Welcome to our latest favorites from Amazon that I’m especially excited to share! This week… The post Our Latest Favorites From Amazon appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 05:00:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Morocco's under 13 vs Guinea's under 13 and guess who won?</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/aE0GRpK</link><description>Tags: funny 3422 points, 263 comments.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:40:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WNBA Expansion Team Golden State Valkyries Unveil Name, Logo</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/14/wnba-expansion-team-golden-state-valkyries-unveil-name-logo/basketball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Franchise name references warrior women from Norse mythology; logo depicts Bay Bridge between Oakland, where they'll train, and San Francisco, where they'll play home games</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 15:56:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Google Play preps a new full-screen app discovery feature and adds more developer tools</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/14/google-play-preps-a-new-full-screen-app-discovery-feature-and-adds-more-developer-tools/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Google Play has a new discovery feature for apps, new ways to acquire users, updates to Play Points, and other enhancements to developer-facing tools. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Rare Bright Spot for a Canine Lover Doing Time: Raising Puppies to Become Service Dogs</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/10/service-dogs-training-prison-essay</link><description>Adam Roberts reflects on the highs and occasional lows of training Labrador retrievers for the Puppies Behind Bars program.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blueberry Lemon Upside-Down Cake</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/blueberry-lemon-upside-cake/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Be prepared to fall in love with this blueberry lemon upside-down cake! A delicious and moist lemon sponge cake bursting…</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Magic Johnson Not Interested In Return To Coaching, Hopes Lakers Get 'Good One'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/14/magic-johnson-not-interested-in-return-to-coaching-hopes-lakers-get-good-one/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Magic Johnson claims he has no idea who the Lakers' next head coach will be ... but he definitely knows who it WON'T be -- Magic Johnson -- 'cause the Hall of Famer tells TMZ Sports those days are long gone. The Purple and Gold are currently…</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:41:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 7-Hour Itch: 3 Women With Eczema Describe the Ways They Combat Nighttime Flare-Ups</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/seven-hour-itch-women-eczema-combat-nighttime-flares?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Three women with eczema describe how they combat nighttime flare-ups.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 09:09:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/how-to-remove-wallpaper/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Wallpaper has made a big comeback as a trendy home design choice. But despite its resurgence, there are still plenty of us dealing with dingy, dated, or downright ugly old wallpaper we don’t want. In our old home, we had to remove wallpaper in so many rooms: the kitchen, the dining room, the foyer, and two different bathrooms! As we traveled from room to room removing wallpaper, we tested 4 different methods, and today we’ll share what we learned. Removing wallpaper doesn’t require special tools or lots of money. It’s a totally doable project for any homeowner. However, it can be a tedious process that can take elbow grease and patience, depending on the size of your room and the stubbornness of your wallpaper. But having removed several rooms worth of decades-old wallpaper, we can confidently say it’s worth the effort! You can also check out more before and afters of our once-wallpapered rooms. Continue reading How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:21:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bullish Breadth (Act Fast)</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/bullish-breadth-act-fast/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, it's Ross Givens here with the Chart of the Day. The percentage of stocks trading above their 50-day moving average, a key metric for medium-term momentum, has surged, signaling a potential continuation of the bull market. Nearly double the levels seen during the April pullback, it mirrors the market's upward trajectory observed from February to mid-March. This resurgence indicates an opportunity for swift action. Learn more about the implications in my detailed analysis below. The post Bullish Breadth (Act Fast) appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2025 Genesis GV80 First Drive: It's what's inside that counts</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/14/2025-genesis-gv80-first-drive-review/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/13145058/GenesisGV80400-copy.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Genesis , First Drives , SUV , Luxury Continue reading 2025 Genesis GV80 First Drive: It's what's inside that counts 2025 Genesis GV80 First Drive: It's what's inside that counts originally appeared on Autoblog on Tue, 14 May 2024 12:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Exactly Does a Property Management Company Do?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/what-does-a-property-management-company-do</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>A property management company plays a vital role in overseeing the daily operations of rental properties to ensure efficient tenant management while maximizing profitability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 22:13:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Enid Public Library Board Bans Pride Display, Entering Third Year of Pride Display Battles</title><link>https://bookriot.com/enid-public-library-bans-pride-display/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Untitled-design-55.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>A Pride display at Enid Public Library has once again been banned by the board, despite having been approved the prior two years. A history of this board's LGBTQ+ display bans.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 16:55:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>While a little competition in the workplace might help bring out the best in everyone involved, an atmosphere rooted in envy, fear, or jealousy can do the exact opposite. This post will help you recognize signs that your coworker is threatened by you, and help you navigate the situation. 1. They Don’t Want You Involved […] The post 10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:07:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Strong Latine Identity Supports U.S. Latine Children’s Well-Being</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/a-strong-latine-identity-supports-u-s-latine-childrens-well-being/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=a-strong-latine-identity-supports-u-s-latine-childrens-well-being</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key Takeaways for caregivers Children tend to have better health and well-being when they have a strong ethnic identity (affinity and adoption of ethnicity-based self-concept). A traditional Latine cultural value (familismo) that emphasizes family bonds is also associated with better developmental outcomes. Caregivers can support the development of U.S. Latine children (and possibly other children […] The post A Strong Latine Identity Supports U.S. Latine Children’s Well-Being appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 03:03:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Walmart is laying off, relocating hundreds of corporate workers across the country. Read the memo</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/14/walmart-to-lay-off-relocate-hundreds-of-corporate-workers.html</link><description>The move follows the closures of the company's health clinics and comes ahead of its earnings report on Thursday.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 18:53:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is the Wiggle Pillow Worth It? The Viral Pillow That Changed My Life</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1401541/is-the-wiggle-pillow-worth-it-heres-how-the-viral-pillow-changed-how-i-sleep-forever?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>We independently selected these deals and products because we love them, and we think you might like them at these prices. E! has affiliate relationships, so we may get a commission if you...</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Your Portfolio Should Include Scarce Assets</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/10/why-your-portfolio-should-include-scarce-assets/</link><description>Portfolios that include both productive and scarce assets can deliver similar performance to the S&amp;P 500 with less risk than those that hold only productive assets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:34:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rich Gen Xers are outpacing baby boomers in buying vacation homes</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/14/housing-market-outlook-vacation-homes-housing-costs-redfin/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1144619544-e1715708934254.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Interest in second homes hasn’t been this low in almost a decade, according to Redfin.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:17:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amazon Home Refresh Tips</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/amazon-home-refresh-tips/</link><description>Embrace the mid-spring refresh with Amazon and give your home a vibrant makeover for the season. Amazon makes it easy… The post Amazon Home Refresh Tips appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 05:00:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Happy Mothers day to all the Mums that love their children like Marianne Bachmeier, pictured here at the trial of her daughters Rapist.</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/avyZreW</link><description>Tags: Mothers Day 14368 points, 607 comments.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:40:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New York Giants Unveil 100th Season Logo, Uniform Patch</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/13/new-york-giants-unveil-100th-season-logo-uniform-patch/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The New York Giants kicked off their 100th season celebration on Monday morning by unveiling a commemorative logo, which will be worn as a patch on their uniforms this fall.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 02:05:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gemini on Android becomes more capable and works with Gmail, Messages, YouTube and more</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/14/gemini-on-android-becomes-more-capable-and-works-with-gmail-messages-youtube-and-more/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Soon, Android users will be able to drag and drop AI-generated images directly into their Gmail, Google Messages and other apps. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Marshall Project Wins the Dart Award for “The Mercy Workers”</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/06/the-marshall-project-wins-the-dart-award-for-the-mercy-workers</link><description>Our feature on mitigation specialists who help save people from the death penalty was recognized for making “significant contributions to public understanding of trauma-related issues.”</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cinnamon Roll Casserole</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/cinnamon-roll-casserole/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Get ready for a tasty treat with this easy cinnamon roll casserole! Using canned cinnamon rolls, this casserole is so…</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Silence of the Lambs' Producer Slams Trump for Praising Hannibal Lecter</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/14/silence-of-the-lambs-producer-slams-trump-praise-hannibal-lecter/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Donald Trump's rant about the "wonderful" Hannibal Lecter isn't sitting well with one of the guys who helped make "The Silence of the Lambs," and he's taking a bite out of DT's rhetoric. Edward Saxon -- part of the Oscar-winning trio that produced…</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:41:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Mother’s Love: The Challenges of Parenting a Child With Eczema</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/mothers-love-challenges-parenting-child-eczema?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Two moms reveal the great lengths they went to in their determination to give their children relief and good health.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 09:18:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aglaonema Plant – Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/aglaonema-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Aglaonema, also called the Chinese Evergreen Plant, is an easy-care houseplant that lives happily in many lighting conditions – even a dark corner of our daughter’s room. There are dozens of different Aglaonema varieties, most with large tropical foliage and colors ranging from silvery-green, red, and even vibrant pink. They’re also tough to kill, so they’re a great option for forgetful plant owners or anyone looking for an easy win in the plant department. These truly have been very low maintenance for us. We purchased our two Aglaonemas (pronounced ag-lee-oh-neem-ah ) to put atop our daughter’s closet. It’s sometimes hard to distinguish different varieties, but we believe that’s an Aglaonema Silver (right) and either a Candy Cane or Princess Silver Queen (left). Aglaonema Quick Facts Here’s what you need to know about your Aglaonema at a glance: Latin name : Aglaonema is the genus under which there are 21 recognized species . Continue reading Aglaonema Plant – Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:47:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Bull Market is Still Young</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/this-bull-market-is-still-young/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, it's Ross Givens here with the Chart of the Day. In analyzing historical data, it's evident that bull markets typically extend for years from the bear market bottom to the peak. Surprisingly, our current market cycle has seen a peak just 19 months post the last bear market bottom, contrasting with the typical 61-month duration. This insight suggests that the current bull market is still in its infancy, promising ample opportunities ahead. Stay tuned as I delve into the implications of this data in today's analysis. The post This Bull Market is Still Young appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Well-built little Chinese EV called the Seagull poses big threat to U.S. auto industry</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/14/well-built-little-chinese-ev-called-the-seagull-poses-big-threat-to-u-s-auto-industry/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/14115403/visitors_inspect_a_byd_seagull_car_during_the_45th_bangkok___.jpeg</image_url><description>Filed under: Green , Electric Continue reading Well-built little Chinese EV called the Seagull poses big threat to U.S. auto industry Well-built little Chinese EV called the Seagull poses big threat to U.S. auto industry originally appeared on Autoblog on Tue, 14 May 2024 11:57:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 16:57:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>21 Smart Ways to Save on College Tuition Costs and Keep Money For Other Investments</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/ways-to-save-on-college-tuition-costs</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Use these practical tips to make paying for college a bit easier for you and your family.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 14:41:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Trailer for The Lord of The Rings: The Rings of Power Season 2</title><link>https://bookriot.com/new-trailer-for-the-lord-of-the-rings-the-rings-of-power-season-2/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Rings-of-Power-season-two-trailer.jpeg.optimal.jpeg</image_url><description>Will be watching season two?</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 16:54:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 551</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-551/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-551</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Job search requires writing and marketing skills. It also requires strong verbal communication. If these skills are not part of your normal work function, you’ll want some help. That’s what this week’s Summary Sunday is all about. There’s no doubt that LinkedIn is one of THE most powerful tools in your career toolbox. It contains […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 551 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 11:37:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Children caught between highly conflicted divorced parents at greater risk of mental health problems</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/children-caught-between-conflicted-divorced-parents/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=children-caught-between-conflicted-divorced-parents</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Interparental conflict after divorce escalates the risk of mental health problems in children and adolescents. Elevated levels of conflict between parents can also induce fear and worry in children about their future and whether they will be adequately taken care of. In turn, a greater fear of abandonment puts children at […] The post Children caught between highly conflicted divorced parents at greater risk of mental health problems appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 08:59:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Education Dept. announces highest interest rate on federal student loans in more than a decade</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/14/education-dept-announces-2024-25-interest-rates-on-student-loans.html</link><description>The U.S. Department of Education announced on Tuesday the interest rates on federal student loans for the 2024-2025 academic year.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 18:49:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kyle Richards Breaks Silence on Mauricio Umansky Moving Out of House</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1401561/kyle-richards-shares-surprising-reaction-to-mauricio-umansky-moving-out-of-their-house?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>Kyle Richards and Mauricio Umansky's breakup just got even more real. Nearly one year after The Real Housewives of Beverly Hills star announced she and her husband had separated after 29 years of...</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 18:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coiled Tight: Smaller Companies Are Primed for Outperformance</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/08/coiled-tight-smaller-companies-are-primed-for-outperformance/</link><description>Small-cap companies are poised for a rebound. The sector is best approached through an active investment strategy where expertise and a deep understanding of the individual businesses and their risk-and-reward characteristics are necessary for success.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:40:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘Judge Judy’ sues National Enquirer parent company over misattributed quote in Menendez Brothers story</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/14/judge-judy-sues-national-enquirer-parent-company-menendez-brothers/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/AP24134678083837.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>“When you fabricate stories about me in order to make money for yourselves with no regard for the truth or the reputation I've spent a lifetime cultivating, it's going to cost you."</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:15:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shell Season</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/shell-season/</link><description>Spring welcomes the captivating allure of shell season. As nature awakens and warmth spreads, ocean treasures inspire wardrobe choices. This… The post Shell Season appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:58:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Guy will do anything to get laid on prom night</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/an7XMGo</link><description>Tags: random , wtf , wholesome 4235 points, 375 comments.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:40:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>La Liga’s Real Betis Focus on Water With Newest Edition of ‘Forever Green’ Kits</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/13/la-ligas-real-betis-focus-on-water-with-newest-edition-of-forever-green-kits/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Club aims to raise awareness about the responsible use of water and the impact climate change is having on fields in Spain and all over the world</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 15:54:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Google gets serious about AI-generated video at Google I/O 2024</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/14/google-gets-serious-about-ai-generated-video/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Veo can capture different visual and cinematic styles, including shots of landscapes and timelapses, and make edits and adjustments to already-generated footage. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weinstein Ruling Poses Quandary: Can #MeToo Coexist With Protections for Defendants?</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/04/sex-crimes-weinstein-me-too</link><description>Proving sex crimes often requires evidence that is generally excluded to protect the rights of the accused.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Thai Chicken Salad</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/thai-chicken-salad/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Crunchy and bright, this Thai Chicken Salad with creamy peanut dressing is bursting with flavor, texture and deliciousness! Prep it in…</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kelly Clarkson Admits to Using Weight Loss Drug After Physical Transformation</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/13/kelly-clarkson-admits-using-weight-loss-drug-medication-physical-transformation/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Kelly Clarkson is getting honest about her physical transformation ... admitting she used a weight loss drug to help shed pounds -- something she'd kinda tip-toed around until now. The singer got candid about her health journey during Monday's…</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:41:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Working It Out: How to Minimize Eczema Flare-ups at the Gym and on the Job</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/minimize-eczema-flare-ups-gym-job?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Three keys to managing your eczema at the gym and then heading off to a productive and itch-free workday.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 07:30:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Corn Plant – Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/corn-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Corn plants ( Dracaena fragrans ) are popular low-maintenance houseplants you’ve probably seen at the nursery, home improvement store, or doctor’s office. I even had one in my college dorm room! You can recognize them by their spear-shaped leaves and woody, cane-line trunks that can grow up to 6 feet tall indoors. But did you know there are several varieties of corn plants? We didn’t! Heck, we didn’t even realize some of our smaller houseplants were in the same corn plant family! Currently, we own two smaller varieties of corn plants, pictured above. The one on the left is a Dracaena Limelight ( Dracaena fragrans ‘Limelight’ ) and the taller plant is a Draecanea Dorado ( Dracaena fragrans ‘Dorado’ ). We actually have several limelights around because we love their vibrant color on shelves, tabletops, and windowsills. Corn Plant Quick Facts Latin name : Dracaena fragrans Common names : Corn plant, cornstalk plant, false palms Light : Bright, indirect light but can tolerate lower-light conditions Watering : Keep soil moist, but not soggy. Continue reading Corn Plant – Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 17:37:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Earnings Divergence Opportunity</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/the-earnings-divergence-opportunity/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, it's Ross Givens here with the Chart of the Day. Amidst economic concerns, analysts have defied expectations by boosting their earnings estimates for S&amp;P 500 companies. This unexpected trend challenges prevailing pessimism about the market's trajectory. In today's analysis, I delve into what this shift means and why it's crucial not to let pessimism hinder your pursuit of current market opportunities. The post The Earnings Divergence Opportunity appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Warm weather's back — and with it, reminders to prevent hot car deaths</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/article/warm-weathers-back-and-with-it-reminders-to-prevent-hot-car-deaths/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/14110953/female_driver_and_cheerful_young_boy_on_back_seat_.jpeg</image_url><description>Filed under: Government/Legal , Safety , Technology , Emerging Technologies Continue reading Warm weather's back — and with it, reminders to prevent hot car deaths Warm weather's back — and with it, reminders to prevent hot car deaths originally appeared on Autoblog on Tue, 14 May 2024 11:26:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 16:26:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Homeowners Are Slashing Prices In This Popular Region—Is There a Golden Opportunity For Investors?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/floridas-gulf-coast-homeowners-are-slashing-prices-according-to-report</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Inventory rose by a staggering 50% year over year in this popular state. Time to strike while the iron's hot?</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 14:10:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Riot’s Deals of the Day for May 14, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/book-riots-deals-of-the-day-for-may-14-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/deals-051424.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>A land of gods and monsters, a *very* special book, a mysterious alien biodome, and more of today's best book deals.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 16:24:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>15 Ways to Own Digital Terrain</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/15-ways-to-own-digital-terrain/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=15-ways-to-own-digital-terrain</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>It is now no longer optional…you must have an online presence! Your career stability and your job search demand it. Here are some tips to help you begin claiming digital terrain and brand it with your unique messaging! Why Should You Own Digital Terrain? You need to stake a claim by owning turf on the […] The post 15 Ways to Own Digital Terrain appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 15:56:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>“Why do they feel sad?” Shared book reading reveals how children learn about others’ emotions</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/shared-book-reading/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=shared-book-reading</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers: It is good for children to identify the emotions of others in conversations with caregivers because it scaffolds their ability to identify others’ emotions on their own. Children who use more emotion talk in parent-child conversations about emotions are more likely to have higher emotion knowledge one year later. Parents can […] The post “Why do they feel sad?” Shared book reading reveals how children learn about others’ emotions appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 08:19:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Google rolls out its most powerful AI models as competition from OpenAI heats up</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/14/google-announces-lightweight-ai-model-gemini-flash-1point5-at-google-i/o.html</link><description>Google on Tuesday announced new additions to its AI model following a flashy rollout a day earlier from OpenAI.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 18:46:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Isla Fisher Breaks Silence After Sacha Baron Cohen Split</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1401570/isla-fisher-breaks-silence-with-personal-update-after-sacha-baron-cohen-breakup?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>Isla Fisher is starting a new chapter. A month after the Wedding Crashers star and Sacha Baron Cohen announced they were divorcing after 13 years of marriage, she expressed her gratitude for the...</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 18:04:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Investment Returns Are NOT Random</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/07/investment-returns-are-not-random/</link><description>Are investment returns random across time as Burton Malkiel suggests in his book, A Random Walk Down Wall Street? There is notable disagreement on this topic. This research finds that practitioners may need to rethink their portfolio optimization routines.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:22:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Harvard protesters voluntarily withdraw after administration agrees to discuss endowment concerns</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/14/harvard-israel-gaza-middle-east-protests-divestment-endowment/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/AP24135530618360-e1715710080392.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Harvard interim President Alan Garber agreed to pursue a meeting between protesters and university officials regarding the students’ questions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:12:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Discovering My Avaline Favorites</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/discovering-my-avaline-favorites/</link><description>Thank you to Avaline for sponsoring this post. Spring symbolizes fresh starts and cleaner living. In my quest to align… The post Discovering My Avaline Favorites appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:50:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The best is Red Eric</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/aYQpxMV</link><description>Tags: Name 4297 points, 423 comments.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:40:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Leak: Los Angeles Dodgers City Connect Jersey Spotted in Japan</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/13/leak-los-angeles-dodgers-city-connect-jersey-spotted-in-tokyo/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Los Angeles Dodgers’ new City Connect uniform was leaked this weekend. The jersey, spotted hanging up in a store in Japan, shows a vibrant pattern that departs from the traditional Dodgers’ style. The photo shows a white jersey speckled with tiny blue, red, and yellow dots, giving the feeling</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 15:25:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gemini comes to Gmail to summarize, draft emails, and more</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/14/gemini-comes-to-gmail-to-summarize-and-draft-emails/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>In addition to the body of the emails themselves, the feature will also be able to analyze attachments, like PDFs. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mississippi Lawmakers Considered Modest Public Defense Reforms. They Rejected All of Them.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/02/mississippi-public-defense-legislative-reforms</link><description>With its refusal to impose oversight or consistent standards in local defense, Mississippi risks falling further behind rest of the U.S., critics say.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Meal Plan #4</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/weekly-menu-plan-4/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Take advantage of this weekly meal plan that has all the favorite recipes that families love! It is so easy…</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sylvester Stallone's 'Holy Grail' Watch Will Fetch Over $5 Mil, Expert Says</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/14/sylvester-stallone-grandmaster-chime-holy-grail-watch-nico-van-der-horst/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Sylvester Stallone is about to score a massive payday after putting his watch collection up for auction, because one of the timepieces could fetch a literal king's ransom. As you might have heard, the 'Rocky' star is selling 11 watches from his…</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:41:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cows Are Potential Spreaders of Bird Flu to Humans</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/food-recipes/food-poisoning/news/20240510/cows-are-potential-spreaders-bird-flu-humans?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Cow udders have the same receptors for flu viruses as humans and birds, raising concerns that cows could become “mixing vessels” that help the bird flu virus spread between people.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 19:36:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Using Solid Stain In Our Outdoor Shower</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/solid-deck-stain-outdoor-shower/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>In all of our years of DIYing, I don’t think we’ve ever used a solid stain before. But we recently had a project that was *perfectly* suited for it and, well, solid stain quickly won us over. It was recommended by a professional house painter to us, specifically because he thought it would be great for our outdoor shower. And we found it easy to apply, it gave us great coverage, and we got an even-better-than-we-expected result (which is always the best kind!). So here’s a post that covers all the pros &amp; cons and hows &amp; whys of solid stain. As you can see, the “canvas” for this staining project was our outdoor shower. We gave it a mini-makeover right after moving in, but we knew it may need more attention and care down the line. Honestly, we dreaded the task of stripping and restaining it – so many nooks &amp; crannies! Continue reading Using Solid Stain In Our Outdoor Shower at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 17:46:51 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>