<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from multiple RSS sources, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 15:17:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Boost Your Cash Flow in 2024 with These “Self-Management” Tips</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-401</link><description>Want more cash flow with less stress while running your rental property portfolio? Then you need self-management! Amelia McGee and Grace Gudenkauf, seasoned investors and the minds behind BiggerPockets’ newest […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 07:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Musk raises $6B for AI startup. Also, is TikTok dodging Apple’s commissions?</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/03/xai-billions-and-apple-vs-tiktok-startups-weekly/</link><description>Welcome to Startups Weekly — Haje’s weekly recap of everything you can’t miss from the world of startups. Sign up here to get it in your inbox every Friday. Musk’s 10-month-old baby, xAI, is closing in on a whoppin’ $6 billion funding round. The social network X, née Twitter — also part of Elon’s tech […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 20:05:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mississippi Lawmakers Considered Modest Public Defense Reforms. They Rejected All of Them.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/02/mississippi-public-defense-legislative-reforms</link><description>With its refusal to impose oversight or consistent standards in local defense, Mississippi risks falling further behind rest of the U.S., critics say.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What's Behind Major Rise in Heart Failure Deaths?</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/heart-disease/heart-failure/news/20240503/heart-failure-mortality-rate-continues-to-rise?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>After falling for over a decade, the death rate climbed for several years and now is about the same as in 1999.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 18:36:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Rational Investor’s Case Against Bitcoin</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-525</link><description>Cryptocurrency enthusiasts can’t fathom why Bitcoin will fail. If you tell them that you’re not investing in Bitcoin or other cryptos, they look at you like an uneducated investor, a […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 07:01:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Three things we learned about Apple’s AI plans from its earnings</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/03/three-things-we-learned-about-apples-ai-plans-from-its-earnings/</link><description>Despite spending more than $100 billion on R&amp;D over the last five years, Apple isn't planning to spin up too many new data centers to run or train AI models.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 19:59:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In This Police Youth Program, a Trail of Sexual Abuse Across the U.S.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/01/police-explorer-sexual-abuse-boy-scouts</link><description>Explorer posts, overseen by the Boy Scouts, are supposed to foster an interest in policing. They have faced nearly 200 allegations of misconduct.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 18:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jump-Start Your Exercise With This Mindset Reset</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/fitness-exercise/news/20240429/jump-start-exercise-with-this-mindset-reset?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>There are far more powerful motivators than “get abs!” to help you start an exercise routine you’ll stick to.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 18:25:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2024 Deals We’re Doing with High Cash Flow and Rock-Bottom Rates (4.75%!)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-947</link><description>Want a low mortgage rate? We mean a really low rate—like 4.75% in 2024 low. What about half a million in profit on a sneaky development deal? Or, maybe you’d […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 07:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fisker stiffed the engineering firm developing its low-cost EV and pickup truck, lawsuit claims</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/03/fisker-pear-alaska-lawsuit-engineering-class-action/</link><description>Henrik Fisker stood on a stage last August and proudly debuted two prototypes designed to catapult his eponymous EV startup Fisker into the mainstream. There was the Pear, a low-cost EV meant for the masses, and the Alaska, Fisker’s entry into the red-hot pickup truck market. In the weeks that followed, Fisker stopped paying the […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 19:53:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Campus Protests Could Shape the 2024 Elections — And Not Just the Presidency</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/30/campus-protests-gaza-arrests-prosecutors-elections</link><description>With hundreds of arrests and more campus standoffs looming, local law enforcement officials could face consequences at the ballot box.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 21:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When Does Old Age Start? It Depends on Who You Ask</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/news/20240502/when-does-old-age-start-many-disagree?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>The goalpost for old age has been moving. Until now.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 18:45:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Home Prices Stagnate in The South and America’s New #1 Housing Market</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-213</link><description>Texas and Florida are seeing stagnating home prices as housing inventory booms while demand slips away. Housing is still expensive, but with more inventory, why is it staying that way? […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 07:02:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Instagram now lets you post a secret Story that viewers can uncover with a DM</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/03/instagram-now-lets-you-post-a-secret-story-that-viewers-can-uncover-with-a-dm/</link><description>Instagram is adding a handful of new features for Stories to give users more creative ways to share content and engage with each other, the company announced on Friday. Most notably, the social network is introducing a new “Reveal” feature that lets you post a hidden Story for your followers to uncover by sending you […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 19:36:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>They Killed Their Abusive Partners. Now Their Sentences Could Be Reconsidered.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/27/oklahoma-oregon-minnesota-domestic-violence</link><description>Oklahoma could re-examine how it punishes people whose crimes came after years of domestic abuse. Other states may follow.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prospects for Crohn's Relief Brighten With New Advancements</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/ibd-crohns-disease/crohns-disease/news/20240502/prospects-crohns-relief-brighten-with-new-advancements?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>More than 1 million Americans live with Crohn’s, a chronic and sometimes crippling bowel disease that affects the intestines and leads to digestive issues. But in 2024, breakthroughs could bring relief in different ways. Here's what to know.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 17:59:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Contractor Nightmares: 5 Red Flags to Watch For and How to Escape a Bad Hire</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/red-flags-to-avoid-with-contractors-and-how-to-escape-a-bad-hire</link><description>What’s easier to find, a unicorn or a rock star contractor? If you asked most value-add real estate investors, the answer would be obvious: “Unicorns, of course.” We all know the inherent […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 17:18:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sprinklr lays off more than 100 employees</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/03/sprinklr-lays-off-more-than-100-employees/</link><description>The new job cuts come over a year after the company cut about 4% of its headcount in February last year.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 19:17:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Being Trans in Prison Is Really Like</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/26/trans-prison-voices-gender-essay</link><description>Amid a wave of anti-trans legislation, and the violence that often follows, four people share their experiences in the criminal justice system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 11:00:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Truth or TV: Is Grey's Anatomy's Parkinson's 'Cure' Real?</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/parkinsons-disease/features/is-greys-anatomys-parkinsons-cure-real?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>How realistic is the Grey’s Anatomy episode that shows a Parkinson’s disease cure? A neurosurgery professor weighs in.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 08:17:35 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>