<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 06:57:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Should I Pay Off My Mortgage or Invest? (We Did the Math)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-554</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Pay off your mortgage or invest? If you’re on the path to FIRE, you’ve probably asked yourself this question. Without a mortgage payment, you could put thousands more in your […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:01:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>She grew up a gearhead — now her startup has raised $4.3M to cut CO2 from trucking</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/13/she-grew-up-a-gearhead-now-her-startup-has-raised-4m-to-cut-co2-from-trucking/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>The irony was not lost on her. Growing up the daughter of a family obsessed with car racing, Danielle Walsh had become — in her late 20s — the head of HSBC’s ‘Future Cities’ project, the global banking giant’s effort to serve clients’ climate change mandates. It was 2018, and she was reporting both into the […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:18:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘Deliberate Indifference’: Court Rulings Challenge Extreme Heat Conditions in Prisons</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/10/texas-heat-louisiana-prison</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>“If it’s 103 outside, it may be 107 to -8 inside of your cell,” said a man who worked in the fields while imprisoned in Texas.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Demand For Section 8 Housing Will Remain High—Here’s Why</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/section-8-housing-will-be-in-high-demand-for-years-to-come</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Many Americans struggle to afford housing and will continue to, making this one of the most surefire ways to keep your properties in demand.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 21:04:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Opera is releasing its redesigned browser on iOS</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/13/opera-is-releasing-its-redesigned-browser-on-ios/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Opera is releasing its redesigned Opera One browser on iOS as a stable release after testing it in the beta phase for weeks. The new browser has a bottom placed search bar for easy browsing, quick search suggestions while typing, and Aria AI assistant integration. While the placed search bar will be the default option, […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tim Walz on Criminal Justice: 5 Things to Know</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/06/tim-walz-kamala-harris-vp-criminal-justice</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Where Minnesota Gov. Tim Walz, Vice President Kamala Harris’ running mate, stands on policing, guns, prison reform and other issues.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Even If the Fed Cuts Rates, Homes Will Still Be Just as Expensive</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/even-if-the-fed-cuts-rates-homes-will-still-be-expensive</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>The Fed is expected to cut rates next month, but that won't solve affordability problems anytime soon.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 20:08:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The crypto founder who didn’t save Puerto Rico after all</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/12/the-crypto-founder-who-didnt-save-puerto-rico-after-all/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>In Puerto Rico, tax breaks enacted in 2012 aimed to juice the economy by encouraging mainland U.S. citizens to do business and live on the island, where they could apply to pay nothing in capital gains taxes. But the tech — and primarily crypto — entrepreneurs who showed up in droves to shield their wealth […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 07:10:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>They Exposed Police Misconduct. Now They’re Paying a Steep Price.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/03/police-congress-corruption-whistleblower</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Whistleblower laws have advanced in public and private sectors, but protections for police who report illegal or unethical behavior lag far behind.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From $17K/Year Teacher Salary to Financial Freedom with Repeatable Rentals</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-1003</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>How does a teacher with a LOW salary achieve financial freedom, let alone invest in real estate? Surprisingly, it’s not as hard as you think, and if you repeat the […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 10:00:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elon Musk and Donald Trump’s X Spaces event crashes</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/12/elon-musk-and-donald-trumps-x-spaces-crashes/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Elon Musk and Donald Trump’s joint X Spaces event appears to have crashed Monday afternoon. The conversation between the owner of X and the former President was scheduled for 5 pm PT, but users received an error message when joining at that time. “This Space is not available,” said a message on X when trying […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 02:00:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Drawing Attention</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/01/news-inside-issue-17</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>News Inside Issue 17 features the opinions of justice-affected people on Trump’s felonies, and a nonfiction comic about death penalty mitigation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Short-Term Rental Demand Returns, So Why Are Hosts Making Less?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-242</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>A couple of years ago, everyone was expecting an “Airbnbust,” where short-term rental investments would sit vacant, hosts would be forced to sell, and hotels would take the reigns as […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 10:00:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Antler doubles down on Southeast Asia with $72M second startup fund</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/12/antler-closes-72m-second-sea-fund-to-ramp-up-startup-investment-in-southeast-asia/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Antler, the Singapore VC that focuses on early-stage investments, just closed its second Southeast Asia fund. It’s raised $72 million to double down on startups in Singapore, Indonesia, Vietnam and Malaysia. This should be welcome news for startups. Like other regions, Southeast Asia has faced a persistent funding slump. Between January and July 2024, tech […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 01:59:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>These Private Centers Lack Oversight. Cuyahoga County Judges Send Kids Anyway.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/01/juvenile-justice-detention-prison-youth-treatment-cuyahoga-county</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Courts are increasingly sending children to private youth care centers, spending millions while detention center overcrowding persists.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>