<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from multiple RSS sources, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:39:40 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Seeing Greene: Is Losing $800/Month in Cash Flow Worth $200K+ Equity?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-949</link><description>Would you buy a rental property that loses money every month? What if, in a few years, that one property could make you hundreds of thousands of dollars? Would the […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 07:02:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rivian loses $1.45 billion as cost-cutting measures continue</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/07/rivian-q1-2024-earnings-results-profit/</link><description>Rivian lost $1.45 billion in the first quarter, showing that its recent company-wide cost-cutting measures have a ways to go before it can approach profitability. The EV-maker brought in $1.2 billion in revenue in the period, coming in just under its record haul from the prior quarter, according to its first-quarter earnings report that was […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:17:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Marshall Project Wins the Dart Award for “The Mercy Workers”</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/06/the-marshall-project-wins-the-dart-award-for-the-mercy-workers</link><description>Our feature on mitigation specialists who help save people from the death penalty was recognized for making “significant contributions to public understanding of trauma-related issues.”</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Postpartum PTSD: Right Diagnosis Can Help Mothers and Babies</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/mental-health/news/20240506/postpartum-ptsd-right-diagnosis-can-help-mothers-and-babies?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Many new mothers aren’t aware that postpartum PTSD even exists, but it’s far from rare. Here's what to know.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:19:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Personal Finance for Beginners: Bank Accounts, Real Estate, and Retirement</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-526</link><description>Personal finance doesn’t have to be complicated. Saving, investing, and retiring early shouldn’t be a stumbling path to wealth, but many Americans feel this way. So, to clear up some […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 07:01:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meta’s AI tools for advertisers can now create full new images, not just new backgrounds</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/07/metas-ai-tools-for-advertisers-can-now-create-new-images-not-just-new-backgrounds/</link><description>Meta claims that it has strong guardrails in place to prevent its system from generating inappropriate ad content or low-quality images.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:00:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weinstein Ruling Poses Quandary: Can #MeToo Coexist With Protections for Defendants?</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/04/sex-crimes-weinstein-me-too</link><description>Proving sex crimes often requires evidence that is generally excluded to protect the rights of the accused.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Living With Major Depressive Disorder</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/depression/features/live-with-mdd?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>See how one person manages the ups and downs of major depressive disorder -- and how her depression inspired her career as a therapist.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:45:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The American Dream Trap: Maneuvering Major Expenses in Your Financial Adventure</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/avoid-wealth-detours-by-managing-big-ticket-expenses</link><description>From the moment we take our first steps, we’re handed a blueprint for the American dream: It’s the classic tale of success, promising a life of stability, security, and financial […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 21:50:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden signs bill to protect children from online sexual abuse and exploitation</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/07/biden-signs-bill-to-protect-children-from-online-sexual-abuse-and-exploitation/</link><description>On April 29, Senators Jon Ossoff (D-GA) and Marsha Blackburn (R-SC) proposed a bipartisan bill to protect children from online sexual exploitation. President Biden officially signed the REPORT Act into law on Tuesday. This marks the first time that websites and social media platforms are legally obligated to report crimes related to federal trafficking, grooming, […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 20:30:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mississippi Lawmakers Considered Modest Public Defense Reforms. They Rejected All of Them.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/02/mississippi-public-defense-legislative-reforms</link><description>With its refusal to impose oversight or consistent standards in local defense, Mississippi risks falling further behind rest of the U.S., critics say.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Therapist’s Perspective</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/depression/features/mdd-therapists-perspective?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>A therapist talks about managing major depressive disorder (MDD): what to expect, strategies for dealing with setbacks, and when to talk to your therapist.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:45:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Adjustable Rate Mortgages a Lifeline for Lower Rates? Or the Most Dangerous Thing You Could Do?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/are-adjustable-rate-mortgages-dangerous-or-a-lifeline-for-lower-rates</link><description>If, like me, you check mortgage interest rates like an expectant parent checks their wife’s contractions, you doubtless will have analyzed every type of loan product in an attempt to inch the […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 21:38:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bloom is reinventing how e-bikes are made in the US</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/07/bloom-is-reinventing-how-e-bikes-are-made-in-the-us/</link><description>The pandemic ushered in an e-bike boom. But like so many other pandemic trends, that boom didn’t last. The last year has seen e-bike startups VanMoof and Cake file for bankruptcy amid a backdrop of micromobility doom and gloom. Tier and Dott merged. Superpedestrian closed up shop. Bird also had to go through a restructuring. […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 20:27:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In This Police Youth Program, a Trail of Sexual Abuse Across the U.S.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/01/police-explorer-sexual-abuse-boy-scouts</link><description>Explorer posts, overseen by the Boy Scouts, are supposed to foster an interest in policing. They have faced nearly 200 allegations of misconduct.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 18:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Handling the Stigma</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/depression/features/mdd-stigma?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Learn from a mental health advocate how the stigma of depression is changing and how acceptance is the first step to managing major depressive disorder.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:44:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Detroit Beat Its Post-Pandemic Downtown Doom Loop—Here’s How Investors Can Benefit</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/detroit-beats-post-pandemic-downtown-doom-loop</link><description>A mayor in handcuffs, a bankrupt city mired in poverty, unemployment, and soaring crime: 10 years ago that was Detroit’s legacy. Today, it is a real estate success story.  Early investors—to quote one […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 21:21:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple unveils a new Magic Keyboard at iPad event</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/07/apple-unveils-a-new-magic-keyboard/</link><description>At its iPad-focused event on Monday, Apple announced a new and improved Magic Keyboard, its keyboard accessory for iPad. The Magic Keyboard has been “completely redesigned” to be much thinner and lighter, Apple says, and now includes a function row for quick access to controls like screen brightness, volume adjustment and play/pause. Beyond that, the […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 20:12:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Campus Protests Could Shape the 2024 Elections — And Not Just the Presidency</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/30/campus-protests-gaza-arrests-prosecutors-elections</link><description>With hundreds of arrests and more campus standoffs looming, local law enforcement officials could face consequences at the ballot box.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 21:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How I Share About My Condition</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/depression/features/mdd-talk-about?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>A person with major depressive disorder shares how they talk about their condition with others.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:44:37 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>