<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 16:43:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Malta is a Hot, Stunning Island Market in Europe—Here’s How to Invest There</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/investing-in-malta-real-estate</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>While golden visas are sunsetting or significantly changing around Europe, there are still a few opportunities for Americans to buy international real estate, to live in or rent out, at […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 19:27:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>You can now customize your For You feed on Threads using swipes</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/03/you-can-now-customize-your-for-you-feed-on-threads-using-swipes/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Instagram Threads is rolling out the ability for users to signal which sort of posts they wanted to see more or less of by swiping. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 21:38:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How We Reported on Homicide Investigations in St. Louis</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/03/st-louis-police-unsolved-murders-methods</link><description>Getting and interpreting homicide clearance data involved litigation, complex analysis and patience.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Federal Experts Talk Bird Flu ‘What Ifs’ in WebMD Live Event</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/cold-and-flu/news/20240516/federal-experts-talk-bird-flu-what-ifs?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>WebMD brought together experts from four federal agencies to talk prevention, monitoring, and what the “what ifs” of bird flu might look like.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:50:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Preferred Equity is an Alternative Asset Class You Can Buy in Real Estate Right Now—These Are the Four Types</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/four-types-of-preferred-equity-and-how-to-evaluate-each</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>“You’re investing in preferred equity? No thanks—I don’t invest in rescue capital!” I’ve heard this comment from prospective investors in different forms more than a few times in the past […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 19:16:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Japanese billionaire pulls plug on private ‘dearMoon’ lunar Starship mission</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/03/japanese-billionaire-pulls-plug-on-private-dearmoon-lunar-starship-mission/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The Japanese billionaire who commissioned SpaceX for a private mission around the moon on a Starship rocket has abruptly canceled the project, citing ongoing uncertainties around when the launch vehicle will be ready to fly. “I signed the contract in 2018 based on the assumption that dearMoon would launch by the end of 2023,” Yusaku […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 20:52:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why 1,000 Homicides in St. Louis Remain Unsolved</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/03/st-louis-police-unsolved-murders</link><description>In one of America’s deadliest cities, police have struggled to solve killings due to staffing shortages, shoddy detective work and lack of community trust.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What’s Next in Health Care for Older Adults: Questions and Answers With John Whyte, MD</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/blog-aging-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>As WebMD’s chief medical officer, John Whyte, MD, is in a unique position to see both the current state of medical care for America’s older adults and the way things are trending for the future. We asked him to share his insight on a few topics, along with a bit of advice.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:29:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Much Should a State’s Landlord-Tenant Laws Affect Your Real Estate Investing Strategy?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/how-changing-landlord-tenant-laws-could-impact-your-real-estate-strategy</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>If you are a new investor with limited capital, having the misfortune of renting to a bad tenant in a tenant-friendly state can cripple you financially and put you off […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 18:47:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>People are using AI music generators to create hateful songs</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/03/people-are-using-ai-music-generators-to-create-hateful-songs/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Malicious actors are abusing generative AI music tools to create homophobic, racist, and propagandic songs — and publishing guides instructing others how to do so. According to ActiveFence, a service for managing trust and safety operations on online platforms, there’s been a spike in chatter within “hate speech-related” communities since March about ways to misuse […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 20:19:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Abortion’s Legal Landscape Post-Roe is Causing Fear and Confusion</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/01/abortion-supreme-court-roe-dobbs</link><description>We spoke with seven reproductive rights organizations — here’s what we found.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Get the Care You Need in a COVID-19 World</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/covid-senior-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>What to expect at the doctor’s office, hospitals, and long-term care facilities, the future of telemedicine, and how to get the best care during COVID-19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 19:50:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Boomers Hoard Houses, Millennials Struggle to Buy, But Gen Z Gets Ahead w/Redfin’s Chen Zhao</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-222</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Millennials can’t afford homes, but somehow, their younger siblings, Gen Z, can. Even with over a decade more work experience than Gen Z, Millennials still feel priced out of the […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 07:02:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What to expect from Apple’s AI-powered iOS 18 at WWDC</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/03/what-to-expect-from-apples-ai-powered-ios-18/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>As WWDC 2024 nears, all sorts of rumors and leaks have emerged about what iOS 18 and its AI-powered apps and features have in store. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 19:46:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I Recorded a Whole Hip-Hop Album on a Death Row Telephone</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/31/north-carolina-death-row-rapper-book-excerpt</link><description>In this new book excerpt, incarcerated rapper Alim “RRome Alone” Braxton describes his early attempts to record vocals over a phone in the dayroom.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Personal Shopper: A Savvy Black Entrepreneur Guides You to Eczema-Friendly Clothes, Creams, Cosmetics, and More</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/savvy-black-entrepreneur-guides-eczema-friendly-clothes-creams-cosmetics?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>A savvy black entrepreneur guides you on an eczema-friendly shopping spree.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:54:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Financial Independence at 29 by Quitting Rentals to Invest in THIS</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-414</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Do you dream of building a real estate empire and reaching financial independence but stop short due to the “tenants and toilets” problem? The irony wasn’t lost on twenty-nine-year-old Dillon […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 07:02:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GM’s Cruise is testing robotaxis in Dallas again</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/03/gms-cruise-is-testing-robotaxis-in-dallas-again/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Dallas is the second city that Cruise is easing its way back into after pulling its entire U.S. fleet late last year. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 19:24:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Legal Doctrine That Shields Police From Many Lawsuits May Be Losing Support</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/25/police-mississippi-courts-judges-qualified-immunity</link><description>A federal judge in Mississippi joined other courts in recently rejecting police arguments that qualified immunity protected their actions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Behind the Spike in Colorectal Cancer Among Young Americans</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/colorectal-cancer/news/20240515/behind-the-spike-in-colorectal-cancer-cases?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Colorectal cancer cases increased a whopping 333% among 15- to 19-year-olds and 185% among 20- to 24-year-olds from 1999 to 2020.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:59:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>