<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 07:26:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Turning $5,000 Into 50+ Doors and a 7-Figure Net Worth Before the Age of 30</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-441</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>You don’t need a huge inheritance or nest egg to start investing in real estate. Just ask Cody Caswell, who landed his first deal at sixteen years old with only […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 10:01:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elon Musk’s X taken to court in Ireland for grabbing EU user data to train Grok without consent</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/07/elon-musks-x-taken-to-court-in-ireland-for-grabbing-eu-user-data-to-train-grok-without-consent/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Elon Musk's X is being taken to court in Ireland for using Europeans' data to train AI models without asking for their consent. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 11:02:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tim Walz on Criminal Justice: 5 Things to Know</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/06/tim-walz-kamala-harris-vp-criminal-justice</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>Where Minnesota Gov. Tim Walz, Vice President Kamala Harris’ running mate, stands on policing, guns, prison reform and other issues.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2024’s Biggest Opportunities (and Risks!) in Real Estate Investing</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-1001</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>Want to make money in real estate investing, EVEN during 2024’s harsh housing market? It’s easier than you might think—and we’ve got the proof. We brought expert investors Ashley Kehr […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 10:01:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Automattic launches AI writing tool that aims to make WordPress blogs more readable and succinct</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/07/automattic-launches-ai-writing-tool-that-aims-to-make-wordpress-blogs-more-readable-and-succinct/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>Automattic, the owner of WordPress.com, has launched a new AI tool designed to help bloggers write more clearly and succinctly. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 10:32:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>They Exposed Police Misconduct. Now They’re Paying a Steep Price.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/03/police-congress-corruption-whistleblower</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Whistleblower laws have advanced in public and private sectors, but protections for police who report illegal or unethical behavior lag far behind.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From Making $40K/Year as a Teacher to Reaching FI in 4 Years by Doing THIS</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-552</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>You can take your time to reach financial independence, but why wait? With a combination of hard work, savvy investing, and additional income streams, today’s guest reached FI by the […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 07:01:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>EQT takes a majority stake in cybersecurity firm Acronis at $3.5B+ valuation</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/07/eqt-takes-a-majority-stake-in-cybersecurity-firm-acronis-at-a-3-5b-valuation/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Cybersecurity remains a white-hot space for investors. In the latest example of that demand, EQT has bought a majority stake in Acronis, a security company that specializes in data protection, cloud and integrated security solutions for managed service providers (which resell services to consumers) and corporate IT teams. The size and value of the stake, […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 08:26:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Drawing Attention</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/01/news-inside-issue-17</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>News Inside Issue 17 features the opinions of justice-affected people on Trump’s felonies, and a nonfiction comic about death penalty mitigation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>San Francisco Leaders Approve Measure to Ban Price-Setting Software To Combat High Rent Prices</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/san-francisco-leaders-approve-measure-to-ban-price-fixing-software</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>The city may become the first in the country to ban tech tools allegedly associated with rent price fixing.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 21:29:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>UK data watchdog to fine NHS vendor Advanced for security failures prior to LockBit ransomware attack</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/06/uk-data-watchdog-fines-nhs-vendor-advanced-for-security-failures-prior-to-lockbit-ransomware-attack/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>The ICO issued the provisional fine in "failing to implement appropriate security measures prior to the attack." © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 00:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>These Private Centers Lack Oversight. Cuyahoga County Judges Send Kids Anyway.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/01/juvenile-justice-detention-prison-youth-treatment-cuyahoga-county</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>Courts are increasingly sending children to private youth care centers, spending millions while detention center overcrowding persists.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Avoid Costly Repairs: Don’t Ignore the Red Flags in a Property Inspection</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/dont-ignore-the-red-flags-in-a-property-inspection</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>Avoid costly surprises when buying property by addressing red flags in inspection reports.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 19:53:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jumia plans to raise more than $100 million in secondary shares to drive stalled user growth</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/06/jumia-plans-to-raise-more-than-100-million-in-secondary-shares-to-drive-stalled-user-growth/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>African e-commerce company Jumia is selling 20 million American depositary shares over the next couple of weeks, TechCrunch has learned. The at-the-market transaction is to take advantage of strong results despite a volatile market. Given Jumia’s share price of around $5.70 when the stock market opened on Tuesday, the e-commerce company could potentially raise approximately […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 00:00:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Facing Rollbacks, Criminal Justice Reformers Argue Policies Make People Safer</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/01/california-illinois-crime-public-safety-reform</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Advocates are refining their rebuttal to “tough on crime” messaging: Don’t focus on punishment, but on reforms that improve public safety.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>