<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 06:56:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Jacksonville Jaguars Reveal 30th Season Logo Following Fan Vote</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/28/jacksonville-jaguars-reveal-30th-season-logo-following-fan-vote/football/</link><description>After asking fans to vote among four unique designs, the Jacksonville Jaguars officially unveiled their new 30th season logo during their 2024 NFL Draft party on Thursday evening.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 15:43:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ryan Gosling's Surprise Appearance At Universal Studios Stunt Show</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/28/ryan-gosling-surprise-appearance-universal-studios-hollywood-fall-guy-stunt-show/</link><description>Ryan Gosling had hearts fluttering and pulses racing ... when he made a surprise cameo at Universal Studios Hollywood's stunt show inspired by his new flick "The Fall Guy." Ry popped up onstage during the promotional "Waterworld" pre-show, 'The…</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 06:56:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NFL Will Allow Players To Wear Guardian Caps In Games</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/28/nfl-will-allow-players-to-wear-guardian-caps-in-games/football/</link><description>The NFL announced it will now allow players to wear Guardian Caps, a 12-ounce soft shell that fits over their helmets, during regular-season games in an effort to reduce head injuries.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 15:25:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Morgan Freeman Spoofs Viral Nicole Kidman AMC Ad at AFI Award Gala</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/28/afi-awards-nicole-kidman-morgan-freeman-amc-ad-spoof/</link><description>Count Morgan Freeman as the latest celeb to parody Nicole Kidman's viral AMC spot ... Only this time it was to honor the actress's many achievements. Nicole received the AFI Life Achievement Award ... and the star-studded audience was treated to a…</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 06:56:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Report: CFL’s Saskatchewan Roughriders to Add Fourth Uniform in 2024</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/27/report-cfls-saskatchewan-roughriders-to-add-fourth-uniform-in-2024/football/</link><description>Riders reportedly adding uniform that's predominantly a darker shade of green than usual; helmet to feature logo filed with Canadian trademark office in 2022</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 18:13:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kristin Cavallari &amp; BF Mark Estes' Loving Stare At Stagecoach</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/28/kristin-cavallari-boyfriend-mark-estes-stagecoach-megan-fox-mgk/</link><description>Kristin Cavallari got nice and cozy under the Coachella Desert skies with hunky young boyfriend Mark Estes ... gazing into each other's eyes at night 2 of the Stagecoach Festival. Kristin posted the photo to her Instagram Story Saturday night,…</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 06:56:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Madison Mallards declare, we are the Wurst</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/27/madison-mallards-declare-we-are-the-wurst/baseball/</link><description>Fresh off the successful unveiling of their Chris Farley–inspired Madison Motivational Speakers alternate identity, the collegiate summer level Madison Mallards unveiled a second temporary rebrand based on a meaty Wisconsin classic. The team will play one game as the Wisconsin Wurst for one game this summer. The identity is based</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 17:41:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Logan Paul and Nina Agdal Hold Gender Reveal Wrestling Match</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/28/logan-paul-nina-agdal-gender-reveal-wrestling-match-wwe/</link><description>Logan Paul and Nina Agdal's gender reveal got downright violent Saturday ... 'cause the pair announced their child's sex via an intense wrestling bout -- with twists and turns galore. The expecting parents decided to learn the news in a knockdown…</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 06:56:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Carolina Disco Turkeys change tune, to play as Yacht Rockers</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/27/carolina-disco-turkeys-change-tune-to-play-as-yacht-rockers/baseball/</link><description>The Carolina Disco Turkeys will trade their bell bottoms, polyester, and sparkly sequins for salmon polo shirts, ascots, and captain’s hats for one game this summer. The team announced this week that they’ll play as the Yacht Rockers, changing the vibe in the ballpark from Stayin’ Alive to Sailing. Yacht</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 15:38:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Russell Brand Says He's Getting Baptized, Opportunity to Leave Past Behind</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/28/russell-brand-he-baptized-talk-leave-past-behind-baptism-sexual-assault-allegations/</link><description>Russell Brand's taking a big step in his faith journey ... announcing he's getting baptized -- and saying it's an opportunity to move on from the past. The controversial actor/podcast host posted a video to his Instagram recently ... telling his…</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 06:56:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>