<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 12:23:37 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Ole Miss Rebels Unveil Powder Blue-Accented Road Jersey</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/24/ole-miss-rebels-unveil-powder-blue-accented-road-jersey/college/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Ole Miss unveiled the first powder blue-accented road jersey in school history on Monday morning, granting the wishes of a large portion of the Rebels' fanbase.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 17:29:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Josh Duggar's Child Porn Appeal Rejected by Supreme Court</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/24/josh-duggar-appeal-rejected-supreme-court/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Josh Duggar's attempt to overturn his child pornography conviction in the U.S. Supreme Court has been rejected ... the justices declined to even hear his appeal. The U.S. Supreme Court denied Josh's attempt at an appeal on Monday, which comes after…</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 12:23:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Washington Capitals Celebrate 50th Anniversary With New Logos, Patches, and More</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/24/washington-capitals-celebrate-50th-anniversary-with-new-logos-jersey-patches-and-more/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Washington Capitals will celebrate their 50th anniversary in 2024-25 with a series of fun events, but most importantly (to us, anyway), a fantastic new series of commemorative anniversary logos and a jersey patch. The logo was designed in collaboration with FANBRANDZ. Over the past decade-plus, this agency has created</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 16:11:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Recording Academy CEO Harvey Mason Jr. Says 'Not Like Us' Diss Eligible For Grammys</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/24/harvey-mason-jr-grammys-kendrick-lamar-not-like-us/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Kendrick Lamar's "Not Like Us" is one of the hottest tracks on the planet, and Recording Academy CEO Harvey Mason Jr. says a diss track winning a Grammy might not be conventional ... but now it's definitely possible! TMZ Hip Hop spoke with the…</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 12:23:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tennessee Volunteers’ New “Smokey Grey” Alternate Jerseys Leak</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/22/tennessee-volunteers-new-smokey-grey-alternate-jerseys-leak/college/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>For the second year in a row, Tennessee had its new “Smokey Grey” alternate jersey leaked by Dick’s Sporting Goods after the retailer had a mannequin wearing the jersey on display on Friday afternoon.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 21:52:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Santa Cruz Beach Boardwalk Roller Coaster Evacuated, Riders Have to Walk Down</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/24/santa-cruz-beach-boardwalk-roller-coaster-evacuated-medical-emergency/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Thrill seekers got more than they bargained for at the Santa Cruz Beach Boardwalk ... folks who were riding the classic roller coaster had to be evacuated near the top of the ride!!! Footage from the beachside theme park shows several riders being…</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 12:23:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2024 MLB All-Star Game, Workout Caps Released</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/21/2024-mlb-all-star-game-workout-caps-released/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The stars at night will be big and bright (emphasis on bright), deep in the heart of Texas next month at the 2024 Major League Baseball All-Star Game. SHOP: Get your 2024 MLB All-Star Game on-field cap right now, right here Today, the league, along with New Era, unveiled the</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 18:54:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Federal Prosecutors Recommend Criminal Charges Over Boeing Safety Issues</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/24/federal-prosecutors-recommend-criminal-charges-boeing-safety-issues/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>The Boeing saga has peaked -- now, federal prosecutors are reportedly recommending Uncle Sam go after the company in court ... and hold them accountable, legally. According to multiple news outlets -- citing people familiar with the situation --…</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 12:23:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Crystal Palace, Valencia Headline Recent Kit Launches From Around Europe</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/21/crystal-palace-valencia-headline-recent-kit-launches-from-around-europe/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Other clubs releasing 2024-25 kits recently include: Getafe CF, Borussia Mönchengladbach, Stade Rennais, RC Lens, FC Nantes, SL Benfica, FC Porto</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 15:16:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ben Affleck Angrily Chews Out Paparazzi As They Flash Him Leaving J Lo House</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/24/ben-affleck-confronts-paparazzi-flash-leaving-jennifer-lopez-house/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Ben Affleck lost his cool on the paparazzi this weekend -- but for good reason ... they were flashing the crap out of him with their cameras, which he rightly noted was dangerous. The actor was spotted leaving his and Jennifer Lopez's marital home…</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 12:23:37 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>