<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 13:48:36 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>New Nonfiction for Your Book Club</title><link>https://bookriot.com/new-nonfiction-for-your-book-club/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/partial-cover-of-Theres-Always-This-Year-On-Basketball-and-Ascension-by-Hanif-Abdurraqib.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>What's the most recent nonfiction book you've read with your book club?</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hyundai and Kia thefts on the decline after anti-theft software upgrade</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/08/07/hyundai-kia-vehicle-theft-rates-going-down-post-software-fix/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1200x675/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/08/07124342/080724-news-Hyundai-Kia.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Hyundai , Kia , Insurance , Ownership Continue reading Hyundai and Kia thefts on the decline after anti-theft software upgrade Hyundai and Kia thefts on the decline after anti-theft software upgrade originally appeared on Autoblog on Wed, 7 Aug 2024 13:15:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 18:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Citi's post-pullback stock shopping list: Where to go after market sell-off</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/07/citis-post-pullback-stock-shopping-list-where-to-go-after-market-sell-off.html</link><description>Investors looking to sift through the sell-off should look for stocks that can withstand an economic shakeout, according to Citi.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 18:43:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 559</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-559/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-559</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Do you understand how recruiters work and how they think? Well, this should help! There’s no magic. Every recruiter has their own set of preferences for sourcing and vetting candidates. But many share tips and insights to give job seekers valuable information. In this week’s summary, you’ll find: Please follow and support the talented experts […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 559 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 12:33:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How parents can support math learning at home and through everyday activities</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/how-parents-can-support-math-learning-at-home/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=how-parents-can-support-math-learning-at-home</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Math skills at kindergarten entry predict children’s academic success in school. Young children usually enjoy learning math and can develop understanding about math in all the content areas they will encounter in school: number, patterns, shapes, spatial relations, and data. Parents can grow their young children’s math knowledge through playful activities […] The post How parents can support math learning at home and through everyday activities appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 23:18:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Boil Corn on the Cob</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/how-to-boil-corn-on-the-cob/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>This is the BEST recipe for how to boil corn on the cob! Fresh summer corn gets boiled in a…</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Best Air Purifying Plants</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/best-air-purifying-plants/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>We love any excuse to buy more plants, and you may have heard they can improve your home’s indoor air quality. But before you blow your paycheck in the name of a healthier home, let’s dive deeper into plants’ air purifying powers. We’ll share which plants we recommend and what benefits you can actually expect from them. We’ve heard for years about how plants act as natural air filters for your home. So let’s dive a little deeper, shall we? 7 Air Purifying Plants If you just came here for a list, our favorite air purifying houseplants are bulleted below. The best part is these are all beautiful, low-maintenance plants. Many also appear on our best low-light indoor plants list too! Dracaena (including Corn Plant ) Snake Plant Aglaonema English Ivy Pothos Bamboo Palm Spider Plant There are certainly more that could be included here, but we narrowed it to the ones that are most often cited by experts AND the plants that we think look best too. Continue reading Best Air Purifying Plants at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 14:15:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gone Fishing</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/08/gone-fishing/</link><description>Outfit Details: Ciao Lucia Dress (pants version here), Staud Bag, Loeffler Randall Sandals, Marissa Klass Necklace In the serene transition from late summer to early… The post Gone Fishing appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 05:00:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Audible Rolls Out AI-Generated Recommendations</title><link>https://bookriot.com/audible-ai-generated-recommendations/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/audible-logo.png</image_url><description>About half of U.S. Audible users have the new feature, currently in beta testing. Plus: JR Ward's 4-book romantasy series, and more.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 17:50:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2025 Mercedes-AMG C 63 S E Performance First Drive: Overkill through complexity</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/08/07/2024-mercedes-amg-c63-e-performance-first-drive-review/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1200x675/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/08/06155426/2025-Mercedes-AMG-C63-action-front-low1.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Mercedes-Benz , First Drives , Luxury , Performance , Sedan Continue reading 2025 Mercedes-AMG C 63 S E Performance First Drive: Overkill through complexity 2025 Mercedes-AMG C 63 S E Performance First Drive: Overkill through complexity originally appeared on Autoblog on Wed, 7 Aug 2024 13:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stocks making the biggest moves midday: Fortinet, Shopify, Lyft and more</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/07/stocks-making-the-biggest-moves-midday-ftnt-shop-lyft-and-more.html</link><description>These are the stocks posting the largest moves in midday trading.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 17:57:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 558</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-558/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-558</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Even though it’s summer, you can still take steps to move your job search forward. Set aside time to continue to learn about today’s job search trends and invest time learning about trends in your field. In this week’s Summary Sunday, you’ll find: I carefully curate articles and posts from sources I trust. I hope […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 558 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 14:14:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Do infants feel excluded? Early signs and why it matters</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/do-infants-feel-excluded/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=do-infants-feel-excluded</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Social exclusion harms individuals of all ages, leading to feelings of loneliness, decreased self-esteem, and even changes in brain activity. Humans’ ability to recognize and react to social exclusion emerges early, suggesting the importance of considering and addressing ostracism even when caring for very young children. Babies are sensitive to social […] The post Do infants feel excluded? Early signs and why it matters appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 01:37:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Italian Corn Salad</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/italian-corn-salad/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>This Italian Corn Salad is bursting with fresh flavors from sweet corn, juicy grape tomatoes, crisp green bell pepper, and…</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Weekend In New Orleans With Kids</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/new-orleans-with-kids/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Since our travel guides to Charleston with kids and Palm Springs with kids have elicited requests for more travel ideas with kids, we’re back with an overdue recap of our 3-night trip to New Orleans. We’d never been to The Big Easy before and were impressed by how family-friendly the city is. It’s not all booze, beads, and Bourbon Street! So here’s a look at where we stayed, what we did, and what we’re excited to do next time we go back – because we will definitely go back! The four of us (well, five if you count our chihuahua!) went to NOLA for 3 nights in November of 2022. At the time, our kids were 8 and 12 years old. So unfortunately we can’t vouch for our suggestions being a good fit for toddlers or younger children. Although I’m sure ours would’ve loved the Louisiana Children’s Museum and Storyland playground back in the day! Continue reading A Weekend In New Orleans With Kids at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 17:17:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Peak Season Patterns</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/08/peak-season-patterns/</link><description>Outfit Details: Emporio Sirenuse Dress, Janessa Leone Hat, Clare V Bag (available here in black), Dior Sandals (less expensive here),… The post Peak Season Patterns appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 05:00:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Project 2025 Architect Delays Book Until After the Election</title><link>https://bookriot.com/heritage-foundation-kevin-roberts-delays-book-project-2025/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/american-flag-flying-from-truck.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>Heritage Foundation president Kevin Roberts has delayed his book, originally slated for September publication, until mid-November.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 17:35:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The baddest Range Rover Sport returns in Edition Two guise</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/08/07/land-rover-range-rover-sport-sv-edition-two/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1200x675/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/08/07110741/RRS_SV_Edition_Two_25MY_01_DX_Nebula_Blue_070824-copy.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Land Rover , SUV , Luxury , Performance Continue reading The baddest Range Rover Sport returns in Edition Two guise The baddest Range Rover Sport returns in Edition Two guise originally appeared on Autoblog on Wed, 7 Aug 2024 12:17:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 17:17:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Warren Buffett now owns more T-bills than the Federal Reserve</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/07/warren-buffett-now-owns-more-t-bills-than-the-federal-reserve.html</link><description>The Omaha-based conglomerate held $234.6 billion in short-term investments in Treasury bills by the end of the second quarter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:34:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 557</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-557/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-557</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Searching for a new job requires clarity on what you want to do and where you want to do it. You need a solid strategy but most importantly you need tenacity. In short, job search is more than hitting the apply button. This week’s summary provides resources, tools and information to help you carry out […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 557 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 11:37:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10 Actions Parents Can Take to Help their Children Be More Resilient in a World of Adversity</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/10-actions-to-help-children-be-more-resilient/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=10-actions-to-help-children-be-more-resilient</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Decades of research points to specific ways parents can build resilience that can help protect children from the challenges of adverse experiences and stress. Strategies include parent-focused tips such as practicing self care, reflecting on one’s own past experiences, and developing emotional control. Additional strategies focus on ways to navigate relationships […] The post 10 Actions Parents Can Take to Help their Children Be More Resilient in a World of Adversity appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 02:36:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cinnamon Roll Cheesecake</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/cinnamon-roll-cheesecake/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Rich and creamy Cinnamon Roll Cheesecake has the delicious flavor of a cinnamon roll in decadent cheesecake form. This irresistible…</description><pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>9 Easy Low-Light Indoor Plants</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/easy-low-light-indoor-plants/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>I used to think every houseplant needed a sunny corner or bright windowsill to thrive. But it turns out many of our favorite go-to houseplants do just fine in shady corners and low-light locations. So before you write off your house as too dark to sustain plant life, check out this list of the best indoor plants for low light. You might be surprised at how many good options there are! Our upstairs family room is the brightest room we’ve ever owned thanks to big unobstructed windows on all 4 sides. But most of our indoor plants live downstairs, where we get far less natural light. Luckily, that hasn’t stopped us from growing our collection of happy healthy houseplants. 9 Houseplants That Don’t Need A Lot Of Light Here are our favorite low-light indoor plants. We list a lot more info on them below, but here’s a quick list to bring on your next trip to the plant store: Snake Plant ZZ Plant Pothos Heartleaf Philodendron English Ivy Aglaonema Cast Iron Plant Monstera Parlor Palm Perhaps our favorite part of this list is that these aren’t ugly “consolation plants” that people begrudgingly buy for dark homes. Continue reading 9 Easy Low-Light Indoor Plants at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 14:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Citrus</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/08/citrus/</link><description>Outfit Details: Altuzurra Dress, NST Studio &amp; Sherman Fields Necklaces, Amanu Sandals (similar here) As late summer unfolds, energize your wardrobe with the vibrant allure of… The post Citrus appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 05:00:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Maureen Johnson Mystery, British Serial Killer Procedural, 500+ Page Mysteries &amp; More!</title><link>https://bookriot.com/new-maureen-johnson-mystery-british-serial-killer-procedural-500-page-mysteries-more/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/partial-cover-of-2.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>What's the last 500+ page mystery/thriller you read?</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NASCAR's Bristol Speedway will host a Major League Baseball game</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/08/07/nascars-bristol-speedway-will-host-a-major-league-baseball-game/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1200x675/format/jpg/quality/100/http://s.aolcdn.com/commerce/blogcdn/www.autoblog.com/media/2010/06/lat-webb-ford1000-255.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Motorsports Continue reading NASCAR's Bristol Speedway will host a Major League Baseball game NASCAR's Bristol Speedway will host a Major League Baseball game originally appeared on Autoblog on Wed, 7 Aug 2024 11:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In a reversal, Disney's media assets are starting to generate more excitement than its parks</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/07/disneys-media-assets-parks.html</link><description>For the first time in more than two years, Disney's media assets are outshining the parks division.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:58:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>5 Ways to Speed Up Your Job Search</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/5-ways-to-speed-up-your-job-search/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=5-ways-to-speed-up-your-job-search</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Is it possible to speed up your job search when the hiring decisions lie in the hands of employers? Yes, there are definitely things you can do to increase your odds. Taking control over what you can control is what I call a proactive job search. Too often job seekers over-rely on posted jobs to […] The post 5 Ways to Speed Up Your Job Search appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 11:04:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Let Children Choose: Autonomy-Supportive Care for Cognitive Growth</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/autonomy-supportive-care-for-cognitive-growth/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=autonomy-supportive-care-for-cognitive-growth</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Executive function (EF) skills: EF skills are brain-based processes that allow us to remember goals, resist impulses, and think flexibly. Early EF skills matter: Developing EF skills early in life is crucial for various outcomes like social competence, emotion regulation, academic achievement, and keeping out of legal trouble. Parental and caregiver […] The post Let Children Choose: Autonomy-Supportive Care for Cognitive Growth appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 14:29:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Catalina French Dressing</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/catalina-french-dressing/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Delicious Catalina French Dressing will give your salad the perfect tangy, sweet flavor! It comes together quickly with a few…</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/how-to-remove-wallpaper/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Wallpaper has made a big comeback as a trendy home design choice. But despite its resurgence, there are still plenty of us dealing with dingy, dated, or downright ugly old wallpaper we don’t want. In our old home, we had to remove wallpaper in so many rooms: the kitchen, the dining room, the foyer, and two different bathrooms! As we traveled from room to room removing wallpaper, we tested 4 different methods, and today we’ll share what we learned. Removing wallpaper doesn’t require special tools or lots of money. It’s a totally doable project for any homeowner. However, it can be a tedious process that can take elbow grease and patience, depending on the size of your room and the stubbornness of your wallpaper. But having removed several rooms worth of decades-old wallpaper, we can confidently say it’s worth the effort! You can also check out more before and afters of our once-wallpapered rooms. Continue reading How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:21:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seaside Inspired Jewelry</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/08/seaside-inspired-jewelry/</link><description>Outfit Details: Chloe Dress (on sale, top version here, shorts here), JB x JB Shell Necklace, Delvaux Bag, Amanu Sandals, Chloe Dress on… The post Seaside Inspired Jewelry appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 05:00:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Victorian England-Set Gothic Fantasy Feels Like Part Jane Eyre, Part Fairytale</title><link>https://bookriot.com/midnight-rooms-by-donyae-coles/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/partial-cover-of-Midnight-Rooms-by-Donyae-Coles.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>🕸️A perfect gothic novel for the summerween lovers 🕸️</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2025 Audi Q7 &amp; 2024 Q8 First Drive Review: Audi's midsize SUVs get midlife updates</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/08/07/2025-audi-q7-sq7-q8-sq8-first-drive-review/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1200x675/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/08/06151315/2025-Audi-SQ7.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Audi , First Drives , Crossover , Luxury , Performance Continue reading 2025 Audi Q7 &amp; 2024 Q8 First Drive Review: Audi's midsize SUVs get midlife updates 2025 Audi Q7 &amp; 2024 Q8 First Drive Review: Audi's midsize SUVs get midlife updates originally appeared on Autoblog on Wed, 7 Aug 2024 11:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sunrun sees market opportunity after SunPower files for bankruptcy, company's shares surge</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/07/sunrun-stock-surges-as-it-sees-opportunity-after-sunpower-files-for-bankruptcy.html</link><description>Sunrun posted a surprise profit and sees opportunity to gain market share.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:07:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 556</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-556/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-556</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Artificial Intelligence is impacting every area of our lives, including job search. This will require each of us to become better critical thinkers to identify the noise from the genuine. Keeping up with the changes in the world of work takes effort, but that’s one reason you are here – each week you’ll discover interesting […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 556 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 11:55:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Children’s digital media exposure as a backdrop for multilingual learning</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/childrens-digital-media-exposure-as-a-backdrop-for-multilingual-learning/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=childrens-digital-media-exposure-as-a-backdrop-for-multilingual-learning</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Multilingual children use digital media regularly, in all their home languages. Digital media use may affect multilingual children’s early language learning by reducing opportunities for back-and-forth conversations with adults. This finding is similar to results of studies of digital media and language learning for children learning only one language. When using […] The post Children’s digital media exposure as a backdrop for multilingual learning appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 20:27:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>French Buttercream</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/french-buttercream/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>French buttercream is a luxurious frosting made with egg yolks as the base and simple syrup for sweetness. This gives…</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aglaonema Plant – Complete Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/aglaonema-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Aglaonema, also called the Chinese Evergreen Plant, is an easy-care houseplant that lives happily in many lighting conditions – even a dark corner of our daughter’s room. There are dozens of different Aglaonema varieties, most with large tropical foliage and colors ranging from silvery-green, red, and even vibrant pink. They’re also tough to kill, so they’re a great option for forgetful plant owners or anyone looking for an easy win in the plant department. These truly have been very low maintenance for us. We purchased our two Aglaonemas (pronounced ag-lee-oh-neem-ah ) to put atop our daughter’s closet. It’s sometimes hard to distinguish different varieties, but we believe that’s an Aglaonema Silver (right) and either a Candy Cane or Princess Silver Queen (left). Aglaonema Quick Facts Here’s what you need to know about your Aglaonema at a glance: Latin name : Aglaonema is the genus under which there are 21 recognized species . Continue reading Aglaonema Plant – Complete Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:47:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Back To School With Amazon</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/08/back-to-school-with-amazon/</link><description>We’re excited to unveil our latest roundup of back-to-school must-haves for kids, exclusively from Amazon. This selection is packed with… The post Back To School With Amazon appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 05:00:18 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>