<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 08:52:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Our Chat with Cards’ President Bill DeWitt III About New City Connect Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/25/our-chat-with-cards-president-bill-dewitt-iii-about-new-city-connect-uniforms/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The St. Louis Cardinals brand new Nike MLB City Connect uniforms will be making their on-field début this afternoon. The red jerseys with “The Lou” scripted across the chest, inspired by the hit song from Nelly, were unveiled on Monday to an overall positive reaction from fans and media alike.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 17:17:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bradley Cooper Plays with Pearl Jam, Hangs with Gigi Hadid at BottleRock</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/26/bradley-cooper-pearl-jam-play-sing-bottlerock-music-festival-gigi-hadid/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Bradley Cooper's proving the star wasn't just born, but alive and kicking ... 'cause he hopped onstage to perform a hit song from his 2018 movie -- alongside a rock legend. The actor put on his singing cap Friday night at BottleRock musical…</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 08:52:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ligue 1’s Lille OSC Put Unique Spin on Traditional Chevron for 2024-25 Home Kits</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/24/ligue-1s-lille-osc-put-unique-spin-on-traditional-chevron-for-2024-25-home-kits/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Club's traditional chevron, which they've used in some form since the 1940s, appears on new kits made up of several tonal mini-chevrons</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 22:01:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Qatar Airways Boeing 787 Hit By Intense Turbulence, 12 Injured</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/26/qatar-airways-boeing-787-dreamline-turbulence-12-injured-dublin/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>A Qatar Airways flight experienced a severe drop Sunday ... injuring a dozen people -- and, eyewitness accounts paint a terrifying scene. The flight -- going from Doha, Qatar to Dublin -- landed safely at the Irish airport Sunday, according to a…</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 08:52:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Memorial Cup Host Saginaw Spirit Unveil Commemorative Jersey for Tourney Opener</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/24/memorial-cup-host-saginaw-spirit-unveil-commemorative-jersey-for-tourney-opener/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Like the Memorial Cup itself, Spirit jersey for Friday's opening game against the Moose Jaw Warriors honors fallen military personnel</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 15:34:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sophia Bush Addresses Ashlyn Harris Engagement Rumors</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/26/sophia-bush-ashlyn-harris-engagement-rumors-instagram-cheeky-saucy/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Sophia Bush's recent handsy Instagram post with Ashlyn Harris got fans shouting about a secret proposal ... and, now she's addressed the rumors online. Here's the deal ... the actress took to her Instagram story to shut down claims she and Harris…</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 08:52:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Announcing Player 97: Our New Brand Vision, Research, Consulting Company</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/24/player-97-consulting-brand-vision-historical-research/misc/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Today, I’m excited to announce the official launch of Player 97, the new consulting, research, and branding company managed by the same friendly faces that have been running SportsLogos.Net. After many years of helping teams, leagues, designers, and other companies, I decided to finally make it official—folks, I am here</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 14:39:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Joe Jonas, Anya Taylor-Joy Among Star-Studded Monaco Grand Prix Attendees</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/26/monaco-grand-prix-joe-jonas-anya-taylor-joy-star-studded/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>The 2024 Monaco Grand Prix got some of Hollywood's biggest and brightest revving their engines ... with actors, models and more rushing to Europe to watch the action. Joe Jonas and Anya Taylor-Joy both put on their Sunday best for race day ...…</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 08:52:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Football in Their DNA: AC Milan Launches 2024-25 Home Kit</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/23/football-in-their-dna-ac-milan-launches-2024-25-home-kit/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Tonal segmented stripes inside red stripes are a visual representation of the human genome; patch on back collar celebrates club's 125th anniversary</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 16:11:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bruce Springsteen Cancels Shows After Doctor Prescribes Vocal Rest</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/26/bruce-springsteen-cancel-four-shows-doctor-prescribe-vocal-rest/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Bruce Springsteen may be The Boss, but he's calling out of work sick ... canceling several shows after doctors said he needed to rest his voice. The singer-songwriter announced the news via Instagram ... posting a statement with The E Street Band…</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 08:52:55 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>