<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 06:58:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>What Price Risk? Unpacking the Equity Risk Premium</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/24/what-price-risk-unpacking-the-equity-risk-premium/</link><description>Stocks are a good wager over the long term, on favorable odds. But stocks remain a bet, and investors must grasp how much returns can vary over long time horizons.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Americans just work harder' than Europeans, says CEO of Norway's $1.6 trillion oil fund, because they have a higher 'general level of ambition'</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/04/25/nicholai-tangen-norges-bank-investment-americans-work-harder/</link><description>"We are not very ambitious. I should be careful about talking about work-life balance, but the Americans just work harder.”</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:43:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Equity Income Investing Redux</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/22/equity-income-investing-redux/</link><description>No doubt the past year has been difficult for equity income investors. But history, inherent biases, mean reversion, and the current market backdrop point to a comeback.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 17:19:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>It’s not just investors watching the Fed</title><link>https://fortune.com/asia/2024/04/25/fed-central-bankers-southeast-asia-time-rate-cuts-ensure-currencies-no-collapse/</link><description>A stronger U.S. dollar can lead to more pressure on currencies in emerging economies which could then trap their respective central banks in a bind.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:34:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: Enrich Your Future</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/18/book-review-enrich-your-future/</link><description>This engaging book is simultaneously memorable and humorous. The numerous sports analogies will have you smiling as you absorb Larry Swedroe's unforgettable investment precepts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 18:07:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ask Andy: How can a startup founder balance work and family?</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/25/ask-andy-startup-advice-work-life-balance-direct-reports/</link><description>Bonobos founder Andy Dunn answers questions about juggling entrepreneurship and parenthood, and about how to organize a fast-growing startup team.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CAPE Is High: Should You Care?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/17/cape-is-high-should-you-care/</link><description>A simple analysis shows that Robert Shiller's cyclically adjusted price-to-earnings ratio changed in the 1990s and that mean-reversion concerns may be misplaced. If CAPE changed three decades ago, however, there is nothing preventing it from doing so again.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 15:18:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A new Cold War is brewing at sea–and the West’s security and prosperity are at stake</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/25/new-cold-war-brewing-sea-west-security-prosperity-trade-shipping-inflation/</link><description>Maritime shipping accounts for 90% of all world trade.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:20:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI to the Rescue? Overhauling the US Power Grid on the Path to Net Zero</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/15/ai-to-the-rescue-overhauling-the-us-power-grid-on-the-path-to-net-zero/</link><description>Once known as secure and profitable investments, utilities are now viewed as enterprises fraught with financial risks. Investors should favor utilities that employ AI and other digital strategies to minimize damage from natural disasters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 21:24:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AstraZeneca encounters a surge in shares as profits exceed expectations, buoyed by demand for cancer drugs</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/04/25/astrazeneca-surge-in-shares-profits-surpassing-expectations-buoyed-by-demand-for-cancer-drugs/</link><description>Astra's shares rose as much as 6.5% in early London trading, the most in over three years.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 10:36:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>