<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 06:58:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Why the New T+1 Settlement Cycle Matters: A Global Index Provider’s Perspective</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/14/why-the-new-t1-settlement-cycle-matters-a-global-index-providers-perspective/</link><description>Shorter settlement periods are meant to protect market participants. But the new T+1 settlement cycle for US equities may have undesirable knock-on effects for financial market participants around the world, including index fund managers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 16:54:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The myth that money supply controls inflation is being revived. Here’s how it failed its most ardent believer–Margaret Thatcher</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/16/monetarism-myth-money-supply-controls-inflation-margaret-thatcher-economy-politics/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-956600200-e1715855480927.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The myth of a golden monetarist age is being revived decades after the U.K. prime minister's experiment failed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 11:34:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Leveraging AI to Identify and Predict Financial Crises</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/13/leveraging-ai-to-identify-and-predict-financial-crises/</link><description>Despite some current limitations, AI stands to offer significant advantages versus traditional approaches to identifying and predicting financial crises.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 14:39:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amazon raised warehouse wages to $15 an hour 5 years ago. Today, half of workers surveyed told researchers they struggle to afford food or rent</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/16/amazon-warehouse-wages-15-hour-half-workers-surveyed-researchers-struggle-afford-food-rent/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1805778998.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Amazon has long been criticized for its treatment of employees, especially those who pack and ship boxes in its warehouses.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 11:20:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Your Portfolio Should Include Scarce Assets</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/10/why-your-portfolio-should-include-scarce-assets/</link><description>Portfolios that include both productive and scarce assets can deliver similar performance to the S&amp;P 500 with less risk than those that hold only productive assets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:34:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Unmarried millennials are twice as likely as boomers to buy homes solo—and 10 times as likely to buy with a friend</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/16/unmarried-millennials-boomers-buying-homes-solo-with-friend-non-romantic-partners/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1199830833-e1715791441651.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Young buyers are being forced to come up with "creative solutions" to an expensive housing market.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coiled Tight: Smaller Companies Are Primed for Outperformance</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/08/coiled-tight-smaller-companies-are-primed-for-outperformance/</link><description>Small-cap companies are poised for a rebound. The sector is best approached through an active investment strategy where expertise and a deep understanding of the individual businesses and their risk-and-reward characteristics are necessary for success.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:40:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rolex seller shares soar after strong U.S. sales—despite it being an 'underdeveloped market'</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/16/rolex-watches-of-switzerland-shares-soar-strong-us-sales/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2152501433-e1715851774281.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Watches of Switzerland Group reported a 14% increase in sales in its fiscal fourth quarter. That helped total sales rise 3% — to $482 million.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 10:47:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Investment Returns Are NOT Random</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/07/investment-returns-are-not-random/</link><description>Are investment returns random across time as Burton Malkiel suggests in his book, A Random Walk Down Wall Street? There is notable disagreement on this topic. This research finds that practitioners may need to rethink their portfolio optimization routines.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:22:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Florida Gov. DeSantis signs bill banning power-generating wind turbines offshore or near the state’s coastline</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/16/florida-gov-desantis-bill-ban-power-generating-wind-turbines-offshore-coastline/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/AP24136740095013-e1715852111757.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>It takes effect July 1 and would also boost expansion of natural gas, reduce regulation on gas pipelines in the state and increase protections against bans on gas appliances such as stoves.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 10:37:20 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>