<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 15:16:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Seeing Greene: Flood Zones, New Builds, &amp; Does Mexico’s Cash Flow Beat the US?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-957</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Have you ever thought about buying rental properties abroad? It might surprise you, but investing overseas could bring in much more cash flow and appreciation than you thought possible. Bobby, […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 07:02:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The ‘vote Trump’ spam that hit Bluesky in May came from decentralized rival Nostr</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/21/the-vote-trump-spam-that-hit-bluesky-in-may-came-from-decentralized-rival-nostr/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The spam reached Bluesky by first crossing over two other decentralized networks: Mastodon and Nostr. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 18:44:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Police Tactics at Some Pro-Palestine Protests Ignore Past Lessons</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/18/police-israel-palestine-campus-protests</link><description>While some universities have sought peaceful approaches, others have used aggressive policing that bucks research from the protests following George Floyd’s murder.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Federal Experts Talk Bird Flu ‘What Ifs’ in WebMD Live Event</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/cold-and-flu/news/20240516/federal-experts-talk-bird-flu-what-ifs?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>WebMD brought together experts from four federal agencies to talk prevention, monitoring, and what the “what ifs” of bird flu might look like.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:50:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Reaching $1M Net Worth and FI in 6 Years with a “Home Run” Rental Property</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-530</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>You DON’T have to spend your entire life chasing financial independence. Play your cards right, and you may not even need a whole decade! With a little hard work and […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 07:01:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>There’s a real appetite for a fintech alternative to QuickBooks</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/21/theres-a-real-appetite-for-a-fintech-alternative-to-quickbooks/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Welcome to TechCrunch Fintech! This week, we’re looking at the continued fallout from Synapse’s bankruptcy, how Layer wants to disrupt SMB accounting, and much more! To get a roundup of TechCrunch’s biggest and most important fintech stories delivered to your inbox every Tuesday at 7:00 a.m. PT, subscribe here. The big story The prospects for […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 18:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Susan Chira to Step Down as The Marshall Project’s Editor-in-Chief in January</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/16/susan-chira-eic-step-down</link><description>Under her stewardship, the news nonprofit more than doubled in size, opened local newsrooms and won its second Pulitzer Prize.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What’s Next in Health Care for Older Adults: Questions and Answers With John Whyte, MD</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/blog-aging-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>As WebMD’s chief medical officer, John Whyte, MD, is in a unique position to see both the current state of medical care for America’s older adults and the way things are trending for the future. We asked him to share his insight on a few topics, along with a bit of advice.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:29:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Half of New Condo Development in Southern Florida is Geared Toward Vacation Rentals—Should You Join the Gold Rush?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/vacation-rental-development-now-make-up-half-of-southern-florida-market</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>According to a new report from ISG World, first cited in The Real Deal, over 50% of South Florida’s new condo developments are tailored toward short-term rentals. It’s a marked distinction from other cities that […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 20:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bill Gates-backed wind startup AirLoom is raising $12M, filings reveal</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/21/bill-gates-backed-wind-startup-airloom-is-raising-12m-filings-reveal/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The company is hoping to produce electricity at $13 per megawatt hour, which would be more than 50% cheaper than traditional onshore wind. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When Bad Cops Become Private Security Guards</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/11/police-private-guard-florida-chicago</link><description>There’s growing evidence that former officers with troubling histories of abuse can easily find second careers in private security.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Get the Care You Need in a COVID-19 World</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/covid-senior-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>What to expect at the doctor’s office, hospitals, and long-term care facilities, the future of telemedicine, and how to get the best care during COVID-19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 19:50:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Much Could a New Real Estate Tax Hurt Investors In Massachusetts—And Will It Even Work?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/massachusetts-weigh-new-real-estate-transfer-tax</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Massachusetts is the latest state considering a transfer tax in a bid to increase funding for affordable housing, but the controversial fee doesn’t bode well for the Bay State’s already pricey real estate sector. […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 19:34:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WitnessAI is building guardrails for generative AI models</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/21/witnessai-is-building-guardrails-for-generative-ai-models/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Generative AI makes stuff up. It can be biased. Sometimes it spits out toxic text. So can it be “safe”? Rick Caccia, the CEO of WitnessAI, believes it can. “Securing AI models is a real problem, and it’s one that’s especially shiny for AI researchers, but it’s different from securing use,” Caccia, formerly SVP of […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 17:19:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Rare Bright Spot for a Canine Lover Doing Time: Raising Puppies to Become Service Dogs</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/10/service-dogs-training-prison-essay</link><description>Adam Roberts reflects on the highs and occasional lows of training Labrador retrievers for the Puppies Behind Bars program.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Personal Shopper: A Savvy Black Entrepreneur Guides You to Eczema-Friendly Clothes, Creams, Cosmetics, and More</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/savvy-black-entrepreneur-guides-eczema-friendly-clothes-creams-cosmetics?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>A savvy black entrepreneur guides you on an eczema-friendly shopping spree.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:54:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I’m in the Final Stretch of Selling My Brooklyn Condo as a 1031 Exchange—Here’s How the Fifth Month Went</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/1031-investor-journal-five</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>In the next few days, our Brooklyn, New York condo will hit the market, and we will begin the first half of our long-planned, much-anticipated, greatly agonized-over 1031 exchange. When all […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 19:24:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>French AI startup H raises $220M seed round</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/21/french-ai-startup-h-raises-220-million-seed-round/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>It’s not often that you hear about a seed round above $10 million. H, a startup based in Paris and previously known as Holistic AI, has announced a $220 million seed round just a few months after the company’s inception. It has managed to raise so much money so quickly because it’s an AI startup […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 17:06:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Marshall Project Wins the Dart Award for “The Mercy Workers”</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/06/the-marshall-project-wins-the-dart-award-for-the-mercy-workers</link><description>Our feature on mitigation specialists who help save people from the death penalty was recognized for making “significant contributions to public understanding of trauma-related issues.”</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Behind the Spike in Colorectal Cancer Among Young Americans</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/colorectal-cancer/news/20240515/behind-the-spike-in-colorectal-cancer-cases?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Colorectal cancer cases increased a whopping 333% among 15- to 19-year-olds and 185% among 20- to 24-year-olds from 1999 to 2020.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:59:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>