<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 06:54:40 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The 8 Biggest Reasons I’m Excited About BPCON</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/reasons-to-attend-bpcon</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>This must-attend event features top real estate insights, unmatched networking, and a luxury all-inclusive experience.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 20:54:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gogoro delays India plans due to policy uncertainty, launches bike-taxi pilot with Rapido</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/16/gogoro-delays-india-plans-due-to-policy-uncertainty-launches-bike-taxi-pilot-with-rapido/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Gogoro has deferred its India plans over delay in government incentives, but the Taiwanese company has partnered with Rapido for a bike-taxi pilot. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FAQ: How The Marshall Project Is Covering the 2024 Election</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/16/election-faq-crime-politics</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Learn more about who we are and how we choose what political stories to cover.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Investors: Make Sure to Capitalize On “Resolutions of Unacceptable Conditions”</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/dealing-with-resolutions-of-unacceptable-conditions</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Inspections are important because you need to know what you're getting into, but they're equally important for the negotiations that can occur after.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 19:52:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A16z offers social media tips after its founder’s ‘attack’ tweet goes viral</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/16/a16z-offers-social-media-tips-after-its-founders-attack-tweet-goes-viral/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>On Friday, the venture firm Andreessen Horowitz tweeted out a link to its guide on how to “build your social media presence” which features advice for founders. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 23:59:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Mother on a Mission for Full Police Transparency</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/16/police-beating-ulysses-wilkerson-mother-video</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Troy, Alabama, police severely beat Ulysses Wilkerson when he was 17. Seven years later, his mom, Angela Williams, is still fighting for answers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rookie Reply: Preparing for a Market Crash, Ending Leases, &amp; Building Teams</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-445</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>As a new investor, a strong real estate team is crucial to your success—especially when you’re looking to land your first deal, complete your first rehab project, or invest out-of-state. […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 10:00:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OpenAI shuts down election influence operation that used ChatGPT</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/16/openai-shuts-down-election-influence-operation-using-chatgpt/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>OpenAI has banned a cluster of ChatGPT accounts linked to an Iranian influence operation that was generating content about the U.S. presidential election, according to a blog post on Friday. The company says the operation created AI-generated articles and social media posts, though it doesn’t seem that it reached much of an audience. This is […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 21:09:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How the 1968 DNC in Chicago Devolved into ‘Unrestrained and Indiscriminate Police Violence’</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/14/chicago-dnc-protests-police-reforms</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>As protesters prepare for the Democratic National Convention in Chicago next week, a half-century old report provides lessons for preventing chaos.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 11:00:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BiggerNews: What Happens if the Housing Market Crashes (&amp; What Will Cause It)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-1005</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Recession fears are increasing. The stock market has taken substantial hits, housing inventory is climbing, and bank account balances are starting to fall. So, with more economic turmoil, we have […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 10:00:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple reportedly has ‘several hundred’ working on a robot arm with attached iPad</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/16/apple-reportedly-has-several-hundred-working-on-a-robot-arm-with-attached-ipad/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Apple is reportedly shifting into the world of home robots after the wheels came off its electric car. According to a new report from Bloomberg, a team of several hundred is working on its potential first product: a robotic arm with an “iPad-like” display attached. The home product would take a page out of Amazon’s […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 20:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aaron Sankin is The Marshall Project’s new Deputy Data Editor</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/13/aaron-sankin-is-the-marshall-projects-new-deputy-data-editor</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Sankin brings deep experience with ambitious data projects.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 20:00:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Retiring Early Before 30 and Why You DON’T Need Millions for FIRE</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-555</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>This might be the fastest path to FIRE we’ve ever seen. In just two years, Emily and James were able to retire early and travel the world full-time. They didn’t […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 07:01:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Another week in the circle of startup life</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/16/another-week-in-the-circle-of-startup-life/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Welcome to Startups Weekly — your weekly recap of everything you can’t miss from the world of startups. I’m Anna Heim from TechCrunch’s international team, and I’ll be writing this newsletter moving forward. Want it in your inbox every Friday? Sign up here. This week, we’re looking at some companies being created, funded, shut down and […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘Deliberate Indifference’: Court Rulings Challenge Extreme Heat Conditions in Prisons</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/10/texas-heat-louisiana-prison</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>“If it’s 103 outside, it may be 107 to -8 inside of your cell,” said a man who worked in the fields while imprisoned in Texas.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>