<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 17:17:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>New England Patriots Subtly Reveal New Secondary Logo</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/09/new-england-patriots-subtly-reveal-new-secondary-logo/football/</link><description>Following a recent visit to Gillette Stadium, former New England Patriots linebacker Brandon Spikes posted a photo of what appears to be the franchise’s new secondary logo prominently displayed inside the facility.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 20:58:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kelly Osbourne Confuses Fans With Kim Zolciak Look in IG Photo</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/09/kelly-osbourne-confuses-fans-mistaken-kim-zolciak-emsculpt/</link><description>Kelly Osbourne had many of her fans scratching their heads Thursday, believing she was Kim Zolciak because it was virtually impossible to tell the two apart. Here’s what happened … celebrity hairdresser Laura Rugetti posted a photo of Kelly on…</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 17:17:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PWHL Announces Bauer as Jersey Partner for 2024-25</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/09/pwhl-announces-bauer-as-jersey-partner-for-2024-25/hockey-2/</link><description>The Professional Women’s Hockey League announced today that Bauer Hockey will serve as the PWHL’s exclusive jersey partner, supplying game and replica jerseys for all six teams in the league, beginning with the 2024-25 season. “Bauer is a leader in supporting the performance needs of the league and many of</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 17:40:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Boeing 737 Plane Catches on Fire in Senegal After Failed Takeoff Attempt</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/09/boeing-737-plane-catch-fire-senegal-failed-takeoff-attempt/</link><description>Yet another Boeing plane is in the news again after multiple mishaps in recent months -- and this time ... it ended with the aircraft partially on fire ... and people running for their lives. Check out this wild footage that shows a 737 tilted off…</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 17:17:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Utah NHL Team Releases 20 Possible Names, Fan Vote Begins</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/08/utah-nhl-team-releases-20-possible-names-fan-vote-begins/hockey-2/</link><description>Utah’s new NHL franchise has released its list of twenty team names it is considering for its inaugural 2024-25 season. Fans can vote for up to four of the twenty finalists on their ballot but can only cast one ballot. Voting starts tonight and will conclude after two weeks on</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 02:38:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prince Harry Showered with Love from Public During Dueling Event with Charles</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/09/prince-harry-showered-love-public-england-dueling-event-king-charles/</link><description>Prince Harry was without his Royal family during his Invictus Games event in London this week -- but he wasn't a man without a country ... 'cause the British public showed up. The Duke of Sussex attended his big shindig at St. Paul's Cathedral…</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 17:17:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Burnley FC Leave Umbro, Sign Kit Deal With Castore</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/08/burnley-fc-leave-umbro-sign-kit-deal-with-castore/soccer/</link><description>Burnley currently in Premier League relegation zone; if they stay up, they'll be one of two clubs in England's top flight outfitted by Castore</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 17:46:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Teresa Giudice Asked Taylor Swift If She Knew Who She Was at Coachella</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/09/teresa-giudice-question-taylor-swift-coachella-real-housewives/</link><description>Teresa Giudice is dishing on how she scored a rare selfie with Taylor Swift at Coachella ... without even being a Swiftie. Remember, the 'Real Housewives of New Jersey' star was in the same VIP section as the singer at weekend 1 of the music…</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 17:17:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Report: Brazil Could Ditch Nike as Kit Supplier After Receiving Massive Offer</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/07/report-brazil-could-ditch-nike-as-kit-supplier-after-receiving-massive-offer/soccer/</link><description>Brazilian news outlet reports CBF has received an offer worth more than five times what Nike currently pays them from either Adidas or Puma</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:29:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Katherine Schwarzenegger Shades Met Gala, No Longer 'Chic &amp; Classy'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/09/katherine-schwarzenegger-shades-met-gala-looks-throwback-maria-shiver-chic-classy/</link><description>Katherine Schwarzenegger isn't going along with the crowd when it comes to the Met Gala being fashion's biggest night -- instead, she thinks it might be its trashiest event. Kat re-shared a throwback pic on IG story ... showing her mother, Maria…</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 17:17:13 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>