<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 13:53:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>National Rent Control, Falling Mortgage Rates, and Fleeing Homebuyers</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-237</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>A new nationwide rent control proposal could cap rent increases for any landlord with a certain amount of properties. But will it actually pass? How would landlords survive when rents […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 07:02:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Uber, Lyft, DoorDash can continue to classify drivers as contractors in California</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/25/uber-lyft-doordash-can-continue-to-classify-drivers-as-contractors-in-california/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The California Supreme Court ruled Thursday that Proposition 22 – the ballot measure that passed in November 2020 and classified app-based gig workers as independent contractors rather than employees – is here to stay. The decision is a win for app-based companies like Uber, Lyft, DoorDash and Instacart, which have fought hard to maintain their […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 18:35:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Photos: Three Years of a Family’s Grief and Healing After a Fatal Police Shooting</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/25/family-photos-cleveland-police-shooting-belmonte</link><description>Photographer Michael Indriolo documents an East Cleveland family’s search for peace after the 2021 police shooting of their 19-year-old brother.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 11:00:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>12 Cities You’ll Regret You Didn’t Invest In 10 Years From Now</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/the-next-wave-of-markets-set-to-boom-in-the-coming-years</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Now that the pandemic boom is over, it's time to scope out the next set of markets gearing up for a boom.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 23:08:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alphabet pours $5B into Waymo, Cruise scraps the Origin and Elon’s bet on autonomy</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/25/alphabet-pours-5b-into-waymo-cruise-scraps-the-origin-and-elons-bet-on-autonomy/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Welcome back to TechCrunch Mobility — your central hub for news and insights on the future of transportation. Sign up here for free — just click TechCrunch Mobility! I don’t know about you, but for me, the past few days have offered up even more evidence that our world is vulnerable to software bugs. Yep, […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 18:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sending Unarmed Responders Instead of Police: What We’ve Learned</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/25/police-mental-health-alternative-911</link><description>There are more than 100 response teams nationwide, but experts say more research on their impact is needed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 11:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Investors Made a Record Share of Home Purchases in Q1</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/investor-share-of-purchases-hits-record-high-q1-2024</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Investor buyers accounted for 14.8% of home sales in the first quarter of 2024—the highest share on record.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 21:01:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Archera helps customers access deep cloud discounts</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/25/archera-helps-customers-access-deep-cloud-discounts/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>In addition to insured commitments, Archera provides consulting services to help build purchasing strategies for customers to optimize their cloud usage. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 17:49:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Marshall Project Launches Investigate This!</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/25/the-marshall-project-launches-investigate-this</link><description>Our toolkits will offer data, storytelling and engagement resources to empower more criminal justice reporting in local communities</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Foreign Investment Curbed by Proposed Housing Rule, But It Comes With Potential Consequences for American Investors</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/foreign-investment-rule-would-block-foreign-purchases-near-military-installations</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>The Treasury Department's proposed rule would make it harder for foreign investors to purchase land near military installations, adding to a 2018 law. The cascading effects could also impact Americans.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 20:36:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Google makes its Gemini chatbot faster and more widely available</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/25/google-speeds-up-its-gemini-chatbot-and-brings-it-to-more-places/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>In its bid to maintain pace with generative AI rivals like Anthropic and OpenAI, Google is rolling out updates to the no-fee tier of Gemini, its AI-powered chatbot. The updates are focused on making the platform more performant — and more widely available. Starting Thursday, Gemini 1.5 Flash — a lightweight multimodal model Google announced […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Investigate the Trend of Declining Prison Staff and Deteriorating Conditions Behind Bars</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/25/how-to-investigate-the-trend-of-declining-prison-staff-and-deteriorating-conditions-behind-bars</link><description>Our toolkit helps you report on how this employment crisis impacts safety and local budgets in your state.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Long-term Rental Properties Aren’t as Great as They’re Hyped Up to Be</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/why-long-term-rental-properties-arent-as-great-as-theyre-hyped-up-to-be</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Long-term rentals may disappoint if you don't consider three key factors: long-term rent growth, appreciation, and the tenant segment the property attracts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 16:42:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TechCrunch Minute: Meta’s new ‘Imagine me’ feature lets you generate AI selfies</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/video/techcrunch-minute-metas-new-imagine-me-feature-lets-you-generate-ai-selfies/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Meta’s AI integrations into apps like Instagram and Facebook have felt pretty useless so far. If I’m just trying to find my friend’s Instagram, why do I have to navigate around a Meta AI interface that is desperately trying to tell me the top five vegetarian protein sources? But with the release of Meta’s new […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Investigate COVID’s Deadly Toll in Your State Prisons</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/25/how-to-investigate-covid-s-deadly-toll-in-your-state-prisons</link><description>Our toolkit helps you report on deadly systemic failures and analyze the pandemic as a case study of how facilities can prepare for the next crisis.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>