<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 06:36:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Nashville Sounds pay tribute to parent club, beer with new Brewskis cap</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/21/nashville-sounds-pay-tribute-to-parent-club-beer-with-new-brewskis-cap/baseball/</link><description>The Triple-A Nashville Sounds have been an affiliate of the Milwaukee Brewers since 2021, and before that from 2005 to 2014. The team is continuing a popular tribute to its parent club this season, playing as the Nashville Brewskis. The Sounds introduced the powder blue alternates designed by Brandon Lamarche</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 16:28:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kim Kardashian to Executive Produce 'Calabasas' TV Show for Netflix</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/21/kim-kardashian-netflix-show-calabasas-emma-roberts/</link><description>Kim Kardashian is bringing Kardashian Kountry to the masses ... as Netflix placed the winning bid on the new scripted show she's set to exec produce titled, "Calabasas." Deadline reports KK and 'AHS' costar Emma Roberts are executive producing the…</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 06:36:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rumble Ponies to honor Rod Serling with Binghamton Creatures alternate</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/21/rumble-ponies-to-honor-rod-serling-with-binghamton-creatures-alternate/baseball/</link><description>The Double-A Binghamton Rumble Ponies will honor one of their hometown’s favorite sons, Twilight Zone creator Rod Serling, with an alternate identity based on the show. For one game this summer, the team will play as the Creatures, with a logo that derives from a Twilight Zone episode called “Nightmare</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 15:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Arnold Schwarzenegger Punked Sylvester Stallone into Starring in Movie Flop</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/21/arnold-schwarzenegger-sylvester-stallone-sly-movie-flop-stop-or-my-mom-will-shoot/</link><description>Arnold Schwarzenegger epically punked Sylvester Stallone into signing on for the most disastrous film of Sly's career, and that's exactly what Arnold wanted to happen! Arnold and Sly sat down with Harvey for a candid, sometimes stunning convo about…</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 06:36:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Denver Broncos’ New Helmet Design Leaks On NFL Draft Prop</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/20/denver-broncos-new-helmet-design-leaks-on-nfl-draft-prop/football/</link><description>The design of the Denver Broncos' new helmets were leaked by former NFL wide receiver Antonio Brown, who shared a photo on social media of an oversized helmet that will be on display at next week's draft.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 17:20:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Taylor Swift's Personal Trainer Reveals Pop Star's Brutal Workout</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/21/taylor-swift-workout-routine-trainer-eras-tour/</link><description>Taylor Swift's workout routine is so brutal that it would make some people throw up while forcing others to lay down on the floor ... so says the pop superstar's trainer Kirk Myers. Myers revealed to Vogue the singer's killer exercise regimen as he…</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 06:36:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nike Releases New Rebel Edition Jerseys for 6 WNBA Teams</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/19/nike-releases-new-rebel-edition-jerseys-for-6-wnba-teams/basketball/</link><description>Teams receiving new Rebel Edition alternate jerseys include Chicago Sky, Connecticut Sun, Las Vegas Aces, Los Angeles Sparks, Phoenix Mercury, Seattle Storm</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:38:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mohamed Hadid Apologizes For Racist, Homophobic Messages Sent to Rep. Ritchie Torres</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/21/mohamed-hadid-bella-gigi-apologize-racist-homophobic-message-sent-representative-ritchie-torres/</link><description>Mohamed Hadid's apologizing for racist and homophobic direct messages he sent to Congressman Ritchie Torres ... while still criticizing Torres for supporting Israel. The real estate developer -- and father to Gigi and Bella Hadid -- posted to…</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 06:36:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New York Mets Unveil City Connect Uniforms Inspired by Subways, Bridges, and Concrete</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/19/new-york-mets-unveil-city-connect-uniforms-inspired-by-subways-bridges-and-concrete/baseball/</link><description>“If you know New York, you know.” That’s the idea behind the New York Mets‘ brand new Nike MLB City Connect uniform, which the club unveiled this morning. The Mets are the second of nine teams scheduled to do so during the 2024 season. They’ll debut April 27 and then</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 15:00:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fire Breaks Out Behind Goal During Dutch Final Soccer Game</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/21/dutch-cup-fire-break-out-soccer-feyenoord-fans-smoke-viral/</link><description>A soccer final in the Netherlands was a real barn burner ... quite literally 'cause a fire broke out behind one of the goals throwing the match into chaos. Feyenoord played NEC Nijmegen in the Dutch Cup Final Sunday -- the championship match of a…</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 06:36:42 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>