<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 07:30:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Warren Moon Has Issue With Houston Texans’ New Oilers-Inspired Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/04/warren-moon-has-issue-with-houston-texans-new-oilers-inspired-uniforms/football/</link><description>While fans in Houston are happy with the Texans adding "H-Town" blue to their new uniforms, former Oilers quarterback Warren Moon doesn’t feel the same way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 17:23:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rihanna, ASAP Rocky Hit Arcade Event for Miami F1</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/05/rihanna-asap-rocky-puma-formula-one-event-perform-e11even-miami-flavor-flav/</link><description>Call Rihanna the queen of speed, at least for this weekend, because she and A$AP Rocky are holding court down in Miami as the city is packed with celebs in town for the F1 Grand Prix. The celeb couple hosted an event Saturday night for Puma ... the…</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 07:30:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>West Virginia Mountaineers Reveal Coal Mining-Inspired Alternate Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/03/west-virginia-mountaineers-reveal-coal-mining-inspired-alternate-uniforms/college/</link><description>On Thursday, just days after it unveiled an entirely new uniform set, West Virginia revealed a black alternate design that pays homage to the state's coal mining history.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 02:25:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Snoop Dogg, T-Pain Keep Vegas Party Going for Pissed 'Lovers &amp; Friends' Fans</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/05/snoop-dog-lovers-friends-vegas-canceled-pool-party-fans/</link><description>Snoop Dogg and T-Pain are doing their part to keep the peace on the Vegas Strip by giving throngs of pissed-off fans something to cheer about after the "Lovers &amp; Friends" festival was canceled last minute. The duo put on an impromptu show…</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 07:30:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MLB, Nike Announces Return of Larger Player Names, Fix to Grey Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/03/mlb-nike-announces-return-of-larger-player-names-fix-to-grey-uniforms/baseball/</link><description>Major League Baseball and Nike today announced they will fix some of the problems with the new uniforms introduced for the 2024 season. The decision follows feedback from players and clubs and months of fan and media complaints, which pointed to several areas needing improvement. Starting in the 2025 season,</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 20:58:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘Lord of the Rings,’ ‘Titanic’ Actor Bernard Hill Reportedly Dead at 79</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/05/bernard-hill-lord-of-the-rings-titanic-actor-dead-dies/</link><description>Bernard Hill -- a character actor known for his roles in some of the biggest late-‘90s and early-2000s flicks -- has died ... according to reports. Multiple outlets are reporting Hill passed away early Sunday morning, saying they the news…</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 07:30:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nats, Orioles to Play in MLB’s First-Ever All-City Connect Uniform Game</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/03/nats-orioles-to-play-in-mlbs-first-ever-all-city-connect-uniform-game/baseball/</link><description>For the first time in Major League Baseball history, two teams will wear their Nike MLB City Connect uniforms in the same game. This morning, the Washington Nationals announced they will don their cherry blossom-themed City Connect uniforms when they host the Baltimore Orioles on Tuesday, May 7 for the</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 15:40:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chance Perdomo's 'Gen V' Role Won't Be Recast After Death, Producers Say</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/05/chance-perdomo-gen-v-role-wont-recast-death-producers-motocycle-accident-dead-dies/</link><description>Chance Perdomo will forever be the only Andre Anderson for "Gen V" ... producers announced Sunday they won't cast another actor in the role after his untimely death. The team behind the popular "The Boys" spin-off announced the news on the show's…</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 07:30:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cincinnati Bengals Reveal Updated Turf Design</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/02/cincinnati-bengals-reveal-updated-turf-design/football/</link><description>The Cincinnati Bengals are in the process of installing new FieldTurf at Paycor Stadium and will have an updated design as a result.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 22:33:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Backstreet Boys Post Video of Howie Dorough Taking Shots For Cinco De Mayo</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/05/backstreet-boys-post-video-howie-dorough-pounding-shots-cinco-de-mayo/</link><description>The Backstreet Boys are giving people ideas on how to spend Cinco de Mayo ... showing fans how the guys celebrate -- with a vid of Howie Dorough slamming shots. The band's official account posted the video Sunday morning ... and, it follows HD's…</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 07:30:49 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>