<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 23:49:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>2024 MLB Armed Forces Day Caps Revealed</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/26/2024-mlb-armed-forces-day-caps-revealed/baseball/</link><description>Major League Baseball and New Era have released their Armed Forces Day ballcaps collection, to be worn across the league over the May 17-18-19 weekend. This year’s caps, crowns, buttons, and visors are black for every team. Each team’s typical cap logo is on the front but re-coloured army green</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 00:28:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>King Charles to Return to Public Duties Amid Funeral-Planning Reports</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/26/king-charles-return-public-duties-amid-funeral-planning-reports-cancer-battle-poorly/</link><description>King Charles seems to be trying to put rumors of his ill health to bed -- the Royal Family just announced he'll return to the spotlight, this after reports his cancer battle isn't going well. The Royal Family's X account posted a pic of the king…</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 23:49:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MLB Announces Return of Players’ Weekend in 2024, Custom Player Caps</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/26/mlb-announces-return-of-players-weekend-in-2024/baseball/</link><description>Major League Baseball is bringing back its Players’ Weekend this season, which will be held August 16-18, 2024, focusing on the players’ personalized gear. It’s the first time MLB will host its Players’ Weekend since 2019. As part of this year’s celebration, players will wear each player’s uniform number on</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 16:16:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bob Barker's Historic L.A. Estate Sells for Well Over Asking Price</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/26/bob-barker-historic-los-angeles-estate-sold-new-owner-millions/</link><description>Bob Barker's historic estate was listed for $2.9 million -- but whoever snapped it up ended up spending even more to buy it ... going well over asking. Real estate sources tell TMZ ... interior designer Julia Dempster sealed the deal Thursday by…</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 23:49:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Moroccan Soccer Team Awarded Default Win After Kits Confiscated by Algerian Customs</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/25/moroccan-soccer-team-awarded-default-win-after-kits-confiscated-by-algerian-customs/soccer/</link><description>Kits feature map of Morocco on the chest that includes disputed Western Sahara territory</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 18:55:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Karrueche Tran Reacts to Chris Brown, Quavo Feud Over Her</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/26/karrueche-tran-reaction-chris-brown-quavo-feud-exes-dating/</link><description>Chris Brown and Quavo are currently tangled in a gnarly rap beef -- and it's all about Karrueche Tran ... who just addressed how she feels about it all on camera. The actress spoke to a pap at LAX Thursday -- who asked her how she felt about the…</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 23:49:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Glacier Range Riders, National Park Service Embroiled in Battle Over Arrowhead Logo</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/25/glacier-range-riders-national-park-service-embroiled-in-battle-over-arrowhead-logo/baseball/</link><description>NPS has filed protests with the U.S. Patent and Trademark Office over logo possible causing confusion that team is affiliated with service</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:56:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bam Margera Addresses UK Tour Cancelation Drama, Adamant He's Sober</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/26/bam-margera-addresses-uk-tour-cancelation-drama-adamant-sober/</link><description>Bam Margera's clearing the air about why his UK tour got the axe -- and while some have suspected it's all about him falling off the wagon ... he's saying he's clean and sober. Here's the deal ... Bam's been across the pond lately for a string of…</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 23:49:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New York Jets: Their Logos, Their Name, Their Colours</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/25/new-york-jets-their-logos-their-name-their-colours/football/</link><description>From their early-sixties inception as the Titans of New York to their modern, throwback-inspired green and white logo, the New York Jets have had several distinctive looks over their 60-plus year history. This team has found itself navigating through different eras, frequently alternating between two primary logos and uniform styles</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:34:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aerial View Shows Gnarly Crash on Set of Eddie Murphy Film 'The Pickup'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/26/eddie-murphy-movie-the-pickup-accident-drone-aerial-crash-video/</link><description>Dramatic drone footage of a stunt-gone-wrong on the set of Eddie Murphy's new movie -- which left 8 crew members hospitalized -- shows an ugly crash ... and it's all on video. In this new angle -- obtained by TMZ -- you can see an armored truck…</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 23:49:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>