<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 07:19:24 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Implementation Shortfalls Hamstring Factor Strategies</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/01/implementation-shortfalls-hamstring-factor-strategies/</link><description>Smart rebalancing rules help portfolio managers capture more of the return that is inherent in their factor strategies. Concentrating on “priority best” trading improves factor portfolio performance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 11:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Richard Branson says it’s ‘very sad’ when people measure wealth as success and finds being called a billionaire ‘insulting’</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/02/richard-branson-called-billionaire-insulting-virgin-group-founder/</link><description>"Maybe in America, ‘billionaire’ is a sign of success, but that rankles me,” Richard Branson, who has an estimated net worth of $2.6 billion, said.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:58:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IFRS Accounting Standard Will Support Better Investment Decisions</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/30/ifrs-accounting-standard-will-support-better-investment-decisions/</link><description>IFRS 18 responds to investors' concerns about challenges in comparing companies' financial performance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 11:34:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Puig is poised for a $15 billion IPO, but CEO Marc Puig has a ‘self-disempowerment’ plan to stop his family from controlling the Spanish beauty empire</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/02/beauty-retail-ipo-ceo-marc-puig-family-business-next-generation-succession-self-disempowerment/</link><description>CEO Marc Puig thinks setting "difficult filters" even for family members is the best way to practice "meritocracy."</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:50:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meir Statman: Your State of Mind Influences Your Investing Success</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/29/meir-statman-your-state-of-mind-influences-your-investing-success/</link><description>Meir Statman shares his insights on the broader aspects of financial well-being and its interconnection with life satisfaction.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 12:58:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI boom still running hot as SK Hynix says its already sold majority of its 2025 allotment of high-bandwidth memory chips</title><link>https://fortune.com/asia/2024/05/02/sk-hynix-ceo-sold-out-chips-2025-ai-boom/</link><description>Comments from CEO of SK Hynix, the world's second largest memory chipmaker, suggest the shortage of AI-related chips isn't ending anytime soon.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:35:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: Trailblazers, Heroes, and Crooks</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/26/book-review-trailblazers-heroes-and-crooks/</link><description>Stephen Foerster, CFA, extracts lessons from exceptional episodes in financial history that ordinary investors and seasoned professionals alike can put to profitable use. The bonus is that you'll be entertained from start to finish.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>To compete with Asia's rising dominance, French billionaire Bollore wants to build an EV battery plant in France</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/02/compete-with-asias-rising-dominance-french-billionaire-bollore-wants-to-build-ev-battery-plant-in-france-cost-2-1-billion/</link><description>Vincent Bollore, CEO of investment group Bollore, is “actively working” on developing the plant with a goal of opening it by 2030.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:20:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Price Risk? Unpacking the Equity Risk Premium</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/24/what-price-risk-unpacking-the-equity-risk-premium/</link><description>Stocks are a good wager over the long term, on favorable odds. But stocks remain a bet, and investors must grasp how much returns can vary over long time horizons.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘Time is running out’ to build more electric truck chargers in Europe</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/02/daimler-truck-ceo-time-running-out-electric-truck-chargers-europe/</link><description>Daimler Truck, Volkswagen’s Traton, and Volvo are planning to spend $534 million to install at least 1,700 chargers in Europe.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:11:07 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>