<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 06:54:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Seeing Greene: Should I Start Flipping Houses in My Market? (How to Know)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-993</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Should I pay off my rentals or scale to more doors? Should I start flipping houses in my local but expensive market or go long-distance? When is the time to […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 07:02:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GM’s Cruise abandons Origin robotaxi, takes $583 million charge</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/23/gms-cruise-abandons-origin-robotaxi-takes-583-million-charge/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>GM’s self-driving car subsidiary Cruise is scrapping plans to build the Origin — a purpose-built robotaxi with no steering wheel or pedals — and will instead use the next-generation Chevrolet Bolt in its operations. GM Chair and CEO Mary Barra told shareholders Tuesday the decision will “simplify their path to scale” and addresses the regulatory […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Five Things to Know About Kamala Harris’ Criminal Justice Record</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/21/kamala-harris-criminal-justice-record</link><description>Here’s where Vice President Kamala Harris, a former prosecutor, stands on important criminal justice issues.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 19:09:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2 Money Moves We’re Making TODAY to Prepare for a Potential Recession</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-548</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Are we in a recession? Are we headed for a recession? No one knows for certain, but you can never be too prepared for an economic downturn. Are you saving […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 07:01:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hackers shut down heating in Ukrainian city with malware, researchers say</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/23/hackers-shut-down-heating-in-ukrainian-city-with-malware-researchers-say/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Cybersecurity firm Dragos and Ukrainian authorities found a cyberattack targeting critical infrastructure in Lviv. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Project 2025 Plans for Trump to Have Unprecedented Power Over the Justice Department</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/20/trump-project-2025-crime-prosecutors</link><description>The policy plan for a second Trump term would turn the department against progressive local prosecutors.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Here’s Why Real Estate Investors Are Turning to ATMs For Diversification</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/why-investors-are-turning-to-atm-investments-for-diversification</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>As real estate conditions continue to tighten, investors are turning to ATMs for steady cash flow.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 20:21:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Telegram’s userbase climbs to 950M, plans to launch app store</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/23/telegrams-userbase-climbs-to-950m-plans-to-launch-app-store/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Messaging app Telegram has reached 950M active users, and it aims to cross the 1 billion mark this year, founder Pavel Durov said. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 08:30:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Love Beyond Bars: Jules and Samantha</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/19/photo-essay-werkheisers-wrongful-conviction</link><description>Jules and Samantha Werkheiser fought their wrongful convictions for over a decade. Here’s their journey of survival — and motherhood — in pictures.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Month Seven of Our 1031 Exchange: We’re Investing in… Restaurants?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/1031-investor-journal-seven</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>With $975,000 to play with, we're looking at options outside of residential real estate.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 20:11:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>India scraps ‘angel tax’ in boost for startups</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/23/india-scraps-angel-tax-in-boost-to-startups/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>India’s federal government has removed the so-called “angel tax” for all classes of investors, delivering a major victory to the country’s startup ecosystem that had lobbied for years against the measure. “To bolster the India startup ecosystem, to boost entrepreneurial spirit and support innovation, I propose abolishing angel tax for all classes of investors,” Finance […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 08:16:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meet the New Generation of Unarmed First Responders in This New Podcast Series</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/18/police-north-carolina-podcast-mental-health</link><description>“The Fifth Branch,” a podcast from The Marshall Project and Tradeoffs, examines new, alternative ways to respond to 911 crisis calls.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Department of Justice’s Next Target: Buyer Agents</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/department-of-justice-targets-buyer-agent-loopholes</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>The DOJ is planning further changes to agent commission structures, which could lead to a significant reduction in traditional commission rates.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 19:52:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kakao founder issued arrest warrant by Seoul court</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/22/kakao-founder-arrested-over-alleged-market-manipulation/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>A Seoul court issued an arrest warrant for Brian Kim, the founder of South Korean internet giant Kakao, on allegations of stock price manipulation related to the company’s takeover of K-pop agency SM Entertainment in 2023. The Seoul Southern District Court said on Tuesday that it had issued a warrant for Kim’s arrest after a […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 05:48:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What We Know About J.D. Vance’s Legislative Action on Criminal Justice</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/17/what-we-know-from-sen-j-d-vance-s-legislative-action-on-criminal-justice-issues</link><description>On immigration and more, Vance has defended and legislated former President Donald Trump’s policy goals.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 23:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>