<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 13:41:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Investment Returns Are NOT Random</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/07/investment-returns-are-not-random/</link><description>Are investment returns random across time as Burton Malkiel suggests in his book, A Random Walk Down Wall Street? There is notable disagreement on this topic. This research finds that practitioners may need to rethink their portfolio optimization routines.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:22:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>U.S. investigators ask Tesla why there have been 20 crashes since carmaker supposedly fixed Autopilot flaws</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/07/tesla-autopilot-recall-crash-investigation-nhtsa/</link><description>"Tesla tried to do the least possible remedy to see what they could get away with,” one observer said.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:58:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Generational Wealth: Does the Apple Fall Far From the Tree?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/06/generational-wealth-does-the-apple-fall-far-from-the-tree/</link><description>There is strong evidence that most “rich families” will be poorer after several generations. Some of the reasons for this are systemic like taxes. But most factors that diminish a family’s wealth over generations are the choices that heirs make.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 12:37:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Boy Scouts no more: Organization changes name to Scouting America as it exits bankruptcy after storm of controversy</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/07/boy-scouts-bankruptcy-name-change-sexual-assault/</link><description>The organization began allowing gay youth in 2013 and ended a blanket ban on gay adult leaders in 2015, and a few years later, announced that girls would be accepted as Cub Scouts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:53:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>State Capitalism in Private Markets: Mission Creep</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/03/state-capitalism-in-private-markets-mission-creep/</link><description>Governments relish mingling in markets. Yet, if past policies are any guide, taxpayers are being shortchanged.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 12:30:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden condemns antisemitism, says people are forgetting that ‘Hamas unleashed this terror’</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/07/biden-condemns-antisemitism-hamas-israel-gaza/</link><description>In remarks at the Capitol, Biden said that on Oct. 7, Hamas "brought to life" this type of hatred with the killing of more than 1,200 Israelis, mostly civilians.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:31:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Implementation Shortfalls Hamstring Factor Strategies</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/01/implementation-shortfalls-hamstring-factor-strategies/</link><description>Smart rebalancing rules help portfolio managers capture more of the return that is inherent in their factor strategies. Concentrating on “priority best” trading improves factor portfolio performance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 11:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>We ranked the best cash back cards available in 2024</title><link>https://fortune.com/recommends/credit-cards/best-cash-back-credit-cards/</link><description>These cash back credit cards can put hundreds of dollars back in your pocket.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:23:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IFRS Accounting Standard Will Support Better Investment Decisions</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/30/ifrs-accounting-standard-will-support-better-investment-decisions/</link><description>IFRS 18 responds to investors' concerns about challenges in comparing companies' financial performance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 11:34:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New York governor regrets saying ‘we have young Black kids growing up in the Bronx who don’t even know what the word computer is’</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/07/new-york-governor-kathy-hochul-regrets-saying-black-kids-computers-bronx/</link><description>Assemblywoman Amanda Septimo, a Bronx Democrat, who said the remark was “harmful, deeply misinformed, and genuinely appalling.”</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:19:31 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>