<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 06:58:52 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Update on Utah’s NHL Team Name, Uniform Info, Tournament Coming?</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/24/update-on-utahs-nhl-team-name-uniform-info-tournament-coming/hockey-2/</link><description>Utah’s new National Hockey League team is starting to assemble their list of possible team names ahead of their inaugural (but not expansion) season this fall. DetroitHockey.Net’s Clark Rasmussen, the king of the trademark search, found two more names possibly trademarked by the group, bringing the total to nine that</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:51:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paris Hilton Acquires Rights to Book About 2000s Tabloid Culture For New Doc</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/24/paris-hilton-new-docuseries-tabloid-2000s-culture-toxic-book-acquire-rights/</link><description>Paris Hilton is putting a spotlight on early '00s tabloid culture, 'cause she's producing a new docuseries examining the way female celebs were treated back then ... including herself. The heiress' production company, 11:11 Media, has acquired the…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 06:58:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Liverpool FC Reportedly Ready to Return to Adidas in 2025</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/24/liverpool-fc-reportedly-ready-to-return-to-adidas-in-2025/soccer/</link><description>New deal with Liverpool reportedly part of an "aggressive push" by Adidas to win high-profile contracts after losing German national team deal</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 17:56:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ryan Garcia Spotted With Two Different Bombshells In Miami After Devin Haney Win</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/24/ryan-garcia-spotted-with-two-different-bombshells-miami-after-devin-haney-win/</link><description>Ryan Garcia is living like a king in Miami after his massive win over Devin Haney ... and it appears he's now holding queen auditions, 'cause the boxing superstar was spotted courting two different beauties during his celebratory trip. TMZ Sports…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 06:58:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Houston Texans Unveil Four New Uniforms, Two New Helmets</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/23/houston-texans-unveil-four-new-uniforms-two-new-helmets/football/</link><description>The Houston Texans unveiled their new uniforms on Tuesday morning, including four distinctly different designs intended to satisfy every corner of the fanbase.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 16:17:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Owen Wilson Turned Down Role in Film Painting O.J. Simpson as Innocent</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/24/owen-wilson-turned-down-lead-role-oj-simpson-movie-innocent/</link><description>Owen Wilson wants nothing to do with a movie leaning into the idea O.J. Simpson was innocent of the infamous '94 murders -- turning down a boatload for the lead part. The partially finished flick's director, Joshua Newton, admits he thought Owen…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 06:58:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Madison Mallards unveil alternates IN A VAN DOWN BY THE RIVER</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/22/madison-mallards-unveil-alternates-in-a-van-down-by-the-river/baseball/</link><description>The collegiate summer level Madison Mallards unveiled an alternate identity today based on a classic Saturday Night Live sketch that featured the late, great Madison native Chris Farley over three decades ago in 1993. The logo and uniforms evoke Farley’s character Matt Foley, a down-on-his-luck motivational speaker who famously lives</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 01:21:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Joe Biden Again Reads Teleprompter Instruction During Speech, 'Pause'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/24/joe-biden-again-reads-teleprompter-instruction-speech-four-more-years-pause/</link><description>President Joe Biden had yet another teleprompter gaffe while speaking at a conference Wednesday ... and it's not the first time the prez fumbled a speech, far from it. JB stopped by the annual conference for North America’s Building Trades…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 06:58:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Minnesota Vikings Alternate, New York Giants Throwback Jerseys Leak</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/22/minnesota-vikings-alternate-new-york-giants-throwback-jerseys-leak/football/</link><description>Former NFL wide receiver Antonio Brown's social media network leaked two more jerseys that will be worn this season, including a Minnesota Vikings alternate and New York Giants throwback design.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 21:24:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gisele Bündchen Seems to Break Down in Tears After Traffic Ticket</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/24/gisele-bundchen-breaks-down-tears-cries-pulled-over-traffic-ticket/</link><description>Gisele Bündchen's day started out rough -- a cop pulled her over in Florida, and she seemed pretty upset over it all ... especially when he handed her a ticket. Check out this video ... you see a Surfside PD officer pulling over a Mercedes…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 06:58:52 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>