<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 22:37:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>With So Much Uncertainty, Can You Reliably Build Generational Wealth From Passive Real Estate Investments?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/can-you-build-generational-wealth-through-passive-real-estate</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>From proposals to cap rent increases, all the way down to rent control, is the uncertainty in today's market enough to make investors leave it altogether?</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 18:22:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bethesda Game Studios employees form a ‘wall-to-wall’ union</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/20/bethesda-game-studios-employees-form-a-wall-to-wall-union/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Employees at Bethesda Game Studios — the Microsoft-owned game developer that produces the Elder Scrolls and Fallout franchises — are joining the Communication Workers of America. Quality assurance testers at Bethesda’s parent organization ZeniMax unionized last year, becoming Microsoft’s first official union in the United States. In its announcement, the CWA calls Bethesda’s new union […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 21:32:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Project 2025 Plans for Trump to Have Unprecedented Power Over the Justice Department</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/20/trump-project-2025-crime-prosecutors</link><description>The policy plan for a second Trump term would turn the department against progressive local prosecutors.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Real Estate Investors Are Making These 6 Costly Mistakes. Don’t Be One of Them.</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/top-6-mistakes-real-estate-investors-are-making-in-2024</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Investors in both stocks and real estate are making the same mistakes right now. Here's what you need to be aware of.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 18:05:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CrowdStrike’s update fail causes global outages and travel chaos</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/20/crowdstrikes-update-fail-causes-global-outages-and-travel-chaos/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>This week saw one of the most widespread IT disruptions in recent years linked to a faulty software update from popular cybersecurity firm CrowdStrike. Businesses across the world reported IT outages, including Windows “blue screen of death” errors on their computers, impacting airlines, banks, retailers, brokerage houses, media companies and railway networks. OpenAI released GPT-4o […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 21:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Love Beyond Bars: Jules and Samantha</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/19/photo-essay-werkheisers-wrongful-conviction</link><description>Jules and Samantha Werkheiser fought their wrongful convictions for over a decade. Here’s their journey of survival — and motherhood — in pictures.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Home Construction Is Undergoing a Revolution. Here’s How Investors Will Benefit.</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/are-3d-homes-the-future-of-home-construction</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Will we be able to hit "print" and generate housing one day? It could be sooner than you think.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 17:49:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Unpacking how Alphabet’s rumored Wiz acquisition could affect VC</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/20/unpacking-how-alphabets-rumored-wiz-acquisition-could-affect-vc/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Alphabet, the parent company of Google, is in advanced talks to acquire cybersecurity startup Wiz for $23 billion, the Wall Street Journal reported on Sunday. TechCrunch’s sources heard similar and added that deal discussions could last into next week. If this deal does end up getting done, it would be Alphabet’s largest acquisition yet. It […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meet the New Generation of Unarmed First Responders in This New Podcast Series</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/18/police-north-carolina-podcast-mental-health</link><description>“The Fifth Branch,” a podcast from The Marshall Project and Tradeoffs, examines new, alternative ways to respond to 911 crisis calls.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Don’t Risk Your Money: Check These Stats Before Selecting Your Investment Market</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/check-these-stats-before-selecting-your-investment-market</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Choosing the right market to invest in is your most important investment decision.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 14:38:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Microsoft says 8.5M Windows devices were affected by CrowdStrike outage</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/20/microsoft-says-8-5m-windows-devices-were-affected-by-crowdstrike-outage/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Around 8.5 million devices — less than 1 percent Windows machines globally — were affected by the recent CrowdStrike outage, according to a Microsoft blog post by David Weston, the company’s vice president of enterprise and OS security. These are the first real numbers released by either Microsoft or CrowdStrike around the scale of yesterday’s […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 18:01:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What We Know About J.D. Vance’s Legislative Action on Criminal Justice</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/17/what-we-know-from-sen-j-d-vance-s-legislative-action-on-criminal-justice-issues</link><description>On immigration and more, Vance has defended and legislated former President Donald Trump’s policy goals.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 23:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A World Without Airbnb &amp; Why “Sinking” Could Cause Your Insurance to Skyrocket</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-991</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Airbnb bans escalate, a “tsunami” could be coming for this real estate niche, and “sinking” cities lead to skyrocketing insurance prices. The housing market changes every week, so we’re here […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 07:02:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Some Black startup founders feel betrayed by Ben Horowitz’s support for Trump</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/20/some-black-startup-founders-feel-betrayed-by-ben-horowitzs-support-for-trump/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Trump is an advocate for a number of policies that could be harmful to people of color. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How a Supreme Court Ruling Could Affect a Case Involving Police Abuse of Youth</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/13/supreme-court-bankruptcy-sackler-boy-scouts</link><description>Another court must now decide how the landmark ruling will impact the Boy Scouts abuse settlement, which involves victims of police sexual abuse.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>