<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from multiple RSS sources, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 18:02:30 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The New Reform That Could Unlock $1B+ for Affordable Housing w/Sharon Cornelissen</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-211</link><description>America is in need of affordable housing; we’re all aware. Buying your first home has become increasingly challenging for everyday people. This is where housing subsidies come in. Federal housing […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 07:02:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Snap says total watch time on its TikTok competitor increased more than 125%</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/25/snap-total-watch-time-on-tiktok-competitor-increased-125/</link><description>As part of its Q1 2024 earning release, Snap revealed that total watch time on its TikTok competitor, Spotlight, increased more than 125% year-over-year. Snapchat launched the TikTok-like feed in late 2020 as a way to compete with the rising popularity of TikTok. The company is touting the success of its short-from video feed a […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 22:09:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Enduring Use of Solitary, and New Proposed Limits That Will Likely Fail (Again)</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/20/solitary-confinement-reform-oklahoma-washington-florida</link><description>Isolation’s damaging effects are widely known. But many facilities confine people — even youth — virtually all day, sometimes in shower stalls.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What to Know About Your Health Insurer’s Formulary Drug List</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/health-insurance/features/formulary-list-medications?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>How do drug formularies work? Learn more about your health insurer's list of preferred drugs and how it can save you money.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 18:23:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sunbelt Surge: 15 Cities Dominating the Growth Charts</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/best-sunbelt-markets-for-growth</link><description>Simply investing in any metro Sunbelt market is not a recipe for success. To catch a cresting wave of appreciation and cash flow, you’ll need to dive deep into the metrics […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:48:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>It’s a sunny day for Google Cloud</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/25/its-a-sunny-day-for-google-cloud/</link><description>Google Cloud had a blockbuster quarter, driving parent company Alphabet's revenues — and stock price — to impressive highs.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 21:56:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Officials Failed to Act When COVID Hit Prisons. A New Study Shows the Deadly Cost.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/18/covid-prison-deaths-data</link><description>People in prison died at 3.4 times the rate of the free population, with the oldest hit hardest. New data holds lessons for preventing future deaths.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shop Around to Save on Drug Prices</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/health-insurance/features/medication-shop-around?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Should you shop around for prescription drugs? Learn ways to compare drug prices to find more affordable options.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 18:21:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Warning: These States and Cities Are Becoming Uninvestable Due to Politics</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/how-politics-is-making-these-states-and-cities-uninvestable</link><description>Taxes and regulations impact your bottom line as an investor—and not always in direct or obvious ways. Unfortunately, as soon as you start talking about either one, the average person closes their […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:27:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rubrik’s shares end trading up almost 16% on the company’s public debut</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/25/rubriks-shares-climb-20-in-its-public-debut/</link><description>This share price gives Rubrik a fully diluted valuation of $6.6 billion, up 88% from its last primary valuation of $3.5 billion in 2019.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 21:50:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Parents Paying for Their Children’s Crimes</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/13/michigan-school-shooting-parents</link><description>Experts warn about a wave of legal consequences for parents like the Crumbleys, while some states consider prosecutions for kids as young as 10.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stroke Risk in Black Americans: Expert Q&amp;A</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/stroke/features/stroke-risk-black-americans?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>The risk of having a stroke, and dying of one, is higher for Black Americans than for other racial and ethnic groups. Find out why – and what helps prevent strokes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 18:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The BEST Ways to Protect Your Rental Property and Keep Your Tenants Safe</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-397</link><description>If you own a rental property, it’s YOUR responsibility to provide a safe environment for tenants. This starts with things like tenant screening, security upgrades, and most importantly, acting swiftly […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:02:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Meta is looking to the fediverse as the future for social media</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/25/why-meta-is-looking-to-the-fediverse-as-the-future-for-social-media/</link><description>Meta’s move into the open social web, also known as the fediverse, is puzzling. Does the Facebook owner see open protocols as the future? Will it embrace the fediverse only to shut it down, shifting people back to its proprietary platforms and decimating startups building in the space? Will it bring its advertising empire to […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 21:37:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I Had a Tough Job at My Brooklyn Jail: Keeping Men From Taking Their Own Lives</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/12/brooklyn-jail-suicide-prevention-aide</link><description>As a suicide prevention aide, I had to make sure my fellow detainees didn’t harm themselves. It was surprisingly easy to get such a complex job.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mobile Stroke Units Can Change Lives</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/stroke/features/mobile-stroke-units?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Mobile stroke units are specially equipped ambulances for stroke patients. Why aren’t they more widespread?</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 18:09:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Building Wealth with OLD Homes and How to Keep Tenants for Longer</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-942</link><description>How do you find investment properties nobody else is looking for—the ones with cash flow potential, equity upside, and wealth-building qualities all the other investors overlook? Simple: buy what nobody […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:02:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Health insurance giant Kaiser will notify millions of a data breach after sharing patients’ data with advertisers</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/25/kaiser-permanente-health-plan-millions-data-breach/</link><description>Kaiser, one of the largest healthcare organizations in the United States, said it was notifying 13.4 million members of a data breach earlier in April.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 20:42:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Supreme Court Case on Homelessness May Limit Prisoner Rights and Expand Executions</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/10/supreme-court-homeless-grants-pass-originalism</link><description>In Grants Pass v. Johnson, a town in Oregon asks the court to reconsider what constitutes “cruel and unusual punishments.”</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Talk to Your Doctor About Drug Costs</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/health-insurance/features/drug-costs-speak-up?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Talking to your doctor about drug costs could help you save on prescriptions. Learn what your doctor can do when you can't afford your medication.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 18:07:17 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>