<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 02:17:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>A Look at the New NHL Practice Jersey Design</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/04/a-look-at-the-new-nhl-practice-jersey-design/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Thanks to the Utah Hockey Club, we got ourselves a look at the new NHL practice jersey design. With the switch from Adidas to Fanatics for 2024-25, we knew there’d be some changes to the on-ice NHL uniform. We’ve already seen that each team’s jersey will now include the Fanatics</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 22:20:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mike Rowe Says Lack of Patriotism Inspired New Doc 'Something to Stand For'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/04/mike-rowe-documentary-film-something-to-stand-for/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Mike Rowe's drumming up support for his new movie "Something to Stand For," urging Americans to rally around at least one thing -- feeling grateful for one great moment in our history. We caught up with Mike on "TMZ Live" ... and he revealed the…</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 02:17:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MLB Teams Wearing USA-Themed Caps Today for Fourth of July</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/04/mlb-teams-wearing-usa-themed-caps-today-for-fourth-of-july/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>All 30 Major League Baseball teams will wear stars-and-stripes-themed caps on-field during today’s games in honour of Independence Day in the United States. This year, all 30 clubs will wear a cream-coloured crown, with teams again having the option of a red or navy blue visor and button. One more</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 16:34:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>American Flag Swimwear Guess Who!</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/04/american-flag-swimwear-guess-who/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Would ya take a good look at these spirited stars who've slipped into their finest American Flag swimsuits?! It's bikini babes galore and they are HOT ... don't get too close or else they'll set your fireworks off! From reality stars to athletes…</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 02:17:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2024 MLB All-Star Game Uniforms Revealed</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/03/2024-mlb-all-star-game-uniforms-revealed/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Major League Baseball has officially unveiled the uniforms their best players will wear when they take the field at Globe Life Field in Arlington later this month. The uniforms, as you’d expect, incorporate some of that Texas style, with an Old West style typeface across the chest and again in</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 02:02:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Genie Bouchard Splits With Longtime Boyfriend Jack Brinkley-Cook</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/04/genie-bouchard-splits-longtime-boyfriend-jack-brinkley-cook-breakup/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Genie Bouchard is single for the summer ... TMZ Sports has learned the tennis star and her longtime boyfriend, Jack Brinkley-Cook, have broken up. Our sources say the two officially headed to Splitsville in April ... calling off a relationship that…</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 02:17:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Leaked Photos Show 2024 MLB All-Star Jerseys</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/03/leaked-photos-show-2024-mlb-all-star-jerseys/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>With just under two weeks until this year’s Mid-Summer Classic, the jerseys for one of the two teams have leaked. Posted by SNY’s Twitter account dedicated to the New York Yankees, the photos show the front and back of a cream-coloured American League jersey bearing the name of Yankees outfielder</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 20:37:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Marlon Wayans' L.A. Home Burglarized, Brother Keenen Home at the Time</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/04/marlon-wayans-home-burgled-safe-stolen-cash-keenen-ivory-wayans/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>A not-so-funny situation for Marlon Wayans and his famously comedic family -- cops say his L.A.-area crib is the latest target of burglars. Law enforcement sources tell TMZ Marlon wasn't home, but his brother Keenen Ivory Wayans was around 2:30 AM…</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 02:17:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Former Employee Suing New York Jets, NFL Over Vintage Logo</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/03/former-employee-suing-new-york-jets-nfl-over-vintage-logo/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>A former employee is suing the New York Jets and the NFL for unspecified damages for designing the team's 1978-97 logo.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:04:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shaquille O'Neal Gave 'Hawk Tuah' Girl Advice on How to Navigate Fame</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/04/shaquille-oneal-gave-hawk-tuah-girl-advice-navigate-fame/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Shaquille O'Neal is giving the "Hawk Tuah" girl some sage advice ... how to navigate her newfound celebrity status. Sources with direct knowledge tell TMZ ... when Shaq and Hailey Welch linked up in Nashville last weekend, the NBA legend started…</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 02:17:49 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>