<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 02:11:30 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Book Review: The New World Economy in 5 Trends</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/24/book-review-the-new-world-economy-in-5-trends/</link><description>A diligent economist and an eclectic bookworm serve up an analysis of megatrends that will have the greatest impact on economies and investments: innovation, productivity, climate, multiglobalization, debt, and aging.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 12:22:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>EU would 'be delighted' to forge closer ties with the U.K.'s next government, according to Economy Commissioner</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/27/eu-delighted-forge-closer-ties-uk-next-government/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-544675524-e1716566253127.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>While Prime Minister Rishi Sunak has edged the U.K. closer to the EU and helped normalize relations with the bloc, Labour has vowed to further improve ties if it wins.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Factor Strategies Belong in Your Completion Portfolio Toolkit</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/23/factor-strategies-belong-in-your-completion-portfolio-toolkit/</link><description>Why wouldn't you include factor strategies in your completion portfolio? A review of the two commonly used approaches for managing institutional assets highlights their symbiotic nature.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 19:09:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Women are now less likely to be in top earning 1% of U.K. finance and professional services jobs than before the pandemic</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/27/gender-pay-progression-women-now-less-likely-top-earning-uk-finance-professional-services-jobs-than-before-pandemic/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Carolyn-McCall-Anthony-harvey-GettyImages-522233198.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>There's been progress, but the more senior you get, the greater the gender gap.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>For the Analyst: Peer Benchmarking Methods to Improve Earnings Forecasts</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/21/for-the-analyst-peer-benchmarking-methods-to-improve-earnings-forecasts/</link><description>Peer benchmarking is a vexing task for financial analysts but one that is critical for forecasting earnings. This straightforward measure can help find peers for relative performance, compensation, and valuation benchmarking.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 12:47:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Here's how ADHD is diagnosed in adults</title><link>https://fortune.com/well/article/adult-adhd-symptoms-behavior-diagnosis/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-642026108.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The disorder can present differently in children and adults.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Building LLMs in the Open-Source Community: A Call to Action for Investment Professionals</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/20/building-llms-in-the-open-source-community-a-call-to-action-for-investment-professionals/</link><description>Large language models like ChatGPT are changing the way we think about investing and reshaping roles in the investment profession.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 16:26:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Bond King' Bill Gross warns Trump would worsen deficits and be 'more disruptive' for the bond market than Biden</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/26/us-deficit-debt-crisis-bond-market-bill-gross-donald-trump-joe-biden/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2154671992-e1716764998346.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>"Trump is the more bearish of the candidates simply because his programs advocate continued tax cuts and more expensive things."</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 00:53:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sustainability Reporting: Navigating Assurance Practices</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/17/sustainability-reporting-navigating-assurance-practices/</link><description>Don't be lulled into a false sense of security by the word "assurance" when evaluating sustainability reports. Assurance practices vary, and investors would be wise to learn more about the different levels of coverage.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 17:57:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A flood of cheap Chinese exports is putting the entire global economy at risk, France’s finance minister warns</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/26/global-economic-outlook-risk-flood-cheap-chinese-exports-france-finance-minister/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2153762782-e1716764049959.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>“We have an issue with the economic model in which China is producing more and more cheaper industrial devices because it could be a threat not only for the EU, not only for the US, but for the global world economy.”</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 00:01:49 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>