<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 06:57:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Coiled Tight: Smaller Companies Are Primed for Outperformance</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/08/coiled-tight-smaller-companies-are-primed-for-outperformance/</link><description>Small-cap companies are poised for a rebound. The sector is best approached through an active investment strategy where expertise and a deep understanding of the individual businesses and their risk-and-reward characteristics are necessary for success.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:40:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shark Tank entrepreneur: E-commerce giants are eating my sister's lunch—and destroying the American Dream</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/10/shark-tank-entrepreneur-e-commerce-giants-are-eating-my-sisters-lunch-and-destroying-the-american-dream/</link><description>Although e-commerce platforms say they do their best to counter knockoffs, our experience proves the opposite.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:52:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Investment Returns Are NOT Random</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/07/investment-returns-are-not-random/</link><description>Are investment returns random across time as Burton Malkiel suggests in his book, A Random Walk Down Wall Street? There is notable disagreement on this topic. This research finds that practitioners may need to rethink their portfolio optimization routines.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:22:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple forced into rare apology for 'tone-deaf' iPad advert</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/10/apple-apology-ipad-crush-advert/</link><description>Apple’s Tor Myhren said the Big Tech giant had "missed the mark" with the video released this week, and apologized to customers who called out the brand for its "tone-deaf" marketing.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:30:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Generational Wealth: Does the Apple Fall Far From the Tree?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/06/generational-wealth-does-the-apple-fall-far-from-the-tree/</link><description>There is strong evidence that most “rich families” will be poorer after several generations. Some of the reasons for this are systemic like taxes. But most factors that diminish a family’s wealth over generations are the choices that heirs make.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 12:37:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Baidu exec who started furor over 24/7 work culture with videos making light of staff wellbeing and warning subordinates to toe the line has resigned</title><link>https://fortune.com/asia/2024/05/10/baidu-exec-247-work-culture-videos-staff-wellbeing-warning-subordinates-toe-line-resigned/</link><description>“I’m not your mother-in-law,” she said in one of the clips she posted to Douyin, China’s version of TikTok.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:26:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>State Capitalism in Private Markets: Mission Creep</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/03/state-capitalism-in-private-markets-mission-creep/</link><description>Governments relish mingling in markets. Yet, if past policies are any guide, taxpayers are being shortchanged.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 12:30:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SoftBank has sold off or written down $29 billion in U.S. Vision Fund assets as Masayoshi Son tries to get his mojo back by turning to AI and chips</title><link>https://fortune.com/asia/2024/05/10/softbank-writes-down-us-vision-fund-assets-pivot-ai-chips-ceo-masayoshi-son/</link><description>One project reportedly being considered by Softbank's CEO: a $100 billion chip venture to compete with Nvidia.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 10:52:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Implementation Shortfalls Hamstring Factor Strategies</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/01/implementation-shortfalls-hamstring-factor-strategies/</link><description>Smart rebalancing rules help portfolio managers capture more of the return that is inherent in their factor strategies. Concentrating on “priority best” trading improves factor portfolio performance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 11:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden administration expected to impose sweeping tariffs on China strategic sectors</title><link>https://fortune.com/asia/2024/05/10/biden-administration-impose-sweeping-tariffs-china-strategic-sectors-evs-batteries-solar-cells/</link><description>The decision is the culmination of a review of so-called Section 301 tariffs first put into place under Trump starting in 2018.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 10:32:41 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>