<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 07:47:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The Power of Clicks, Likes, and Shares: Promote the Right Kind of Financial Content</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/16/the-power-of-clicks-likes-and-shares-promote-the-right-kind-of-financial-content/</link><description>Not all financial content creators on social media are created equal. A broad differentiation can be made between influencers, knowledge sharers, and aspiring thought leaders.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 14:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump lawyers accuse former fixer Michael Cohen of lying to jury</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/17/trump-lawyers-fixer-michael-cohen-lying-jury-obsessed-jail/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/AP24137440205450-e1715945880204.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Whether the defense is successful in undermining Cohen's testimony could determine Trump's fate in the case.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 12:40:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why the New T+1 Settlement Cycle Matters: A Global Index Provider’s Perspective</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/14/why-the-new-t1-settlement-cycle-matters-a-global-index-providers-perspective/</link><description>Shorter settlement periods are meant to protect market participants. But the new T+1 settlement cycle for US equities may have undesirable knock-on effects for financial market participants around the world, including index fund managers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 16:54:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sir Richard Branson—who hates being called a billionaire—sees net worth fall back to 2000 levels</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/17/richard-branson-net-worth-falls-back-3-billion-year-2000-hates-being-called-billionaire/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1434426517-e1715943659708.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Branson took a $126 million hit to his fortune last year as he continued to fight several fires at his Virgin Group.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 12:39:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Leveraging AI to Identify and Predict Financial Crises</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/13/leveraging-ai-to-identify-and-predict-financial-crises/</link><description>Despite some current limitations, AI stands to offer significant advantages versus traditional approaches to identifying and predicting financial crises.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 14:39:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A deepfake ‘CFO’ tricked the British design firm behind the Sydney Opera House in $25 million fraud</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/17/arup-deepfake-fraud-scam-victim-hong-kong-25-million-cfo/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1744769333-e1715942474314.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>“Our financial stability and business operations were not affected," an Arup spokesperson said.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 12:32:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Your Portfolio Should Include Scarce Assets</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/10/why-your-portfolio-should-include-scarce-assets/</link><description>Portfolios that include both productive and scarce assets can deliver similar performance to the S&amp;P 500 with less risk than those that hold only productive assets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:34:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Taiwan is now exporting and investing more in the U.S. than China in major pivot away from Beijing</title><link>https://fortune.com/asia/2024/05/17/taiwan-exporting-investing-more-us-china-major-pivot-away-beijing/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/AP24135146409859-e1715943293440.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The U.S. displaced mainland China as the top destination for Taiwan’s exports in the first quarter of the year for the first time since the start of 2016, when comparable data became available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 11:56:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coiled Tight: Smaller Companies Are Primed for Outperformance</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/08/coiled-tight-smaller-companies-are-primed-for-outperformance/</link><description>Small-cap companies are poised for a rebound. The sector is best approached through an active investment strategy where expertise and a deep understanding of the individual businesses and their risk-and-reward characteristics are necessary for success.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:40:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nearly half of Gen Z and millennial workers have left a job, or plan to, because of climate concerns</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/17/gen-z-millennial-sustainability-jobs-climate-change-deloitte/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2042292838-e1715940128917.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Instead of sitting with their climate change anxiety, Gen Z and millennials are trying to save the planet by quitting jobs that aren’t eco-friendly.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 11:35:46 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>