<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 07:38:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Are We in a Recession?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-247</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Are we in a recession? A lot of people certainly think so. After a surprisingly accurate recession indicator went off weeks ago, more and more Americans have begun to believe […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 10:00:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>France formally charges Telegram founder, Pavel Durov, over organized crime on messaging app</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/29/france-formally-charges-telegram-founder-pavel-durov-over-organized-crime-on-app/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>After spending four days in police custody, the founder and CEO of messaging app Telegram, Pavel Durov, was put under formal investigation in France on Thursday for a wide range of criminal charges. He was also released from custody on the condition that he does not leave French territory during the investigation. Bail was set […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 11:03:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>5 Things to Know About How Survivors Get Incarcerated for Their Abusers’ Crimes</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/28/accomplice-liability-laws-what-to-know</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Little-known laws allow people to be punished for crimes they didn’t directly commit. Survivors of domestic violence are especially vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Find Real Estate Deals (and Analyze Them) in 5 Easy Steps</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-webinar</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Find real estate deals faster with a BiggerPockets Pro Membership. Use code “PDEAL24” for 20% off plus thousands of dollars in bonuses and access to investment calculators, BiggerPockets deal finder, […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 10:00:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI dominates India’s Reliance annual general meeting</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/29/ai-dominates-india-reliance-annual-general-meeting/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Reliance Industries, India’s largest company by market capitalization, is not sitting out the AI frenzy that has gripped the tech world. At the company’s 47th annual general meeting Thursday, Reliance chairman Mukesh Ambani and other executives made nearly three-dozen mentions of AI in two hours, detailing plans to integrate the technology across Reliance’s vast business […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 10:50:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How a Drop in Border Crossings May Change the Presidential Campaign</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/24/kamala-harris-dnc-border-donald-trump</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>The Democratic National Convention sought to address one of the party’s biggest weaknesses with voters.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Where New Investors Should Be Looking to Buy This Fall</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/best-markets-for-new-investors-fall-2024</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>As autumn approaches, new investors should take advantage of seasonal trends to get into these five markets.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 21:49:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Durex India spilled customers’ private order data</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/28/durex-india-spilled-customers-private-order-data/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Durex India has exposed customers' personal information, including full names, email and postal addresses, and order details. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 04:30:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Prosecutors Fight Exonerations</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/17/wrongful-conviction-innocence-claims-missouri-st-louis</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>As laws are passed to support the wrongfully convicted, some officials in the legal system push back.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Realistic Path to Wealth: Investing in Real Estate WHILE Working a W2</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-1010</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Wondering how to invest in real estate so you can finally quit your job? Then, this episode might surprise you. While most real estate educators online are constantly stressing how […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 10:00:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple’s new iOS developer beta lets you remove objects from pictures using AI</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/28/apple-introduces-ai-powered-object-removal-with-the-latest-ios-update/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Apple has added yet more AI features in its latest developer betas for iOS 18.1, and this time we're getting the ability to remove objects from photos. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:58:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FAQ: How The Marshall Project Is Covering the 2024 Election</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/16/election-faq-crime-politics</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Learn more about who we are and how we choose what political stories to cover.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rental Property Analysis in 2024: Find Cash Flow Even</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-450</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Deal analysis is an essential tool in the investor’s toolkit and maybe the most crucial skill for breaking into real estate investing. Have you ever wondered how other investors can […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 10:00:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NEA quietly reenters the secondaries market</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/28/nea-quietly-reenters-the-secondaries-market/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>New Enterprise Associates (NEA) is getting back into the secondaries game. The Silicon Valley-based VC raised more than $468 million for NEA Secondary Opportunity Fund, according to an SEC filing. The fundraise closed on July 3, according to a source familiar with the matter, but hasn’t received much attention. The fund raised capital from more […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:57:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Mother on a Mission for Full Police Transparency</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/16/police-beating-ulysses-wilkerson-mother-video</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Troy, Alabama, police severely beat Ulysses Wilkerson when he was 17. Seven years later, his mom, Angela Williams, is still fighting for answers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>