<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 06:55:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Could West Virginia Mountaineers Wear 1965 Throwback Uniforms In 2025?</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/22/could-west-virginia-mountaineers-wear-1965-throwback-uniforms-in-2025/college/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>A recent exchange on social media between West Virginia's athletic director, head coach and a fan indicates throwback uniforms might be in the works for next season.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 22:17:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Patrick Mahomes Defends Harrison Butker, 'That's A Good Person'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/22/patrick-mahomes-defends-harrison-butker-good-person/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Patrick Mahomes is sticking up for Harrison Butker ... praising the kicker as a man of good character following his controversial commencement speech earlier this month. Butker is at the center of a ton of criticism after speaking at Benedictine…</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 06:55:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OHL’s Guelph Storm File Trademarks for Three New Logos</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/22/ohls-guelph-storm-file-trademarks-for-three-new-logos/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>It's unclear if the Storm would keep their crimson, silver and black color scheme as trademark filing images are usually only available in grayscale</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 20:47:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Judge Blocks Graceland Auction, Lending Company Drops Claim on Elvis' Home</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/22/graceland-auction-blocked-riley-keough-lisa-marie-presley-elvis/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>12:35 PM PT -- Now it's a total victory for Riley Keough ... as Naussany Investments and Private Lending has withdrawn all claims on Graceland, with prejudice -- meaning it can't be refiled. In a statement, the company said it meant no harm to…</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 06:55:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2024 MLB Father’s Day Caps Revealed</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/22/2024-mlb-fathers-day-caps-revealed/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Father’s Day is quickly approaching. In the world of Major League Baseball, this means we’ll see baby blue-themed baseball caps and ribbons on the uniforms of Major League Baseball players, coaches, managers, and umpires for all games played on Sunday, June 16th. SHOP: 2024 MLB Father’s Day team caps available</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 15:50:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jelly Roll's Teen Daughter Caught on Camera Sneaking Out of the House</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/22/jelly-roll-teen-daughter-caught-on-camera-sneaking-out/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Jelly Roll's daughter Bailee Ann just went through every teen's rite of passage -- trying, and failing, to sneak outta the house for a night of fun. The 16-year-old's stepmom Bunnie XO playfully roasted her on TikTok, sharing the hilarious security…</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 06:55:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>They’ve Got the Power: Washington, D.C., USL Super League Club Unveils Name, Logo</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/21/theyve-got-the-power-washington-d-c-usl-super-league-club-unveils-name-logo/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Crest features black, red and white shield with eagle wing cutting through the middle; lightning bolts in negative represent three communities in D.C. metro area</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 21:15:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kid Falls Unconscious After Being Choked Out by Bully, Video</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/22/bully-chokes-boy-unconscious-dillon-danis/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Everyone knows kids can be cruel, but nowhere was that more evident recently than in a video making the rounds on social media showing a boy getting choked out by an adolescent bully. Check out the horrific footage posted to X by MMA Fighter Dillon…</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 06:55:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ranking the Possible 2024 Stanley Cup Final Uniform Matchups</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/21/ranking-the-possible-2024-stanley-cup-final-uniform-matchups/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The 2024 Stanley Cup Playoffs are winding down, and with that comes a good sense of who will face off in this year’s Stanley Cup Final. At the moment, we’re left with just the Dallas Stars and Edmonton Oilers in the Western Conference and the Florida Panthers and New York</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 19:27:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cameron Brink Wants To Flaunt Body For S.I. Swimsuit Issue, 'Super Empowering'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/22/cameron-brink-sports-illustrated-swimsuit-issue/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>WNBA star Cameron Brink is waiting by the phone to get a call from the folks at Sports Illustrated ... revealing she'd love the opportunity to pose for the publication's famous swimsuit issue!! The L.A. Sparks rookie -- who recently graced the…</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 06:55:54 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>