<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 07:09:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>2024-25 College Football Uniform Preview: ACC Edition</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/21/2024-25-college-football-uniform-preview-acc-edition/college/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>We're taking a look at every uniform, logo and field change that has taken place across college football this offseason, starting with the ACC.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 06:04:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TikToker Kyle Marisa Roth Cause of Death Revealed</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/20/tiktoker-kyle-marisa-roth-cause-death/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>TikTok star Kyle Marisa Roth's cause of death has been revealed 4 months after her untimely passing shocked her followers ... with her autopsy report ruling her death as "natural." In new documents obtained by TMZ ... Maryland's Chief Medical…</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 07:09:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Midwest All-Stars, an MLB Team that Lasted Just One Game in 1970</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/19/the-midwest-all-stars-an-mlb-team-that-lasted-just-one-game-in-1970/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>What happens when a league’s schedule makers forget to include a team for an entire weekend? In 1970, the American League was forced to solve that exact problem when they inadvertently left the Boston Red Sox off the Grapefruit League schedule entirely over the weekend of March 7-8. Of course,</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 20:30:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alicia Silverstone Fans Concerned After She Munches On Poisonous Berry</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/20/alicia-silverstone-poisonous-berry/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>3:20 PM PT -- Alicia Silverstone confirmed she's still with us Tuesday afternoon, posting on Instagram, "Alive and well! Don’t worry… I didn’t swallow 😉😛" Alicia Silverstone had fans freaking out over her health ... with some even…</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 07:09:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NFL Second, Third Helmet Concept Series – AFC West</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/18/nfl-second-third-helmet-concept-series-afc-west/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Our newest concept series that creates second and/or third helmet designs for every NFL team continues with the AFC West.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 17:07:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Noor Alfallah Says Al Pacino's An 'Amazing' Father To Their Son, Unsure About Marriage</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/20/noor-alfallah-al-pacino-father-marriage/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Al Pacino's GF Noor Alfallah heaped some serious praise on the acting icon's fatherhood skills -- but don't be fooled ... 'cause her stance on not tying the knot anytime soon hasn't budged. We caught up with Noor in Beverly Hills Monday ... and…</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 07:09:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>First Look at the 2025 MLB Spring Training Logos</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/17/first-look-at-the-2025-mlb-spring-training-logos/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Is it that time of the year already? This week, Major League Baseball released its new official logos for its 2025 Spring Training schedule. This year’s logos for the annual six-week slate of exhibition games include an all-new primary mark, a slightly modified alternate design, and designs for both the</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 16:08:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hulk Hogan Jokes About Body-Slamming Kamala Harris</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/20/hulk-hogan-body-slam-kamala-harris/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Hulk Hogan is not turning down the temperature on political violence ... 'cause he's talking about performing one of his famous wrestling moves on Kamala Harris ... though he's blaming it on alcohol. The Hulkster was at the Thirsty Cowboy in…</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 07:09:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2024-25 European Football Kit Preview: Serie A</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/17/2024-25-european-football-kit-preview-serie-a/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>123rd season of top-flight soccer in Italy kicks off on Saturday, August 17, with defending champs Inter Milan taking on Genoa CFC</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kylie Jenner Poses in New Swimwear She Calls 'Sexiest Drop Yet'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/20/kylie-jenner-previews-new-swimsuit-release/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Kylie Jenner is reminding you summer isn't quite over, posing for a series of spicy pics ahead of what she calls ... her "sexiest" swimwear ever! The reality TV star revealed new swimsuit shots Monday and Tuesday for her upcoming Khy satin swimwear…</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 07:09:18 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>