<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 08:10:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Ohio State Exploring Selling Stadium Naming Rights, Jersey Advertisement Space</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/06/ohio-state-exploring-selling-stadium-naming-rights-jersey-advertisement-space/college/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Ohio State athletic director Ross Bjork said the Buckeyes are exploring selling the naming rights to Ohio Stadium and advertisement space on their jerseys.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 03:17:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>West Virginia Cop Resigns After Threatening To Shoot Woman In Viral Traffic Stop Video</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/06/west-virginia-cop-unemployed-threatening-shoot-woman-viral-traffic-stop/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>2:04 PM PT -- Ryan Umina, the attorney for the town of Monongah, tells TMZ ... Nathan Latham resigned this morning and the city is still investigating the incident. The Mayor of Monongah, JohnBoy Palmer, confirmed Nathan Lanham is no longer…</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 08:10:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Colorado Buffaloes’ New Football Jerseys Leaked By CTESPN</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/06/colorado-buffaloes-new-football-jerseys-leaked-by-ctespn/college/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Colorado is set to unveil new football uniforms ahead of the 2024 season, and former NFL wide receiver Antonio Brown gave us a sneak peek at the jersey design over the weekend.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 06:35:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Justin Timberlake Failed Field Sobriety Tests Before DWI Arrest: Police</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/06/justin-timberlake-failed-field-sobriety-tests-before-driving-while-intoxicated-arrest/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Justin Timberlake's lawyer may be convinced the singer wasn't intoxicated during his DWI arrest ... but new police documents paint a totally different picture of JT's state on June 18. In the documents ... the pop star verbally refused a…</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 08:10:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Premier League Away Kits Dominate Recent Unveilings From Around Europe</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/02/premier-league-away-kits-dominate-recent-unveilings-from-around-europe/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Clubs launching kits include Liverpool, Brighton, Fulham, Bournemouth, Nottingham Forest, Wolves, Le Havre, Stade de Reims, Montepellier, Roma, Parma, RB Leipzig, VFB Stuttgart, Girona</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 21:41:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gymnast MyKayla Skinner Says She's Received Death Threats Amid Simone Biles Feud</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/06/gymnast-mykayla-skinner-death-threats-simone-biles-feud/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Former Team USA gymnast MyKayla Skinner says she's been targeted with a ton of hate after Simone Biles shaded her on social media ... claiming her family has even received death threats amid the drama -- and she's begging for it all to stop.…</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 08:10:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Carolina Panthers Add 30th Season Logo To Jerseys</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/02/carolina-panthers-add-30th-season-logo-to-jerseys/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Carolina Panthers will celebrate their 30th season this fall with a commemorative logo, which they quietly unveiled back in May and added to their jerseys ahead of Thursday's Fan Fest at Clemson's Memorial Stadium.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 17:02:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Olympic Stars Share BTS Look Into 2024 Olympics In Paris</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/06/olympic-athletes-behind-scenes-social-media-photos/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Yes, you've seen the glory shots of the rough n' tough Olympians doin' their thang and shooting for Gold in Paris ... but through their own lens, the athletes have been sharing thrilling moments and we've specially selected the top-notch photos…</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 08:10:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Macon Some Changes: SPHL’s Mayhem Unveil New Suite of Logos</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/01/macon-some-changes-sphls-mayhem-unveil-new-suite-of-logos/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Primary logo once again depicts a Viking, only this time just the head with a red beard and eyebrows and wearing a shiny silver horned helmet</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 23:36:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kim Kardashian Seeks Restraining Order Against Alleged Stalker</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/06/kim-kardashian-seeks-restraining-order/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Kim Kardashian has a scary connection to Emma Roberts ... they both were victims of the same alleged stalker. Kim just filed legal docs, obtained by TMZ, asking a judge to grant a restraining order against Melvin Jeffery Conley. According to the…</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 08:10:17 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>