<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from multiple RSS sources, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 01:07:08 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>I Would Have Lost Our Investors $5.5 Million—What Would You Have Done In This Situation?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/i-nearly-lost-our-investors-5-million</link><description>What were you doing on the morning of Jan. 17, 2020? While the world was learning about a strange new virus approaching our shores, my business partner, Ben, and I […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 22:58:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ICONIQ Growth raises $5.75B seventh flagship fund</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/03/iconiq-raises-5-15b-toward-seventh-flagship-fund/</link><description>ICONIQ Growth has raised $5.21 billion across two funds associated with the seventh growth fund family, according to SEC filings. However, the firm’s actual fundraise was $5.75 billion, according to a source familiar with the firm.  The late-stage investment unit is a part of ICONIQ Capital, which launched in 2011 as a private office managing […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 22:38:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mississippi Lawmakers Considered Modest Public Defense Reforms. They Rejected All of Them.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/02/mississippi-public-defense-legislative-reforms</link><description>With its refusal to impose oversight or consistent standards in local defense, Mississippi risks falling further behind rest of the U.S., critics say.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What's Behind Major Rise in Heart Failure Deaths?</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/heart-disease/heart-failure/news/20240503/heart-failure-mortality-rate-continues-to-rise?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>After falling for over a decade, the death rate climbed for several years and now is about the same as in 1999.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 18:36:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The One Renovation Guaranteed to Increase ROI—No, It’s Not the Kitchen or Bathroom</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/renovations-guranteed-to-result-in-positive-roi</link><description>Gearing up for your first rehab? Whether it’s a flip or BRRRR, I’ve got earth-shattering news for you that will change everything you thought you knew about value-adds in real estate: If you’re trying […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 22:46:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Luminar cuts 20% of staff and outsources lidar production</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/03/luminar-layoffs-reduction-restructuring-lidar/</link><description>Lidar company Luminar is slashing its workforce by 20% and will lean harder on its contract manufacturing partner as part of a restructuring that will shift the company to a more “asset-light” business model, as it aims to scale production. The cuts will affect around 140 employees, and are starting immediately. Luminar is also cutting […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 22:34:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In This Police Youth Program, a Trail of Sexual Abuse Across the U.S.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/01/police-explorer-sexual-abuse-boy-scouts</link><description>Explorer posts, overseen by the Boy Scouts, are supposed to foster an interest in policing. They have faced nearly 200 allegations of misconduct.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 18:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jump-Start Your Exercise With This Mindset Reset</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/fitness-exercise/news/20240429/jump-start-exercise-with-this-mindset-reset?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>There are far more powerful motivators than “get abs!” to help you start an exercise routine you’ll stick to.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 18:25:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Mortgage Interest Deduction Is Overrated and Definitely Not Something to Fight Over</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/mortgage-interest-deduction-is-not-a-fight-worth-fighting</link><description>After the National Association of Realtors agreed to pay $418 million and eliminate the 6% commission to settle the lawsuit against it, attention in some quarters is now being turned to the mortgage interest deduction.  […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 22:33:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>X launches Stories, delivering news summarized by Grok AI</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/03/x-launches-stories-on-x-delivering-news-summarized-by-grok-ai/</link><description>X's Premium subscribers will be able to read a summary of posts on X associated with each trending story featured on the For You tab in Explore.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 21:14:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Campus Protests Could Shape the 2024 Elections — And Not Just the Presidency</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/30/campus-protests-gaza-arrests-prosecutors-elections</link><description>With hundreds of arrests and more campus standoffs looming, local law enforcement officials could face consequences at the ballot box.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 21:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When Does Old Age Start? It Depends on Who You Ask</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/news/20240502/when-does-old-age-start-many-disagree?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>The goalpost for old age has been moving. Until now.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 18:45:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Boost Your Cash Flow in 2024 with These “Self-Management” Tips</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-401</link><description>Want more cash flow with less stress while running your rental property portfolio? Then you need self-management! Amelia McGee and Grace Gudenkauf, seasoned investors and the minds behind BiggerPockets’ newest […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 07:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Match-owned Archer hits over half a million installs amid dating app slump</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/03/match-owned-archer-hits-over-half-a-million-installs-amid-dating-app-slump/</link><description>With Match and other online dating companies facing a downturn, Archer’s growth is certainly notable.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 20:43:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>They Killed Their Abusive Partners. Now Their Sentences Could Be Reconsidered.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/27/oklahoma-oregon-minnesota-domestic-violence</link><description>Oklahoma could re-examine how it punishes people whose crimes came after years of domestic abuse. Other states may follow.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prospects for Crohn's Relief Brighten With New Advancements</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/ibd-crohns-disease/crohns-disease/news/20240502/prospects-crohns-relief-brighten-with-new-advancements?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>More than 1 million Americans live with Crohn’s, a chronic and sometimes crippling bowel disease that affects the intestines and leads to digestive issues. But in 2024, breakthroughs could bring relief in different ways. Here's what to know.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 17:59:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Rational Investor’s Case Against Bitcoin</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-525</link><description>Cryptocurrency enthusiasts can’t fathom why Bitcoin will fail. If you tell them that you’re not investing in Bitcoin or other cryptos, they look at you like an uneducated investor, a […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 07:01:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Musk raises $6B for AI startup. Also, is TikTok dodging Apple’s commissions?</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/03/xai-billions-and-apple-vs-tiktok-startups-weekly/</link><description>Welcome to Startups Weekly — Haje’s weekly recap of everything you can’t miss from the world of startups. Sign up here to get it in your inbox every Friday. Musk’s 10-month-old baby, xAI, is closing in on a whoppin’ $6 billion funding round. The social network X, née Twitter — also part of Elon’s tech […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 20:05:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Being Trans in Prison Is Really Like</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/26/trans-prison-voices-gender-essay</link><description>Amid a wave of anti-trans legislation, and the violence that often follows, four people share their experiences in the criminal justice system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 11:00:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Truth or TV: Is Grey's Anatomy's Parkinson's 'Cure' Real?</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/parkinsons-disease/features/is-greys-anatomys-parkinsons-cure-real?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>How realistic is the Grey’s Anatomy episode that shows a Parkinson’s disease cure? A neurosurgery professor weighs in.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 08:17:35 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>