<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 01:01:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Book Review: Pause to Think</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/08/09/book-review-pause-to-think/</link><description>This book is direct, delightful, and articulate in suggesting that we take a slow rather than fast approach to getting things thoughtfully done. It touches the minds and hearts of investment professionals.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 12:59:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Iranians are creating fake websites and impersonating activists to create chaos in the U.S., Microsoft found</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/08/09/iranians-are-creating-fake-news-websites-impersonating-activists-chaos-microsoft/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/GettyImages-2153349224-e1723252665431.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Microsoft's report revealed its findings that suggest Iran is evolving its tactics for another election that’s likely to have global implications.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 02:21:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is Illiquidity a Blessing in Disguise for Some Investors?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/08/07/is-illiquidity-a-blessing-in-disguise-for-some-investors/</link><description>Rather than running away from illiquidity, investment professionals, investors, and regulators alike should recognize its potential benefits and consider a more balanced approach.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 17:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Customer service chatbots are buggy and disliked by consumers. Can AI make them better?</title><link>https://fortune.com/asia/2024/08/09/ai-chatbots-customers-service-accenture-zurich-lenovo-brainstorm-ai-singapore/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/53892573781_4f4b44b97a_o-e1723243509145.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Speakers at Fortune Brainstorm AI Singapore shared how how they're already using AI to make customer service faster and more useful.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 00:06:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scenario Planning, Foresight, and the Power of Imagination: Navigating an Uncertain Future</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/08/05/scenario-planning-foresight-and-the-power-of-imagination-navigating-an-uncertain-future/</link><description>By fostering resilience through the consideration of various outcomes, investment practitioners can better anticipate and manage the complexities and disruptions that characterize today's dynamic environment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 17:28:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>VoePass plane suddenly drops from the sky and crashes in Brazil, killing all 61 on board</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/08/09/voepass-plane-crash-brazil-killing-61-atr-72-turboprop/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/GettyImages-2165576250-e1723240636125.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The aircraft involved in the crash was an ATR 72 model, a twin-engine turboprop model that typically seats about 70 people. ATR is a joint venture between Airbus SE and Italy’s Leonardo SpA.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 23:08:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Private Equity: In Essence, Plunder?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/08/02/private-equity-in-essence-plunder/</link><description>To understand what private equity is at its worst is a call to action, personally and professionally.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 16:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Railroad giant threatens to revoke workers’ hard-won schedule improvements</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/08/09/union-pacific-railroad-threatens-schedules/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/GettyImages-1464687858-e1723240002797.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The $145 billion Union Pacific railroad offered paid sick days for the first time last year and they helped make the attendance system more manageable, but not being able to plan on their days off still takes a toll on engineers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 22:56:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Small Caps, Large Caps, and Interest Rates</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/08/01/small-caps-large-caps-and-interest-rates/</link><description>The relationship between stocks and interest rates is not reliably stable. There are periods when equities are highly rate sensitive, and periods when they aren't.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 12:39:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden reverses policy on weapons sales to Saudi Arabia as Mideast war upends U.S. priorities</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/08/09/joe-biden-weapons-sales-saudi-arabia-israel-hamas-war-precision-guided-munitions/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/GettyImages-1241918344-e1723238139266.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Saudi Arabia is now deemed too important to US goals to end the Israel-Hamas war and in the growing conflict with Iran and its proxies.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 22:31:25 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>