<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 06:55:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>An Apparent Leak of the New Anaheim Ducks Uniforms &amp; Logo?</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/18/apparent-leak-of-new-anaheim-ducks-uniforms-logo/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Just one day after the Anaheim Ducks dropped a tantalizing teaser, an eager Reddit user may have spoiled the party. Thanks to a few dozen folks sending me messages, we learned that earlier today, Reddit user The_Illa_Vanilla posted an image to the Reddit/Hockey boards purportedly showing the new Anaheim Ducks</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 21:50:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Howie Mandel Says Wife Wasn't Drunk In Vegas Accident, Was High on Weed Gummies</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/18/howie-mandel-wife-accident-las-vegas-weed-gummies-tipsy-hotel/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Howie Mandel is setting the record straight on his wife's "tipsy" fall in Las Vegas, which left her in a pool of blood ... he says she wasn't drunk, she was just feeling the effects of some marijuana gummies!!! The "America's Got Talent" judge…</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 06:55:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Baltimore Ravens Add New Purple and Gold Helmet</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/18/baltimore-ravens-add-new-purple-and-gold-helmet/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Purple will reign in Baltimore this fall. The Baltimore Ravens just announced their new alternate ‘Purple Rising’ helmet, to be worn for one game this upcoming season. The shell is purple, with two gold stripes going down the middle and a gold facemask. The team’s wordmark is on the front</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 15:37:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Christina Ricci Selling L.A. Area Home for $2.2 Million</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/18/christina-ricci-selling-los-angeles-home-for-sale/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Christina Ricci is unloading her Los Angeles area home -- and she's aiming to double her earnings with the price tag. The actress listed her Woodland Hills, CA home Monday ... and if you have an extra couple million (and change) lying around, the…</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 06:55:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anaheim Ducks Drop a Mighty Good Teaser</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/17/anaheim-ducks-drop-a-mighty-good-teaser/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Anaheim Ducks today posted a teaser graphic that teases a potential new Mighty Ducks of Anaheim themed uniform. Posted to their various social media channels, the teaser shows a closeup of the eye of the mask from the club’s original Mighty Ducks logo but with some subtle modernizations. Unfortunately,</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 22:39:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Justin Timberlake Still Planning to Perform in Chicago Despite DWI Arrest</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/18/justin-timberlake-still-planning-perform-chicago-despite-dwi-arrest/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Justin Timberlake isn't shying away from the spotlight following his DWI arrest -- in fact, he's stepping right into it later this week ... 'cause he's all set to perform in the Windy City. Sources with direct knowledge tell TMZ ... JT will, in…</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 06:55:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Uruguay Launches First Home and Away Kits Under New Nike Deal</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/17/uruguay-launches-first-home-and-away-kits-under-new-nike-deal/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Kits are not yet available for retail purchase; AUF warns that any shirts out there are fakes and they will take "necessary legal action" against counterfeiters</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 20:53:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tommy Richman Laughs Off Funkmaster Flex Dissing 'Million Dollar Baby'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/18/tommy-richman-million-dollar-baby-funkmaster-flex-coyote-album/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Tommy Richman's breakout hit "Million Dollar Baby" isn't winning over Funkmaster Flex -- one of NYC's biggest DJs and gatekeepers -- but, luckily, Tommy has more than one song, and holds no grudges! TMZ Hip Hop caught up with the buzzing…</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 06:55:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TCU Horned Frogs Unveil New, Simplified Football Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/17/tcu-horned-frogs-unveil-new-simplified-football-uniforms/college/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>TCU unveiled new uniforms on Monday morning, simplifying the design the Horned Frogs have worn since 2019.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 20:06:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Conor McGregor Not In Rehab, Chael Sonnen's Claim 'Incorrect'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/18/conor-mcgregor-not-in-rehab-chael-sonnen-claim-incorrect/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Conor McGregor is NOT currently receiving treatment for substance abuse, despite Chael Sonnen suggesting otherwise ... 'cause a rep for the UFC superstar tells TMZ Sports he's not in rehab. The American Gangster dropped the bombshell allegation on…</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 06:55:45 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>