<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 06:40:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>BiggerNews: The Fed Is Finally Ready to Cut Rates, but How Low Will They Go?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-1017</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>The next Fed meeting is crucial for real estate investors and the economy. So, what will the Fed do? Are we getting the 0.25% rate cut that many experts predict, […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 10:00:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SoftBank-backed Delhivery contests metrics in rival Ecom Express’ IPO filing</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/13/softbank-backed-delhivery-contests-metrics-in-rival-ecom-express-ipo-filing/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Indian logistics firm Delhivery has publicly contested the accuracy of metrics presented by competitor Ecom Express in its draft initial public offering prospectus, a rare confrontation in the lead-up to the latter’s market debut. Delhivery, which is backed by SoftBank and already publicly listed, claims that Ecom Express has inaccurately represented Delhivery’s business metrics when […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 11:09:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Not ‘Mini-Adult Court’: Lawyers Lacking Qualifications Defended 1,200 Cuyahoga County Kids</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/09/12/cuyahoga-juvenile-courts-appointed-public-defender</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Juvenile Court judges will now track qualifications, but insist the state system creates barriers keeping experienced attorneys from defending kids.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rookie Reply: The Best Property Types and Amenities for Short-Term Rentals</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-457</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Analyzing Airbnbs is tough, especially for a new investor. Which properties make the best vacation rentals? Which amenities should you prioritize? Do you need an exit strategy if things go […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 10:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alternative app stores will be allowed on Apple iPad in the EU from September 16</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/13/alternative-app-stores-allowed-on-the-ipad-in-the-eu-starting-september-16/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>It was a matter of time, but Apple is going to allow third-party app stores on the iPad starting next week, on September 16. This change will occur with the next major release of iPadOS, the operating system specifically designed for the iPad. The move is related to the European Union’s Digital Markets Act (DMA), […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 10:50:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>She Ate a Poppy Seed Salad Just Before Giving Birth. Then They Took Her Baby Away.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/09/09/drug-test-pregnancy-pennsylvania-california</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Hospitals use drug tests that return false positives from poppy seed bagels, decongestants and Zantac. Yet newborns are being taken from parents based on the results.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Aren’t More “Normal” People Achieving FIRE?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-563</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Has BiggerPockets Money become too focused on FIRE (financial independence, retire early)? For the past seven years, we’ve been bringing you shows highlighting the journeys of those who left their […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 07:01:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Three and Vodafone’s $19B merger hits the skids as UK rules the deal would adversely impact customers and MVNOs</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/13/three-and-vodafones-19b-merger-hits-the-skids-as-uk-rules-the-deal-is/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>The U.K.’s antitrust regulator has delivered its provisional ruling in a longstanding battle to combine two of the country’s major telecommunication operators. The Competition and Markets Authority (CMA) says that Three and Vodafone’s planned $19 billion merger — announced 15 months ago — could lead to higher prices for consumers, diminished service such as smaller […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 08:18:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Seemingly Endless Cycle of Reforms in Juvenile Justice</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/09/07/the-seemingly-endless-cycle-of-reforms-in-juvenile-justice</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>As Ohio considers closing youth detention facilities, recent efforts in other states have hit roadblocks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Would You Vote for Any of These Market-Changing Economic Policies?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-251</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>No matter who wins your vote during the presidential debates, odds are, the housing market will still have its problems. We’ve got high building costs, low inventory, and slow bureaucratic […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 10:00:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oprah just had an AI special with Sam Altman and Bill Gates — here are the highlights</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/12/ophah-just-had-an-ai-special-with-sam-altman-and-bill-gates-here-are-the-highlights/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Late Thursday evening, Oprah Winfrey aired a special on AI, appropriately titled “AI and the Future of Us.” Guests included OpenAI CEO Sam Altman, tech influencer Marques Brownlee, and current FBI director Christopher Wray. The dominant tone was one of skepticism — and wariness. Oprah noted in prepared remarks that the AI genie is out […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 05:03:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>You’re About to Deliver Your Baby. This Faulty Drug Test Could Take Your Newborn Away.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/09/07/drug-test-hospital-pregnancy</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Listen to our investigation into how hospitals use unreliable test results to report parents to child welfare agencies.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 08:01:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Eviction Diversion Programs Are Driving Rates (and Costs) Down</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/how-eviction-diversion-programs-are-driving-eviction-rates-down</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>If there’s a downside to investing in real estate, it’s dealing with nonpaying tenants. Many people prefer to put their money in the stock market because even with diligent screening, […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 22:04:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>XP Health grabs $32M to bring employees more affordable vision care</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/12/xp-health-grabs-32m-to-bring-employees-more-affordable-vision-care/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Antonio Moraes, the grandson of a late prominent Brazilian billionaire, was never interested in joining the family-owned conglomerate of construction companies and a bank. Shortly after graduating from college, he founded one of Brazil’s first impact funds, which invested primarily in companies that made healthcare more accessible and affordable. But while attending Stanford University, where […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 00:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Serious Case of Prison Visit Blues</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/09/06/tariq-maqbool-prison-visit-pandemic-covid-19</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Tariq MaQbool reflects on disruptive COVID-era visitation restrictions that remain in effect at New Jersey State Prison.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>