<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from multiple RSS sources, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:15:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The BEST Ways to Protect Your Rental Property and Keep Your Tenants Safe</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-397</link><description>If you own a rental property, it’s YOUR responsibility to provide a safe environment for tenants. This starts with things like tenant screening, security upgrades, and most importantly, acting swiftly […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:02:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nvidia acquires AI workload management startup Run:ai</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/24/nvidia-acquires-ai-workload-management-startup-runai/</link><description>Nvidia is acquiring Run:ai, a Tel Aviv-based company that makes it easier for developers and operations teams to manage and optimize their AI hardware infrastructure, for an undisclosed sum. Ctech reported earlier this morning the companies were in “advanced negotiations” that could see Nvidia pay upwards of $1 billion for Run:ai. Evidently, negotiations went on […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:02:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Enduring Use of Solitary, and New Proposed Limits That Will Likely Fail (Again)</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/20/solitary-confinement-reform-oklahoma-washington-florida</link><description>Isolation’s damaging effects are widely known. But many facilities confine people — even youth — virtually all day, sometimes in shower stalls.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Misconceptions About Genomic Tests</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/cancer/features/genomic-testing-misconceptions?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>There's a lot of confusion about the purpose of genomic tests. Find out how to separate fact from fiction.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 22:28:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Building Wealth with OLD Homes and How to Keep Tenants for Longer</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-942</link><description>How do you find investment properties nobody else is looking for—the ones with cash flow potential, equity upside, and wealth-building qualities all the other investors overlook? Simple: buy what nobody […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:02:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Security bugs in a popular phone-tracking app exposed users’ precise locations</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/24/security-flaws-isharing-tracking-app-exposed-millions-precise-locations/</link><description>The location-sharing app iSharing, which has 35 million users, fixed vulnerabilities that exposed users' personal information and precise location data.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:01:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Officials Failed to Act When COVID Hit Prisons. A New Study Shows the Deadly Cost.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/18/covid-prison-deaths-data</link><description>People in prison died at 3.4 times the rate of the free population, with the oldest hit hardest. New data holds lessons for preventing future deaths.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Where Will the Legit Health Info Go If TikTok Goes Dark?</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/a-to-z-guides/news/20240423/what-happens-to-legit-health-info-if-tiktok-banned?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>If TikTok goes dark, it could render unavailable the work of those who have made the site a go-to for expert- and user-generated videos on topics that cover the spectrum of consumer health.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 19:21:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Investor’s Guide to a Single-Family Rental Emergency Fund</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/the-investors-guide-to-a-single-family-rental-emergency-fund</link><description>As real estate investors, your emergency funds are a critical line of defense against unexpected costs. It prevents you from dipping into your budget to handle them. But what should you really use an emergency fund […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 19:23:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Block lets Square merchants convert a part of their daily sales to bitcoin</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/24/block-now-lets-square-merchants-convert-a-part-of-their-daily-sales-to-bitcoin/</link><description>Block, the company behind Square, Cash App and other services, announced a new program today allowing merchants using Square’s solutions to convert a percentage of their daily sales to bitcoin. The feature, rolling out in the U.S. starting today, will transfer 1-10% of Square sellers’ daily sales to their personal Cash App account. This amount […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:00:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Parents Paying for Their Children’s Crimes</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/13/michigan-school-shooting-parents</link><description>Experts warn about a wave of legal consequences for parents like the Crumbleys, while some states consider prosecutions for kids as young as 10.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are 'Man Vans' Coming to a Parking Lot Near You Soon?</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/prostate-cancer/news/20240422/prostate-cancer-screening-goes-mobile?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>"Game Changer Vehicles" – mobile medical units in a roving RV – are helping to bring cancer screening to where it's needed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 19:18:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seeing Greene: Are Home Warranties Worth It &amp; When to Pay Off Debt vs. Invest?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-941</link><description>Should you pay off debt or invest? Many online financial gurus would tell you in a heartbeat that paying off debt is the number one priority…but is that always true? […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 07:02:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Diddo’s new funding will bring its shoppable TV API to streaming platforms</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/24/diddos-new-funding-will-bring-its-shoppable-tv-api-to-streaming-platforms/</link><description>Diddo is an API for streaming services and other platforms to integrate shoppable video, enabling consumers to buy their favorite characters’ clothing and accessories directly on their screens. The company announced Wednesday that it raised $2.8 million in seed funding. Diddo was founded in late 2022 by Rishi Nair, Ryan Sullivan, and Pamela Chen. Funnily […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:00:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I Had a Tough Job at My Brooklyn Jail: Keeping Men From Taking Their Own Lives</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/12/brooklyn-jail-suicide-prevention-aide</link><description>As a suicide prevention aide, I had to make sure my fellow detainees didn’t harm themselves. It was surprisingly easy to get such a complex job.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chronic Spontaneous Urticaria: What to Know</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/features/urticaria-chronic-spontaneous?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>What you should know about chronic spontaneous urticaria (CSU), including symptoms, triggers, treatment, and a link to autoimmune disease.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 14:35:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Get PAID to Live in an Affordable City &amp; Fast-Track Financial Freedom</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-522</link><description>Moving is hard. But could relocating to a low-cost-of-living area help you lead a more fulfilling life and achieve financial freedom? As today’s guest came to find out, the benefits […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 07:01:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spotify submits a new update to Apple with pricing information for EU users</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/24/spotify-submits-a-new-update-to-apple-with-pricing-information-for-eu-users/</link><description>Spotify said today that it has submitted a new version of its app for EU users with pricing information and basic site information. Critically, the version doesn’t contain the link to the website. The music streaming company said it is not opting into Apple’s new Digital Markets Act (DMA) changes that charge a “core technology […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:56:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Supreme Court Case on Homelessness May Limit Prisoner Rights and Expand Executions</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/10/supreme-court-homeless-grants-pass-originalism</link><description>In Grants Pass v. Johnson, a town in Oregon asks the court to reconsider what constitutes “cruel and unusual punishments.”</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CSU: What to Wear and What to Avoid</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/features/what-to-wear-with-csu?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Find out what’s best to wear to prevent and manage chronic spontaneous urticaria (CSU), also called chronic hives.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 14:35:33 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>