<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 06:49:40 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>How to Find, Evaluate, and Offer on Rental Properties in 2024</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-no-number-3</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Want financial freedom through real estate? Then, you’ll need to know how to buy a rental property. Don’t worry; even as a beginner, you can take three basic steps to […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 07:02:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>India’s WazirX confirms security breach following a $230M ‘suspicious transfer’</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/18/indias-wazirx-confirms-security-breach-after-230-million-suspicious-transfer/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The Mumbai-based firm said one of its multisig wallets had suffered a security breach, and it was temporarily pausing all withdrawals from the platform. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 10:19:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meet the New Generation of Unarmed First Responders in this New Podcast Series.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/18/police-north-carolina-podcast-mental-health</link><description>“The Fifth Branch,” a podcast from The Marshall Project and Tradeoffs, examines new, alternative ways to respond to 911 crisis calls.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>These Are the Passive Investments I’m Most Excited About Right Now</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/passive-real-estate-investments-im-investing-in-right-now</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>With so many ways to invest in real estate today, finding the right path for you can be tough. Take a look at what Brian is considering.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 20:42:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Samsung to acquire UK-based knowledge graph startup Oxford Semantic Technologies</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/18/samsung-to-acquire-uk-based-knowledge-graph-startup-oxford-semantic-technologies/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The Korean tech giant is acquiring Oxford Semantic Technologies, a U.K.-based knowledge graph startup that has built an AI reasoning engine. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 10:14:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What We Know From Sen. J.D. Vance’s Legislative Action on Criminal Justice Issues</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/17/what-we-know-from-sen-j-d-vance-s-legislative-action-on-criminal-justice-issuessen-j-d-vance-s-bills-target-campus-protests-immigration-and-abortion</link><description>On immigration and criminal justice, Vance has defended and legislated former President Donald Trump’s policy goals.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 23:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Loan Modifications Are Bringing 3% Interest Rates Back, Even for Residential Real Estate</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/new-loan-modifications-bring-three-percent-rates-back</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Yes, investment properties can qualify for the program if they meet certain requirements.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 20:15:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Artificial Agency raises $16M to use AI to make NPCs feel more realistic in video games</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/18/artificial-agency-raises-video-game-npcs-ai/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>A team of former Google DeepMind researchers are betting that their unique behavior engine for NPCs will make games more fun and dynamic. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How a Supreme Court Ruling Could Affect a Case Involving Police Abuse of Youth</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/13/supreme-court-bankruptcy-sackler-boy-scouts</link><description>Another court must now decide how the landmark ruling will impact the Boy Scouts abuse settlement, which involves victims of police sexual abuse.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden Proposes Rent Increase Limits, With Penalties for Landlords Who Don’t Listen</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/biden-proposes-rent-increase-caps-at-five-percent</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Also in the proposal is a push for 15,000 affordable housing units and increased development in Las Vegas.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 19:43:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Israel’s startup scene shows reslience despite nine months of war</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/18/israels-startup-scene-shows-reslience-despite-nine-months-of-war/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>When the war between Israel and Hamas broke out last October, we examined its potential impact on the tech ecosystems in Israel and Palestine. Nine months later, the prevailing sentiment in Israel, based on my conversation with founders and investors, is that the conflict has made the startup and VC ecosystem more resilient, especially its […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 08:12:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jackson, Mississippi, Wants Curfew Centers to Cut Crime. Here’s What Other Cities Learned.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/09/jackson-mississippi-youth-curfew-centers</link><description>After a teen’s murder, city officials hope a curfew and youth centers will get kids off the street. Young people are skeptical.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 11:00:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Million-Dollar Real Estate Business YOU Can Start Today with Just $150</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-433</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Starting a real estate business is one of the best ways to achieve financial freedom, replace your W2 income, and leave your nine-to-five. Why? Because you don’t need a ton […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 07:02:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deel acquires Hofy to build its own IT device management service</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/18/deel-acquires-hofy-to-build-its-own-it-device-management-service/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Both of Hofy's co-founders, Sami Bouremoum and Michael Ginzo, along with the rest of the startup's leadership team and 120 employees, are joining Deel to build Deel IT. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Love Beyond Bars: Miguel and Silvia</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/05/photo-essay-wrongful-conviction-love-story</link><description>While Miguel Solorio did 25 years for a crime he didn’t commit, his wife, Silvia, was right by his side. Here’s their California love story in pictures.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>