<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 23:49:01 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Book Review: Trailblazers, Heroes, and Crooks</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/26/book-review-trailblazers-heroes-and-crooks/</link><description>Stephen Foerster, CFA, extracts lessons from exceptional episodes in financial history that ordinary investors and seasoned professionals alike can put to profitable use. The bonus is that you'll be entertained from start to finish.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Activist hedge fund Elliott bets $1 billion on British platinum producer</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/26/activist-hedge-fund-elliott-paul-singer-british-platinum/</link><description>The activist hedge fund led by Paul Singer has exposure to almost 33.6 million Anglo American shares via derivatives, per a filing.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 01:59:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Price Risk? Unpacking the Equity Risk Premium</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/24/what-price-risk-unpacking-the-equity-risk-premium/</link><description>Stocks are a good wager over the long term, on favorable odds. But stocks remain a bet, and investors must grasp how much returns can vary over long time horizons.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pottery Barn parent Williams-Sonoma fined for marketing its furniture as 'crafted' in the U.S. when it was actually made in China</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/26/pottery-barn-williams-sonoma-china-furniture/</link><description>In addition to paying a penalty, the company will be required to submit annual compliance reports, the FTC said.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 01:35:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Equity Income Investing Redux</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/22/equity-income-investing-redux/</link><description>No doubt the past year has been difficult for equity income investors. But history, inherent biases, mean reversion, and the current market backdrop point to a comeback.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 17:19:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Philadelphia-based Republic Bank implodes in first failure of the year</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/26/philadelphia-bank-implodes-failure/</link><description>Republic First Bank had roughly $6 billion in assets and $4 billion in deposits as of Jan. 31.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 01:12:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: Enrich Your Future</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/18/book-review-enrich-your-future/</link><description>This engaging book is simultaneously memorable and humorous. The numerous sports analogies will have you smiling as you absorb Larry Swedroe's unforgettable investment precepts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 18:07:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The top 5 books these mental health experts say will help you combat burnout at work and build healthy habits</title><link>https://fortune.com/well/article/self-help-books-work-stress-burnout/</link><description>What to read when you're feeling overwhelmed at work.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CAPE Is High: Should You Care?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/17/cape-is-high-should-you-care/</link><description>A simple analysis shows that Robert Shiller's cyclically adjusted price-to-earnings ratio changed in the 1990s and that mean-reversion concerns may be misplaced. If CAPE changed three decades ago, however, there is nothing preventing it from doing so again.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 15:18:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Billionaire Miami Dolphins owner wants South Florida to be more like Manhattan—'I still love a challenge'</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/26/billionaire-miami-dolphins-owner-florida-manhattan/</link><description>“I want to make West Palm a model city for the country," said Related Cos. founder, Stephen Ross.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 00:43:54 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>