<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 06:56:24 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Opportunities in the Evolving Cannabis Consumption Market</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/08/13/the-changing-nature-of-cannabis-consumption/</link><description>For investors in the space, the changing cannabis consumption landscape opens challenges and opportunities in product creation, marketing, and targeting new consumer groups.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:46:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wizz Air bets on unlimited flights for €499 to woo frugal passengers, but there’s a catch</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/08/15/wizz-air-bets-on-unlimited-flights-for-e499-to-woo-frugal-passengers-but-theres-a-catch/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/GettyImages-2157754851-e1723716422227.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The ailrine is launching a first-of-its-kind model in Europe, but buyers should beware of the conditions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 11:11:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From Sandpiles to Angel Investments</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/08/12/from-sandpiles-to-angel-investments/</link><description>The presence of power law returns in angel investing, with the potential for significant contributions from a handful of investments, has implications for portfolio construction, investment strategies, and diversification.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 13:19:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jamie Dimon wants to hit millionaires with the ‘Buffett Rule’ to tackle national debt</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/08/15/jamie-dimon-warren-buffett-rule-tax-income-national-debt/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/GettyImages-1806232655-e1723714165622.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>'The Buffett Rule' was coined after the Berkshire Hathaway CEO highlighted he pays the same percentage share of income tax as his secretary Debbie Bosanek.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 10:54:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: Pause to Think</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/08/09/book-review-pause-to-think/</link><description>This book is direct, delightful, and articulate in suggesting that we take a slow rather than fast approach to getting things thoughtfully done. It touches the minds and hearts of investment professionals.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 12:59:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The American Dream is collapsing, and it’s knocking billionaires off their pedestals</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/08/15/the-american-dream-is-collapsing-and-its-knocking-billionaires-off-their-pedestals/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/GettyImages-1410297049-e1723670108219.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Americans are souring on the wealthy, calling them to task amidst surging inequality.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 10:11:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is Illiquidity a Blessing in Disguise for Some Investors?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/08/07/is-illiquidity-a-blessing-in-disguise-for-some-investors/</link><description>Rather than running away from illiquidity, investment professionals, investors, and regulators alike should recognize its potential benefits and consider a more balanced approach.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 17:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mystery of Stonehenge deepens as scientists discover altar stone was hauled 750 kilometers from Scotland: The question is how?</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/08/15/mystery-of-stonehenge-deepens-as-scientists-discover-altar-stone-was-hauled-750-kilometers-from-scotland/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/GettyImages-521905633-e1723712150629.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The Neolithic circle of giant stones has been a source of wonder and mystery for nearly 5,000 years.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 10:08:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scenario Planning, Foresight, and the Power of Imagination: Navigating an Uncertain Future</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/08/05/scenario-planning-foresight-and-the-power-of-imagination-navigating-an-uncertain-future/</link><description>By fostering resilience through the consideration of various outcomes, investment practitioners can better anticipate and manage the complexities and disruptions that characterize today's dynamic environment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 17:28:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Donald Trump’s economic pitch derailed by off-message rants at North Carolina rally</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/08/15/donald-trump-economic-pitch-north-carolina-rally/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/GettyImages-2166178746-e1723712893576.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The former president mixed pledges to slash energy prices and “unleash economic abundance” with familiar off-script tangents on Kamala Harris’ laugh, and President Joe Biden’s son.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 10:08:51 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>