<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 13:06:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Demand for Rentals is Rebounding as Affordability Begins to Improve w/Jay Parsons</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-228</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Downward pressure on rent prices is causing a “cascade” effect across all unit types. Whether you live in a luxury apartment or budget-friendly multifamily building on a busy street, you’ve […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 07:02:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Emergence thinks it can crack the AI agent code</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/24/emergence-thinks-it-can-crack-the-ai-agent-code/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Yet another generative AI venture has raised a bundle of money. And, like the others before it, it’s promising the moon. Emergence, whose co-founders include Satya Nitta, the former head of global AI solutions at IBM’s research division, on Monday emerged from stealth with $97.2 million in funding from Learn Capital plus credit lines totaling […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Death Row Prisoner’s Parting Interview</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/24/texas-death-row-prisoner-final-interview</link><description>Days before his scheduled execution in Texas, Ramiro Gonzales speaks on faith, legacy — and apologizing to the family of his victim, Bridget Townsend.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Federal Experts Talk Bird Flu ‘What Ifs’ in WebMD Live Event</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/cold-and-flu/news/20240516/federal-experts-talk-bird-flu-what-ifs?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>WebMD brought together experts from four federal agencies to talk prevention, monitoring, and what the “what ifs” of bird flu might look like.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:50:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Start Mobile Home Investing (The Right Way) for Just $15,000</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-976</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Can you start investing in real estate with just $15,000? Yep, and mobile home investing is how you do it. We know what you’re thinking, “I don’t want to own […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 07:02:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OpenAI buys a remote collaboration platform</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/24/openai-buys-a-remote-collaboration-platform/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>OpenAI is on an M&amp;A tear. Days after acquiring database tech firm Rockset, OpenAI has purchased Multi (previously Remotion), a startup developing a enterprise-focused, video-first collaboration platform. A source familiar with the matter says that the deal is technically an acquihire and that most of Multi’s team — around five people — will join OpenAI […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 17:27:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The New Battle Over an Old Institution: Forced Prison Labor</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/22/prison-slavery-forced-labor-lawsuits-bills</link><description>Inside the latest legal and legislative efforts to close state constitutional loopholes that allow slavery as punishment for a crime.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What’s Next in Health Care for Older Adults: Questions and Answers With John Whyte, MD</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/blog-aging-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>As WebMD’s chief medical officer, John Whyte, MD, is in a unique position to see both the current state of medical care for America’s older adults and the way things are trending for the future. We asked him to share his insight on a few topics, along with a bit of advice.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:29:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Making $15K/Year &amp; Living with His Mom to 5 Deals in 5 Years with LOW Money</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-423</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>You DON’T need a ton of money to find and fund real estate deals. Despite earning just $15,000 per year, today’s guest found the perfect property for him and scrounged […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 07:02:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Car dealership outages drag on after CDK cyberattacks</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/24/car-dealership-outages-drag-on-after-cdk-cyberattack/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Car dealerships and auto shops around the U.S. enter a second week of disruption following cyberattacks at software maker CDK. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 16:00:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mississippi Wants to Allow Some Votes From Jails and Prisons. Red Tape May Stop It.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/20/mississippi-voting-from-prison-and-jails</link><description>A new state law will allow more people in jails and prisons to cast absentee ballots, but many obstacles remain.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Get the Care You Need in a COVID-19 World</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/covid-senior-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>What to expect at the doctor’s office, hospitals, and long-term care facilities, the future of telemedicine, and how to get the best care during COVID-19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 19:50:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What to Do When a Tenant Violates the Lease: A Landlord’s Guide</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/what-to-do-when-a-tenant-violates-the-lease</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Learn what to do when a tenant violates the lease. This guide covers common violations, step-by-step handling, and prevention strategies for landlords.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 01:35:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Matt Rogers, Nest and Mill co-founder, talks mastering consumer tech at Disrupt 2024</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/24/matt-rogers-nest-and-mill-co-founder-talks-mastering-consumer-tech-at-disrupt-2024/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Consumer technology is hard, but few people have mastered it as well as Matt Rogers, co-founder of Nest and now Mill, his new startup that promises to turn your table scraps into planet-saving treasure. Mill burst out of the gate last year after spending some time in stealth refining its waste bin, an easy to […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Minneapolis Cop Who Beat Him Pleaded Guilty. He Still Fears the Department Won’t Change.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/16/police-minneapolis-beating-jaleel-stallings</link><description>Jaleel Stallings was swept up in the chaos of protests over George Floyd’s murder. The outcome changed his life.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Personal Shopper: A Savvy Black Entrepreneur Guides You to Eczema-Friendly Clothes, Creams, Cosmetics, and More</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/savvy-black-entrepreneur-guides-eczema-friendly-clothes-creams-cosmetics?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>A savvy black entrepreneur guides you on an eczema-friendly shopping spree.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:54:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Airbnb’s Algorithm: How Often Should You Update Your Listing?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/how-often-should-you-update-your-airbnb-listing</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Is there a way to game Airbnb's algorithm?</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 15:54:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Google is bringing Gemini access to teens using their school accounts</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/24/google-is-bringing-gemini-access-to-teens-using-their-school-accounts/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Google announced on Monday that it’s bringing its AI technology Gemini to teen students using their school accounts, after having already offered Gemini to teens using their personal accounts. The company is also giving educators access to new tools alongside this release. Google says that giving teens access to Gemini can help prepare them with the […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 15:55:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>More States Restricting ‘Excited Delirium’ as Cause of Death in Police Custody</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/15/police-custody-excited-delirium-meaning</link><description>Authorities use the term to describe the condition of some people who die. But some medical organizations say it’s useless or racist pseudoscience.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Behind the Spike in Colorectal Cancer Among Young Americans</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/colorectal-cancer/news/20240515/behind-the-spike-in-colorectal-cancer-cases?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Colorectal cancer cases increased a whopping 333% among 15- to 19-year-olds and 185% among 20- to 24-year-olds from 1999 to 2020.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:59:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>