<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:43:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>He’s Back! AHL’s Bridgeport Islanders Revive Fisherman For New Primary Logo</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/11/hes-back-ahls-bridgeport-islanders-revive-fisherman-for-new-primary-logo/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>AHL affiliate of the New York Islanders borrow one of their parent club's most infamous logos and make a few changes to come up with their new look</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 20:47:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Barack Obama Daps Up Team USA With Hilarious 'Key &amp; Peele' Style Handshakes</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/11/barack-obama-daps-up-team-usa-key-and-peele-style-handshakes-nba-olympics/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Barack Obama's living in a 'Key &amp; Peele' skit ... the former President reenacted one of their most hilarious bits as #44 showed love to LeBron James and Team USA! If you haven't seen it (shame on you!), Jordan Peele, portraying Obama in the…</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:43:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Charly Launches New Kits for 5 Liga MX Clubs, Including Bespoke Shirts for Women’s Teams</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/11/charly-launches-new-kits-for-5-liga-mx-clubs-including-bespoke-shirts-for-womens-teams/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Liga MX teams outfitted by sportswear brand include Club Santos Laguna, Club León, Atlas FC, CF Pachuca and Xolos de Tijuana</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 18:22:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Uruguay's Darwin Núñez Brawls With Fans In Stands After Copa América Game</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/11/uruguay-darwin-nunez-brawls-fans-in-stands-after-copa-america-game/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>The ending of the Uruguay vs. Colombia Copa América game took an ugly turn ... as Darwin Núñez was so furious with some opposing fans, he actually rushed into the stands to brawl with them. The wild scene happened at Bank of America Stadium in…</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:43:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Women’s 3-on-3 Basketball League Unveils  Logo</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/10/new-womens-3-on-3-basketball-league-unveils-logo/basketball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Unrivaled league will feature six teams of five players each playing compressed full-court 3-on-3 games in Miami starting in January 2025</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:10:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Barack Obama was Given Heads-Up about George Clooney's Biden Op-Ed</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/11/barack-obama-notified-george-clooney-new-york-times-step-down-joe-biden/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Barack Obama was notified beforehand George Clooney's shocking op-ed was going to be published in the New York Times, encouraging Joe Biden to drop out of the 2024 presidential race, according to a new report. Sources told Politico ... Clooney…</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:43:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Boston Celtics Partner With Amica For New Jersey Patch</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/10/boston-celtics-partner-with-amica-for-new-jersey-patch/basketball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The reigning NBA champion Boston Celtics have announced a multi-year jersey patch partnership with Amica, a Rhode Island-based auto, home and life insurance company. “The Boston Celtics jersey is not only recognized all across New England, it’s recognized all across the world,” team president Rich Gotham said during a press</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 17:05:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Orlando Bloom Strips Down, Goes For A Swim at Italian Beach</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/11/orlando-bloom-strips-shirtless-beach-swim-italy-sardinia-photos-naked-katy-perry/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Orlando Bloom's getting an Italian tan ... soaking up rays in Sardiania without his fiancée Katy Perry -- who's on the island with him but skipped out on the surf and sun. The actor made hearts race in just his barely-there shorts, showing off his…</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:43:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Winston-Salem Dash pay tribute to Windy City with Italian Beef alternate</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/10/winston-salem-dash-pay-tribute-to-windy-city-with-italian-beef-alternate/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Winston-Salem, North Carolina, is not exactly known for its Italian beef, but the High-A Winston-Salem Dash will wear jerseys featuring the sandwiches later this season. Italian beef sandwiches—made of slow roasted beef and giardiniera, an Italian relish of pickled vegetables—are a signature food item in Chicago, where the Dash’s parent</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 15:18:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alleged Drunk Driver Smashes Through Nail Salon in Shocking Video</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/11/drunk-driver-slams-nail-salon-long-island-new-york-dead-kill/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>An alleged drunk driver in New York careened through a nail salon at top speed ... and, the unbelievable moment was caught on video. The shocking clip -- published by the New York Post -- shows the car speeding out of a Long Island parking lot late…</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:43:17 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>