<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:45:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The New Ballpark that Could’ve Saved the Montreal Expos</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/14/the-new-ballpark-that-couldve-saved-the-montreal-expos/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>In the 1990s, the Montreal Expos were struggling. Their decrepit stadium resulted in disastrous attendance numbers, and the loss of crucial ticket and concession revenue led to a steady stream of the team’s most talented players walking away the second they hit free agency. The 1994 player’s strike, which cancelled</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 17:45:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Patrick Mahomes Says Taylor Swift is Behind Travis Kelce's New Bushy Hairdo</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/14/patrick-mahomes-taylor-swift-travis-kelce-long-hair-beard/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Taylor Swift is exerting her influence over her boyfriend Travis Kelce, especially when it comes to his appearance ... so says Patrick Mahomes. Mahomes -- the Kansas City Chiefs QB -- participated in a town hall discussion Tuesday on SiriusXM NFL…</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:45:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2024-25 European Football Kit Preview: La Liga</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/14/2024-25-european-football-kit-preview-la-liga/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>94th season of Spanish top-flight domestic soccer league gets underway on Thursday, August 15, with pair of matches</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ángel Salazar Filming Indie 'Scarface' Spin-Off Before Death</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/14/scarface-angel-salazar-spin-off/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Ángel Salazar -- famous for playing Al Pacino's trusted sidekick "Chi Chi" in "Scarface" -- was filming an indie spin-off of the iconic gangster movie when he died ... and we've got the first look at him in action. Director Eric Spade Rivas tells…</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:45:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cincinnati Bengals Unveil New Orange Pants Following Madden Leak</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/12/cincinnati-bengals-unveil-new-orange-pants-following-madden-leak/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Cincinnati Bengals unexpectedly unveiled their new orange alternate pants on Monday evening following a leak on EA Sports’ Madden NFL 25 video game. The Bengals have never worn orange pants, as they only had white pants as an option from their inaugural season in 1968 to 2002 before adding</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 00:06:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Simone Biles' Biological Mother Wants To Reconcile, 'Would Like To Make Amends'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/14/simone-biles-birth-mom-shanon-forgiveness/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Simone Biles' biological mother is ready to meet the Olympic hero face-to-face ... saying after decades of being out of her life, she wants to make things right. When Biles was a toddler, she was placed in foster care as her mom, Shanon, battled…</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:45:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>QMJHL’s Saint John Sea Dogs Celebrate 20th Anniversary With Commemorative Logo</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/12/qmjhls-saint-john-sea-dogs-celebrate-20th-anniversary-with-commemorative-logo/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Logo highlights Sea Dogs' three Quebec Maritime Junior Hockey League championships and two Memorial Cup titles over first 20 years in Saint John, New Brunswick</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:04:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Christopher Dorner's Gun Recovered During Arrest of Armed Robbery Suspects</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/13/christopher-dorner-gun-found/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>A firearm registered to notorious cop killer Christopher Dorner was recovered during the arrest of two men suspected in the armed robbery of a $1 million watch ... and the crazy thing is Dorner's been dead for over a decade. Prosecutors in Los…</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:45:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adidas Brings Back Classic Trefoil Logo on Third Kits for 5 Elite European Clubs</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/12/adidas-brings-back-classic-trefoil-logo-on-third-kits-for-5-elite-european-clubs/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Company's logo first introduced in 1972 appears on new third kits for Real Madrid, Manchester United, Arsenal, Bayern Munich and Juventus</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 16:31:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ex-MMA Fighter Lumumba Sayers Arrested, Allegedly Killed Man To Avenge Son's Death</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/14/lumumba-sayers-murder/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Former mixed martial artist Lumumba Sayers -- who once fought ex-UFC star Derek Brunson inside a cage -- was arrested for murder over the weekend ... after he allegedly shot and killed a man to avenge his son's death. The Commerce City Police…</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:45:35 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>