<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 06:53:33 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Job Numbers Turn Out to Be Overinflated, Will the Fed Make a Hard Pivot?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-249</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>One startup is aiming to end traditional real estate commissions for good. Jobs numbers get their most significant downgrade in over a decade, forcing the Fed to rethink its rate-cutting […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 10:00:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kinsome aims to bridge the generation gap with its new app for kids and grandparents</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/05/kinsome-new-communication-app-for-kids-and-grandparents/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Over a year ago, former Session M exec Eben Pingree received the news that his mother was diagnosed with Alzheimer’s. Two days later, his father-in-law was given the same diagnosis. To create lasting memories and help his three young children bond with their grandparents, Pingree — along with his co-founders Mike Gerbush, Ashley Hawking, and […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Efforts to Cut Long Prison Sentences Have Stalled</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/31/wisconsin-california-sentence-prison</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Crime victim advocates and conservative groups are resisting moves to revisit “truth-in-sentencing” laws.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Concessions Are Rising, But Private Landlords Should Never Offer Them</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/private-landlords-should-never-offer-concessions</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Are you worried about your local rental market cooling off, fearing that you will have a property sit on the market for too long? Well, chances are you are priced […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 16:10:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Reonic raises €13 million to help small installers of green tech like heat pumps and solar panels</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/04/reonic-raises-e13-million-to-help-small-installers-of-green-tech-like-heat-pumps-and-solar-panels/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>European regulators are pushing hard for greener energy. The REPowerEU plan calls for 10 million additional heat pumps to be added by 2027, and solar panels are also on the rise. But most installations are done by small businesses that could be more productive with better work processes. This is where German startup Reonic comes […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How a Massachusetts Cop Allegedly Groomed, Controlled and Killed Sandra Birchmore</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/30/police-explorer-sexual-abuse-massachusetts-birchmore</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Matthew Farwell met her in a police Explorer program. Prosecutors say he abused her for years before she became pregnant and he killed her.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Should Investors Start Using 40-Year Mortgages?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/should-investors-consider-using-a-40-year-mortgage</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>News that the Federal Reserve is about to start cutting interest rates has electrified the real estate industry, with homeowners and investors eagerly waiting to see how low rates will […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 15:54:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Boom’s macOS camera app lets you customize your video call appearance</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/04/boom-is-a-macos-camera-app-for-customizing-your-video-call-layout/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>As someone who talks to many people outside my time zone, I often spend at least a few minutes on a video call explaining my location, time, and weather. That information became easier to convey with a Mac app called Boom, now available as a freemium product. Boom is a bootstrapped company built by former […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 03:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>5 Things to Know About How Survivors Get Incarcerated for Their Abusers’ Crimes</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/28/accomplice-liability-laws-what-to-know</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Little-known laws allow people to be punished for crimes they didn’t directly commit. Survivors of domestic violence are especially vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Rental Property Toolkit: How to Build Your Buy Box and Source More Deals</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-453</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Struggling to land your next rental property? Even in today’s housing market, there’s a great deal out there with your name on it—you just need to know where to look. […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 10:00:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Those ‘Founder mode’ memes keep coming</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/04/those-founder-mode-memes-keep-coming/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>If you spend time on X or Threads, where snarky memes rise and fall, you’ve probably seen posts referencing “founder mode” over the last few days, like this: https://www.threads.net/@carnage4life/post/C_eaQAxyIcV Or maybe this: You may even have seen this parody about “goblin mode.” The chatter ties to a recent blog post that Y Combinator founder and […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 00:14:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How a Drop in Border Crossings May Change the Presidential Campaign</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/24/kamala-harris-dnc-border-donald-trump</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>The Democratic National Convention sought to address one of the party’s biggest weaknesses with voters.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Real Estate Risk: How to Dodge It, When to Take It, and Using It to Build Wealth</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-1013</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Real estate risk can make you wealthy or cause your portfolio to come crashing down. Like any type of investing, real estate can be risky. However, the amount of risk […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 10:00:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Andreessen Horowitz shutters its Miami office after two years</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/04/andreessen-horowitz-shutters-its-miami-office-after-two-years/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Andreessen Horowitz (a16z) has closed a satellite office in Miami Beach just two years into a five-year lease it signed for an 8,300-square-foot space. The reason? Disuse, reports Bloomberg. Miami — once a hotspot for crypto, an area of interest for a16z — has struggled to retain venture cash and entrepreneurial talent in recent years, […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 23:48:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Prosecutors Fight Exonerations</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/17/wrongful-conviction-innocence-claims-missouri-st-louis</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>As laws are passed to support the wrongfully convicted, some officials in the legal system push back.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>