<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 00:27:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>PSG Pay Homage to Eiffel Tower With New Away Kit – Plus More European Kit Launches</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/05/psg-pay-homage-to-eiffel-tower-with-new-away-kit-plus-more-european-kit-launches/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Other clubs unveiling 2024-25 kits include Napoli, Wolves, West Ham, Stade de Reims, Mallorca, Real Betis, Villarreal, Bochum, Stuttgart, Mainz 05 and Union Berlin</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 20:20:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sexy Stars On Boats ... Feeling A Lil' Nauti!</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/05/sexy-stars-boats-feeling-little-nauti/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Land Ho! You'll be hopping on board in no time once you cast your eyes on these stars out on the open sea! Celebs never hold back on a boat ... It's nothing but smooth sailing, but which fine fish is the sexiest catch? All hands on deck with celebs…</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 00:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Look at the New NHL Practice Jersey Design</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/04/a-look-at-the-new-nhl-practice-jersey-design/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Thanks to the Utah Hockey Club, we got ourselves a look at the new NHL practice jersey design. With the switch from Adidas to Fanatics for 2024-25, we knew there’d be some changes to the on-ice NHL uniform. We’ve already seen that each team’s jersey will now include the Fanatics</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 22:20:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jake Paul Cops $650k Diamond Chain With New W Body Care Logo</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/05/jake-paul-cops-650k-diamond-chain-new-w-body-care-logo/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Jake Paul is celebrating the launch of his new W body care line in the flashiest way possible ... by getting a $650k diamond pendant and chain to rep the brand!! TMZ Sports has learned Paul -- a 9-1 cruiserweight boxer, Internet sensation and…</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 00:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MLB Teams Wearing USA-Themed Caps Today for Fourth of July</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/04/mlb-teams-wearing-usa-themed-caps-today-for-fourth-of-july/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>All 30 Major League Baseball teams will wear stars-and-stripes-themed caps on-field during today’s games in honour of Independence Day in the United States. This year, all 30 clubs will wear a cream-coloured crown, with teams again having the option of a red or navy blue visor and button. One more</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 16:34:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Crazy Town Singer Shifty Shellshock Talked Sobriety Months Before Fatal OD</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/05/crazy-town-singer-shifty-shellshock-seth-binzer-talked-sobriety-before-death-od/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Late Crazy Town frontman Shifty Shellshock was sober and happy a few months before his accidental drug overdose ... and seemed committed to staying on the wagon. TMZ obtained footage from one of Shifty's final interviews before his sudden death,…</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 00:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2024 MLB All-Star Game Uniforms Revealed</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/03/2024-mlb-all-star-game-uniforms-revealed/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Major League Baseball has officially unveiled the uniforms their best players will wear when they take the field at Globe Life Field in Arlington later this month. The uniforms, as you’d expect, incorporate some of that Texas style, with an Old West style typeface across the chest and again in</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 02:02:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ex-'Howard Stern Show' Star Elisa Jordana Pleads Guilty To Battery</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/05/howard-stern-show-elisa-jordana-pleads-guilty-battery-mental-health-evaluation-ordered/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Elisa Jordana's putting her legal troubles behind her ... copping a plea in her battery case... but officials will take a look at her mental health as part of the deal. The former 'Howard Stern Show' star took a plea deal back in May ... receiving…</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 00:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Leaked Photos Show 2024 MLB All-Star Jerseys</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/03/leaked-photos-show-2024-mlb-all-star-jerseys/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>With just under two weeks until this year’s Mid-Summer Classic, the jerseys for one of the two teams have leaked. Posted by SNY’s Twitter account dedicated to the New York Yankees, the photos show the front and back of a cream-coloured American League jersey bearing the name of Yankees outfielder</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 20:37:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Comedian Tony Knight Dead At 54</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/05/comedian-tony-knight-dead-at-54-tree-branch-france/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Comedian Tony Knight died following a freak accident ... when a large tree branch fell on top of him and several others at a festival in France. Knight died in June while attending the "Rock'&amp;'Cars" festival in Lavaur, France, a family member…</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 00:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>