<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 23:55:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>State Capitalism in Private Markets: Mission Creep</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/03/state-capitalism-in-private-markets-mission-creep/</link><description>Governments relish mingling in markets. Yet, if past policies are any guide, taxpayers are being shortchanged.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 12:30:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gas stove pollution harms poor and minority Americans the most, due in part to different home sizes, study says</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/04/gas-stove-pollution-harm-poor-minority-home-sizes-differences/</link><description>The researchers estimated that gas and propane stoves contribute to as many as 19,000 adult deaths annually in the US, as well as 200,000 childhood asthma cases and $1 billion in societal harm.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 01:52:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Implementation Shortfalls Hamstring Factor Strategies</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/01/implementation-shortfalls-hamstring-factor-strategies/</link><description>Smart rebalancing rules help portfolio managers capture more of the return that is inherent in their factor strategies. Concentrating on “priority best” trading improves factor portfolio performance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 11:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Social-media sensation 'Shug' the zebra is recaptured after evading a rodeo clown and horse trainers to spend nearly a week on the run</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/04/shug-zebra-recaptured-social-media-meme-seattle-washington/</link><description>Local residents and animal control officers corralled "Shug" in the community of Riverbend, about 30 miles east of Seattle.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 01:20:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IFRS Accounting Standard Will Support Better Investment Decisions</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/30/ifrs-accounting-standard-will-support-better-investment-decisions/</link><description>IFRS 18 responds to investors' concerns about challenges in comparing companies' financial performance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 11:34:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are cold plunges and saunas safe for kids? What parents need to know about the benefits and risks</title><link>https://fortune.com/well/article/cold-plunge-sauna-kids-safety/</link><description>More adults have been incorporating saunas and cold plunges into their wellness routines, and increasingly, their kids are, too.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meir Statman: Your State of Mind Influences Your Investing Success</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/29/meir-statman-your-state-of-mind-influences-your-investing-success/</link><description>Meir Statman shares his insights on the broader aspects of financial well-being and its interconnection with life satisfaction.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 12:58:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The NCAA and top college conferences could pay $3 billion and share revenue with athletes to settle an antitrust lawsuit</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/04/ncaa-revenue-sharing-athletes-antitrust-lawsuit-sec-acc-big-ten-big-12/</link><description>Schools in the Big Ten, Big 12, Atlantic Coast Conference and Southeastern Conference could be on the hook for about $30 million per year, which would include about $20 million annually directed to their athletes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 23:54:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: Trailblazers, Heroes, and Crooks</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/26/book-review-trailblazers-heroes-and-crooks/</link><description>Stephen Foerster, CFA, extracts lessons from exceptional episodes in financial history that ordinary investors and seasoned professionals alike can put to profitable use. The bonus is that you'll be entertained from start to finish.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>India and Japan hit back at Joe Biden's comments calling them 'xenophobic' countries like Russia and China</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/04/joe-biden-india-japan-xenophobic-countries-russia-china-presidential-election/</link><description>Biden made the remarks during a campaign fundraising event on Wednesday.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 23:32:28 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>