<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 06:58:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>MLB All-Star Game Logos, Like Super Bowls, May Get a Templated Look Going Forward</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/23/mlb-all-star-game-logos-like-super-bowls-may-get-a-templated-look-going-forward/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Standardized sports logos are trending, from the Super Bowl to literally everything in the NBA. But what about Major League Baseball’s All-Star Game… Well, guess what? It looks like baseball’s annual Mid-Summer Classic is ready to join the club. “You might start to see some similarities in the format and</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 21:37:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Solange Rips Treatment Of Black Woman in U.S. After Sonya Massey Shooting</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/23/solange-sonya-massey-bodycam-police-shooting-outrage-america/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>The fatal police shooting of Sonya Massey has saddened Solange Knowles like many Americans -- and she's making a nuanced point about this being a regular thing in the U.S. After taking in the brutal body cam footage that was released this week --…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 06:58:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stellar Real Madrid Away Kit Headlines Recent Launches from Spain, Rest of Europe</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/23/stellar-real-madrid-away-kit-headlines-recent-launches-from-spain-and-rest-of-europe/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Inter Milan adds gold flourishes to home kit to celebrate 20th Serie A title; other clubs unveiling 24-25 kits include Aston Villa, Real Valladolid, Girona, Osasuna, Borussia Dortmund, Stade Rennais, Toulouse</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 17:27:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gov. Wes Moore Says Democrats Will Win Election On Hope, Not Trump Fear</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/23/wes-moore-democrats-keys-election-hope-future-not-prosecuting-donald-trump/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Gov. Wes Moore says Democrats will hold the White House by selling voters on VP Kamala Harris' vision for the future -- and he explained why prosecuting Donald Trump on the campaign trail won't be enough. Maryland's head honcho joined us Tuesday on…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 06:58:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2025 MLB All-Star Game Logo Revealed; Hosted by Atlanta Braves</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/22/2025-mlb-all-star-game-logo-revealed-hosted-by-atlanta-braves/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Atlanta… You’re on the clock. Four years after they lost the game with just months to go, the Atlanta Braves are back and ready to host. Major League Baseball, along with the team, today unveiled the logo for the 2025 MLB All-Star Game, to be played at Truist Field on</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 00:18:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elon Musk Says 'Woke Mind Virus' Killed His Transgender Child, 'My Son Is Dead'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/23/elon-musk-transgender-daughter-killed-woke-mind-virus/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Elon Musk says his transgender daughter is dead in his eyes -- saying he feels she was brainwashed by the "woke mind virus." The Tesla chief did an interview with Jordan Peterson on Daily Wire this week, where he made the alarming comments ...…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 06:58:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are The Kansas City Chiefs Considering Alternate Uniforms?</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/22/are-the-kansas-city-chiefs-considering-alternate-uniforms/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Don't expect the Kansas City Chiefs to get an alternate uniform anytime soon, though their owner appears to be warming up to the idea.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 22:23:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sonya Massey Shooting, Ben Crump Claims Deputy Moved Closer For Better Shot</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/23/sonya-massey-ben-crump-deputy-moved-closer-better-shot/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>The sheriff's deputy who shot and killed Sonya Massey claims he feared she was going to throw a pot of boiling water on him, but based on the horrifying police body cam ... her family and their attorney aren't buying it. Ben Crump is representing…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 06:58:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New York Jets Unveil “The Classic” Throwback Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/22/new-york-jets-unveil-the-classic-throwback-uniforms/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Although it’s only been five years since they moved away from the design, the New York Jets unveiled a familiar throwback uniform that will be worn against the Buffalo Bills on Monday Night Football on Oct. 14.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 20:04:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Francis Ngannou Opens Up On 15-Month Old Son's Death, 'What Do You Mean He's Gone?'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/23/francis-ngannou-opens-up-about-death-of-his-15-month-old-son-in-podcast-apperance/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Francis Ngannou is speaking into a mic for the first time since his 15-month-old son died suddenly back in March ... and his words are nothing short of heartbreaking. Ngannou made an appearance on Joe Rogan's "JRE MMA Show" Tuesday and he talked…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 06:58:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>