<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from multiple RSS sources, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 06:37:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Crucial Questions to Ask an Agent and How to Negotiate Commissions</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-940</link><description>Everyone knows how to find a real estate agent. But an investor-friendly agent—one who will find deals for you, run the numbers, hook you up with contractors, and help you […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 07:02:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TLcom Capital closes second fund at $154M to back early-stage startups across Africa</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/22/tlcom-capital-closes-second-fund-at-154m-to-back-early-stage-startups-across-africa/</link><description>Venture capital activity in Africa has shown resilience over the past six months, with major firms backing startups on the continent closing their funds despite the ongoing funding winter.  In the latest development, TLcom Capital, an African VC firm with offices in Lagos and Nairobi and a focus on early-stage startups, has concluded fundraising for […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 10:06:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Enduring Use of Solitary, and New Proposed Limits That Will Likely Fail (Again)</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/20/solitary-confinement-reform-oklahoma-washington-florida</link><description>Isolation’s damaging effects are widely known. But many facilities confine people — even youth — virtually all day, sometimes in shower stalls.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Migraine: What to Do When Your Pain Is Dismissed</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/migraines-headaches/features/steps-take-when-migraine-pain-dismissed?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>A migraine diagnosis is a key part of your treatment plan. Here’s what to do if your doctor isn’t taking your pain seriously.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 23:19:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why More Investors Are Building Wealth with “Walkable” Properties w/Jeff Speck</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-210</link><description>Over the past few years, you’ve probably heard the term “walkability” thrown out. For those who have lived in big cities, this is a common factor to use when deciding […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 07:02:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Green search engine Ecosia launches a cross-platform browser</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/22/ecosia-launches-a-cross-platform-browser-starts-an-affiliate-link-program/</link><description>Ecosia, the search engine that funds tree-planting initiatives with its search ad profits, has launched a new cross-platform browser to grow its online footprint. The new browser, available for Mac, Windows, iOS, and Android, is built on top of Google’s open source browser project Chromium, which explains why there aren’t many differences to Google’s own […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 08:00:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Officials Failed to Act When COVID Hit Prisons. A New Study Shows the Deadly Cost.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/18/covid-prison-deaths-data</link><description>People in prison died at 3.4 times the rate of the free population, with the oldest hit hardest. New data holds lessons for preventing future deaths.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When Your Period Signals a Problem</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/women/features/when-your-period-signals-problem?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Pain, bleeding, and missed periods may be signs that something is wrong.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 22:46:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>5 Real Estate Deals Using Other People’s Money</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-396</link><description>You want to invest in real estate, but you don’t have the money. Are you out of luck? Good news—money is NOT a dealbreaker. There are several levers you can […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 07:02:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seraphim Space launches second VC fund with nine investments already under its belt</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/21/seraphim-space-new-fund/</link><description>Following its first close with limited partners including Eutelsat, the early stage fund will build a global portfolio of 30 startups that will be backed at the seed and Series A stages.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 07:00:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Parents Paying for Their Children’s Crimes</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/13/michigan-school-shooting-parents</link><description>Experts warn about a wave of legal consequences for parents like the Crumbleys, while some states consider prosecutions for kids as young as 10.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hate Taking Pills? For Some Drugs, You Won’t Need To</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/drug-medication/features/hate-taking-pills-for-some-drugs-you-wont-need-to?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>New dissolving films and mouth patches could replace pills for prescriptions</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:48:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 25 Best Sunbelt Markets for Cash Flow—And a Closer Look at the Top 4</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/best-sunbelt-housing-markets-for-cash-flow</link><description>Jazz icon and Los Angeles native Roy Ayers once famously sang, “Everybody Loves The Sunshine.” Never have truer words been said. The Sunbelt states are having their moment in the (ahem) sun, with […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 21:27:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Peak XV’s Piyush Gupta is leaving firm to start own secondary-focused VC fund</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/21/peak-xv-piyush-gupta-leaves-to-start-own-secondary-focused-vc-fund/</link><description>Piyush Gupta, one of the operating leaders at Peak XV Partners, is leaving the firm at the end of this month to start his own fund, four people familiar with the matter told TechCrunch. Gupta joined Peak XV, formerly known as Sequoia Capital India &amp; SEA, in 2017, leading the influential venture firm’s strategic development […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 06:07:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I Had a Tough Job at My Brooklyn Jail: Keeping Men From Taking Their Own Lives</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/12/brooklyn-jail-suicide-prevention-aide</link><description>As a suicide prevention aide, I had to make sure my fellow detainees didn’t harm themselves. It was surprisingly easy to get such a complex job.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Heart-Liver Surgery May Help Patients Excluded from Transplant List</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/heart-disease/features/heart-liver-surgery-may-help-patients-excluded-from-transplant-list?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Patients with both heart and liver diseases are usually turned away from organ transplant lists. A new dual procedure aims to give them another chance.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:41:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is New York’s Eviction Bill a Compromise? Or Just More Pain for Landlords and a Blueprint for Other States to Follow?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/new-york-housing-bill-causes-uproar-from-both-sides</link><description>New York State legislative leaders have agreed on a preliminary housing deal aimed at tackling affordability and supply problems, which are especially severe in New York City.  The legislation, which was intended to balance the interests of tenants […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 19:55:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tinder gets a ‘Share My Date’ feature for users to send date plans to their curious friends</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/21/tinder-gets-a-share-my-date-feature-for-users-to-send-date-plans-to-their-curious-friends/</link><description>It’s not uncommon for people to screenshot dating profiles and send them to their friends and loved ones, either to get feedback or to let them know who they’re seeing that weekend. Now, Tinder users are able to share their date plans directly from the app thanks to a new feature called “Share My Date.” […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 05:00:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Supreme Court Case on Homelessness May Limit Prisoner Rights and Expand Executions</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/10/supreme-court-homeless-grants-pass-originalism</link><description>In Grants Pass v. Johnson, a town in Oregon asks the court to reconsider what constitutes “cruel and unusual punishments.”</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Living With CLL in the Later Stages</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/cancer/lymphoma/features/living-with-late-stage-cll?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>When chronic lymphocytic leukemia (CLL) reaches its advanced stages, it can be stressful and exhausting. But you don’t have to go it alone.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:16:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>