<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 06:58:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Airbnb Has Changed: Make More Money Even with Regulations &amp; New Competition</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-994</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Airbnb has changed, and if you don’t change with it, you could see your income start to dwindle. The good news? If you get ahead of the curve, you could […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 07:02:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pearl raises $58M to help dentists make better diagnoses using AI</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/24/pearl-raises-58m-to-help-dentists-make-better-diagnoses-using-ai/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Dental care is a necessity, yet many patients lack confidence in their dentists’ ability to provide accurate diagnoses and appropriate treatments. Some dentists over treat patients, leading to unnecessary expenses, while others may miss critical issues that could develop into more significant and costly problems in the future. While seeking a second opinion from another […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>5 Things to Know About Kamala Harris’ Criminal Justice Record</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/21/kamala-harris-criminal-justice-record</link><description>Here’s where Vice President Kamala Harris, a former prosecutor, stands on important criminal justice issues.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 19:09:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>“Snowballing” to 12 Doors in 4 Years &amp; Replacing TWO Six-Figure Salaries</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-436</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Owning rentals could help you become financially free, afford you more time with family, and allow you to travel the world. Whether you’re stuck in a career you dislike or […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 07:02:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spanish startup Exoticca raises a €60M Series D for its tour packages platform</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/23/spanish-startup-exoticca-raises-a-e60m-series-d-for-tour-packages-platform/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Exoticca’s platform connects flights, hotels, meals, transfers, transportation and more, plus the local companies at the destinations. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Project 2025 Plans for Trump to Have Unprecedented Power Over the Justice Department</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/20/trump-project-2025-crime-prosecutors</link><description>The policy plan for a second Trump term would turn the department against progressive local prosecutors.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seeing Greene: Should I Start Flipping Houses in My Market? (How to Know)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-993</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Should I pay off my rentals or scale to more doors? Should I start flipping houses in my local but expensive market or go long-distance? When is the time to […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 07:02:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mark Zuckerberg imagines content creators making AI clones of themselves</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/23/mark-zuckerberg-imagines-content-creators-making-ai-clones-of-themselves/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Content creators are busy people. Most spend more than 20 hours a week creating new content for their respective corners of the web. That doesn’t leave much time for audience engagement. But Mark Zuckerberg, Meta’s CEO, thinks that AI could solve this problem. In an interview with internet personality Rowan Cheung, Zuckerberg laid out his […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 03:22:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Love Beyond Bars: Jules and Samantha</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/19/photo-essay-werkheisers-wrongful-conviction</link><description>Jules and Samantha Werkheiser fought their wrongful convictions for over a decade. Here’s their journey of survival — and motherhood — in pictures.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2 Money Moves We’re Making TODAY to Prepare for a Potential Recession</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-548</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Are we in a recession? Are we headed for a recession? No one knows for certain, but you can never be too prepared for an economic downturn. Are you saving […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 07:01:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elon Musk sets new date for Tesla robotaxi reveal, calls everything beyond autonomy ‘noise’</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/23/elon-musk-sets-new-date-for-tesla-robotaxi-reveal-calls-everything-beyond-autonomy-noise/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Elon Musk says he will show off Tesla’s purpose-built “robotaxi” prototype during an event October 10, after scrapping a previous plan to reveal it August 8. Musk said Tesla will also show off “a couple of other things,” but didn’t explain what that meant. The comments, made on Tesla’s second-quarter earnings call Tuesday, largely confirms […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 00:50:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meet the New Generation of Unarmed First Responders in This New Podcast Series</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/18/police-north-carolina-podcast-mental-health</link><description>“The Fifth Branch,” a podcast from The Marshall Project and Tradeoffs, examines new, alternative ways to respond to 911 crisis calls.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Here’s Why Real Estate Investors Are Turning to ATMs For Diversification</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/why-investors-are-turning-to-atm-investments-for-diversification</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>As real estate conditions continue to tighten, investors are turning to ATMs for steady cash flow.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 20:21:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alphabet to invest another $5B into Waymo</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/23/alphabet-to-invest-another-5b-into-waymo/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Alphabet will spend an additional $5 billion on its self-driving subsidiary, Waymo, over the next few years, according to Ruth Porat, the company’s chief financial officer. Porat announced the commitment to a new “multi-year investment” Tuesday during Alphabet’s second-quarter earnings call. “This new round of funding, which is consistent with recent annual investment levels, will […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 22:49:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What We Know About J.D. Vance’s Legislative Action on Criminal Justice</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/17/what-we-know-from-sen-j-d-vance-s-legislative-action-on-criminal-justice-issues</link><description>On immigration and more, Vance has defended and legislated former President Donald Trump’s policy goals.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 23:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>