<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 07:44:01 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>10 of the Best New Nonfiction Book Releases of August 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/new-nonfiction-books-august-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/off-center-collage-1.png</image_url><description>What's the last nonfiction book you read?</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2024 Lexus GX 550 Road Test: Family adventure trip to Oregon</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/article/lexus-gx-550-road-test/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1200x675/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/07/29153506/2024-Lexus-GX-550-Premium-with-Mt-Bachelor1.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Lexus , SUV , Luxury , Off-Road Vehicles , Road Tests Continue reading 2024 Lexus GX 550 Road Test: Family adventure trip to Oregon 2024 Lexus GX 550 Road Test: Family adventure trip to Oregon originally appeared on Autoblog on Thu, 1 Aug 2024 06:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>5 things to know before the stock market opens Thursday</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/01/5-things-to-know-before-the-stock-market-opens-thursday-august-1.html</link><description>Here are the most important news items that investors need to start their trading day.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 12:23:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 559</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-559/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-559</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Do you understand how recruiters work and how they think? Well, this should help! There’s no magic. Every recruiter has their own set of preferences for sourcing and vetting candidates. But many share tips and insights to give job seekers valuable information. In this week’s summary, you’ll find: Please follow and support the talented experts […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 559 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 12:33:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Do infants feel excluded? Early signs and why it matters</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/do-infants-feel-excluded/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=do-infants-feel-excluded</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Social exclusion harms individuals of all ages, leading to feelings of loneliness, decreased self-esteem, and even changes in brain activity. Humans’ ability to recognize and react to social exclusion emerges early, suggesting the importance of considering and addressing ostracism even when caring for very young children. Babies are sensitive to social […] The post Do infants feel excluded? Early signs and why it matters appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 01:37:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cookie in a Mug</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/cookie-in-a-mug/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>This cookie in a mug recipe is the perfect way to satisfy your cookie craving. In just a few minutes,…</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Best Air Purifying Plants</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/best-air-purifying-plants/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>We love any excuse to buy more plants, and you may have heard they can improve your home’s indoor air quality. But before you blow your paycheck in the name of a healthier home, let’s dive deeper into plants’ air purifying powers. We’ll share which plants we recommend and what benefits you can actually expect from them. We’ve heard for years about how plants act as natural air filters for your home. So let’s dive a little deeper, shall we? 7 Air Purifying Plants If you just came here for a list, our favorite air purifying houseplants are bulleted below. The best part is these are all beautiful, low-maintenance plants. Many also appear on our best low-light indoor plants list too! Dracaena (including Corn Plant ) Snake Plant Aglaonema English Ivy Pothos Bamboo Palm Spider Plant There are certainly more that could be included here, but we narrowed it to the ones that are most often cited by experts AND the plants that we think look best too. Continue reading Best Air Purifying Plants at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 14:15:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Back To School With Amazon</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/08/back-to-school-with-amazon/</link><description>We’re excited to unveil our latest roundup of back-to-school must-haves for kids, exclusively from Amazon. This selection is packed with… The post Back To School With Amazon appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 05:00:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10 of the Best New Children’s Books Out August 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/new-childrens-books-august-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/picture-books.png</image_url><description>What's your favorite new children's book of 2024 so far?</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2025 Ford Maverick Lobo revives the street-oriented sport truck</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/08/01/2025-ford-maverick-lobo-reveal-sport-truck/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1200x675/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/07/31172014/2025-Ford-Maverick-Lobo_01-copy.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Ford , Truck , Performance Continue reading 2025 Ford Maverick Lobo revives the street-oriented sport truck 2025 Ford Maverick Lobo revives the street-oriented sport truck originally appeared on Autoblog on Thu, 1 Aug 2024 06:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wayfair CEO likens home goods slowdown to 2008 financial crisis: 'Customers remain cautious'</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/01/wayfair-w-earnings-q2-2024.html</link><description>Online home goods company Wayfair has seen sluggish demand against high interest rates, but repreive could come if the federal reserve cuts rates in September</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 12:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 558</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-558/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-558</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Even though it’s summer, you can still take steps to move your job search forward. Set aside time to continue to learn about today’s job search trends and invest time learning about trends in your field. In this week’s Summary Sunday, you’ll find: I carefully curate articles and posts from sources I trust. I hope […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 558 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 14:14:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10 Actions Parents Can Take to Help their Children Be More Resilient in a World of Adversity</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/10-actions-to-help-children-be-more-resilient/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=10-actions-to-help-children-be-more-resilient</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Decades of research points to specific ways parents can build resilience that can help protect children from the challenges of adverse experiences and stress. Strategies include parent-focused tips such as practicing self care, reflecting on one’s own past experiences, and developing emotional control. Additional strategies focus on ways to navigate relationships […] The post 10 Actions Parents Can Take to Help their Children Be More Resilient in a World of Adversity appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 02:36:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sheet Pan Steak Fajitas</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/sheet-pan-steak-fajitas/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Sheet pan steak fajitas are beautiful and bursting with flavor. Easy to throw together on busy weeknights, they feature tender…</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Weekend In New Orleans With Kids</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/new-orleans-with-kids/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Since our travel guides to Charleston with kids and Palm Springs with kids have elicited requests for more travel ideas with kids, we’re back with an overdue recap of our 3-night trip to New Orleans. We’d never been to The Big Easy before and were impressed by how family-friendly the city is. It’s not all booze, beads, and Bourbon Street! So here’s a look at where we stayed, what we did, and what we’re excited to do next time we go back – because we will definitely go back! The four of us (well, five if you count our chihuahua!) went to NOLA for 3 nights in November of 2022. At the time, our kids were 8 and 12 years old. So unfortunately we can’t vouch for our suggestions being a good fit for toddlers or younger children. Although I’m sure ours would’ve loved the Louisiana Children’s Museum and Storyland playground back in the day! Continue reading A Weekend In New Orleans With Kids at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 17:17:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Newest At NET-A-PORTER</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/07/net-a-porter-collage/</link><description>Thank you to NET-A-PORTER for sponsoring this post. As we gear up for August, dive into the latest offerings from… The post Newest At NET-A-PORTER appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 05:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Barnes &amp; Noble’s Purchase of Indie Bookstore Approved by Court</title><link>https://bookriot.com/barnes-nobles-purchase-of-indie-bookstore-approved-by-court/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/image-of-barnes-and-noble.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>What do you think of Barnes &amp; Noble's plans surrounding the future of the Tattered Cover?</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 19:23:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>REI Co-op Base Camp 4 Tent Review - Spacious and sturdy car camping comfort</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/article/rei-co-op-base-camp-4-tent-review-spacious-and-sturdy-car-camping-comfort/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1200x675/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/07/03085146/REI-Base-Camp-4-Tent.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Commerce Continue reading REI Co-op Base Camp 4 Tent Review - Spacious and sturdy car camping comfort REI Co-op Base Camp 4 Tent Review - Spacious and sturdy car camping comfort originally appeared on Autoblog on Thu, 1 Aug 2024 05:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>U.S. rugby star Ilona Maher says Olympic bronze medal may have saved the team</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/01/us-rugby-star-ilona-maher-talks-bronze-medal-michele-kang-investment.html</link><description>Ilona Maher reflects on bringing U.S. Rugby its first Olympic medal, the state of women's sports and the growth of rugby.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 557</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-557/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-557</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Searching for a new job requires clarity on what you want to do and where you want to do it. You need a solid strategy but most importantly you need tenacity. In short, job search is more than hitting the apply button. This week’s summary provides resources, tools and information to help you carry out […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 557 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 11:37:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Children’s digital media exposure as a backdrop for multilingual learning</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/childrens-digital-media-exposure-as-a-backdrop-for-multilingual-learning/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=childrens-digital-media-exposure-as-a-backdrop-for-multilingual-learning</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Multilingual children use digital media regularly, in all their home languages. Digital media use may affect multilingual children’s early language learning by reducing opportunities for back-and-forth conversations with adults. This finding is similar to results of studies of digital media and language learning for children learning only one language. When using […] The post Children’s digital media exposure as a backdrop for multilingual learning appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 20:27:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>One-Pan Lemon Chicken Orzo</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/lemon-chicken-orzo/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>One-Pan Lemon Chicken Orzo is a comforting, well-rounded meal! Tender, juicy chicken pieces are joined with orzo pasta in a…</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>9 Easy Low-Light Indoor Plants</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/easy-low-light-indoor-plants/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>I used to think every houseplant needed a sunny corner or bright windowsill to thrive. But it turns out many of our favorite go-to houseplants do just fine in shady corners and low-light locations. So before you write off your house as too dark to sustain plant life, check out this list of the best indoor plants for low light. You might be surprised at how many good options there are! Our upstairs family room is the brightest room we’ve ever owned thanks to big unobstructed windows on all 4 sides. But most of our indoor plants live downstairs, where we get far less natural light. Luckily, that hasn’t stopped us from growing our collection of happy healthy houseplants. 9 Houseplants That Don’t Need A Lot Of Light Here are our favorite low-light indoor plants. We list a lot more info on them below, but here’s a quick list to bring on your next trip to the plant store: Snake Plant ZZ Plant Pothos Heartleaf Philodendron English Ivy Aglaonema Cast Iron Plant Monstera Parlor Palm Perhaps our favorite part of this list is that these aren’t ugly “consolation plants” that people begrudgingly buy for dark homes. Continue reading 9 Easy Low-Light Indoor Plants at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 14:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jump Start To Early Fall With Nordstrom</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/07/jump-start-to-early-fall-with-nordstrom/</link><description>Outfit Details: Nordstrom Shirt (on sale), Skirt (similar here and here), Sandals, Similar Necklace Thank you to Nordstrom for sponsoring… The post Jump Start To Early Fall With Nordstrom appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 05:00:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Memoir Where Memory Loss Is Time Travel</title><link>https://bookriot.com/tell-me-everything-you-dont-remember/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/partial-cover-of-TELL-ME-EVERYTHING-YOU-DONT-REMEMBER-THE-STROKE-THAT-CHANGED-MY-LIFE-.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>What disability memoirs have you read this month?</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Junkyard Gem: 2002 Daewoo Nubira SE Sedan</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/07/31/junkyard-gem-2002-daewoo-nubira/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1200x675/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/07/09123729/99-2002-Daewoo-Nubira-in-California-junkyard-photo-by-Murilee-Martin.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Daewoo , Automotive History , Economy Cars , Sedan Continue reading Junkyard Gem: 2002 Daewoo Nubira SE Sedan Junkyard Gem: 2002 Daewoo Nubira SE Sedan originally appeared on Autoblog on Wed, 31 Jul 2024 18:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Three 'pain trades:' Bank of America tells clients to be on the right side of these market moves</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/01/three-trades-that-will-make-investors-pay-the-most-per-bofa.html</link><description>Heading into year's end, Bank of America sees three "pain trades" that investors should look out for.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>5 Ways to Speed Up Your Job Search</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/5-ways-to-speed-up-your-job-search/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=5-ways-to-speed-up-your-job-search</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Is it possible to speed up your job search when the hiring decisions lie in the hands of employers? Yes, there are definitely things you can do to increase your odds. Taking control over what you can control is what I call a proactive job search. Too often job seekers over-rely on posted jobs to […] The post 5 Ways to Speed Up Your Job Search appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 11:04:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>La exposición de los niños a los medios digitales como contexto para el aprendizaje multilingüe</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/la-exposicion-de-los-ninos-a-los-medios-digitales-como-contexto-para-el-aprendizaje-multilingue/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=la-exposicion-de-los-ninos-a-los-medios-digitales-como-contexto-para-el-aprendizaje-multilingue</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Puntos clave para los cuidadores Los niños multilingües usan frecuentemente los medios digitales y los usan en los distintos idiomas que se hablan en su hogar. El uso de los medios digitales (por ej., la televisión, el computador o los “smartphones”) puede afectar negativamente el desarrollo del lenguaje en los niños que son multilingües porque […] The post La exposición de los niños a los medios digitales como contexto para el aprendizaje multilingüe appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 20:26:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Meal Plan #12</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/weekly-meal-plan-12/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>This weekly meal plan has so many of my favorite recipes in it! It has meals that even my kiddos…</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/how-to-remove-wallpaper/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Wallpaper has made a big comeback as a trendy home design choice. But despite its resurgence, there are still plenty of us dealing with dingy, dated, or downright ugly old wallpaper we don’t want. In our old home, we had to remove wallpaper in so many rooms: the kitchen, the dining room, the foyer, and two different bathrooms! As we traveled from room to room removing wallpaper, we tested 4 different methods, and today we’ll share what we learned. Removing wallpaper doesn’t require special tools or lots of money. It’s a totally doable project for any homeowner. However, it can be a tedious process that can take elbow grease and patience, depending on the size of your room and the stubbornness of your wallpaper. But having removed several rooms worth of decades-old wallpaper, we can confidently say it’s worth the effort! You can also check out more before and afters of our once-wallpapered rooms. Continue reading How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:21:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sun-Kissed</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/07/sun-kissed/</link><description>Outfit Details: Byan Top &amp; Pants, Valentino Hat, Dior Sandals, Zara Bag Fall in love with the effortlessly chic and radiant allure of sun-kissed styles.… The post Sun-Kissed appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 05:00:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Celtic Mythology Reads to Whisk You Away</title><link>https://bookriot.com/celtic-mythology-reads/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/Celtic-books.png</image_url><description>What are your favorite books featuring Celtic mythology?</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NHTSA moves toward a forced recall of 51 million airbag inflators</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/07/31/nhtsa-moves-toward-a-forced-recall-of-51-million-airbag-inflators/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/crop/6000x3375+0+0/resize/1200x675/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/07/31172242/dangerous_airbags.jpeg</image_url><description>Filed under: Recalls , Safety , Parts and Accessories Continue reading NHTSA moves toward a forced recall of 51 million airbag inflators NHTSA moves toward a forced recall of 51 million airbag inflators originally appeared on Autoblog on Wed, 31 Jul 2024 17:45:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 22:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biogen beats expectations, hikes outlook as Alzheimer's drug and other new products gain traction</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/01/biogen-biib-earnings-q2-2024.html</link><description>Uptake of Biogen's breakthrough Alzheimer's drug, Leqembi, appears to be picking up, with roughly $40 million in sales for the quarter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 11:56:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 556</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-556/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-556</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Artificial Intelligence is impacting every area of our lives, including job search. This will require each of us to become better critical thinkers to identify the noise from the genuine. Keeping up with the changes in the world of work takes effort, but that’s one reason you are here – each week you’ll discover interesting […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 556 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 11:55:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Becoming Confident in Parenting Abilities</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/confidence-in-parenting/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=confidence-in-parenting</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Parental self-efficacy (i.e., a parent’s confidence in their own ability to care for their infant and respond to the infant’s needs) is the first step to a good parent-child relationship. Research has explored the development of maternal self-efficacy beginning during pregnancy and continuing after childbirth. Mothers who have previous childbirth and […] The post Becoming Confident in Parenting Abilities appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 10:06:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pita Pizza</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/pita-pizza/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Pita pizza is like having your own personalized mini-pizza! Grab some ready-made pitas, pile on your favorite toppings, and indulge…</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aglaonema Plant – Complete Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/aglaonema-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Aglaonema, also called the Chinese Evergreen Plant, is an easy-care houseplant that lives happily in many lighting conditions – even a dark corner of our daughter’s room. There are dozens of different Aglaonema varieties, most with large tropical foliage and colors ranging from silvery-green, red, and even vibrant pink. They’re also tough to kill, so they’re a great option for forgetful plant owners or anyone looking for an easy win in the plant department. These truly have been very low maintenance for us. We purchased our two Aglaonemas (pronounced ag-lee-oh-neem-ah ) to put atop our daughter’s closet. It’s sometimes hard to distinguish different varieties, but we believe that’s an Aglaonema Silver (right) and either a Candy Cane or Princess Silver Queen (left). Aglaonema Quick Facts Here’s what you need to know about your Aglaonema at a glance: Latin name : Aglaonema is the genus under which there are 21 recognized species . Continue reading Aglaonema Plant – Complete Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:47:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summer Shimmer</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/07/summer-shimmer/</link><description>Outfit Details: Julia Amory Dress, Chanel Bag (similar here), Mar Soreli Flats, Marissa Klass Rings, Louis Abel Earrings A subtle summer shimmer shines so… The post Summer Shimmer appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 05:00:51 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>