<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 18:02:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Moroccan Soccer Team Awarded Default Win After Kits Confiscated by Algerian Customs</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/25/moroccan-soccer-team-awarded-default-win-after-kits-confiscated-by-algerian-customs/soccer/</link><description>Kits feature map of Morocco on the chest that includes disputed Western Sahara territory</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 18:55:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oklahoma Bus Driver Viciously Attacked By Passenger, Forces Crash</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/25/oklahoma-city-bus-driver-attacked-passenger-crash-building-video-arrest/</link><description>A bus driver found himself in the middle of a brutal attack last week, which was captured on video ... and which resulted in a huge crash, not to mention an arrest. Cops allege passenger Tihron Harrison flipped into a rage Saturday while riding one…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 18:02:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Glacier Range Riders, National Park Service Embroiled in Battle Over Arrowhead Logo</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/25/glacier-range-riders-national-park-service-embroiled-in-battle-over-arrowhead-logo/baseball/</link><description>NPS has filed protests with the U.S. Patent and Trademark Office over logo possible causing confusion that team is affiliated with service</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:56:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cops Locate Alleged Nikola Jokic Brother Punch Victim, Continue Investigation</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/25/cops-locate-alleged-nikola-jokic-brother-punch-victim-continue-investigation/</link><description>Cops are continuing to make headway in their investigation into Nikola Jokic's brother ... telling TMZ Sports they've located the man who Strahinja Jokic punched in the face earlier this week. A spokesperson for the Denver Police Dept. said on…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 18:02:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New York Jets: Their Logos, Their Name, Their Colours</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/25/new-york-jets-their-logos-their-name-their-colours/football/</link><description>From their early-sixties inception as the Titans of New York to their modern, throwback-inspired green and white logo, the New York Jets have had several distinctive looks over their 60-plus year history. This team has found itself navigating through different eras, frequently alternating between two primary logos and uniform styles</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:34:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pet Shop Boys' Neil Tennant Doesn't Think Taylor Swift Has Hit Songs</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/25/pet-shop-boys-neil-tennant-doesnt-think-taylor-swift-has-hit-songs/</link><description>Pet Shop Boys singer Neil Tennant doesn't think Taylor Swift has any famous songs ... even though he's been presented with evidence to the contrary. The British musician blasted Taylor's A-list status while recently chatting with The Guardian --…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 18:02:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Update on Utah’s NHL Team Name, Uniform Info, Tournament Coming?</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/24/update-on-utahs-nhl-team-name-uniform-info-tournament-coming/hockey-2/</link><description>Utah’s new National Hockey League team is starting to assemble their list of possible team names ahead of their inaugural (but not expansion) season this fall. DetroitHockey.Net’s Clark Rasmussen, the king of the trademark search, found two more names possibly trademarked by the group, bringing the total to nine that</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:51:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gucci Mane Disses Diddy On 'TakeDat' Track, Recreates Biggie Bathtub Scene</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/25/gucci-mane-diddy-diss-takedat-misa-hylton-notorious-big/</link><description>Gucci Mane decided it best he enter the 2024 rap wars and his chosen target is Diddy!!! Mr. Zone 6 is kicking Diddy while he's down with the new track, "TakeDat" ... ruthlessly appropriates the Bad Boy mogul's catchphrase, but that's far from the…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 18:02:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Liverpool FC Reportedly Ready to Return to Adidas in 2025</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/24/liverpool-fc-reportedly-ready-to-return-to-adidas-in-2025/soccer/</link><description>New deal with Liverpool reportedly part of an "aggressive push" by Adidas to win high-profile contracts after losing German national team deal</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 17:56:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Texas Mayor Receives Noose In Threatening Package, FBI Investigating</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/25/texas-mayor-noose-threatening-package-note-leave-race-campaign-arcola-texas/</link><description>Cops in Texas have launched an investigation with the help of the FBI after a small town's Mayor received a threatening package in the mail ... which included a noose. Arcola, TX's Mayor Fred Burton -- who's Black -- received the package Tuesday…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 18:02:31 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>