<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from multiple RSS sources, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 06:48:32 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Seeing Greene: Are Home Warranties Worth It &amp; When to Pay Off Debt vs. Invest?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-941</link><description>Should you pay off debt or invest? Many online financial gurus would tell you in a heartbeat that paying off debt is the number one priority…but is that always true? […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 07:02:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amazon launches a new grocery delivery subscription in the US</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/23/amazon-launches-a-new-grocery-delivery-subscription-in-the-u-s/</link><description>Amazon said today that it has launched a new grocery delivery subscription for Prime members and customers with an EBT card (Electronic Benefit Transfer) in the U.S. if you’re living in one of the 3,500 eligible cities and towns. The company started testing grocery delivery in three locations last year: Denver, Colorado; Sacramento, California; and […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 11:21:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Enduring Use of Solitary, and New Proposed Limits That Will Likely Fail (Again)</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/20/solitary-confinement-reform-oklahoma-washington-florida</link><description>Isolation’s damaging effects are widely known. But many facilities confine people — even youth — virtually all day, sometimes in shower stalls.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are 'Man Vans' Coming to a Parking Lot Near Your Soon?</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/prostate-cancer/news/20240422/prostate-cancer-screening-goes-mobile?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>"Game Changer Vehicles" – mobile medical units in a roving RV – are helping to bring cancer screening to where it's needed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 19:18:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Don’t Overlook This When Buying an Investment Property—Learn From My Mistake</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/dont-overlook-this-when-buying-an-investment-property</link><description>Let’s get one thing straight: Real estate investing isn't a get-rich-quick scheme. If you think you can just waltz in and start raking in cash without a solid game plan, you're setting yourself up for a financial face-plant.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 04:28:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mozilla finds that most dating apps are not great guardians of user data</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/23/mozilla-finds-that-most-dating-apps-are-not-great-guardians-of-user-data/</link><description>Dating apps are not following great privacy practices and are collecting more data than ever in order to woo GenZ users, a new study by Mozilla pointed out. Researchers reviewed dating apps in terms of privacy in 2021. In the latest report, they noted that dating apps have become more data-hungry and intrusive. The organization studied […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 10:45:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Officials Failed to Act When COVID Hit Prisons. A New Study Shows the Deadly Cost.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/18/covid-prison-deaths-data</link><description>People in prison died at 3.4 times the rate of the free population, with the oldest hit hardest. New data holds lessons for preventing future deaths.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chronic Spontaneous Urticaria: What to Know</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/features/urticaria-chronic-spontaneous?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>What you should know about chronic spontaneous urticaria (CSU), including symptoms, triggers, treatment, and a link to autoimmune disease.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 14:35:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Should You Invest for Cash Flow or Appreciation? Let’s Reevaluate in an Era of High Interest Rates</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/invest-for-real-estate-cash-flow-or-appreciation-in-high-interest-rate-environment</link><description>For real estate investors, the question of cash flow versus appreciation is as old as time. However, in an era of high interest rates, buying properties for cash flow isn’t easy. That doesn’t mean investing should […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 20:32:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adobe claims its new image generation model is its best yet</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/23/adobe-claims-its-new-image-generation-model-is-its-best-yet/</link><description>Firefly, Adobe’s family of generative AI models, doesn’t have the best reputation among creatives. The Firefly image generation model in particular has been derided as underwhelming and flawed compared to Midjourney, OpenAI’s DALL-E 3, and other rivals, with a tendency to distort limbs and landscapes and miss the nuances in prompts. But Adobe is trying […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 10:00:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Parents Paying for Their Children’s Crimes</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/13/michigan-school-shooting-parents</link><description>Experts warn about a wave of legal consequences for parents like the Crumbleys, while some states consider prosecutions for kids as young as 10.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CSU: What to Wear and What to Avoid</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/features/what-to-wear-with-csu?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Find out what’s best to wear to prevent and manage chronic spontaneous urticaria (CSU), also called chronic hives.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 14:35:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Do You Think It’s a Tough Time to Invest? It’s Not When You Can Get Deals Like This</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/its-not-a-tough-time-to-invest-when-you-can-get-deals-like-this</link><description>Are you sitting on the sidelines in this market? Many investors are. There’s a lot of fear and caution. But we’re not. And you don’t need to be, either.  Of […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 20:13:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rivian targets gas-powered Ford and Toyota trucks and SUVs with $5,000 ‘electric upgrade’ discount</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/22/rivian-targets-gas-powered-ford-and-toyota-trucks-and-suvs-with-5000-electric-upgrade-discount/</link><description>Rivian is offering discounts up to $5,000 on its EVs — and a year of free charging — to customers willing to trade in their gas-powered trucks and SUVs. The deal, which kicked off April 22, is aimed directly at some of the best-selling and most ubiquitous gas-powered trucks and SUVs on the market today, […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 03:10:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I Had a Tough Job at My Brooklyn Jail: Keeping Men From Taking Their Own Lives</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/12/brooklyn-jail-suicide-prevention-aide</link><description>As a suicide prevention aide, I had to make sure my fellow detainees didn’t harm themselves. It was surprisingly easy to get such a complex job.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Treatment Plan for Chronic Spontaneous Urticaria</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/features/csu-meds-lifestyle?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>The hives of CSU can be tricky to manage. You and your doctor can try medications to ease your symptoms. But other changes might make a difference, too.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 14:35:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Wave of Zoning Law Changes Could Have Huge Impacts for Investors and Housing—Here’s What You Need to Know</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wave-of-zoning-law-changes-could-have-major-impacts-on-investors</link><description>The U.S. is facing a housing deficit of about 3.2 million units, and the situation is especially dire in urban areas like New York. It’s one of the reasons prospective homebuyers are finding […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 19:56:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>UnitedHealth says Change hackers stole health data on ‘substantial proportion of people in America’</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/22/unitedhealth-change-healthcare-hackers-substantial-proportion-americans/</link><description>The health tech giant processes 15 billion health transactions a year, and handles health information for about half of all Americans.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 23:35:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Supreme Court Case on Homelessness May Limit Prisoner Rights and Expand Executions</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/10/supreme-court-homeless-grants-pass-originalism</link><description>In Grants Pass v. Johnson, a town in Oregon asks the court to reconsider what constitutes “cruel and unusual punishments.”</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When the Hives of CSU Don’t Go Away on Their Own</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/features/hives-dont-go-away?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>CSU can be frustrating, but the worst part might be when the hives don’t go away on their own. New treatments can help.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 14:35:09 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>