<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 07:30:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>State Capitalism in Private Markets: Mission Creep</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/03/state-capitalism-in-private-markets-mission-creep/</link><description>Governments relish mingling in markets. Yet, if past policies are any guide, taxpayers are being shortchanged.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 12:30:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>China President Xi's European charm offensive turns to trade and 'fair competition' as he meets with France's Macron</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/06/china-president-xi-europe-trade-fair-competition-france-macron/</link><description>As France prepares to host the Summer Olympics, Macron said he would ask Xi to use his influence to make the Games “a diplomatic moment of peace.”</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 12:16:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Implementation Shortfalls Hamstring Factor Strategies</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/01/implementation-shortfalls-hamstring-factor-strategies/</link><description>Smart rebalancing rules help portfolio managers capture more of the return that is inherent in their factor strategies. Concentrating on “priority best” trading improves factor portfolio performance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 11:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Democrats race to design ways to best use AI in 2024 campaign</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/06/democrats-ai-2024-campaign-trump-outmaneuvered-social-media-2016/</link><description>The technology that could transform American elections — and perhaps threaten democracy itself.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 11:41:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IFRS Accounting Standard Will Support Better Investment Decisions</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/30/ifrs-accounting-standard-will-support-better-investment-decisions/</link><description>IFRS 18 responds to investors' concerns about challenges in comparing companies' financial performance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 11:34:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'The Fall Guy' posts weak $28.5 million opening, providing Hollywood a lukewarm start to the summer movie season</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/06/barbenheimer-stars-fall-guy-weak-285-million-opening-hollywood-summer-movie-season/</link><description>The modest start for “The Fall Guy” hints at larger concerns for the film industry.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 11:12:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meir Statman: Your State of Mind Influences Your Investing Success</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/29/meir-statman-your-state-of-mind-influences-your-investing-success/</link><description>Meir Statman shares his insights on the broader aspects of financial well-being and its interconnection with life satisfaction.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 12:58:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Former Trump campaign manager who used Cambridge Analytica to target Facebook ads in 2016 run has returned with his own AI platform</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/06/trump-campaign-manager-brad-pascale-cambridge-analytica-facebook-ads-2016-ai-platform-nucleus/</link><description>Brad Parscale, the digital campaign operative who helped engineer Trump’s 2016 presidential victory, vows that his new, AI-powered platform will dramatically overhaul not just polling, but campaigning.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 10:55:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: Trailblazers, Heroes, and Crooks</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/26/book-review-trailblazers-heroes-and-crooks/</link><description>Stephen Foerster, CFA, extracts lessons from exceptional episodes in financial history that ordinary investors and seasoned professionals alike can put to profitable use. The bonus is that you'll be entertained from start to finish.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Starbucks ex-CEO Howard Schultz says chain needs a major fix after biggest sales miss in years: 'There must be contrition'</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/06/starbucks-ex-ceo-howard-schultz-chain-major-fix-biggest-sales-miss-years/</link><description>Shares plummeted after sales dropped this month for the first time since the early days of Covid in 2020.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 10:34:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>