<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:50:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>What Price Risk? Unpacking the Equity Risk Premium</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/24/what-price-risk-unpacking-the-equity-risk-premium/</link><description>Stocks are a good wager over the long term, on favorable odds. But stocks remain a bet, and investors must grasp how much returns can vary over long time horizons.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Domino's will tip you if you tip your driver</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/25/dominos-pizza-tip-drivers-discounts-promotion/</link><description>Tip $3, get a $3 coupon.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:44:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Equity Income Investing Redux</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/22/equity-income-investing-redux/</link><description>No doubt the past year has been difficult for equity income investors. But history, inherent biases, mean reversion, and the current market backdrop point to a comeback.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 17:19:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>High interest rates catch up to economic growth as GDP slows dramatically to 1.6%</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/25/economy-gdp-growth-high-interest-rates-1-6/</link><description>Consumers kept spending at a solid pace, but overall, the economy's “momentum is cooling," said one economist.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:22:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: Enrich Your Future</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/18/book-review-enrich-your-future/</link><description>This engaging book is simultaneously memorable and humorous. The numerous sports analogies will have you smiling as you absorb Larry Swedroe's unforgettable investment precepts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 18:07:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sam Altman’s Worldcoin eyeing partnerships with PayPal and OpenAI</title><link>https://fortune.com/crypto/2024/04/25/sam-altman-worldcoin-partnerships-paypal-openai/</link><description>Tools for Humanity has dropped hints it soon could be collaborating with major tech and finance companies, despite a declining rate of new users.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:13:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CAPE Is High: Should You Care?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/17/cape-is-high-should-you-care/</link><description>A simple analysis shows that Robert Shiller's cyclically adjusted price-to-earnings ratio changed in the 1990s and that mean-reversion concerns may be misplaced. If CAPE changed three decades ago, however, there is nothing preventing it from doing so again.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 15:18:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PBS Retro brings back your childhood favorite shows</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/25/pbs-retro-channel-free-fast-tv/</link><description>Options include Mister Rogers Neighborhood, Zoboomafoo and Reading Rainbow.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:05:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI to the Rescue? Overhauling the US Power Grid on the Path to Net Zero</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/15/ai-to-the-rescue-overhauling-the-us-power-grid-on-the-path-to-net-zero/</link><description>Once known as secure and profitable investments, utilities are now viewed as enterprises fraught with financial risks. Investors should favor utilities that employ AI and other digital strategies to minimize damage from natural disasters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 21:24:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Movement Labs raises $38 million to build layer 2 blockchain on Ethereum with Facebook tech</title><link>https://fortune.com/crypto/2024/04/25/movement-labs-funding-polychain-ethereum-monad-blockchain-facebook/</link><description>Polychain led the Series A funding round, which included participation from Hack VC, dao5, and Robot Ventures.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 15:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>