<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 06:43:03 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NFL Second, Third Helmet Concept Series – AFC East</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/19/nfl-second-third-helmet-concept-series-afc-east/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Our newest concept series creates second and/or third helmet designs for every NFL team, starting with the AFC East.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 14:24:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gayle King Defends Justin Timberlake After DWI, Says He Isn't Irresponsible</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/19/gayle-king-defends-justin-timberlake-after-dwi-arrest-not-irresponsible/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Gayle King's sticking up for Justin Timberlake ... saying he's a responsible, upstanding dude who just made a one-off bad decision when he allegedly chose to drink and drive. The newscaster gave her take on "CBS Mornings" Wednesday after a segment…</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 06:43:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>An Apparent Leak of the New Anaheim Ducks Uniforms &amp; Logo?</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/18/apparent-leak-of-new-anaheim-ducks-uniforms-logo/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Just one day after the Anaheim Ducks dropped a tantalizing teaser, an eager Reddit user may have spoiled the party. Thanks to a few dozen folks sending me messages, we learned that earlier today, Reddit user The_Illa_Vanilla posted an image to the Reddit/Hockey boards purportedly showing the new Anaheim Ducks</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 21:50:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Simone Biles Breaks Down In Tears Over Tokyo Olympics Struggles In Doc Trailer</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/19/simone-biles-cries-after-withdrawing-from-tokyo-olympics-in-new-trailer/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Simone Biles is pulling back the curtains on the personal struggles she experienced during the 2020 Olympics ... sharing footage of herself breaking down in tears as she discussed her mental health as part of an upcoming documentary. Netflix just…</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 06:43:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Baltimore Ravens Add New Purple and Gold Helmet</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/18/baltimore-ravens-add-new-purple-and-gold-helmet/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Purple will reign in Baltimore this fall. The Baltimore Ravens just announced their new alternate ‘Purple Rising’ helmet, to be worn for one game this upcoming season. The shell is purple, with two gold stripes going down the middle and a gold facemask. The team’s wordmark is on the front</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 15:37:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Justin Timberlake Warned Miami Crowd 'Be Careful Out There' Before DWI Bust</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/19/justin-timberlake-warned-miami-crowd-be-careful-days-before-dwi-arrest/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Justin Timberlake had sage advice for one of his concert crowds just two nights before his DWI arrest ... and his words of wisdom could have come in handy for himself in Sag Harbor. TMZ obtained video from Justin's Saturday tour stop in Miami,…</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 06:43:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anaheim Ducks Drop a Mighty Good Teaser</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/17/anaheim-ducks-drop-a-mighty-good-teaser/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Anaheim Ducks today posted a teaser graphic that teases a potential new Mighty Ducks of Anaheim themed uniform. Posted to their various social media channels, the teaser shows a closeup of the eye of the mask from the club’s original Mighty Ducks logo but with some subtle modernizations. Unfortunately,</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 22:39:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Louisiana to Require Ten Commandments Posters in Classrooms</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/19/louisiana-require-ten-commandments-displayed-classrooms-jeff-landry-bill/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Louisiana's getting back to basics in its education system, 'cause a new law requiring schools to display some of the oldest written rules in every class just kicked in ... and holy cow! The new law demands a poster-sized display of the Biblical…</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 06:43:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Uruguay Launches First Home and Away Kits Under New Nike Deal</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/17/uruguay-launches-first-home-and-away-kits-under-new-nike-deal/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Kits are not yet available for retail purchase; AUF warns that any shirts out there are fakes and they will take "necessary legal action" against counterfeiters</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 20:53:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Justin Timberlake DWI Arrest Sparks the Fury of Mothers Against Drunk Driving</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/19/justin-timberlake-dwi-arrest-spark-fury-mothers-against-drunk-driving-madd-ceo/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Justin Timberlake has a prime opportunity to save lives in the wake of his arrest, but only if he's willing to own up to the alleged DWI ... so says Mothers Against Drunk Driving. Stacey D. Stewart, CEO of MADD, tells TMZ that JT is seriously lucky…</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 06:43:03 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>