<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 06:39:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NBA Unveils New Logo For Emirates NBA Cup</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/13/nba-unveils-new-logo-for-emirates-nba-cup/basketball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The NBA recently unveiled a new logo for the Emirates NBA Cup, the league’s second annual in-season tournament that will culminate with the championship game at T-Mobile Arena in Las Vegas on Dec. 17.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 16:08:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Harrison Butker Fires Back At Serena Williams For ESPYs Diss</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/13/harrison-butker-serena-williams-fires-back-espy-awards-women-sport/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Harrison Butker fired back at Serena Williams for her critical comments about him onstage while he was sitting in the audience at the ESPY Awards this week. Butker took a shot at the tennis legend for dissing his views about women becoming…</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 06:39:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ohtani, Harper Top the Most Popular MLB Jerseys List for 2024</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/12/ohtani-harper-top-the-most-popular-mlb-jerseys-list-for-2024/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Los Angeles Dodgers superstar Shohei Ohtani’s popularity shows no signs of slowing down as it was announced today that his jersey ranked on top of the most popular jersey list for the first half of the 2024 season. This marks the second consecutive season in which Ohtani has led the</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 19:39:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alec Baldwin Breaks Silence on Shocking 'Rust' Case Dismissal</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/13/alec-baldwin-breaks-silence-rust-case-dismissal-prejudice-manslaughter-trial-thanks-supporters/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Alec Baldwin's finally ready to talk about the his manslaughter trial ... posting a grateful tribute to his friends and fans who stuck by his sides. The actor posted a photo to Instagram moments ago ... a profile shot from the trial -- and, given…</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 06:39:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Atlético de Madrid Pays Homage to Double-Winning Squad – Plus Other Recent European Kit Unveilings</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/12/atletico-de-madrid-pays-homage-to-double-winning-squad-plus-other-recent-european-kit-unveilings/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Other clubs launching new kits include Athletic Bilbao, Celta Vigo, Crystal Palace, Montpellier, RB Leipzig, Werder Bremen, Augsburg, Hellas Verona, Lazio</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 18:43:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'One Tree Hill' Star Jana Kramer Marries Allan Russell in Scotland</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/13/jana-kramer-marry-golfer-allan-russell-scotland-wedding/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Jana Kramer's a married woman once again ... tying the knot with her beau Allan Russell -- in his native Scotland! The actress-turned-podcaster officially tied the knot with Russell -- a pro soccer coach -- Saturday at Carnell Estate in the British…</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 06:39:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Virginia Tech Hokies Unveil New Football Uniforms Following Video Game Leak</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/11/virginia-tech-hokies-unveil-new-football-uniforms-following-video-game-leak/college/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Virginia Tech unveiled new uniforms on Thursday – one day earlier than expected – after having them leaked during a livestream of EA Sports' new College Football 25 video game.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 01:51:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Travis Kelce Comforts Bloodied Fan After Hitting Her with Golf Ball, Video Shows</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/13/travis-kelce-comforts-bloodied-fan-hit-her-golf-ball-video-shows-acc-tournament/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Travis Kelce had a couple shots get away from him during his charity golf game Friday ... and, one left a woman bloodied, video obtained by TMZ shows. The video captures the aftermath of the incident ... with eyewitnesses telling TMZ Travis…</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 06:39:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Purdue Boilermakers Reveal New Football Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/11/purdue-boilermakers-reveal-new-football-uniforms/college/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Purdue unveiled new uniforms on Thursday that feature a striping pattern inspired by the Boilermakers' helmets under legendary coach Joe Tiller.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 23:48:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kim, Khloe Kardashian Covered in Diamonds for Day 2 of Billionaire Wedding</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/13/kim-khloe-kardashian-covered-diamonds-day-2-billionaire-wedding/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Kim and Khloe Kardashian's trip to India will end soon enough, but their outfits are gonna live on forever ... 'cause they're covered in diamonds -- and, we all know how long they last. The reality TV sisters hit the second day of Anant Ambani and…</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 06:39:05 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>