<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 13:06:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Ole Miss Rebels Unveil Powder Blue-Accented Road Jersey</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/24/ole-miss-rebels-unveil-powder-blue-accented-road-jersey/college/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Ole Miss unveiled the first powder blue-accented road jersey in school history on Monday morning, granting the wishes of a large portion of the Rebels' fanbase.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 17:29:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MTV's 'Real World' Star Sarah Becker Dead at 52 By Suicide</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/23/mtvs-real-world-star-sarah-becker-dead-at-52/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Sarah Becker -- a reality television star who appeared on MTV's "The Real World" -- has died by suicide ... TMZ has learned. A family member of Becker confirmed the tragic news to TMZ ... telling us she died early last week at her home in Illinois.…</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 13:06:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Washington Capitals Celebrate 50th Anniversary With New Logos, Patches, and More</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/24/washington-capitals-celebrate-50th-anniversary-with-new-logos-jersey-patches-and-more/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Washington Capitals will celebrate their 50th anniversary in 2024-25 with a series of fun events, but most importantly (to us, anyway), a fantastic new series of commemorative anniversary logos and a jersey patch. The logo was designed in collaboration with FANBRANDZ. Over the past decade-plus, this agency has created</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 16:11:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Says 'Apprentice' Showed Him Good Ratings Excuse Horrible Behavior</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/23/donald-trump-apprentice-good-ratings-horrible-behavior-mean-book/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Donald Trump says he learned people could get away with abhorrent behavior as long as they had good ratings like he did on "The Apprentice" ... according to a bombshell book. The ex-prez made the claims during an interview with Variety…</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 13:06:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tennessee Volunteers’ New “Smokey Grey” Alternate Jerseys Leak</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/22/tennessee-volunteers-new-smokey-grey-alternate-jerseys-leak/college/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>For the second year in a row, Tennessee had its new “Smokey Grey” alternate jersey leaked by Dick’s Sporting Goods after the retailer had a mannequin wearing the jersey on display on Friday afternoon.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 21:52:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Guess Who This Birthday Cutie Turned Into!</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/24/guess-who-this-birthday-cutie-turned-into/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Before this lil' Florida gal in her Minnie Mouse tee turned into a Bravoleb, she was just a theater kid dancing around the house, riding horses at just 6 years old and dreaming of becoming a Broadway star! She may have started out as Scheana Shay's…</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 13:06:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2024 MLB All-Star Game, Workout Caps Released</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/21/2024-mlb-all-star-game-workout-caps-released/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The stars at night will be big and bright (emphasis on bright), deep in the heart of Texas next month at the 2024 Major League Baseball All-Star Game. SHOP: Get your 2024 MLB All-Star Game on-field cap right now, right here Today, the league, along with New Era, unveiled the</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 18:54:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>L.A. Stilt House From 'Heat' Sells for More than a  Million</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/24/la-stilt-house-from-heat-sold/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>The famed Stilt House from Michael Mann's crime film "Heat" has a new owner ... as someone has nabbed up the notable property for a pretty penny. The iconic East L.A. home -- which was featured in a pivotal scene in the Robert De Niro and Al…</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 13:06:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Crystal Palace, Valencia Headline Recent Kit Launches From Around Europe</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/21/crystal-palace-valencia-headline-recent-kit-launches-from-around-europe/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Other clubs releasing 2024-25 kits recently include: Getafe CF, Borussia Mönchengladbach, Stade Rennais, RC Lens, FC Nantes, SL Benfica, FC Porto</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 15:16:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jon Voight Credits Granddaughter With Helping Mom Angelina Jolie Win Tony</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/24/jon-voight-angelina-jolie-vivienne-tonys-outsiders-brad-pitt-broadway/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Jon Voight's super stoked his daughter Angelina Jolie won her first Tony Award ... a win he says may not have happened had his granddaughter not found the play! We caught up with the legendary actor at LAX and asked about his daughter's big win for…</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 13:06:59 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>