<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 06:16:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The Ripple Effect: Minnesota Twins Launch New City Connect Uniform</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/10/the-ripple-effect-minnesota-twins-launch-new-city-connect-uniform/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Minnesota Twins dropped their new 10,000 Lakes themed City Connect uniform. We spoke with the team and explored every aspect of the new uniform together.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 14:34:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Power' Star Michael Rainey Jr. Allegedly Sexually Assaulted on Live Stream</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/10/michael-rainey-jr-sexually-assaulted-livestream-tylil-show-sister/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>3:23 PM PT -- 50 Cent weighed in on our post and downplayed notions of S.A. in favor of an "aggressive advance" and denied Michael Rainey Jr. would press charges. We'll have to see if he's officially speaking for his young star. 12:47 PM PT --…</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 06:16:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Minnesota Golden Gophers Unveil New Football Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/08/minnesota-golden-gophers-unveil-new-football-uniforms/college/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Minnesota unveiled three new uniforms on Friday morning, marking the first significant overhaul to the Golden Gophers’ look since the 2018 season.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 16:30:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Carrie Underwood Falls Off Stage on Tail End of South Carolina Concert</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/10/carrie-underwood-falls-off-stage-south-carolina-concert-country-music-fest/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Carrie Underwood capped off her concert this weekend by belting out tunes in the rain -- but there was an even more dramatic finish as she was exiting the stage ... 'cause she fell. The singer was the headlining performance Sunday night at the…</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 06:16:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MLB World Tour London 2024 Logos, Caps, and More – Mets vs. Phillies</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/08/mlb-world-tour-london-2024-logos-caps-and-more-mets-vs-phillies/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The New York Mets and Philadelphia Phillies are in England this weekend for a two-game series, the next stop on Major League Baseball’s 2024 World Tour. It’s the third time the league has gone to the United Kingdom for regular season baseball, having done so previously in 2019 with the</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 16:17:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Madonna's Lawyer Slams 'False' Settlement News in Delayed Concert Lawsuit</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/10/madonna-lawyer-slams-false-settlement-delayed-concert-lawsuit/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>1:38 PM PT -- At a hearing Monday, the judge presiding over this case ended up siding with Madonna's legal team -- namely, there was clearly NO settlement that had been struck, and some kind of miscommunication occurred. He struck the settlement…</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 06:16:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Newcastle United Make Long-Awaited Return to Adidas With 24-25 Home Kit</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/07/newcastle-united-make-long-awaited-return-to-adidas-with-24-25-home-kit/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Kit honors Magpies' traditional black and white vertical stripes and draws inspiration from kit Newcastle wore during the 2002-03 season</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 16:28:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vancouver Seaplane Crashes into Boat During Takeoff, Shocking Footage</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/10/crazy-footage-seaplane-crashing-boat-vancouver/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Two people ended up in the hospital after a small floatplane collided with a pleasure boat in Vancouver -- and the video footage is jaw-dropping ... 'cause it uses the vessel like a ramp. Check out the chaos unfold from Saturday -- the Harbour Air…</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 06:16:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10 Smaller European Countries Get New 2024-26 Kits Thanks to UEFA Kit Assistance Scheme</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/07/10-smaller-european-countries-get-new-2024-26-kits-thanks-to-uefa-kit-assistance-scheme/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>In partnership with Italian manufacturer Erreà, program allows associations that lack bargaining power to get too-caliber kits for their national teams</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 16:04:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>George Lopez Hecklers Not Considered Unruly, Casino Stands By Statement</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/10/george-lopez-hecklers-not-considered-unruly-casino-stands-by-statement/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>The casino where George Lopez cut his set short this weekend is doubling down on their criticism of him -- saying the loud crowd wasn't heckling in their eyes ... they were just adoring fans. A rep for Eagle Mountain Casino -- where George…</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 06:16:51 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>