<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 01:18:52 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>How to Find Real Estate Deals (and Analyze Them) in 5 Easy Steps</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-webinar</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Find real estate deals faster with a BiggerPockets Pro Membership. Use code “PDEAL24” for 20% off plus thousands of dollars in bonuses and access to investment calculators, BiggerPockets deal finder, […]</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 10:00:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Validus, a Singapore-based digital SME lending platform, secures $50M debt financing to help enterprises in Indonesia</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/01/validus-a-singapore-based-digital-sme-lending-platform-secures-50m-debt-financing-to-help-enterprises-in-indonesia/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Validus, a Singapore-based digital lending platform for small and medium businesses, has secured $50 million in debt financing from HSBC under the ASEAN Growth Fund strategy. Validus will use the proceeds to support the financial inclusion of micro, small and medium enterprises (MSMEs) in Indonesia, addressing the challenges they face in accessing financial resources. With […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Efforts to Cut Long Prison Sentences Have Stalled</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/31/wisconsin-california-sentence-prison</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Crime victim advocates and conservative groups are resisting moves to revisit “truth-in-sentencing” laws.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I’m a Buyer’s Agent. Here’s How the New NAR Rules Have Impacted My Business</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/how-the-new-nar-rules-have-impacted-my-business</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Now that the new NAR rules are in effect, Corby Goade, a buyer's agent in Idaho, gives us a look at the real-world impacts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 19:56:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple may ditch those old familiar USB-A ports in the new Mac mini</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/01/apple-may-ditch-those-old-familiar-usb-a-ports-in-the-new-mac-mini/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>The Mac mini will be the next Apple device to say goodbye to USB-A, according to Bloomberg’s Mark Gurman. Apple customers have probably gotten used to seeing the familiar, rectangular USB-A ports replaced with their thinner USB-C siblings. And while USB-C has its advantages, the transition can sometimes leave users confused and scrambling for adapters. […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 21:50:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How a Massachusetts Cop Allegedly Groomed, Controlled and Killed Sandra Birchmore</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/30/police-explorer-sexual-abuse-massachusetts-birchmore</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Matthew Farwell met her in a police Explorer program. Prosecutors say he abused her for years before she became pregnant and he killed her.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lawton, Oklahoma, is the Best Market For New Short-Term Rentals? That’s What the Data Says</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/lawton-oklahoma-is-the-best-market-for-short-term-rental-investors</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Some short-term rental markets are difficult to operate in. Others are downright saturated. But this one, according to the data, is where you need to be.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 19:34:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The case against AI art</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/01/the-case-against-ai-art/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>No matter who powerful generative AI becomes, writer Ted Chiang says it will never create true art. Chiang is one of the most admired science fiction authors writing today, best known for the novella “Story Of Your Life” (which was adapted into the movie “Arrival”). But he’s also published terrific pieces for The New Yorker […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 18:37:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>5 Things to Know About How Survivors Get Incarcerated for Their Abusers’ Crimes</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/28/accomplice-liability-laws-what-to-know</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Little-known laws allow people to be punished for crimes they didn’t directly commit. Survivors of domestic violence are especially vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>5 Ways Real Estate Investors Influence Housing Market Health</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/five-ways-investors-impact-a-housing-market</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Investors make an impact on the housing market, and often in positive ways despite the negative coverage. Here's how.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 18:56:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Palantir’s CTO, and 13th employee, has become a secret weapon for Valley defense tech startups</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/01/tktk/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Palantir CTO Shyam Sankar is determined to help Palantir become a driving force for defense tech startups. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How a Drop in Border Crossings May Change the Presidential Campaign</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/24/kamala-harris-dnc-border-donald-trump</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>The Democratic National Convention sought to address one of the party’s biggest weaknesses with voters.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BiggerNews: How Harris/Trump’s Housing Policies Could Impact Affordability</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-1011</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Housing affordability is at a forty-year low, and we bet you can feel it. Buying a house seems impossibly far away for first-time homebuyers, rent prices are still far past […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 10:00:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘Emotion AI’ may be the next trend for business software, and that could be problematic</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/01/emotion-ai-could-be-the-next-trend-for-business-software-and-that-could-be-problematic/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>As businesses experiment with embedding AI everywhere, one area starting to gain more attention is Emotion AI. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 16:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Prosecutors Fight Exonerations</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/17/wrongful-conviction-innocence-claims-missouri-st-louis</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>As laws are passed to support the wrongfully convicted, some officials in the legal system push back.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>