<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 07:00:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>First Look at the 2025 MLB Spring Training Logos</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/17/first-look-at-the-2025-mlb-spring-training-logos/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Is it that time of the year already? This week, Major League Baseball released its new official logos for its 2025 Spring Training schedule. This year’s logos for the annual six-week slate of exhibition games include an all-new primary mark, a slightly modified alternate design, and designs for both the</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 16:08:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Two Doctors Charged in Matthew Perry's Death Can Still Prescribe Medicine</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/17/matthew-perry-doctors-charged-prescribe-medicine/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>The two physicians charged in connection with Matthew Perry's death not only still have their medical licenses, but they can still -- SHOCKINGLY -- prescribe medication to any of their patients, TMZ has learned. Last week, Dr. Mark Chavez and Dr.…</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 07:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2024-25 European Football Kit Preview: Serie A</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/17/2024-25-european-football-kit-preview-serie-a/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>123rd season of top-flight soccer in Italy kicks off on Saturday, August 17, with defending champs Inter Milan taking on Genoa CFC</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ariana Madix's Brother Jeremy Busted For Possessing a Mountain of Weed</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/17/ariana-madix-brother-jeremy-weed-vanderpump-rules/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Ariana Madix's brother Jeremy is in major trouble with the law ... police say he and an accomplice were busted with suitcases filled with over 100 pounds of marijuana. According to court documents, obtained by TMZ ... Jeremy Madix – who has…</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 07:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CFL Running Back Becomes First Pro Football Player to Wear Guardian Cap in Regular Season Game</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/16/cfl-running-back-becomes-first-pro-football-player-to-wear-guardian-cap-in-regular-season-game/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Saskatchewan Roughriders running back Thomas Bertrand-Hudon wears concussion prevention cover in game against Montreal Alouettes on Friday, August 16</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 03:05:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Travis Kelce Catches Wild, Behind the Back Pass From Patrick Mahomes</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/17/travis-kelce-patrick-mahomes-behind-back-pass/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Travis Kelce and Patrick Mahomes look in midseason form already ... 'cause the two just connected on a crazy behind the back pass. The play happened just moments ago during the Lions vs Chiefs preseason game ... on third down with three yards to…</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 07:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Phoenix Suns, Washington Wizards’ 2024-25 City Edition Shorts Leak On Social Media</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/16/phoenix-suns-washington-wizards-2024-25-city-edition-shorts-leak-on-social-media/basketball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Continuing today’s theme, the Phoenix Suns and Washington Wizards’ new City Edition shorts were leaked on social media on Friday morning.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 18:43:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Brian Cox Says Hugh Jackman, Ryan Reynolds Can 'Do More' Than Superhero Movies</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/17/brian-cox-hugh-jackman-ryan-reynolds-superhero/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Brian Cox ain't holding back on superhero flicks ... saying guys like Hugh Jackman and Ryan Reynolds are too talented for 'em -- but, he can't knock them for taking the cash. The actor spoke at a panel for the Edinburgh International Film Festival…</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 07:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Memphis Grizzlies’ Sounds-Inspired City Edition, Vancouver Classic Edition Shorts Leak</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/16/memphis-grizzlies-sounds-inspired-city-edition-vancouver-classic-edition-shorts-leak/basketball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Although tipoff of the 2024-25 NBA season is still two months away, the Memphis Grizzlies’ new City and Classic Edition shorts were leaked in our forums on Thursday.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 17:28:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Matthew Perry Shouldn't Be Remembered For Death, 'Friends' Creator Says</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/17/matthew-perry-death-remember-friends-creator/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Matthew Perry's death getting attention amid the numerous arrests made by law enforcement ... but, one of his oldest collaborators wants people to remember his life instead. Marta Kauffman -- creator of the hit series "Friends" -- discussed the…</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 07:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>