<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 12:44:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>West Virginia Mountaineers Unveil New Football Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/29/west-virginia-mountaineers-unveil-new-football-uniforms/college/</link><description>West Virginia unveiled new uniforms over the weekend that pay homage to different eras of Mountaineer football while maintaining a few modern touches.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 19:39:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TMZ TV Hot Takes: Brian Cox, Jon Bon Jovi, Logan Paul &amp; Patrick Mahomes</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/01/tmz-tv-hot-takes-brian-cox-jon-bon-jovi-logan-paul-and-patrick-mahomes/</link><description>We're only a few days into a new week ... and there's already so much to discuss!!! First up, on "TMZ Live," Harvey and Charles discuss Brian Cox slamming the Bible as the worst book ever ... sounding off on organized religion altogether. Next up,…</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 12:44:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Grit and Glow: Tampa Bay Rays Unveil Skateboard-Inspired City Connect Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/29/grit-and-glow-tampa-bay-rays-unveil-skateboard-inspired-city-connect-uniforms/baseball/</link><description>The Tampa Bay Rays unveiled their new Nike MLB City Connect Series uniform today, taking inspiration from the region’s skateboarding culture while also mixing in a few fun little nods to the team’s history. These uniforms are set to make their on-field debut during a special weekend series from May</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 16:42:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ex-NFLer Jay 'Finesse' Ajayi Drops Debut Rap Single, Hoping For Future Collab W/ Travis Scott</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/01/jay-ajayi-finesse-travis-scott-rapper-super-bowl-champ-new-music-nfl/</link><description>Former Super Bowl champion Jay Ajayi has traded in his cleats for a mic -- officially entering the music game with a debut rap single this week -- and he's hoping the response to the tunes is so good, it'll lead to a future collab with Travis…</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 12:44:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jacksonville Jaguars Reveal 30th Season Logo Following Fan Vote</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/28/jacksonville-jaguars-reveal-30th-season-logo-following-fan-vote/football/</link><description>After asking fans to vote among four unique designs, the Jacksonville Jaguars officially unveiled their new 30th season logo during their 2024 NFL Draft party on Thursday evening.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 15:43:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Richard Simmons Weighs In On McCarthy-Streisand Ozempic Drama</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/01/richard-simmons-ozempic-comment-melissa-mccarthy-barbra-streisand/</link><description>The drama between Melissa McCarthy and Barbra Streisand over an Ozempic question ain't over yet ... 'cause Richard Simmons is now weighing on the matter. In a Facebook post Tuesday night, the legendary exercise guru threw his full support behind…</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 12:44:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NFL Will Allow Players To Wear Guardian Caps In Games</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/28/nfl-will-allow-players-to-wear-guardian-caps-in-games/football/</link><description>The NFL announced it will now allow players to wear Guardian Caps, a 12-ounce soft shell that fits over their helmets, during regular-season games in an effort to reduce head injuries.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 15:25:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Bachelorette' Star Jason Tartick Does Dinner with New Girlfriend</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/01/jason-tartick-kat-stickler-grab-dinner-with-daughter/</link><description>'Bachelorette' alum Jason Tartick is taking his new relationship with TikTok star Kat Stickler out of the shadows and into the spotlight ... as the pair stepped out for a dinner date Monday evening. The couple hit the town in Tampa, FL at the…</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 12:44:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Report: CFL’s Saskatchewan Roughriders to Add Fourth Uniform in 2024</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/27/report-cfls-saskatchewan-roughriders-to-add-fourth-uniform-in-2024/football/</link><description>Riders reportedly adding uniform that's predominantly a darker shade of green than usual; helmet to feature logo filed with Canadian trademark office in 2022</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 18:13:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Britney Spears Calls Sister Jamie Lynn 'Bitch' in Rambling Car Video</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/30/britney-spears-calls-sister-jamie-lynn-bitch-rambling-video-car/</link><description>Britney Spears is back to attacking her little sister, Jamie Lynn Spears -- out here calling her a "bitch" ... this while going on and on about things that just don't make sense. The pop star posted a few since-deleted videos to her Instagram Story…</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 12:44:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>