<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:15:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Houston Texans Unveil Four New Uniforms, Two New Helmets</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/23/houston-texans-unveil-four-new-uniforms-two-new-helmets/football/</link><description>The Houston Texans unveiled their new uniforms on Tuesday morning, including four distinctly different designs intended to satisfy every corner of the fanbase.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 16:17:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Larry Nassar Victims Get $138M Payout From Gov Over Botched FBI Investigation</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/23/larry-nassar-victims-reach-settlement-botched-investigation-fbi-justice-gymnastics/</link><description>Victims of disgraced former Team USA doctor Larry Nassar will receive a massive $138.7 million payout from the U.S. Department of Justice. The U.S. Department of Justice announced Tuesday they'd be shelling out the huge payment to 139 victims ...…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:15:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Madison Mallards unveil alternates IN A VAN DOWN BY THE RIVER</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/22/madison-mallards-unveil-alternates-in-a-van-down-by-the-river/baseball/</link><description>The collegiate summer level Madison Mallards unveiled an alternate identity today based on a classic Saturday Night Live sketch that featured the late, great Madison native Chris Farley over three decades ago in 1993. The logo and uniforms evoke Farley’s character Matt Foley, a down-on-his-luck motivational speaker who famously lives</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 01:21:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dermot Mulroney Fiercely Defends Sydney Sweeney After Hateful Comments</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/23/dermot-mulroney-defends-sydney-sweeney-hollywood-producer-criticism/</link><description>Dermot Mulroney believes Sydney Sweeney is so much more than a pretty face -- despite the fact some believe she's just getting by in showbiz on good looks and a rockin' bod. We caught up with the actor in L.A. Tuesday ... where he addressed…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:15:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Minnesota Vikings Alternate, New York Giants Throwback Jerseys Leak</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/22/minnesota-vikings-alternate-new-york-giants-throwback-jerseys-leak/football/</link><description>Former NFL wide receiver Antonio Brown's social media network leaked two more jerseys that will be worn this season, including a Minnesota Vikings alternate and New York Giants throwback design.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 21:24:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jelly Roll Quit Social Media Over Body-Shaming, Says Wife Bunnie Xo</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/23/jelly-roll-quit-social-media-body-shaming-wife-bunnie-xo/</link><description>Jelly Roll might be country's hottest artist right now, but he's still dealing with online bullying ... and his wife, Bunnie XO, says it finally pushed him to a breaking point. The model came to her husband's defense during an episode of her "Dumb…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:15:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Denver Broncos Unveil New “Mile High” Uniforms, Revive Throwback Design</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/22/denver-broncos-unveil-new-mile-high-uniforms-tease-throwback/football/</link><description>Although a series of leaks ruined the surprise, the Denver Broncos officially unveiled new uniforms on Monday morning, marking the first significant overhaul of their look in 27 years.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 16:35:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nikola Jokic's Brother Punches Fan In Heated Altercation, NBA Investigating</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/23/nikola-jokic-brother-punches-fan-heated-altercation-nuggets-lakers-game/</link><description>8:20 AM PT -- TMZ Sports has learned ... the NBA is currently looking into the situation. Nikola Jokic's brother was in no mood to celebrate the Nuggets' comeback win over the Lakers on Monday ... 'cause he straight-up punched a fan in the stands…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:15:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nashville Sounds pay tribute to parent club, beer with new Brewskis cap</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/21/nashville-sounds-pay-tribute-to-parent-club-beer-with-new-brewskis-cap/baseball/</link><description>The Triple-A Nashville Sounds have been an affiliate of the Milwaukee Brewers since 2021, and before that from 2005 to 2014. The team is continuing a popular tribute to its parent club this season, playing as the Nashville Brewskis. The Sounds introduced the powder blue alternates designed by Brandon Lamarche</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 16:28:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kanye Plans to Launch 'Yeezy Porn,' Consulting with Stormy Daniels' Ex</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/23/kanye-west-launch-yeezy-porn-partner-stormy-daniels-ex-husband/</link><description>Kanye West has his sights set on a new business venture, and it's all about people having sex on camera -- the guy's looking to professionally dive into porn at long last ... TMZ has learned. A rep for Yeezy tells TMZ ... Ye's been kicking around…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:15:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>