<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from multiple RSS sources, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 12:04:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Scaling from 0 to 20+ Doors Using These “Self-Management” Tools &amp; Tips</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-938</link><description>If there’s one thing that’ll make or break your real estate portfolio, it’s property management. When done correctly, property management can feed you consistent, passive income without the everyday stressors […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 07:02:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Brave Search is adopting AI to answer your queries</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/17/brave-search-is-adopting-ai-to-answer-your-queries/</link><description>The new "Answer with AI" feature returns neatly formatted answers for questions like "People who walked on the moon," "List of all actors who played Batman" or "How do descale Nespresso pixie."
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 17:00:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Parents Paying for Their Children’s Crimes</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/13/michigan-school-shooting-parents</link><description>Experts warn about a wave of legal consequences for parents like the Crumbleys, while some states consider prosecutions for kids as young as 10.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Truth About Whole-Body Scans</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/a-to-z-guides/features/truth-about-whole-body-scans?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>What to know about whole-body CT scans and DEXA scans for body composition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 23:15:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Hidden Property Damage That Could Ruin Your Home Renovation…</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-394</link><description>Added home renovation costs can ruin your plans to own the perfect rental property. When this happens, how do you come up with the extra funds? More importantly, how do […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 07:02:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cherub, an angel investing community inspired by dating apps, entices investors and founders to pair up</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/17/cherub-the-raya-of-angel-investing-is-reinventing-angel-rounds-with-a-950-subscription/</link><description>Jaclyn Johnson and Angeline Vuong were on a hike deliberating how hard it can be for people to get started in angel investing when they realized they had stumbled upon a startup idea. 
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 16:42:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I Had a Tough Job at My Brooklyn Jail: Keeping Men From Taking Their Own Lives</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/12/brooklyn-jail-suicide-prevention-aide</link><description>As a suicide prevention aide, I had to make sure my fellow detainees didn’t harm themselves. It was surprisingly easy to get such a complex job.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When to Call a Pediatrician</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/parenting/baby/features/when-call-pediatrician?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Your child is sick. Do you know if you should call the pediatrician, or wait? Use this guide to know when to make the call.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 22:44:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seeing Greene: Paying Off Rentals, Estimating Crime, &amp; Replacing Your Salary</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-937</link><description>Should I pay off my rental property or reinvest? How do I replace my six-figure salary with cash flow from real estate investing? And what’s the best way to analyze […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 07:02:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>a16z-backed Rewind pivots to build AI-powered pendant to record your conversations</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/17/a16z-backed-rewind-pivots-to-build-ai-powered-pendant-to-record-your-conversations/</link><description>a16z-backed Rewind is now pivoting to build AI-powered meeting suit along with a hardware product to record your conversations.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 16:34:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Supreme Court Case on Homelessness May Limit Prisoner Rights and Expand Executions</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/10/supreme-court-homeless-grants-pass-originalism</link><description>In Grants Pass v. Johnson, a town in Oregon asks the court to reconsider what constitutes “cruel and unusual punishments”.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Your Baby’s Reflux: What to Do</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/parenting/baby/features/soothing-baby-reflux?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>When is spitting up normal, and when is it a problem? Learn signs to watch out for, as a pediatrician and parent who’s been there share their wisdom.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 22:41:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The BEST Side Hustles You Can Start in 2024 (Outside of Real Estate!)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-520</link><description>The best side hustles can put some extra cash in your pocket, help you leave your W2 job, or even launch you toward FIRE. If you’re looking to make money […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 07:01:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ByteDance gets 24 hours to show EU a DSA risk assessment for TikTok Lite</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/17/byedance-rfi-tiktok-lite/</link><description>TikTok owner ByteDance is facing fresh questions about its compliance with the European Union’s Digital Services Act (DSA), an online governance and content moderation framework that puts a legal obligation on larger platforms to mitigate systemic risks in areas like youth mental health. The EU’s latest concerns about TikTok’s DSA compliance center on the launch […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 16:19:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What an Eclipse Lockdown Reveals about Dignity in Prisons and Jails</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/06/eclipse-new-york-prison-discrimination</link><description>Recent lawsuits regarding the rights of incarcerated people and guards include gender, religious discrimination, and the right to watch the eclipse</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How New Ideas Are Changing Advanced Breast Cancer Research</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/breast-cancer/features/breast-cancer-new-research?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>There are many reasons for women who have advanced breast cancer to be hopeful. For starters, the way we treat and study advanced, or metastatic, breast cancer is improving.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 18:01:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Beyond the Mailbox: Innovative Direct Mail Strategies That Win in Today’s Market</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/direct-mail-strategies-for-real-estate-investors</link><description>This article is presented by DealMachine. Read our editorial guidelines for more information. Breaking news: Direct mail is still a key factor in real estate marketing, and it has the potential to be […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 20:24:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NeuBird is building a generative AI solution for complex cloud-native environments</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/17/neubird-generative-ai-solution-for-complex-cloud-environments-raises-22-million/</link><description>NeuBird founders Goutham Rao and Vinod Jayaraman came from Portworx, a cloud-native storage solution they eventually sold to PureStorage in 2019 for $370 million. It was their third successful exit.  When they went looking for their next startup challenge last year, they saw an opportunity to combine their cloud-native knowledge, especially around IT operations, with […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 16:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I Made 13 Cents an Hour as a Prison Janitor. Here’s Why I Donated My Wages to Gaza Relief</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/05/prison-janitor-donates-gaza-relief-islam</link><description>It’s a common misconception that once someone enters jail or prison, they lose their interest in the outside world.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Heart Attack Hits Young Women, But Doctors Often Unaware</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/heart-disease/news/20240416/scad-heart-attacks-a-ticking-time-bomb-for-young-women?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>SCAD accounts for 1 in 3 acute heart events in younger women. Many doctors are not aware it exists.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 17:52:20 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>