<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Aggregated RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/aggregated_feed.xml</link><description>This is an aggregated feed of multiple RSS sources.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 08:23:36 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Cleveland Browns Legend Leaks Team’s New Helmet for 2024</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/16/cleveland-browns-legend-leaks-teams-new-helmet-for-2024/football/</link><description>Despite last suiting up for the Browns thirty years ago, Eric Metcalf is still turning heads in Cleveland. Late last night, the Cleveland Browns legend posted a mini Browns helmet he received in the mail from the team with the caption, “OG making a comeback in ’24!!!”. The problem was</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 18:31:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jacksonville Jaguars Tease Throwback Uniforms On Social Media</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/15/jacksonville-jaguars-tease-throwback-uniforms-on-social-media/football/</link><description>The Jacksonville Jaguars shared a video on social media that strongly hinted at the franchise wearing throwback uniforms during the upcoming season.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 20:05:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New York Jets Go Throwback Uniforms Full-Time, Unveil New Green, Black Versions</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/15/new-york-jets-go-throwback-uniforms-full-time-unveil-new-green-black-versions/football/</link><description>The New York Jets have officially promoted their "Legacy" throwback uniforms to full-time road status and unveiled corresponding green home and black alternate uniforms.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 14:26:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Report: Coyotes to Utah “Not a Traditional Relocation”</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/14/report-coyotes-to-utah-not-a-traditional-relocation/hockey-2/</link><description>The Arizona Coyotes and owner Alex Meruelo may get the coveted Cleveland Browns deal as part of the club’s anticipated move to Salt Lake City for next season. According to a Tweet from ESPN’s Greg Wyshynski, after the club shifts to Utah, Meruelo may be able to bring the Coyotes</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 15:54:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Denver Broncos Uniform Redesign Contest Results</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/14/denver-broncos-uniform-redesign-contest-results/football/</link><description>We're excited to announce the winners of our Denver Broncos uniform redesign contest, which received more than 60 submissions on social media and through email.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 15:38:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deaf Newcastle Fans Get A Whole New Feel for the Game With Vibrating Kits</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/13/deaf-newcastle-fans-get-a-whole-new-feel-for-the-game-with-vibrating-kits/soccer/</link><description>Haptic kits that use sensors to vibrate when action takes place on the pitch introduced for Saturday's match against Tottenham Hotspur</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 20:02:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Uruguay Signs Kit Deal With Nike in Time for 2024 Copa América</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/13/uruguay-sits-kit-deal-with-nike-in-time-for-2024-copa-america/soccer/</link><description>AUF produced two sets of kits for national teams in-house in months between Puma deal running out at end of 2023 and new Nike contract</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 18:29:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New York Mets Tease Purple “NY” Logo, City Connect Uniform Coming April 19th?</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/12/new-york-mets-tease-purple-ny-logo-city-connect-uniform-coming-april-19th/baseball/</link><description>The New York Mets have dropped a couple of teasers for (what we assume is) their new City Connect uniform, and, well, it guarantees we’re in for an interesting next few days. Posted to their various social media channels, the posts simply read “Coming next Friday” with a 15-second embedded</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 23:48:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MLB’s Jackie Robinson Day Caps, Jerseys, and More for ’24</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/12/mlbs-jackie-robinson-day-caps-jerseys-and-more-for-24/baseball/</link><description>Major League Baseball will once again celebrate Jackie Robinson’s life and legacy this year with the annual Jackie Robinson Day on Monday, April 15. As is tradition, every Major League player, coach, and manager will wear Robinson’s retired #42 in-game on Monday. Regardless of the team’s colours or uniform styles,</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 21:48:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Logo of Singer Karol G to Feature on Front of FC Barcelona Jerseys</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/12/logo-of-singer-karol-g-to-feature-on-front-of-fc-barcelona-jerseys/soccer/</link><description>Colombian singer joins Drake, Rosalía and Rolling Stones as artists whose logos have appeared on Barça's jerseys as part of Spotify deal</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 21:35:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Logo Unveiled for National Indigenous Junior Hockey Championships</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/11/logo-unveiled-for-national-indigenous-junior-hockey-championships/hockey-2/</link><description>Inaugural tournament for male and female players from the ages of 18 to 20 to take place in Toronto in June 2025</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 16:07:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NFL Relaxes Uniform Policy To Allow Teams To Wear Third Helmet Design</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/11/nfl-relaxes-uniform-policy-to-allow-teams-to-wear-third-helmet-design/football/</link><description>The NFL has relaxed its uniform policy to allow teams to wear a third helmet beginning with the 2025 season, though the option was offered to teams going through a redesign this offseason.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 13:59:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>They’re good dogs, Trenton: Thunder honor bat dogs with Goldens alternate</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/10/theyre-good-dogs-trenton-thunder-honor-bat-dogs-with-goldens-alternate/baseball/</link><description>The Trenton Thunder, a member of the collegiate summer level MLB Draft League, will pay tribute to their tradition of bat dogs with the team’s first alternate identity in six years. The Thunder will play two games as the Trenton Goldens, an homage to the family of golden retrievers who</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 23:57:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CanPL’s Cavalry FC Embrace Winter With ‘Blizzard Camo’ Third Kits for 2024</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/10/canpls-cavalry-fc-embrace-winter-with-blizzard-camo-third-kits-for-2024/soccer/</link><description>2024 third kit harkens back to green camouflage jersey that served as Cavalry's alternate shirt during inaugural season in 2019</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 20:17:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MLS Rolls Out New Design for One Planet Kits; Won’t Be Worn in Games This Season</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/09/mls-rolls-out-new-design-for-one-planet-kits-wont-be-worn-in-games-this-season/soccer/</link><description>Shirts feature pattern of graffiti flowers and leaves; will be worn ahead of matches as MLS celebrates 7th annual Greener Goals Week of Service</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 21:44:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Taking A Look At The Logo For The 2025 Final Four In San Antonio</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/09/taking-a-look-at-the-logo-for-the-2025-final-four-in-san-antonio/basketball/</link><description>While they’re still cleaning up confetti following UConn’s 75-60 win over Purdue on Monday night, we’re already looking forward to next year’s NCAA Men’s Final Four, which will take place at the Alamodome in San Antonio on April 5 and 7, 2025.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 21:21:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jazz Owner Asks Fans for Possible Utah NHL Team Names</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/09/jazz-owner-asks-fans-for-possible-utah-nhl-team-names/hockey-2/</link><description>With speculation and excitement surrounding the possibility of the National Hockey League coming to “The Beehive State,” Utah Jazz owner Ryan Smith has added more fuel to the fire with a Tweet seeking suggestions for a potential team name. Of course, the fans came through with an abundance of names,</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:35:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Looking At Purdue, UConn’s National Championship Uniform History</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/08/looking-at-purdue-uconns-national-championship-uniform-history/basketball/</link><description>Taking a look at Purdue and UConn's national championship uniform history ahead of tonight's title game at State Farm Stadium in Glendale, Arizona.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 19:55:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MiLB teams commemorate eclipse with on-field gear</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/08/milb-teams-commemorate-eclipse-with-on-field-gear/baseball/</link><description>Do not look directly at these logos without protective eyewear! Many of the affiliated Minor League Baseball teams along the path of today’s eclipse had or are having promotions to commemorate the rare celestial event. MiLB is calling the series of coordinated events, most of which entail giving away branded</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 12:24:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oakland Athletics Trademark New Names for Sacramento</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/07/oakland-athletics-trademark-new-names-for-sacramento/baseball/</link><description>Despite comments suggesting the Oakland Athletics would be known only as “The Athletics” or “The A’s” when they move to Sacramento next season, the team appears to be considering other, more traditional options. Public records available from the United States Patent and Trademark Office show the Oakland Athletics trademarked two</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 15:52:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gypsy Rose's Estranged Husband Thinks Ken's Call Tanked Marriage</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/17/gypsy-rose-husband-ryan-anderson-ken-call-ruined-marriage/</link><description>Gypsy Rose Blanchard's marriage hit rocky waters after a post-prison phone call from her ex-fiancé -- something we now know her estranged husband finds awfully suspicious. Here's the deal ... sources with direct knowledge tell TMZ that Gypsy's…</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 08:23:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kim Kardashian Poses in Gold Minidress in Pics Taken by North West</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/16/kim-kardashian-poses-in-gold-minidress-in-pics-taken-by-north-west/</link><description>North West appears to be a natural photographer ... taking several striking shots of her mom Kim Kardashian during their vacay in Turks and Caicos. Kim showed off North's handiwork behind the lens with a bunch of pics of herself posing in a gold…</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 08:23:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ohio Man Shoots &amp; Kills Uber Driver After Both of Them Were Scammed</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/16/ohio-man-shoots-kills-uber-driver-both-scammed/</link><description>An Ohio man has been charged in the fatal shooting of an Uber driver, whom he reportedly thought was involved in an elaborate plot to scam him ... and ditto for the woman, BTW. Per reports, 81-year-old William Brock told authorities in Clark County…</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 08:23:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Johnny Depp Will Return to Acting, But Focusing on New Career Chapter</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/17/johnny-depp-will-return-to-acting-focusing-on-directing-not-dating/</link><description>Johnny Depp hasn't retired from acting, despite the fact he's currently giving all his attention to directing right now ... TMZ has learned. Sources close to Johnny tell TMZ ... the Oscar nominee isn't done with performing in front of the camera,…</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 08:23:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Caitlin Clark's H.S. Coach Proud Of Star's Journey To WNBA, Didn't Predict This!</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/17/caitlin-clarks-h-s-coach-proud-of-star-s-journey-to-wnba-didn-t-predict-this/</link><description>Caitlin Clark has always been a baller, but even her own high school coach, Kristin Meyer, never saw this level of stardom coming, telling TMZ Sports, "I can't say that I honestly predicted this!" Don't get it twisted, Meyer knew from the get-go…</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 08:23:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TMZ TV Hot Takes: Courtney Love, Gypsy Rose Blanchard, Devin Haney &amp; Ryan Garcia</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/17/tmz-tv-hot-takes-courtney-love-gypsy-rose-blanchard-devin-haney-ryan-garcia/</link><description>The week has only just started but, in case you're behind, here are some TMZ TV hot takes to catch up on. First up, on "TMZ Live," Harvey and Charles discuss Courtney Love's biting criticism of Taylor Swift. She even came for Beyoncé, too!!! Next,…</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 08:23:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Carter In 'Cinderella Story' 'Memba Him?!</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/17/carter-in-cinderella-story-memba-him/</link><description>American actor Dan Byrd was 18 years old when he played Carter -- the nerdy high schooler and aspiring actor who comes into his own -- in the 2004 high school movie "A Cinderella Story." Dan joined several big Hollywood names on the big screen…</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 08:23:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Katie Couric Says Bryant Gumbel Had 'Sexist Attitude' About Maternity Leave</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/16/katie-couric-bryant-gumbel-sexist-attitude-maternity-leave-today/</link><description>Katie Couric says Bryant Gumbel gave her a hard time back in the day over maternity ... which Katie thinks spoke to something deeper, even if he was joking. The famed newswoman stopped by Bill Maher's 'Club Random' podcast Sunday ... in which she…</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 08:23:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jenna Jameson's Wife Files for Divorce After Less Than Year of Marriage</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/16/jenna-jameson-wife-jessi-lawless-files-divorce-year-marriage/</link><description>11:53 AM PT -- Jenna Jameson just responded to the news, taking to her IG Story and writing, "I keep it classy." Jenna Jameson is once again headed for divorce -- this time, it's her wife who wants to end their marriage ... and she's claiming the…</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 08:23:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Riley Strain's Mom Says He Told Her His Drink Tasted Funny Before Death</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/16/riley-strain-mom-he-texted-drink-tasted-odd-before-death/</link><description>Riley Strain's mom claims her son complained about his drink not tasting right ahead of his disappearance and subsequent death ... and the implication is that he was roofied. Michelle Whiteid and her family sat with NewsNation for an interview…</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 08:23:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TikTok Star Kyle Marisa Roth Dead At 36</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/16/tiktok-star-kyle-marisa-roth-dead-dies/</link><description>TikTok star Kyle Marisa Roth -- famous for dishing on controversial Hollywood blind items and showbiz gossip -- has suddenly died ... something her family confirmed this week. Kyle's sister Lindsay Roth broke the news Monday on her IG -- saying her…</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 08:23:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Red Lobster Reportedly Considering Filing for Bankruptcy, Jokes Fly</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/16/red-lobster-considering-filing-bankruptcy/</link><description>Red Lobster is reportedly mulling over bankruptcy, and while this is far from the end for them as a business ... some online are certainly treating it that way, with jokes galore. According to Bloomberg, the famous seafood restaurant chain is…</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 08:23:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elephant Roams Montana Streets After Escaping Circus</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/16/elephant-roams-montana-street-after-escaping-circus/</link><description>Residents of Butte, Montana were in for a surprise Tuesday ... when a circus elephant escaped from its home and began freely roaming in the streets, captured in wild video. According to multiple reports, the elephant broke free from Jordan World…</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 08:23:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>O.J. Simpson Did Not Die with Millions, Says Estate Executor</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/16/malcolm-lavergne-oj-simpson-estate-executor-nevada-bank-account/</link><description>O.J. Simpson's estate is NOT flush with the kinda cash you'd expect -- nor is it enough to satisfy his debt to Ron Goldman's family ... at least that's what his executor is claiming. We got Simpson's longtime attorney Malcolm LaVergne Tuesday on…</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 08:23:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Taylor Swift's Fans Form Long Lines For 'Poets' Pop-Up Ahead of New Album</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/16/taylor-swift-fans-long-lines-the-grove-tortured-poets-pop-up-new-album/</link><description>Taylor Swift fans are nothing if not committed, and with her new album dropping Friday ... they're going all out to scoop up every little detail they can, including at pop-ups. Swifties were out in full force Tuesday to catch a glimpse of a…</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 08:23:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trevor Bauer Sexual Accuser Charged W/ Defrauding Ex-MLB Star</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/16/trevor-bauer-sexual-accuser-charged-w-defrauding-ex-mlb-star/</link><description>A woman who accused Trevor Bauer of sexual assault has just been hit with a criminal charge ... after she allegedly defrauded the former Cy Young winner into paying her for an abortion he believes never happened. The charge -- fraudulent schemes…</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 08:23:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chrissy Teigen Defends Bezos' Fiancée Lauren Sánchez Against Troll's Mean Diss</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/16/chrissy-teigen-defends-jeff-bezos-fiancee-lauren-sanchez-troll-comment/</link><description>Chrissy Teigen's standing up for Jeff Bezos' fiancée Lauren Sanchez -- this after a notorious restaurateur unleashed a barrage of venom toward ... for no real reason at all. Balthazar owner Keith McNally randomly threw up a bunch of IG pics of…</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 08:23:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Christine Quinn Claims Husband Never Paid for Son's Hospital Bills from Birth</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/16/christine-quinn-claim-husband-never-paid-son-hospital-bills-birth/</link><description>Christine Quinn claims her estranged husband never paid for hospital bills tied to their son's birth -- and now she's gunning for primary custody of the kid amid their ongoing divorce. The "Selling Sunset" star just filed a response to Christian…</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 08:23:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Video Shows Dubai Airport Flooded After Massive Rain Storm</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/16/dubai-airport-flooding-video-heavy-rain-oman-deaths/</link><description>Dubai airport's looking more like a marina, after a year's worth of rain flooded the desert metropolis in just one day! Check it out ... the tarmac at Dubai International -- the second busiest in the world -- was completely covered in water…</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 08:23:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kenny Loggins Reveals Why Huey Lewis Replaced Prince On 'We Are the World'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/16/kenny-loggins-we-are-the-world-huey-lewis-great-replacement-prince/</link><description>'80s hitmaker Kenny Loggins is peeling back another layer on the legendary recording of "We Are the World" -- revealing how he scored his pal Huey Lewis a solo when Prince bowed out. Kenny spilled the tea on a recent episode of Huey Lewis' Apple…</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 08:23:36 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>