<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:50:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Recent Romantasy and Other Romance Books for Your Book Club</title><link>https://bookriot.com/recent-romantasy-and-other-romance-books-for-your-book-club/</link><description>What kind of romance do you like reading with book clubs? You like it spicy or nah?</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Report: Here's how far used Tesla prices have fallen in the past year</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/04/24/report-heres-how-far-used-tesla-prices-have-fallen-in-the-past-year/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/04/24120709/0x0-ModelY-04.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under:
					    Green,Tesla,Used Car Buying,Electric
Continue reading Report: Here's how far used Tesla prices have fallen in the past year
Report: Here's how far used Tesla prices have fallen in the past year originally appeared on Autoblog on Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:45:00 EDT.  Please see our terms for use of feeds.
Permalink | 
						Email this | 
					    Comments</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>U.S. Chamber of Commerce, business groups sue FTC over ban on noncompete clauses</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/04/24/chamber-of-commerce-sues-ftc-for-banning-noncompete-clauses.html</link><description>The U.S. Chamber of Commerce has long threatened to sue the FTC over the noncompete ban.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 552</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-552/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-552</link><description>When you are searching for a job, you will inevitably run into unexpected scenarios. You will have questions, experience self-doubt and even feel discouraged. You’ll also experience great wins, meet wonderful people and discover new things about yourself. That’s the roller-coaster of job search. Consider Summary Sunday your resource for getting questions answered and showing […]
The post Summary Sunday: Issue 552 appeared first on Career Sherpa.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 11:37:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A case for public preschool: New study reveals preschool benefits to be longer-lasting and substantial</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/benefits-of-public-preschool/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=benefits-of-public-preschool</link><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Preschool lays a foundation for elementary school students to succeed. In the United States, as children approach kindergarten entry, it is increasingly common for 4-year-olds to be in non-parental group care and education, often in a center- or school-based setting where they can learn alongside peers. For children from low-income communities, […]
The post A case for public preschool: New study reveals preschool benefits to be longer-lasting and substantial appeared first on Child and Family Blog.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 08:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lemon Angel Pie</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/lemon-angel-pie/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/lemon-angel-pie-1-1200x1799-1.jpg</image_url><description>Lemon angel pie is a delightful dessert straight from heaven! It has a creamy lemon filling inside a sweet, airy…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Star Jasmine – Plant Growing &amp; Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/star-jasmine-plant-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2024/04/Star-Jasmine-Flower-Close-Up-650x488.jpg</image_url><description>Star jasmine is a fast-growing and fragrant evergreen vine that not only gives you great coverage &amp; privacy as a climbing or creeping vine, it also bursts into blooms with incredible-smelling flowers in the spring. The plant is native to Asia, but is incredibly popular in the Southeastern United States and areas of California. In warm environments like these, star jasmine is also super easy to care for and grow. Just another reason we love it!
Star jasmine can grow as a dense ground cover, but we prefer to use it as a climbing vine. This does require a trellis, pergola, stakes, or some other structure for it to grow up. Those are easy to make and we have DIY tutorials for a wire trellis on a wall as well as a freestanding privacy trellis. 
Star Jasmine Quick Facts
Here’s what you need to know about star jasmine at a glance:

Latin name: Trachelospermum jasminoides
Plant type: Evergreen climbing vine
Flowers: White star-shaped blooms in late spring &amp; early summer
Sun exposure: Full sun to part shade
Growth rate: Fast-growing (3 to 6 feet per year)
Mature size: Up to 20 feet
Soil: Well-draining loamy soil.

Continue reading Star Jasmine – Plant Growing &amp; Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:02:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mother’s Day With Etsy</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/04/mothers-day-with-etsy/</link><description>Thank you to Etsy for sponsoring this post. Finding the perfect Mother’s Day gift can be a delightful experience when…
The post Mother’s Day With Etsy appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:00:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>For the New Yorkers: 2024 Gotham Book Prize Finalists Announced</title><link>https://bookriot.com/2024-gotham-book-prize-finalists-announced/</link><description>We love a New York-based book. How many of these are on your TBR?</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 17:49:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Save up to 50% on a Rove dash cam thanks to this killer spring sale</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/article/save-up-to-50-percent-on-a-rove-dash-cam-thanks-to-this-killer-spring-sale/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/04/23163014/Rove-R3-Featured.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under:
					    Commerce
Continue reading Save up to 50% on a Rove dash cam thanks to this killer spring sale
Save up to 50% on a Rove dash cam thanks to this killer spring sale originally appeared on Autoblog on Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:25:00 EDT.  Please see our terms for use of feeds.
Permalink | 
						Email this | 
					    Comments</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:25:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meta's earnings report comes as 'Magnificent Seven' stock looks to return to all-time high</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/04/24/metas-earnings-come-as-magnificent-seven-name-aims-to-return-to-all-time-high.html</link><description>After its most recent report, shares of the Facebook parent shot up 20%.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:44:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you</link><description>While a little competition in the workplace might help bring out the best in everyone involved, an atmosphere rooted in envy, fear, or jealousy can do the exact opposite. This post will help you recognize signs that your coworker is threatened by you, and help you navigate the situation. 1. They Don’t Want You Involved […]
The post 10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You appeared first on Career Sherpa.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:07:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fathers’ views on family and work after COVID-19 lockdowns</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/fathers-views-on-family-and-work-after-covid-19-lockdowns/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fathers-views-on-family-and-work-after-covid-19-lockdowns</link><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Fathers often want to be present for their children and contribute to household tasks, but they can lack opportunities and confidence; they may see themselves as “helpers” instead of parents. Australian fathers in our small study reported that they spent more time with their children during the COVID-19 lockdowns, and they […]
The post Fathers’ views on family and work after COVID-19 lockdowns appeared first on Child and Family Blog.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Easy Sheet Pan Lasagna</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/sheet-pan-lasagna/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/sheet-pan-lasagna-.jpg</image_url><description>This super easy sheet pan lasagna is stacked with sautéed ground beef and Italian sausage that are cooked together, marinara sauce, creamy spinach ricotta,…</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best Greige Paint Colors (According To Experts)</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/best-greige-paint-colors/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2024/04/Best-Greige-Paint-Square-Graphic-650x614.jpg</image_url><description>“Greige” is that sweet spot between gray &amp; beige, and it’s a paint color that’s both trendy and timeless. In fact, we’ve been on the greige bandwagon for nearly 20 years – well before we’d even heard that term! But finding the perfect greige can be daunting. There are 100s of neutral paint colors that could be considered greige, so we’ve waded through dozens of expert round-ups to see what colors come up over and over again. (Yes, I made a spreadsheet. And yes, I liked it). 
We weren’t surprised to see our favorite greige paint show up on this Iist, but the color that ranked #1 was a bit of a shock to us! 
What Is Greige?
Greige is an umbrella term for any color that dances the line between gray and beige (gray + beige = greige).
Continue reading The Best Greige Paint Colors (According To Experts) at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 17:43:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trending Turquoise</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/04/trending-turquoise/</link><image_url>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240326-jb-vince-blazer-proenza-schouler-dress-1007729-1024x1536.jpg</image_url><description>Outfit Details: Vince Blazer, Proenza Schouler Dress (on sale), Giuseppe Di Morabito Bag, Jimmy Choo Heels (similar here) Mid-spring is the perfect time…
The post Trending Turquoise appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 05:00:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 2024 Women’s Prize Shortlists Are Here</title><link>https://bookriot.com/the-2024-womens-prize-shortlists/</link><description>The shortlists for both the Women's Prize in Fiction and Women's Prize in Nonfiction for 2024 have been announced.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 17:08:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2025 BMW i4 and 4 Series Gran Coupe refreshed with tweaks throughout</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/04/24/2025-bmw-i4-and-4-series-gran-coupe-refreshed-with-tweaks-throughout/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/04/24110940/2025_bmw_4series_gran_coupe_02.jpeg</image_url><description>Filed under:
					    Green,BMW,Electric,Luxury,Performance,Sedan
Continue reading 2025 BMW i4 and 4 Series Gran Coupe refreshed with tweaks throughout
2025 BMW i4 and 4 Series Gran Coupe refreshed with tweaks throughout originally appeared on Autoblog on Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:41:00 EDT.  Please see our terms for use of feeds.
Permalink | 
						Email this | 
					    Comments</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:41:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TikTok creators fear for their livelihoods after U.S. lawmakers pass bill that could lead to ban</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/04/24/tiktok-creators-fear-for-their-livelihoods-after-biden-signs-law.html</link><description>A TikTok ban could take years due to potential legal challenges, but creators worry about how they'll make a living if it goes away.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 17:59:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 551</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-551/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-551</link><description>Job search requires writing and marketing skills. It also requires strong verbal communication. If these skills are not part of your normal work function, you’ll want some help. That’s what this week’s Summary Sunday is all about. There’s no doubt that LinkedIn is one of THE most powerful tools in your career toolbox. It contains […]
The post Summary Sunday: Issue 551 appeared first on Career Sherpa.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 11:37:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Strong Latine Identity Supports U.S. Latine Children’s Well-Being</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/a-strong-latine-identity-supports-u-s-latine-childrens-well-being/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=a-strong-latine-identity-supports-u-s-latine-childrens-well-being</link><description>Key Takeaways for caregivers Children tend to have better health and well-being when they have a strong ethnic identity (affinity and adoption of ethnicity-based self-concept). A traditional Latine cultural value (familismo) that emphasizes family bonds is also associated with better developmental outcomes. Caregivers can support the development of U.S. Latine children (and possibly other children […]
The post A Strong Latine Identity Supports U.S. Latine Children’s Well-Being appeared first on Child and Family Blog.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 03:03:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Properly Measure Baking Ingredients</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/how-to-measure-baking-ingredients/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/measuring-ingredients-.jpg</image_url><description>Whether you are a seasoned baker or just starting out, this informational post has all of my tips and tricks…</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Golden Pothos – Plant Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/golden-pothos-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2024/04/Golden-Pothos-Overhead-650x455.jpg</image_url><description>Pothos are easily our #1 favorite houseplant and the golden pothos is by far the most popular variety. They’re loved by beginners and plant experts alike because they’re affordable, attractive, and easy to care for. They’re quick-growing plants with beautiful trailing vines that add loads of life and color to any space. We have pothos in nearly EVERY room of our house!
There are over a dozen kinds of pothos (Epipremnum aureum), most of which share similar characteristics and care instructions as the golden pothos. You can read more about other varieties we love, like the marble queen pothos and neon pothos.
Golden Pothos Quick Facts
Here’s what you need to know about your golden pothos at a glance:

Latin name: Epipremnum aureum
Common names: Golden pothos, devil’s ivy, devil’s vine, hunter’s rove
Mistaken for: Neon pothos, marble queen pothos
Light: Prefers medium, indirect light but is low-light tolerant
Watering: Every 7-10 days during its growing season, or if the soil is dry &amp; leaves are drooping
Soil: Standard potting mix as long as it drains well
Ideal Humidity: Average household humidity, ideally 50-70%
Ideal Temperature: 65-85 degrees
Cold Hardiness: USDA Zones 10-12

What Is A Golden Pothos?
Continue reading Golden Pothos – Plant Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sandals For Littles</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/04/sandals-for-littles/</link><description>It’s the delightful little moments with my girls that bring the biggest smiles, especially when it comes to the simple…
The post Sandals For Littles appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 05:00:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Title: Book Riot’s Romance Deals for April 24, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/title-book-riots-romance-deals-for-april-24-2024/</link><description>A M/M Queer Historical Romance, Wicked Royals, a Bridgerton Tale, and More of Today's Best Romance Deals</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:31:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Declutter your car with this highly-rated trunk organizer</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/article/organize-your-trunk-and-cargo-space-with-this-essential-foldable-car-organizer/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/04/23140155/CarStorage-Main.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under:
					    Commerce
Continue reading Declutter your car with this highly-rated trunk organizer
Declutter your car with this highly-rated trunk organizer originally appeared on Autoblog on Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:30:00 EDT.  Please see our terms for use of feeds.
Permalink | 
						Email this | 
					    Comments</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meta to report first-quarter results after the bell</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/04/24/meta-meta-q1-2024-earnings-.html</link><description>Meta reports first-quarter results after market close on Wednesday, and analysts expect to see the fastest year-over-year sales growth in almost three years.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>15 Ways to Own Digital Terrain</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/15-ways-to-own-digital-terrain/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=15-ways-to-own-digital-terrain</link><description>It is now no longer optional…you must have an online presence! Your career stability and your job search demand it. Here are some tips to help you begin claiming digital terrain and brand it with your unique messaging!   Why Should You Own Digital Terrain? You need to stake a claim by owning turf on the […]
The post 15 Ways to Own Digital Terrain appeared first on Career Sherpa.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 15:56:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Children caught between highly conflicted divorced parents at greater risk of mental health problems</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/children-caught-between-conflicted-divorced-parents/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=children-caught-between-conflicted-divorced-parents</link><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Interparental conflict after divorce escalates the risk of mental health problems in children and adolescents. Elevated levels of conflict between parents can also induce fear and worry in children about their future and whether they will be adequately taken care of. In turn, a greater fear of abandonment puts children at […]
The post Children caught between highly conflicted divorced parents at greater risk of mental health problems appeared first on Child and Family Blog.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 08:59:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cookie Salad</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/cookie-salad/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/cookie-salad.jpg</image_url><description>Serve this fun and delicious cookie salad as a dessert or side dish! Everyone will love the sweet fluffy pudding…</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Neon Pothos – Plant Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/neon-pothos-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2024/04/Neon-Pothos-On-Floating-Shelf-Close-650x469.jpg</image_url><description>Our top recommendation for an easy, starter houseplant? Pothos, pothos, pothos! They’re low-stress, high-impact, and fast-growing vines that are great for both beginners and experts. The golden pothos may be the most common variety but don’t overlook its more vibrant cousin: the neon pothos. We’ve got several neon pothos in our home, and they’re beautiful and so easy! So here’s all you need to know before you get your own.
There are over a dozen varieties of pothos, most of which share similar care instructions to the neon pothos. You can read more about other pothos we love, like the golden pothos and marble queen pothos.
Neon Pothos Quick Facts
Here’s what you need to know about your neon pothos at a glance:

Latin name: Epipremnum aureum ‘Neon’ 
Common names: Neon pothos, neon devil’s ivy
Mistaken for: Golden pothos
Light: Prefers bright, indirect light but is low-light tolerant
Watering: Every 7-10 days during its growing season, or if the soil is dry &amp; leaves are drooping
Soil: Standard potting mix as long as it drains well
Ideal Humidity: Average household humidity, ideally 50-70%
Ideal Temperature: 65-85 degrees
Cold Hardiness: USDA Zones 10-12

What Is A Neon Pothos?
Continue reading Neon Pothos – Plant Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 19:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Saks April Spring Sale</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/04/saks-april-spring-sale/</link><description>Thank you to Saks Fifth Avenue for sponsoring this post. Step into the allure of the season with Saks Fifth…
The post Saks April Spring Sale appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 05:00:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best Children’s Book Deals of the Day for April 24, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/the-best-childrens-book-deals-of-the-day-for-april-24-2024/</link><description>Marker magic, rainforest discovery, Critter Club, a pangolin girl, and more of today's best children's book deals.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:45:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cited for DUI at four times the legal limit — but he hadn't drunk a drop</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/04/24/cited-for-dui-at-four-times-the-legal-limit-but-he-hadnt-drunk-a-drop/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/04/24140539/Screenshot-2024-04-24-at-14.04.45.png</image_url><description>Filed under:
					    Government/Legal,Weird Car News,Ethanol,Police/Emergency
Continue reading Cited for DUI at four times the legal limit — but he hadn't drunk a drop
Cited for DUI at four times the legal limit — but he hadn't drunk a drop originally appeared on Autoblog on Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:24:00 EDT.  Please see our terms for use of feeds.
Permalink | 
						Email this | 
					    Comments</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:24:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ford is set to report earnings after the bell. Here's what Wall Street expects</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/04/24/ford-f-earnings-q1-2024.html</link><description>While Ford is expected to report XXXXXXXXXX year-over-year, analysts are keeping a watchful eye on how many subscribers it adds this quarter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 550</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-550/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-550</link><description>Job search strategies change based on the economy, the level and type of work you are looking for, and your personal situation. In other words, there’s no absolute right way for everyone. However, there are best practices you should know about. In this week’s Summary Sunday, you’ll learn about: I carefully curate these articles and […]
The post Summary Sunday: Issue 550 appeared first on Career Sherpa.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 10:44:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>“Why do they feel sad?” Shared book reading reveals how children learn about others’ emotions</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/shared-book-reading/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=shared-book-reading</link><description>Key takeaways for caregivers: It is good for children to identify the emotions of others in conversations with caregivers because it scaffolds their ability to identify others’ emotions on their own. Children who use more emotion talk in parent-child conversations about emotions are more likely to have higher emotion knowledge one year later. Parents can […]
The post “Why do they feel sad?” Shared book reading reveals how children learn about others’ emotions appeared first on Child and Family Blog.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 08:19:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Creamy Lemon Parmesan Chicken</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/creamy-lemon-parmesan-chicken/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/creamy-lemon-parmesan-chicken-2-4.jpg</image_url><description>Creamy Lemon Parmesan Chicken is an incredible restaurant-quality meal you can make in under 30 minutes. Tender, juicy chicken is…</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 13:00:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Marble Queen Pothos – Plant Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/marble-queen-pothos-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2024/04/Marble-Queen-Pothos-Close-Up-650x526.jpg</image_url><description>Even though the marble queen isn’t the most popular pothos variety, it’s one of our personal favorites! Like all pothos plants, they’re a perfect starter houseplant because they’re resilient, low-maintenance, and fast-growing. Plus, we think it has some of prettiest leaves of all.
There are over a dozen kinds of pothos, most of which share similar characteristics and care instructions as the marble queen. You can read more about other pothos we love, like the golden pothos and neon pothos.
Marble Queen Quick Facts
Here’s what you need to know about your marble queen pothos at a glance:

Latin name: Epipremnum aureum ‘Marble Queen’ 
Common names: Marble queen pothos, marble pothos, pothos marble
Mistaken for: Golden pothos, snow queen pothos
Light: Prefers medium, indirect light but is low-light tolerant
Watering: Every 7-10 days during its growing season, or if the soil is dry &amp; leaves are drooping
Soil: Standard potting mix as long as it drains well
Ideal Humidity: Average household humidity, ideally 50-70%
Ideal Temperature: 60-85 degrees
Cold Hardiness: USDA Zones 10-12

What Is A Marble Queen Pothos?
Continue reading Marble Queen Pothos – Plant Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 18:39:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Strapless For Spring</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/04/strapless-for-spring/</link><image_url>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240325-jb-the-wolf-gang-dress-1006813-1024x1536.jpg</image_url><description>Outfit Details: The Wolf Gang Dress, Dior Sandals, Prada Sunglasses, Gucci Bag (similar here and here) Strapless tops and dresses for spring are the season’s…
The post Strapless For Spring appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 05:00:12 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>