<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:28:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Bullish Breadth (Act Fast)</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/bullish-breadth-act-fast/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, it's Ross Givens here with the Chart of the Day. The percentage of stocks trading above their 50-day moving average, a key metric for medium-term momentum, has surged, signaling a potential continuation of the bull market. Nearly double the levels seen during the April pullback, it mirrors the market's upward trajectory observed from February to mid-March. This resurgence indicates an opportunity for swift action. Learn more about the implications in my detailed analysis below. The post Bullish Breadth (Act Fast) appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Junkyard Gem: 2005 Honda Accord, Hello Kitty Edition</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/11/junkyard-gem-2005-honda-accord-hello-kitty-edition/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/04/24102933/99-2005-Honda-Accord-Hello-Kitty-Edition-in-Colorado-junkyard-photo-by-Murilee-Martin.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Design/Style , Humor , Weird Car News , Honda , Automotive History , Sedan Continue reading Junkyard Gem: 2005 Honda Accord, Hello Kitty Edition Junkyard Gem: 2005 Honda Accord, Hello Kitty Edition originally appeared on Autoblog on Sat, 11 May 2024 12:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Florida Is the Perfect Rent-to-Own Market—Should You Take Advantage?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/why-florida-is-the-perfect-rent-to-own-market</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>The Sunshine State offers the exact combination of factors that make this investment option attractive.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 14:08:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Riot’s YA Book Deals of the Day for May 11, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/book-riots-ya-book-deals-of-the-day-for-may-11-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Untitled-design-51.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>A Korean folktale retelling, a dark academia mystery, the search for a teen's husband, and more of today's best YA book deals.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 553</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-553/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-553</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Tools and technology change rapidly. Yet as wonderful as technology can be, it doesn’t replace the need for human connection through interactions. Keep this in mind as you are searching for a new job. It’s your human connections that often open doors! In this week’s collection of news and tips for job seekers, you’ll find: […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 553 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 12:19:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A case for public preschool: New study reveals preschool benefits to be longer-lasting and substantial</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/benefits-of-public-preschool/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=benefits-of-public-preschool</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Preschool lays a foundation for elementary school students to succeed. In the United States, as children approach kindergarten entry, it is increasingly common for 4-year-olds to be in non-parental group care and education, often in a center- or school-based setting where they can learn alongside peers. For children from low-income communities, […] The post A case for public preschool: New study reveals preschool benefits to be longer-lasting and substantial appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 08:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Musk's Starlink satellites disrupted by major solar storm</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/11/musks-starlink-satellites-disrupted-by-major-solar-storm.html</link><description>Starlink owns around 60% of the roughly 7,500 satellites orbiting Earth and is a dominant player in satellite internet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 23:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2023 NBA turnovers per game leaders</title><link>https://deadspin.com/2023-nba-turnovers-per-game-leaders-1851036203</link><description>This article is based on data from Sportradar. Read more...</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:10:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chad Michael Murray’s Daughter Reacts to A Cinderalla Story</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1401405/chad-michael-murray-shares-daughters-reaction-to-watching-a-cinderella-story?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>Nomad is re-entering the chat. Twenty years after starring in A Cinderella Story alongside Hilary Duff, Chad Michael Murray knows fans are still nostalgic over his Fighting Frogs quarterback...</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Your Portfolio Should Include Scarce Assets</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/10/why-your-portfolio-should-include-scarce-assets/</link><description>Portfolios that include both productive and scarce assets can deliver similar performance to the S&amp;P 500 with less risk than those that hold only productive assets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:34:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>79% of parents have drugged their kids to help them sleep</title><link>https://fortune.com/well/2024/05/11/kids-sleep-aids-drugs-melatonin-ambien-thc/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-164413892-e1715378064649.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Millennials and Gen Z parents have resorted to this practice most, using melatonin, Benadryl—even prescriptions—to help their children at bedtime, Sleep Doctor finds.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 03:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amazon Home Refresh Tips</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/amazon-home-refresh-tips/</link><description>Embrace the mid-spring refresh with Amazon and give your home a vibrant makeover for the season. Amazon makes it easy… The post Amazon Home Refresh Tips appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 05:00:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ride</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/an7XBRB</link><description>Tags: telegram bad shofer , wtf , savage , funny , dark humor 5155 points, 332 comments.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 07:25:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mother’s Day 2024: Pink Caps, Pink Ribbons as MLB Salutes Mom</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/11/mothers-day-2024-pink-caps-pink-ribbons-as-mlb-salutes-mom/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>It’s Mother’s Day here in North America, which means we’ll see pink-themed baseball caps and ribbons on the uniforms of Major League Baseball players, coaches, managers, and umpires during games played on Sunday, May 12th. SHOP: 2024 MLB Mother’s Day team caps available right now This will be the eighth</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:07:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Apple’s ‘Crush’ ad is so misguided</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/11/why-apples-crush-ad-is-so-misguided/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Welcome to Week in Review: TechCrunch’s newsletter recapping the week’s biggest news. This week Apple unveiled new iPad models at its Let Loose event, including a new 13-inch display for the iPad Air, as well as Tandem OLED and a new M4 chip for the iPad Pro. But its ad for the new iPad Pro […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 21:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When Bad Cops Become Private Security Guards</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/11/police-private-guard-florida-chicago</link><description>There’s growing evidence that former officers with troubling histories of abuse can easily find second careers in private security.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Thai Chicken Salad</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/thai-chicken-salad/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Crunchy and bright, this Thai Chicken Salad with creamy peanut dressing is bursting with flavor, texture and deliciousness! Prep it in…</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What's The Big Frigin' Difference?!</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/11/whats-the-big-frigin-difference/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>WHAT'S POPPIN' ya'll?! You ready to take on the sneaky switcharoos in these two images of rapper-singer Jack Harlow? It may be hard to keep your eyes off this stunna, but while you're at it take a peek at the pottery. Fresh off the Met Gala earlier…</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:28:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Working It Out: How to Minimize Eczema Flare-ups at the Gym and on the Job</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/minimize-eczema-flare-ups-gym-job?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Three keys to managing your eczema at the gym and then heading off to a productive and itch-free workday.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 07:30:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/how-to-remove-wallpaper/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Wallpaper has made a big comeback as a trendy home design choice. But despite its resurgence, there are still plenty of us dealing with dingy, dated, or downright ugly old wallpaper we don’t want. In our old home, we had to remove wallpaper in so many rooms: the kitchen, the dining room, the foyer, and two different bathrooms! As we traveled from room to room removing wallpaper, we tested 4 different methods, and today we’ll share what we learned. Removing wallpaper doesn’t require special tools or lots of money. It’s a totally doable project for any homeowner. However, it can be a tedious process that can take elbow grease and patience, depending on the size of your room and the stubbornness of your wallpaper. But having removed several rooms worth of decades-old wallpaper, we can confidently say it’s worth the effort! You can also check out more before and afters of our once-wallpapered rooms. Continue reading How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:21:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Bull Market is Still Young</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/this-bull-market-is-still-young/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, it's Ross Givens here with the Chart of the Day. In analyzing historical data, it's evident that bull markets typically extend for years from the bear market bottom to the peak. Surprisingly, our current market cycle has seen a peak just 19 months post the last bear market bottom, contrasting with the typical 61-month duration. This insight suggests that the current bull market is still in its infancy, promising ample opportunities ahead. Stay tuned as I delve into the implications of this data in today's analysis. The post This Bull Market is Still Young appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chinese car exports jump 38% in April</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/11/chinese-car-exports-jump-38-in-april/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/crop/5272x2966+0+178/resize/800x450!/format/jpg/quality/85/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/10124149/cars_parked_at_the_international_cargo_terminal.jpeg</image_url><description>Filed under: Green , Electric Continue reading Chinese car exports jump 38% in April Chinese car exports jump 38% in April originally appeared on Autoblog on Sat, 11 May 2024 11:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What If We Replaced Income Taxes with Property and Sales Taxes? Would Real Estate Investing Even Work?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/should-the-us-eliminate-income-taxes-and-replace-it-with-sales-and-property-tax</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>A few reasons for—and against—this proposed shift in U.S. tax laws.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:15:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Riot’s Deals of the Day for May 11, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/book-riots-deals-of-the-day-for-may-11-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/deals-051124.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>A twisty and unexpected thriller, a long-forgotten queen, a post-apocalyptic journey of survival, and more of today's best book deals.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 552</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-552/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-552</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>When you are searching for a job, you will inevitably run into unexpected scenarios. You will have questions, experience self-doubt and even feel discouraged. You’ll also experience great wins, meet wonderful people and discover new things about yourself. That’s the roller-coaster of job search. Consider Summary Sunday your resource for getting questions answered and showing […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 552 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 11:37:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fathers’ views on family and work after COVID-19 lockdowns</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/fathers-views-on-family-and-work-after-covid-19-lockdowns/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fathers-views-on-family-and-work-after-covid-19-lockdowns</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Fathers often want to be present for their children and contribute to household tasks, but they can lack opportunities and confidence; they may see themselves as “helpers” instead of parents. Australian fathers in our small study reported that they spent more time with their children during the COVID-19 lockdowns, and they […] The post Fathers’ views on family and work after COVID-19 lockdowns appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Donald Trump shuts down rumors about considering Nikki Haley for vice president</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/11/donald-trump-shuts-down-nikki-haley-vp-rumors.html</link><description>Donald Trump has several names on his VP shortlist already, including Sen. Tim Scott, Rep. Elise Stefanik and Gov. Doug Burgum.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 18:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2023 NHL goals against average leaders</title><link>https://deadspin.com/2023-nhl-goals-against-average-leaders-1851061822</link><description>This article is based on data from Sportradar. Read more...</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:10:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chris Pine Recalls Losing Out on The O.C. Role Due to "Bad Acne</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1401426/chris-pine-reflects-on-losing-out-on-the-o-c-role-due-to-his-bad-acne?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>More than 20 years ago, Chris Pine almost played Ryan Atwood opposite Mischa Barton on the hit series The O.C. But there was just one problem that ultimately made him lose out on the role—despite...</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 01:12:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coiled Tight: Smaller Companies Are Primed for Outperformance</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/08/coiled-tight-smaller-companies-are-primed-for-outperformance/</link><description>Small-cap companies are poised for a rebound. The sector is best approached through an active investment strategy where expertise and a deep understanding of the individual businesses and their risk-and-reward characteristics are necessary for success.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:40:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weaning off Ozempic slowly instead of quitting abruptly can help prevent patients from regaining weight, study says</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/11/ozempic-wegovy-semaglutide-how-to-keep-weight-off-gradual-reduction/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1429558470-e1715471332955.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>These patients had reached their target weight and reduced their semaglutide dose over nine weeks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 01:03:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shell Season</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/shell-season/</link><description>Spring welcomes the captivating allure of shell season. As nature awakens and warmth spreads, ocean treasures inspire wardrobe choices. This… The post Shell Season appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:58:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Advice from Gabriel</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/aByQrGz</link><description>Tags: for your health 4704 points, 194 comments.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 07:25:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>EA Sports’ College Football 25 Deluxe Edition Cover Revealed</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/10/ea-sports-college-football-25-deluxe-edition-cover-revealed/college/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The deluxe edition cover of EA Sports' College Football 25 was revealed in an update to the PlayStation Store on Friday morning, generating even more excitement for the long-awaited video game ahead of its summer release.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 19:00:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>U.K. agency releases tools to test AI model safety</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/11/u-k-agency-releases-tools-to-test-ai-model-safety/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The U.K. Safety Institute, the U.K.’s recently established AI safety body, has released a toolset designed to “strengthen AI safety” by making it easier for industry, research organizations and academia to develop AI evaluations. Called Inspect, the toolset — which is available under an open source license, specifically an MIT License — aims to assess certain […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 21:12:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Rare Bright Spot for a Canine Lover Doing Time: Raising Puppies to Become Service Dogs</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/10/service-dogs-training-prison-essay</link><description>Adam Roberts reflects on the highs and occasional lows of training Labrador retrievers for the Puppies Behind Bars program.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Meal Plan #4</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/weekly-menu-plan-4/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Take advantage of this weekly meal plan that has all the favorite recipes that families love! It is so easy…</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FaZe Banks Says Miami Grand Prix Felt 'Bigger Than Super Bowl,' So Many Celebs!</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/11/faze-banks-says-miami-grand-prix-felt-bigger-than-super-bowl-so-many-celebs/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>The Formula One Miami Grand Prix blew the Super Bowl outta the water in the VIP department ... so says gamer FaZe Banks, who tells TMZ Sports last weekend's event was "insane!!" Folks like Patrick and Brittany Mahomes, Kendall Jenner, Steve Aoki,…</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:28:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cows Are Potential Spreaders of Bird Flu to Humans</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/food-recipes/food-poisoning/news/20240510/cows-are-potential-spreaders-bird-flu-humans?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Cow udders have the same receptors for flu viruses as humans and birds, raising concerns that cows could become “mixing vessels” that help the bird flu virus spread between people.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 19:36:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aglaonema Plant – Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/aglaonema-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Aglaonema, also called the Chinese Evergreen Plant, is an easy-care houseplant that lives happily in many lighting conditions – even a dark corner of our daughter’s room. There are dozens of different Aglaonema varieties, most with large tropical foliage and colors ranging from silvery-green, red, and even vibrant pink. They’re also tough to kill, so they’re a great option for forgetful plant owners or anyone looking for an easy win in the plant department. These truly have been very low maintenance for us. We purchased our two Aglaonemas (pronounced ag-lee-oh-neem-ah ) to put atop our daughter’s closet. It’s sometimes hard to distinguish different varieties, but we believe that’s an Aglaonema Silver (right) and either a Candy Cane or Princess Silver Queen (left). Aglaonema Quick Facts Here’s what you need to know about your Aglaonema at a glance: Latin name : Aglaonema is the genus under which there are 21 recognized species . Continue reading Aglaonema Plant – Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:47:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Earnings Divergence Opportunity</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/the-earnings-divergence-opportunity/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, it's Ross Givens here with the Chart of the Day. Amidst economic concerns, analysts have defied expectations by boosting their earnings estimates for S&amp;P 500 companies. This unexpected trend challenges prevailing pessimism about the market's trajectory. In today's analysis, I delve into what this shift means and why it's crucial not to let pessimism hinder your pursuit of current market opportunities. The post The Earnings Divergence Opportunity appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Marcus Armstrong honors cancer patients with special livery for Indy Grand Prix</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/11/marcus-armstrong-honors-cancer-patients-with-special-livery-for-indy-grand-prix/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/10123734/indycar_indianapolis_auto_racing-2.jpeg</image_url><description>Filed under: Motorsports Continue reading Marcus Armstrong honors cancer patients with special livery for Indy Grand Prix Marcus Armstrong honors cancer patients with special livery for Indy Grand Prix originally appeared on Autoblog on Sat, 11 May 2024 10:30:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Couple Goals: Navigating Real Estate Investment Decisions With Your Significant Other</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-investing-with-your-significant-other</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>7 steps to earn your significant other's support in real estate investing.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:52:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Fall Became The Big Season in Book Publishing</title><link>https://bookriot.com/today-in-books-may-10-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Screenshot-2024-05-10-at-11.09.05 AM.png</image_url><description>How Fall Became The Big Season in Publishing, SHOGUN Season 2 news, a RED, WHITE, &amp; ROYAL BLUE sequel, and Amazon's Big Book Sale is Live...and Good.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 19:14:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>While a little competition in the workplace might help bring out the best in everyone involved, an atmosphere rooted in envy, fear, or jealousy can do the exact opposite. This post will help you recognize signs that your coworker is threatened by you, and help you navigate the situation. 1. They Don’t Want You Involved […] The post 10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:07:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Strong Latine Identity Supports U.S. Latine Children’s Well-Being</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/a-strong-latine-identity-supports-u-s-latine-childrens-well-being/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=a-strong-latine-identity-supports-u-s-latine-childrens-well-being</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key Takeaways for caregivers Children tend to have better health and well-being when they have a strong ethnic identity (affinity and adoption of ethnicity-based self-concept). A traditional Latine cultural value (familismo) that emphasizes family bonds is also associated with better developmental outcomes. Caregivers can support the development of U.S. Latine children (and possibly other children […] The post A Strong Latine Identity Supports U.S. Latine Children’s Well-Being appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 03:03:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Do this 1 thing to curb your kid's anxiety today, says researcher behind 'The Anxious Generation'</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/11/do-this-1-thing-to-curb-your-kids-anxiety-today.html</link><description>If you want to make a change today that will positively impact your child's health start by talking to your kids' friends' parents.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2023 NBA steals per game leaders</title><link>https://deadspin.com/2023-nba-steals-per-game-leaders-1851036198</link><description>This article is based on data from Sportradar. Read more...</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:10:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gypsy Rose Blanchard Tastes First In-N-Out Burger, Gives Honest Review</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1401424/gypsy-rose-blanchard-tastes-her-first-in-n-out-burger-and-gives-her-honest-review?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>Gypsy Rose Blanchard has tasted her first double-double dose of freedom. On May 9, more than four months after she was released from prison, the 32-year-old shared a TikTok video of herself...</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 23:11:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Investment Returns Are NOT Random</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/07/investment-returns-are-not-random/</link><description>Are investment returns random across time as Burton Malkiel suggests in his book, A Random Walk Down Wall Street? There is notable disagreement on this topic. This research finds that practitioners may need to rethink their portfolio optimization routines.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:22:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prosecutors seek 40-year sentence for man who broke into Nancy Pelosi's home and attacked her husband with a hammer</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/11/nancy-pelosi-husband-paul-pelosi-attacker-david-depape-40-year-sentence/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1258955917-e1715468517717.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>“There is nothing about the history and characteristics of the defendant that warrant leniency,” federal prosecutors wrote in court documents.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 00:13:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Discovering My Avaline Favorites</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/discovering-my-avaline-favorites/</link><description>Thank you to Avaline for sponsoring this post. Spring symbolizes fresh starts and cleaner living. In my quest to align… The post Discovering My Avaline Favorites appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:50:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anybody know if she ever found the patient??</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/aD2w0xx</link><description>Tags: wtf , dark humor , humor , random , funny 15759 points, 739 comments.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 07:25:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New USL Super League Team Dallas Trinity FC Unveils Name, Logo</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/10/new-usl-super-league-team-dallas-trinity-fc-unveils-name-logo/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>New professional women's soccer team in North Texas will begin inaugural season in August and play out of historic Cotton Bowl stadium</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 16:10:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>At the AI Film Festival, humanity triumphed over tech</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/11/at-the-ai-film-festival-humanity-triumphed-over-tech/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>AI startup Runway's second annual AI Film Festival showcased movies that incorporated AI tech in some fashion, from backgrounds to animations. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Marshall Project Wins the Dart Award for “The Mercy Workers”</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/06/the-marshall-project-wins-the-dart-award-for-the-mercy-workers</link><description>Our feature on mitigation specialists who help save people from the death penalty was recognized for making “significant contributions to public understanding of trauma-related issues.”</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Garlic Balsamic Mushrooms</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/garlic-balsamic-mushrooms/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>The depth of flavors in these garlic balsamic mushrooms is next level! Sauteed mushrooms are coated in a sweet balsamic…</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Matisyahu Says Macklemore's 'Hind's Hall' Is Antisemitic, Won't Free Palestine</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/11/matisyahu-macklemore-hinds-hall-antisemitic-not-free-palestine-israel-hamas/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Matisyahu says Macklemore's new track isn't about freeing Palestine, as Mack claims -- instead, it only sows deeper discord by pushing what he sees as antisemitic tropes. We caught up with the Jewish singer-songwriter in L.A., and he tells TMZ he's…</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:28:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Age-Related Macular Degeneration: Putting a Hole in Our World</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/eye-health/news/20240510/age-related-macular-degeneration-putting-hole-our-world?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Estimates show that by 2040, age-related macular degeneration may affect nearly 300 million people worldwide. And we are very limited in our ability to treat or prevent it. Here's what to know.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 19:31:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Corn Plant – Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/corn-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Corn plants ( Dracaena fragrans ) are popular low-maintenance houseplants you’ve probably seen at the nursery, home improvement store, or doctor’s office. I even had one in my college dorm room! You can recognize them by their spear-shaped leaves and woody, cane-line trunks that can grow up to 6 feet tall indoors. But did you know there are several varieties of corn plants? We didn’t! Heck, we didn’t even realize some of our smaller houseplants were in the same corn plant family! Currently, we own two smaller varieties of corn plants, pictured above. The one on the left is a Dracaena Limelight ( Dracaena fragrans ‘Limelight’ ) and the taller plant is a Draecanea Dorado ( Dracaena fragrans ‘Dorado’ ). We actually have several limelights around because we love their vibrant color on shelves, tabletops, and windowsills. Corn Plant Quick Facts Latin name : Dracaena fragrans Common names : Corn plant, cornstalk plant, false palms Light : Bright, indirect light but can tolerate lower-light conditions Watering : Keep soil moist, but not soggy. Continue reading Corn Plant – Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 17:37:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Opportunity Window is Closing</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/the-opportunity-window-is-closing/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, it's Ross Givens here with the Chart of the Day. In market dynamics, volatility often mirrors market trends – as volatility rises, markets tend to dip, and as it falls, markets typically climb. Looking at historical data, this relationship holds true across various market conditions. Currently, with volatility showing signs of calming down, it suggests that the market might be on its way out of the recent pullback. Discover more insights on this intriguing correlation in today's analysis below. The post The Opportunity Window is Closing appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Colton Herta hopes to protect narrow points lead through IndyCar's biggest month</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/11/colton-herta-hopes-to-protect-narrow-points-lead-through-indycars-biggest-month/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/crop/3280x1845+0+57/resize/800x450!/format/jpg/quality/85/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/10122835/indycar_indianapolis_auto_racing1.jpeg</image_url><description>Filed under: Motorsports Continue reading Colton Herta hopes to protect narrow points lead through IndyCar's biggest month Colton Herta hopes to protect narrow points lead through IndyCar's biggest month originally appeared on Autoblog on Sat, 11 May 2024 10:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BiggerNews: Why Low Mortgage Rates Can’t Solve Our Affordability Crisis</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-951</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Housing prices won’t budge, but there could be some relief on the horizon for homebuyers. As America’s affordability crisis continues to strain consumers, one of the most considerable costs, housing, […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 07:02:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paperbacks and Hardcovers On Sale On Amazon for 50% Off</title><link>https://bookriot.com/amazon-book-sale-may-10-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/amazon-books-on-sale.png</image_url><description>Emily Henry, Toni Morrison, J.R.R. Tolkien, Dr. Seuss and more books on sale for 50% off today!</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 19:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 551</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-551/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-551</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Job search requires writing and marketing skills. It also requires strong verbal communication. If these skills are not part of your normal work function, you’ll want some help. That’s what this week’s Summary Sunday is all about. There’s no doubt that LinkedIn is one of THE most powerful tools in your career toolbox. It contains […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 551 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 11:37:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Children caught between highly conflicted divorced parents at greater risk of mental health problems</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/children-caught-between-conflicted-divorced-parents/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=children-caught-between-conflicted-divorced-parents</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Interparental conflict after divorce escalates the risk of mental health problems in children and adolescents. Elevated levels of conflict between parents can also induce fear and worry in children about their future and whether they will be adequately taken care of. In turn, a greater fear of abandonment puts children at […] The post Children caught between highly conflicted divorced parents at greater risk of mental health problems appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 08:59:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Photos from across the globe show spectacular displays of the aurora borealis</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/11/the-aurora-borealis-in-pictures-.html</link><description>The aurora borealis is typically only visible in high north latitudes, but this time, it stretched as far south as Louisiana.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 16:44:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2023 NBA free throws per game leaders</title><link>https://deadspin.com/2023-nba-free-throws-per-game-leaders-1851036206</link><description>This article is based on data from Sportradar. Read more...</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:09:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kylie &amp; Kendall Jenner Showcase Chic Styles on Vegas Work Trip</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1401421/kylie-jenner-and-kendall-jenner-showcase-chic-styles-on-their-sister-work-day-in-las-vegas?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>Kylie and Kendall take Las Vegas! Kylie Jenner and Kendall Jenner made a joint and stylish appearance in Las Vegas May 10. The Kylie Cosmetics founder wore a red sleeveless Whistle Latex midi...</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Generational Wealth: Does the Apple Fall Far From the Tree?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/06/generational-wealth-does-the-apple-fall-far-from-the-tree/</link><description>There is strong evidence that most “rich families” will be poorer after several generations. Some of the reasons for this are systemic like taxes. But most factors that diminish a family’s wealth over generations are the choices that heirs make.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 12:37:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>South Dakota Gov. Kristi Noem is banned from nearly 20% of her own state as fight with Native American tribes heats up</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/11/kristi-noem-banned-20-percent-south-dakota-native-american-tribes/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2151899368-e1715466996572.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Two more tribes banished her this week over comments she made earlier this year about tribal leaders benefitting from drug cartels.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 23:53:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spring Slumber</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/spring-slumber/</link><description>In the gentle embrace of mid-spring, there’s a delightful charm in refreshing my sleepwear collection. I tend to gravitate towards… The post Spring Slumber appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 20:00:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What an unexpected response :)</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/azxLVXj</link><description>Tags: wholesome 5910 points, 321 comments.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 07:25:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paris Saint-Germain Draws From Urban Art Scene for 2024-25 Home Kit</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/10/paris-saint-germain-draws-from-urban-art-scene-for-2024-25-home-kit/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Traditional red-and-white Hechter stripe returns to center of jersey, but is "reinterpreted with a fluid and dynamic brushstroke style"</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 15:29:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Women in AI: Rachel Coldicutt researches how technology impacts society</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/11/women-in-ai-rachel-coldicutt-researches-how-technology-impacts-society/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Rachel Coldicutt is the founder of Careful Industries, which researches the social impact technology has on society. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 18:00:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weinstein Ruling Poses Quandary: Can #MeToo Coexist With Protections for Defendants?</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/04/sex-crimes-weinstein-me-too</link><description>Proving sex crimes often requires evidence that is generally excluded to protect the rights of the accused.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Creamy Cucumber Salad</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/creamy-cucumber-salad/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Creamy Cucumber Salad is a delicious and refreshing side dish. All it takes is a handful of fresh simple ingredients…</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aoki Simmons Posts Response to Kimora's Embarrassment Over Her Older BF</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/11/aoki-simmons-responds-kimora-lee-simmons-kissing-older-man-vittorio-assaf/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>The Simmons family mother-daughter standoff is getting more public ... as Aoki appears to be firing back at her mom Kimora Lee Simmons for commenting about Aoki's brief fling with much older restaurateur Vittorio Assaf. Aoki posted a quote Friday…</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:28:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Healthy Lifestyle Can Add Years to Life, Despite 'Bad' Genes</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/balance/news/20240509/defeat-bad-genes-with-healthy-lifestyle?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Turn around those bad family genes with four lifestyle changes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 19:47:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Using Solid Stain In Our Outdoor Shower</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/solid-deck-stain-outdoor-shower/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>In all of our years of DIYing, I don’t think we’ve ever used a solid stain before. But we recently had a project that was *perfectly* suited for it and, well, solid stain quickly won us over. It was recommended by a professional house painter to us, specifically because he thought it would be great for our outdoor shower. And we found it easy to apply, it gave us great coverage, and we got an even-better-than-we-expected result (which is always the best kind!). So here’s a post that covers all the pros &amp; cons and hows &amp; whys of solid stain. As you can see, the “canvas” for this staining project was our outdoor shower. We gave it a mini-makeover right after moving in, but we knew it may need more attention and care down the line. Honestly, we dreaded the task of stripping and restaining it – so many nooks &amp; crannies! Continue reading Using Solid Stain In Our Outdoor Shower at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 17:46:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Keep Buying the Dips</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/how-to-keep-buying-the-dips/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, it's Ross Givens here with the Chart of the Day. In recent weeks, market movements have shifted to a more favorable pattern, oscillating within a consolidation range after a turbulent start to April. Now, signs suggest a potential breakout from this range, signaling a crucial turning point for traders. Learn how to navigate this evolving market landscape in today's Insight of the Day. The post How to Keep Buying the Dips appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nissan reports 92% jump in profit as sales surge</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/11/nissan-reports-92-jump-in-profit-as-sales-surge/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/10125027/japan-automobile-climate-energy.jpeg</image_url><description>Filed under: Earnings/Financials , Nissan Continue reading Nissan reports 92% jump in profit as sales surge Nissan reports 92% jump in profit as sales surge originally appeared on Autoblog on Sat, 11 May 2024 09:30:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rookie Reply: The Rental Property Expenses You CAN’T Afford to Miss</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-404</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>How do you know if a rental property will make enough cash flow before you buy? Budgeting is KEY. When breaking down a deal, it’s critical that you account for […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 07:02:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Riot’s Deals of the Day for May 10, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/book-riots-deals-of-the-day-for-may-10-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/collage-ofdeals-for-5-10-2024.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>Viola Davis' Memoir, Lovecraft Country, E.L. James, Korean Independence, and More of Today's Best Book Deals</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 18:05:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>15 Ways to Own Digital Terrain</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/15-ways-to-own-digital-terrain/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=15-ways-to-own-digital-terrain</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>It is now no longer optional…you must have an online presence! Your career stability and your job search demand it. Here are some tips to help you begin claiming digital terrain and brand it with your unique messaging! Why Should You Own Digital Terrain? You need to stake a claim by owning turf on the […] The post 15 Ways to Own Digital Terrain appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 15:56:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>“Why do they feel sad?” Shared book reading reveals how children learn about others’ emotions</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/shared-book-reading/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=shared-book-reading</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers: It is good for children to identify the emotions of others in conversations with caregivers because it scaffolds their ability to identify others’ emotions on their own. Children who use more emotion talk in parent-child conversations about emotions are more likely to have higher emotion knowledge one year later. Parents can […] The post “Why do they feel sad?” Shared book reading reveals how children learn about others’ emotions appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 08:19:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This inflation-focused ETF may be in a sweet spot</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/11/inflation-etf-may-be-in-a-sweet-spot-even-if-fed-cuts-rates.html</link><description>Horizon Kinetics' James Davolos thinks his firm's inflation-focused ETF is "ideally positioned" for gains this year.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2023 NBA field goals per game leaders</title><link>https://deadspin.com/2023-nba-field-goals-per-game-leaders-1851036211</link><description>This article is based on data from Sportradar. Read more...</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:09:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Travis Kelce Dances With Niecy Nash on Set of Grotesquerie</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1401419/travis-kelce-dances-with-niecy-nash-on-set-of-grotesquerie?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>While his girlfriend Taylor Swift debuted new choreography on her Eras tour, Travis Kelce got a dance lesson of his own. On May 10, Niecy Nash shared a behind-the-scenes video from the set of Ryan...</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 19:56:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>State Capitalism in Private Markets: Mission Creep</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/03/state-capitalism-in-private-markets-mission-creep/</link><description>Governments relish mingling in markets. Yet, if past policies are any guide, taxpayers are being shortchanged.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 12:30:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>An auction for a private lunch with Marc Benioff raises $1.5 million in his first year replacing Warren Buffett, who netted $19 million for his final auction</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/11/marc-benioff-lunch-auction-charity-fundraiser-warren-buffett-berkshire-hathaway/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/AP24132717573074-e1715464954343.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The weeklong eBay auction that raises money for the Glide Foundation in San Francisco wrapped up Friday night.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 23:20:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coral Crush</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/coral-crush/</link><description>Outfit Details: Sir Top &amp; Skirt (also love the dress version), Loro Piana Hat, Prada Sunglasses Spring welcomes the delightful hue of coral, a color that perfectly… The post Coral Crush appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 05:00:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>7 out of 10 Europeans believe that their country takes in too many migrants. I agree!</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/aLnQP5g</link><description>Tags: Europe , Deport , Wtf , Politics , Stop the Invasion of EU 8063 points, 719 comments.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 07:25:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Report: WNBA Expanding to Toronto for 2026</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/10/report-wnba-expanding-to-toronto-for-2026/basketball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The WNBA is crossing the border! According to a CBC report, Toronto will be getting a Women’s National Basketball Association expansion franchise for the 2026 WNBA season. Kilmer Sports Inc., led by Toronto billionaire Larry Tanenbaum, will own the franchise. The report says the league’s official announcement is expected to</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 14:25:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SAP’s chief sustainability officer isn’t interested in getting your company to do the right thing</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/11/saps-chief-sustainability-officer-isnt-interested-in-getting-your-company-to-do-the-right-thing/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>SAP Chief Sustainability Officer Sophia Mendelsohn wants to incentivize companies to be green because it's profitable, not just because it's right. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mississippi Lawmakers Considered Modest Public Defense Reforms. They Rejected All of Them.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/02/mississippi-public-defense-legislative-reforms</link><description>With its refusal to impose oversight or consistent standards in local defense, Mississippi risks falling further behind rest of the U.S., critics say.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Beginner’s Guide to Baking Bread</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/beginners-guide-to-baking-bread/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>You want to make bread, but where do you start? My beginner’s guide to baking bread is here to save…</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Christy Martin Honored by Sydney Sweeny Casting, Wants to Train with Her</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/11/christy-martin-honored-sydney-sweeny-casting-want-train-boxing-biopic/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Christy Martin's happy Sydney Sweeney's lacing up her boxing gloves ... saying she's thrilled Syd's playing her in a new biopic, and she wants to make sure her ring moves look authentic. The boxing legend tells TMZ ... she's excited for Syd's…</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:28:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Taking Racism out of the Kidney Disease Equation</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/a-to-z-guides/features/end-of-racist-kidney-math?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Kidney care in the U.S. is at a watershed moment of moving past a deeply entrenched, institutionally racist equation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 04:17:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ZZ Plant – Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/zz-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>The ZZ plant is another one of our favorite low-maintenance houseplants. They’re easy to care for, hard to kill, and always look full &amp; leafy. They’ve even earned the nickname “Eternity Plant” because they’re practically indestructible! That’s why they’re a top choice for commercial spaces, doctor’s offices, and busy homes like ours. Don’t you love a house plant you can forget about? ZZ plants are sold in a variety of sizes, meaning they’re great for shelves, tabletops, and small surfaces as well as larger statements on the floor. We have some that are over 3 feet tall with their pots! ZZ Plant Quick Facts Here’s what you need to know about your ZZ plant at a glance: Latin name : Zamioculcas zamiifolia Plant family : Araceae or Arums, which includes Philodendron , Alocasia, Aglaonema, Monstera , and Peace Lily Common name s: ZZ plant, Zanzibar Gem, Zuzu plant, Emerald Palm, Eternity plant Native to : East Africa Light : Medium indirect light, but is also low-light tolerant Watering : Every 2-3 weeks during its growing season Soil : Standard potting mix as long as it drains well Ideal Humidity : Average household humidity, ideally 40-50% Ideal Temperature : 65°F to 75°F Cold Hardiness : USDA Zones 9b-11 What Is A ZZ Plant? Continue reading ZZ Plant – Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 19:36:48 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>