<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 22:36:09 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>New Utah Hockey Club Logo Appears on NHL.com</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/31/new-utah-hockey-club-logo-appears-on-nhl-com/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>There appears to be a new logo for the new Utah NHL team, one that actually looks like a logo and comes from a pretty legitimate source. The logo, which we hadn’t seen before tonight, was uploaded to NHL.com — about as official a source as you can get. Now,</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 00:03:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Donald Trump's Pal Bernard Kerik Says Prez's Safety Too Risky in Prison</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/01/donald-trump-bernard-kerik-says-should-serve-time-separately-safety/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Donald Trump's longtime friend Bernard Kerik has some thoughts on how he should serve his time if his guilty verdict lands him behind bars. Kerik -- who served as Commissioner for the New York City Department of Correction as well as the NYPD…</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 22:36:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blue Jays Players, Staff Share Design Process and Thoughts on City Connect Uniform</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/31/blue-jays-players-staff-share-design-process-and-thoughts-on-city-connect-uniform/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Following the release of their new “Pitch Blue” City Connect uniform Thursday night, the Toronto Blue Jays held a uniform release party on the rooftop patio of Lavelle in Downtown Toronto. SportsLogos.Net was invited down to get a close-up look at the new caps and skyline-clad jerseys, chat with some</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 23:12:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WeHo Pride Has Cops Bracing For Palestinian Protesters, Angry Trumpers</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/01/weho-pride-protestors-cops-trump/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Looks like WeHo Pride kicking off this weekend might be more tense than celebratory ... we've learned cops are gearing up for the worst amid recent global events. Law enforcement sources tell TMZ ... with the Pro-Palestine Rally going down in West…</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 22:36:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aston Villa Officially Switches Over to New Crest</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/31/aston-villa-officially-switches-over-to-new-crest/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Official unveiling confirms crest that was first leaked back in January 2024 and was used in graphics around Adidas kit deal announcement earlier in May</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 17:00:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bill Maher Says College Protesters Should Fight for Gender Equality, Not Hamas</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/01/bill-maher-apartheid-social-justice-issue-new-rule/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Bill Maher did a pivot Friday night ... actually complimenting the pro-Hamas college protesters for believing in something that was bigger than themselves ... but then he lowered the boom, saying they missed the cause they should be embracing by a…</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 22:36:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Green is the Color: CFL’s Saskatchewan Roughriders Unveil ‘Rider Nation’ Alternate Uniform</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/31/green-is-the-color-cfls-saskatchewan-roughriders-unveil-rider-nation-alternate-uniform/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Alternate uniform introduces new S logo on helmet, sleeves and pants along with two new shades of green; will be worn for two regular season home games in 2024</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 15:43:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Caroline Manzo Accuses Brandi Glanville Of Sexually Assaulting Her</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/01/caroline-manzo-brandi-glanville-sexual-assault-real-housewives-bravo/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Caroline Manzo is painting more of a portrait of what happened to her allegedly at the hands of Brandi Glanville – and the new allegations are nothing less than shocking! First, the back story ... the 'Real Housewives of New Jersey' star filed a…</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 22:36:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fly By Night: Toronto Blue Jays Unveil City Connect Uniform</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/30/fly-by-night-toronto-blue-jays-unveil-city-connect-uniform/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Starting a new chapter to find what they’re after, the Toronto Blue Jays unveiled their first-ever Nike MLB City Connect uniform tonight. The new ‘Night Mode’ uniform, as the team is calling it, was first revealed via a video posted to their social media channels. It’s a head-to-toe blue so</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 00:45:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jennifer Lopez Cancels Tour Amid Ben Affleck Separation Speculation</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/31/jennifer-lopez-cancels-tour-amid-ben-affleck-separation-speculation/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Jennifer Lopez will not be hitting the road this summer after all -- as the singer is canceling her planned tour outright, even before it starts ... TMZ has learned. A rep for Live Nation tells us Jen's "THIS IS ME...LIVE" tour -- which was…</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 22:36:09 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>