<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 07:25:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>For the Land: Cleveland Guardians Unveil New City Connect Uniform Set</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/12/for-the-land-cleveland-guardians-unveil-new-city-connect-uniform-set/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>These uniforms are CLE-an. The Cleveland Guardians became the latest team to unveil their Nike MLB City Connect Uniform, doing so via a video posted to their social media accounts late Sunday night. Overall, the navy blue, red, and sandstone uniform draws most of its inspiration from the iconic Guardians</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 01:00:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anita Baker Cancels ATL Show at Last Minute, Upends Mother's Day Gifts</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/12/anita-baker-cancels-last-minute-atlanta-mothers-day-concert/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Some Anita Baker fans are scrambling for Mother's Day gifts this morning after the singer had to pull the plug on her show in Atlanta just a few minutes before it was supposed to start. Anita's show at State Farm Arena was packed Saturday night, as…</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 07:25:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MLS’s Portland Timbers Introduce Tillamook as New Front-of-Shirt Sponsor</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/12/mlss-portland-timbers-introduce-tillamook-as-new-front-of-shirt-sponsor/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Oregon-based dairy farmers' cooperative takes over prime real estate on front of Timbers' shirts; previous sponsor dropped after only one game</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 23:40:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tom Brady Sends Mother's Day Wish to Exes Gisele, Bridget After Roast Jokes</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/12/tom-brady-mothers-day-tribute-gisele-bundchen-pissed-roast-divorce-jokes/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Tom Brady's attempting, perhaps, his greatest comeback ever -- kicking off Mother's Day with warm words for the mothers of his children, one week after they took several stray shots during his roast. Tom posted several shots of his own mom, Galynn,…</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 07:25:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Serie A Players Honor Moms By Putting Their Names on Game Jerseys</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/12/serie-a-players-honor-moms-by-putting-their-names-on-game-jerseys/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Players on seven Serie A clubs wear mothers' first names or maiden names on the backs of their jerseys in matches held all weekend long</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 22:58:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Taylor Swift Fans Shocked by Baby Left on Floor During Paris Concert</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/12/taylor-swift-baby-floor-eras-tour-concert-paris/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Taylor Swift fans have bad blood with a fellow Swiftie who left their infant lying on the floor of the Paris arena where Taylor's performing. The shocking photo has gone viral, for obvious reasons, after it was posted by a woman who says she was at…</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 07:25:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hub City Spartanburgers unveil new name, brand</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/12/hub-city-spartanburgers-unveil-new-name-brand/uncategorized/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The newest entry in the world of Minor League Baseball branding is the Hub City Spartanburgers, just unveiled yesterday. The Single-A affiliate of the Texas Rangers, newly relocated from Kinston, North Carolina, will play in Spartanburg, South Carolina. The town of Spartanburg earned the nickname Hub City because historically, it</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 19:51:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cindy Crawford Says She Had Survivor’s Guilt After Brother’s Death</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/12/cindy-crawford-suffer-suvivors-guilt-brother-death-jeffrey-family-cancer/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Cindy Crawford’s getting real about her brother dying at a young age ... saying her dad wanted a boy, so she and her sisters felt like they should’ve died instead. The legendary supermodel opened up about her survivor’s guilt in a new episode…</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 07:25:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mother’s Day 2024: Pink Caps, Pink Ribbons as MLB Salutes Mom</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/11/mothers-day-2024-pink-caps-pink-ribbons-as-mlb-salutes-mom/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>It’s Mother’s Day here in North America, which means we’ll see pink-themed baseball caps and ribbons on the uniforms of Major League Baseball players, coaches, managers, and umpires during games played on Sunday, May 12th. SHOP: 2024 MLB Mother’s Day team caps available right now This will be the eighth</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:07:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rihanna, A$AP Rocky Celebrate RZA's 2nd Birthday, Adults Party Hard Too</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/12/rhianna-asap-rza-second-birthday-party/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Rihanna and A$AP Rocky aren't about to let their son RZA and his little friends have all the fun celebrating his birthday. The couple's firstborn will reach the ripe old age of 2 on Monday, but Mom and Dad threw a big party for him Saturday night…</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 07:25:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>