<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from multiple RSS sources, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 07:12:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>BiggerNews: 100% Financing for First-Time Home Buyers is HERE</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-939</link><description>If you’re a first-time home buyer, now may be one of the best times to get a loan in recent history, according to mortgage advisor Jeff Welgan. With new no-money-down […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 07:02:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tesla recalls the Cybertruck for faulty accelerator pedals that can get stuck</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/19/tesla-cybertruck-throttle-accelerator-pedal-stuck/</link><description>Tesla is recalling all 3,878 Cybertrucks that it has shipped to date, due to a problem where the accelerator pedal can get stuck, putting drivers at risk of a crash, according to the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. The recall caps a tumultuous week for Tesla. The company laid off more than 10% of its […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 11:31:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Officials Failed to Act When COVID Hit Prisons. A New Study Shows the Deadly Cost.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/18/covid-prison-deaths-data</link><description>People in prison died at 3.4 times the rate of the free population, with the oldest hit hardest. New data holds lessons for preventing future deaths.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Don’t Worry, Gen Z, Your Face Isn’t Aging Faster Than Others</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/beauty/news/20240418/no-gen-z-isnt-aging-faster?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Some members of Generation Z are worried they are aging more quickly, thanks to social media influencers selling products. But skin care experts said the claim is false. Rather, it largely boils down to perception.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 20:16:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rookie Reply: Using a Car as a Down Payment (!?), ADUs, &amp; House Hacking 101</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-395</link><description>House hacking and renting by the room are two of the easiest ways for rookies to dive into the world of real estate investing. Both investing strategies are affordable, low-risk, […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 07:02:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fintech CRED secures in-principle approval for payment aggregator license</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/19/fintech-cred-secures-in-principle-approval-for-payment-aggregator-license/</link><description>CRED has received the in-principle approval for payment aggregator license in a boost to the Indian fintech startup that could help it better serve its customers and launch new products and experiment with ideas faster. The Bengaluru-headquartered startup, valued at $6.4 billion, received the in-principle approval from the Reserve Bank of India for the payment […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 09:37:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Parents Paying for Their Children’s Crimes</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/13/michigan-school-shooting-parents</link><description>Experts warn about a wave of legal consequences for parents like the Crumbleys, while some states consider prosecutions for kids as young as 10.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Changing Entrenched Health Beliefs Is Not Impossible</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/vaccines/news/20240418/changing-entrenched-health-beliefs-not-impossible?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Some people with deep-rooted beliefs on a wide range of health topics – from COVID vaccination to mental health stigma to foods including genetically modified organisms – could be persuaded to rethink their positions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 18:11:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Full-Time FIRE and Traveling the World…All Thanks to Rentals!</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-521</link><description>Could real estate investing help you reach financial freedom much sooner than you thought possible? Today’s guest had his world turned upside down by one tragic incident, but he was […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 07:01:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Internet users are getting younger; now the UK is weighing up if AI can help protect them</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/18/internet-users-are-getting-younger-now-the-uk-is-weighing-up-if-ai-can-help-protect-them/</link><description>Artificial intelligence has been in the crosshairs of governments over how it might be misused for fraud, disinformation and other malicious online activity; now a U.K. regulator wants to explore how AI is used on the other side: in the fight against malicious content when it involves children. Ofcom, the regulator charged with enforcing the […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 00:52:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I Had a Tough Job at My Brooklyn Jail: Keeping Men From Taking Their Own Lives</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/12/brooklyn-jail-suicide-prevention-aide</link><description>As a suicide prevention aide, I had to make sure my fellow detainees didn’t harm themselves. It was surprisingly easy to get such a complex job.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Facing My Smoking Triggers</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/smoking-cessation/features/facing-my-smoking-triggers?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Smoking Triggers: Learn to identify and manage triggers to quit smoking.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 21:52:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The On the Market Awards: These Markets and Strategies Will WIN in 2024!</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-209</link><description>Welcome to the first-ever On the Market Housing Market Awards! This year, we’re giving out awards for the best housing market in the country, best beginner real estate investing strategy, […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 07:02:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hugging Face releases a benchmark for testing generative AI on health tasks</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/18/hugging-face-releases-a-benchmark-for-testing-generative-ai-on-health-tasks/</link><description>Hugging Face has published a new leaderboard and benchmark for evaluating generative AI models on health-related tasks and questions.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 23:07:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Supreme Court Case on Homelessness May Limit Prisoner Rights and Expand Executions</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/10/supreme-court-homeless-grants-pass-originalism</link><description>In Grants Pass v. Johnson, a town in Oregon asks the court to reconsider what constitutes “cruel and unusual punishments”.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Get Past Your Fears About Quitting Smoking</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/smoking-cessation/features/your-quit-smoking-fears-debunked?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Common quit smoking fears are debunked by experts, who offer tips on how to face and overcome worries such as weight gain or becoming stressed out.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 21:51:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seven Reasons Why the Housing Market STILL Hasn’t Recovered From the Pandemic</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/why-the-housing-market-still-has-not-recovered-from-the-pandemic</link><description>The pandemic swept through the U.S. housing market like a tsunami. Radical price hikes and all-time low inventory accompanied massive migration away from pricey big cities. Four years later, the […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 22:36:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tesla still plans to build 1,800-mile charging corridor for semi trucks despite Biden funding snub</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/18/tesla-semi-big-rig-charging-corridor-biden-funding/</link><description>Tesla is pushing forward with a plan to build an electric big rig charging corridor stretching from Texas to California, despite being snubbed by a lucrative federal funding program that’s part of President Biden’s Bipartisan Infrastructure Law. But the original scope of the project could still change, TechCrunch has learned. The company had been seeking […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 21:28:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What an Eclipse Lockdown Reveals about Dignity in Prisons and Jails</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/06/eclipse-new-york-prison-discrimination</link><description>Recent lawsuits regarding the rights of incarcerated people and guards include gender, religious discrimination, and the right to watch the eclipse</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Surprise Pregnancy: Could It Happen to You?</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/sex/birth-control/features/surprise-unplanned-pregnancy?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Almost half of all pregnancies in the U.S. are unplanned. Find out how this happens so often, from user error to irregular periods.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 21:14:05 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>