<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 02:02:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Book Review: The New World Economy in 5 Trends</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/24/book-review-the-new-world-economy-in-5-trends/</link><description>A diligent economist and an eclectic bookworm serve up an analysis of megatrends that will have the greatest impact on economies and investments: innovation, productivity, climate, multiglobalization, debt, and aging.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 12:22:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meet the 102-year-old healthy-living pioneer who was espousing ‘wellness’ long before it was a trend</title><link>https://fortune.com/well/article/102-year-old-rancho-la-puerta-owner-on-longevity/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Deborah-100-e1716477772675.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The founder of the famed Rancho la Puerta resort says that not worrying is more important than what kind of water you drink.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Factor Strategies Belong in Your Completion Portfolio Toolkit</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/23/factor-strategies-belong-in-your-completion-portfolio-toolkit/</link><description>Why wouldn't you include factor strategies in your completion portfolio? A review of the two commonly used approaches for managing institutional assets highlights their symbiotic nature.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 19:09:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Families of slain Uvalde victims sue Meta, 'Call of Duty' maker, and gun manufacturer: 'This three-headed monster knowingly exposed him to the weapon'</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/24/families-of-slain-uvalde-victims-sue-meta-instagram-video-game-gun/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1975542608-e1716592199789.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>“There is a direct line between the conduct of these companies and the Uvalde shooting,” said Josh Koskoff, an attorney for the families.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 00:11:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>For the Analyst: Peer Benchmarking Methods to Improve Earnings Forecasts</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/21/for-the-analyst-peer-benchmarking-methods-to-improve-earnings-forecasts/</link><description>Peer benchmarking is a vexing task for financial analysts but one that is critical for forecasting earnings. This straightforward measure can help find peers for relative performance, compensation, and valuation benchmarking.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 12:47:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A law firm tried to blame a 9-year-old girl for not noticing an iPhone camera a former American Airlines flight attendant secretly taped to a toilet seat</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/24/law-firm-blamed-girl-camera-lavatory-flight-attendant/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2151750944_ae66ab-e1716591110117.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>A former American Airlines attendant is accused of luring girls to use the lavatory after taping his iPhone to the toilet seat and explaining that the seat was broken.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 23:53:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Building LLMs in the Open-Source Community: A Call to Action for Investment Professionals</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/20/building-llms-in-the-open-source-community-a-call-to-action-for-investment-professionals/</link><description>Large language models like ChatGPT are changing the way we think about investing and reshaping roles in the investment profession.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 16:26:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CEO at $14 billion electronics firm can’t talk about his resignation following an internal investigation</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/24/jabil-ceo-kenneth-wilson-tech-electronics-banned-exit-million/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1263932803-e1716584694885.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The former exec can only say “no comment” in response to queries, according to restrictive covenants with an unusual provision.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 23:00:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sustainability Reporting: Navigating Assurance Practices</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/17/sustainability-reporting-navigating-assurance-practices/</link><description>Don't be lulled into a false sense of security by the word "assurance" when evaluating sustainability reports. Assurance practices vary, and investors would be wise to learn more about the different levels of coverage.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 17:57:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Front-end developers: These are the states where you’ll find the highest average salaries</title><link>https://fortune.com/education/careers/front-end-developer-salary/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1435042864-e1715022493220.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Front-end developers work on the visual aspect of websites, and can earn relatively high annual salaries. The states where they’re paid the most, though, may surprise you.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 22:54:23 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>