<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from multiple RSS sources, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 06:57:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The On the Market Awards: These Markets and Strategies Will WIN in 2024!</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-209</link><description>Welcome to the first-ever On the Market Housing Market Awards! This year, we’re giving out awards for the best housing market in the country, best beginner real estate investing strategy, […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 07:02:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ChatGPT is a squeeze away with Nothing’s upgraded earbuds</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/18/chatgpt-is-a-squeeze-away-with-nothings-upgraded-earbuds/</link><description>Nothing today announced a pair of refreshes to its earbud line. The naming conventions are a touch convoluted here, but the Nothing Ear is an update to the Nothing Ear (2), while the Nothing Ear (a) is more of a spiritual successor to the Nothing Ear Stick. The most notable bit of today’s news, however, […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 11:45:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Officials Failed to Act When COVID Hit Prisons. A New Study Shows the Deadly Cost.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/18/covid-prison-deaths-data</link><description>People in prison died at 3.4 times the rate of the free population, with the oldest hit hardest. New data holds lessons for preventing future deaths.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Facing My Smoking Triggers</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/smoking-cessation/features/facing-my-smoking-triggers?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Smoking Triggers: Learn to identify and manage triggers to quit smoking.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 21:52:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seven Reasons Why the Housing Market STILL Hasn’t Recovered From the Pandemic</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/why-the-housing-market-still-has-not-recovered-from-the-pandemic</link><description>The pandemic swept through the U.S. housing market like a tsunami. Radical price hikes and all-time low inventory accompanied massive migration away from pricey big cities. Four years later, the […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 22:36:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Google fires 28 employees after sit-in protest over controversial Project Nimbus contract with Israel</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/18/google-fires-28-employees-after-sit-in-protest-over-controversial-project-nimbus-contract-with-israe/</link><description>Google has terminated the employment of 28 employees following a prolonged sit-in protest at the company’s Sunnyvale and New York offices. The protests were in response to Project Nimbus, a $1.2 billion cloud computing contract inked by Google and Amazon with the Israeli government and its military three years ago. The controversial project, which also […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 11:41:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Parents Paying for Their Children’s Crimes</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/13/michigan-school-shooting-parents</link><description>Experts warn about a wave of legal consequences for parents like the Crumbleys, while some states consider prosecutions for kids as young as 10.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Get Past Your Fears About Quitting Smoking</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/smoking-cessation/features/your-quit-smoking-fears-debunked?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Common quit smoking fears are debunked by experts, who offer tips on how to face and overcome worries such as weight gain or becoming stressed out.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 21:51:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I’m Four Months Into a 1031 Exchange—Now It’s All About Finding the Best Deal in the Haystack</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/1031-investor-journal-four</link><description>We are less than a month away from listing our Brooklyn, New York condo, which we bought for $375,000 back in 2004, the same week we got married. 20 years, two […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 21:58:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Orbex’s new funding may accelerate its Prime microlauncher into orbit</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/18/orbexs-new-funding-may-accelerate-its-prime-microlauncher-into-orbit/</link><description>UK-based small launch developer Orbex got another boost from Scotland’s national bank and other investors as it gears up for its first orbital launch, though that mission still does not have a set date. Founded in 2015, Orbex is one of a handful of firms racing to develop the next generation of European launch vehicles. […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 08:00:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I Had a Tough Job at My Brooklyn Jail: Keeping Men From Taking Their Own Lives</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/12/brooklyn-jail-suicide-prevention-aide</link><description>As a suicide prevention aide, I had to make sure my fellow detainees didn’t harm themselves. It was surprisingly easy to get such a complex job.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Surprise Pregnancy: Could It Happen to You?</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/sex/birth-control/features/surprise-unplanned-pregnancy?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Almost half of all pregnancies in the U.S. are unplanned. Find out how this happens so often, from user error to irregular periods.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 21:14:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mindset, Above All, Matters Most—Here’s My Four-Step Formula For Transforming My Mind</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/four-step-formula-to-improve-mindset</link><description>Why does mindset matter most? The answer is quite simple, yet surprisingly hard to believe: Mindset matters most because having the right one allows you to have the proper focus, […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 20:17:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>India’s VerSe acquires Apple News+ rival Magzter</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/17/dailyhunt-parent-acquires-newsstand-app-magzter/</link><description>VerSe Innovation, the parent firm of Indian news aggregator app Dailyhunt, has acquired the popular digital newsstand platform Magzter, the two said Thursday. VerSe, based in Bengaluru, didn’t disclose the financial terms of the deal for Magzter, which is headquartered in New York and counted Singapore Press Holdings among its backers. The acquisition of Magzter, […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 03:36:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Supreme Court Case on Homelessness May Limit Prisoner Rights and Expand Executions</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/10/supreme-court-homeless-grants-pass-originalism</link><description>In Grants Pass v. Johnson, a town in Oregon asks the court to reconsider what constitutes “cruel and unusual punishments”.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Truth About Whole-Body Scans</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/a-to-z-guides/features/truth-about-whole-body-scans?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>What to know about whole-body CT scans and DEXA scans for body composition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 23:15:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scaling from 0 to 20+ Doors Using These “Self-Management” Tools &amp; Tips</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-938</link><description>If there’s one thing that’ll make or break your real estate portfolio, it’s property management. When done correctly, property management can feed you consistent, passive income without the everyday stressors […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 07:02:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Consumer Financial Protection Bureau fines BloomTech for false claims</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/17/consumer-financial-protection-bureau-fines-bloomtech-for-false-claims/</link><description>The CFPB is permanently banning BloomTech from consumer lending activities and its CEO, Austen Allred, from student lending for a period of 10 years.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 00:02:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What an Eclipse Lockdown Reveals about Dignity in Prisons and Jails</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/06/eclipse-new-york-prison-discrimination</link><description>Recent lawsuits regarding the rights of incarcerated people and guards include gender, religious discrimination, and the right to watch the eclipse</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When to Call a Pediatrician</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/parenting/baby/features/when-call-pediatrician?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Your child is sick. Do you know if you should call the pediatrician, or wait? Use this guide to know when to make the call.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 22:44:42 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>