<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 13:53:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Jacksonville Jaguars Unveil New “Shell White” Alternate Helmets</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/25/jacksonville-jaguars-unveil-new-shell-white-alternate-helmets/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Confirming our report from April, the Jacksonville Jaguars unveiled their new "Shell White"alternate helmets early Thursday morning.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 12:21:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Punter Kyle Ulbrich Camping Out At Dolphins' Facility In Hopes Of Landing Tryout</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/25/punter-kyle-ulbrich-camping-miami-dolphins-facility-hopes-landing-nfl-tryout/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Former Middle Tennessee State punter Kyle Ulbrich is taking a unique approach to making an NFL roster ... he's currently camped outside the Miami Dolphins' practice facility -- hoping to get a tryout with the squad! TMZ Sports spoke with the NFL…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 13:53:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Notre Dame Unveils Shamrock Series Uniforms For Game Against Army At Yankee Stadium</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/24/notre-dame-unveils-shamrock-series-uniforms-for-game-against-army-at-yankee-stadium/college/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Notre Dame unveiled its latest Shamrock Series uniforms, which are inspired by the "Four Horsemen" and will be worn against Army at Yankee Stadium on Nov. 23.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 21:21:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shifty Shellshock's L.A. Celebration of Life Plans Finalized</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/25/shifty-shellshock-celebration-life-event-finalized/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Shifty Shellshock's friends and family are ready for his grand send-off ... plans for his celebration of his life are finalized, and TMZ has all the details. The Crazy Town frontman is being honored Aug. 11 at Academy LA ... and some fans will be…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 13:53:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MLB All-Star Game Logos, Like Super Bowls, May Get a Templated Look Going Forward</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/23/mlb-all-star-game-logos-like-super-bowls-may-get-a-templated-look-going-forward/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Standardized sports logos are trending, from the Super Bowl to literally everything in the NBA. But what about Major League Baseball’s All-Star Game… Well, guess what? It looks like baseball’s annual Mid-Summer Classic is ready to join the club. “You might start to see some similarities in the format and</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 21:37:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>George Floyd's Ex Heartbroken Over Sonya Massey, Thinks Kamala Can End Police Brutality</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/25/george-floyd-ex-roxie-washington-sonya-massey-kamala-harris-police-brutality/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>The mother of George Floyd's daughter is weighing in on the police-involved shooting that took Sonya Massey's life ... calling on Kamala Harris to help end this endemic killing. Roxie Washington -- who shared her daughter, Gianna, with George…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 13:53:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stellar Real Madrid Away Kit Headlines Recent Launches from Spain, Rest of Europe</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/23/stellar-real-madrid-away-kit-headlines-recent-launches-from-spain-and-rest-of-europe/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Inter Milan adds gold flourishes to home kit to celebrate 20th Serie A title; other clubs unveiling 24-25 kits include Aston Villa, Real Valladolid, Girona, Osasuna, Borussia Dortmund, Stade Rennais, Toulouse</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 17:27:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FBI Director Says Donald Trump May or May Not Have Been Struck By Bullet</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/25/fbi-director-donald-trump-not-struck-bullet-shooting-glass/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>9:31 AM PT -- Steven Cheung, a rep for Donald Trump, tells TMZ ... "Anyone who believes this conspiracy bullshit is either mentally deficient or willfully peddling falsehoods for political reasons." Donald Trump may or may not have been struck by a…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 13:53:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2025 MLB All-Star Game Logo Revealed; Hosted by Atlanta Braves</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/22/2025-mlb-all-star-game-logo-revealed-hosted-by-atlanta-braves/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Atlanta… You’re on the clock. Four years after they lost the game with just months to go, the Atlanta Braves are back and ready to host. Major League Baseball, along with the team, today unveiled the logo for the 2025 MLB All-Star Game, to be played at Truist Field on</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 00:18:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Celine Dion Waves To Serenading Fans After Olympics Performance Rehearsals</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/25/celine-dion-waves-fans-paris-hotel-olympic-rehearsals/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Celine Dion returned to her hotel after a marathon day of Olympic rehearsals in Paris to find a surprise concert of her own -- courtesy of her fans singing and cheering for her one day before her grand stage comeback. Check out the vid ... the…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 13:53:20 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>