<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 06:54:03 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Sources: Minnesota Vikings To Unveil “Winter Whiteout” Alternate Uniforms On June 7</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/02/sources-minnesota-vikings-to-unveil-winter-whiteout-alternate-uniforms-on-june-7/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>According to multiple sources, the Minnesota Vikings will unveil their new “Winter Whiteout” alternate uniforms this Friday.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 23:31:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adele Goes on Profanity-Laced Rant in Support of Pride Month</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/02/adele-pride-las-vegas-lgbtq-gay-community-show/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Adele doesn't play around when it comes to her support of the LGBTQ+ community – and one of her concertgoers found that out the hard way after mouthing off about Pride month. The singer was performing onstage at the Las Vegas Colosseum at Caesars…</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 06:54:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Baseball Players Wearing #4 Patch Today for Lou Gehrig Day</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/02/baseball-players-wearing-4-patch-today-for-lou-gehrig-day/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Why are baseball players wearing a number 4 patch on their uniforms today? Major League Baseball is recognizing Lou Gehrig Day on Sunday, June 2, 2024, an annual event dedicated to raising awareness for ALS (Amyotrophic Lateral Sclerosis) and commemorating Lou Gehrig’s legacy. This year, all MLB teams will wear</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 17:11:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Travis Kelce Pressed by Jason Sudeikis to Marry Taylor Swift</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/02/travis-kelce-taylor-swift-propose-jason-sudeikis-marry-skit/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Travis Kelce had an on-the-surface uncomfortable moment Saturday night when Jason Sudeikis pressed him on sealing the deal with Taylor Swift, but it was all planned out. The 2 dudes, along with Robert Smigel and George Wendt performed a skit at the…</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 06:54:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Utah Hockey Club Logo Appears on NHL.com</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/31/new-utah-hockey-club-logo-appears-on-nhl-com/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>There appears to be a new logo for the new Utah NHL team, one that actually looks like a logo and comes from a pretty legitimate source. The logo, which we hadn’t seen before tonight, was uploaded to NHL.com — about as official a source as you can get. Now,</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 00:03:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bianca Censori Goes Nearly Naked in Public Once Again</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/02/bianca-censori-naked-bathing-suit-kanye-italy/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Bianca Censori was back at it Saturday ... showing off her incredible figure while wearing practically nothing, which should come as no surprise to anyone at this point. Yup, there was Bianca rocking a teenie weenie white swimsuit in Prato, Italy…</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 06:54:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blue Jays Players, Staff Share Design Process and Thoughts on City Connect Uniform</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/31/blue-jays-players-staff-share-design-process-and-thoughts-on-city-connect-uniform/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Following the release of their new “Pitch Blue” City Connect uniform Thursday night, the Toronto Blue Jays held a uniform release party on the rooftop patio of Lavelle in Downtown Toronto. SportsLogos.Net was invited down to get a close-up look at the new caps and skyline-clad jerseys, chat with some</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 23:12:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cher Breaks Silence on Boyfriend Alexander Edwards' Role in Cannes Fight</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/02/cher-applaud-boyfriend-alexander-edwards-fight-cannes-travis-scott-tyga/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Cher's got her man's back after his rapper rumble at Cannes ... applauding him for his role in a loving social media post -- and, claiming he didn't kick off the brawl. The singer-songwriter posted to X Saturday, breaking her silence on the…</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 06:54:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aston Villa Officially Switches Over to New Crest</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/31/aston-villa-officially-switches-over-to-new-crest/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Official unveiling confirms crest that was first leaked back in January 2024 and was used in graphics around Adidas kit deal announcement earlier in May</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 17:00:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Katy Perry Edits Harrison Butker Speech To Pro LGBTQ+, Women's Rights</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/02/katy-perry-harrison-butker-commencement-speech-lgbtq-womens-rights/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Katy Perry knows how to switch things up ... she has turned Kansas City Chief's Kicker Harrison Butker into a butt-kicker in support of women's and LGBTQ+ rights! Katy posted an extreme edit of Butker's Benedictine College commencement speech,…</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 06:54:03 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>