<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 23:17:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Jamaican National Teams, Adidas Roll Out Stunning New Home and Away Kits</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/06/jamaican-national-teams-adidas-roll-out-stunning-new-home-and-away-kits/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Pattern embossed on yellow home kit and in full color on black away kit features Jamaican national symbols like the doctor bird and lignum vitae</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 22:18:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Precious' Star Gabourey Sidibe Gives Birth, Welcomes Twins With Husband</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/06/precious-gabourey-sidibe-gives-birth-welcomes-twins/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Gabourey Sidibe has a precious update to announce ... she's welcomed twins with husband Brandon Frankel -- a couple months ago. The Oscar nominee -- most famous from the movie "Precious" -- and her husband shared the happy news on Thursday,…</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 23:17:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Canada Marks 80th Anniversary of D-Day With Poppy Armband, Pennant vs. Netherlands</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/06/canada-marks-80th-anniversary-of-d-day-with-poppy-armband-pennant-vs-netherlands/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Canadian troops were instrumental in liberating the Netherlands from German rule in 1944-1945 and supplying much-needed food and medical aid</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 20:29:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Iconic 'Full House' Home Back Up For Sale at $6.5 Million</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/06/full-house-home-for-sale-again-san-francisco-millions/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>An iconic Victorian home in San Francisco famously used for exterior shots in sitcoms "Full House" and "Fuller House" is back up for grabs ... and it's more expensive this time around. The four-bedroom estate on SF's "Postcard Row" just hit the…</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 23:17:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2024 NBA Finals Uniform Schedule Announced: Mavs vs Celtics</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/06/2024-nba-finals-uniform-schedule-announced-mavs-vs-celtics/basketball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The 2024 NBA Finals pits the Boston Celtics against the Dallas Mavericks. The Celtics are looking to win their 18th NBA championship all-time and once again become the franchise with the most NBA titles (they are currently tied with the Lakers); the Celtics last won in 2008, which was their</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 19:31:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Will Smith Gets Slapped in 'Bad Boys 4,' Apparent Mocking of Oscars Moment</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/06/will-smith-slapped-bad-boys-ride-or-die-oscars-reference-chris-rock/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Will Smith is not ignoring the elephant in the room -- there's a scene in his new 'Bad Boys' movie where he's repeatedly slapped, a pretty clear nod to his infamous Chris Rock moment ... but the question is why now? Early reviews for "Bad Boys:…</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 23:17:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Utah NHL Team Announces List of Six Finalist Names</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/06/utah-nhl-team-announces-list-of-six-finalist-names/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Utah’s new NHL team has entered the final round of its fan-driven naming process, and six names have been announced as the top contenders. The club revealed that more than 520,000 fans participated in the first round, with these top six names moving on to the decisive vote: Utah Blizzards</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:08:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gunman Shoots at Passing Cars on Busy California Street, Kills Father of 4</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/06/california-gunman-fires-shoots-passing-cars-street-father-four-killed/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>A gunman unloaded a full clip of bullets at passing cars on a busy California street -- and he ended up killing a dad ... something that was caught on video. The horrifying incident played out in Riverside County Monday -- where law enforcement…</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 23:17:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Minnesota Vikings Unveil “Winter Warrior” Alternate Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/06/minnesota-vikings-unveil-winter-warrior-alternate-uniforms/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Minnesota Vikings have unveiled their new "Winter Warrior" alternate uniforms, which will be worn against the Chicago Bears on Dec. 16.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 13:49:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Viral Suspended License Driver Never Had One At All, Arrested Again</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/06/viral-driver-suspended-license-never-had-arrest-judge-zoom-driving/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Talk about pressing your luck, the guy who Zoom'd into court while behind the wheel -- to face a suspended license charge, mind you -- shouldn't have been driving ... like, ever! Corey Harris -- who went viral in the aftermath of the court video…</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 23:17:45 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>