<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 10:16:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Uncovering the Patterns Behind Falling Rents in Sprawling Cities</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/uncovering-the-patterns-behind-falling-rents-in-sprawling-cities</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Smart investors can target these areas with lasting growth potential.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 14:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Workday acquires AI-powered document platform Evisort</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/17/workday-acquires-ai-powered-document-platform-evisort/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Workday today announced it’s acquiring Evisort, an AI-powered contract management platform, for an undisclosed amount. In a statement, Terrance Wampler, group general manager at Workday, said that Evisort’s tech will enable Workday to add a range of AI-powered document processing tools to its existing finance and HR software. “Evisort will help us deliver on our […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 14:53:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Could People Facing the Death Penalty Lose the Right to Tell Juries Their Life Stories?</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/09/17/supreme-court-death-penalty-jury-overturn-precedent</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Some defense lawyers fear that a conservative Supreme Court could overturn that precedent.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 11:00:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Make Truly Passive Income with “Syndication” Real Estate</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-564</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Visit PassivePockets, your resource for passive investing with syndications. Passive investing is most people’s goal, especially if they’re trying to achieve FIRE. They don’t want to be weighed down by […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 07:01:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cisco’s second layoff of 2024 affects thousands of employees</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/17/ciscos-second-layoff-of-2024-affect-thousands-of-employees/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Cisco's executives made tens of millions in compensation, while cutting thousands of jobs in two separate rounds of layoffs. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 14:50:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>5 Things to Know About How the Parkland Shooter’s Life Was Spared</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/09/17/how-nikolas-cruz-avoided-death-penalty-takeaways</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways from our investigation into how Nikolas Cruz’s defense team convinced jurors not to impose the death penalty.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 11:00:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Banks Face Pressure to Fund Affordable Housing Projects, Opening an Opportunity for Investors</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/banks-face-pressure-from-government-to-fund-affordable-housing-projects</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Banks are feeling pressure from the federal government to fund affordable housing projects, and they're pushing back. But in the middle of the fight is a possible profitability route for investors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 21:23:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Arzeda is using AI to design proteins for artificial sweeteners and more</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/17/arzeda-is-using-ai-to-design-proteins-for-artificial-sweeteners-and-more/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>AI is increasingly being applied to protein design, the process of creating new proteins with specific, target characteristics. Protein design’s applications are myriad, but it’s a promising way of discovering drug-based treatments to combat diseases and creating new homecare, agriculture, food-based and materials products. One among the many vendors developing AI tech to design proteins, […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Hardest Case for Mercy</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/09/17/school-shooting-death-penalty-parkland-nikolas-cruz</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Inside the effort to spare the Parkland school shooter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Calculating Return on Time Could Transform Your Entire Portfolio. Here’s How.</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/calculating-return-on-time-can-transform-your-investments</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>When you start investing in real estate, you’re often driven by the promise of financial windfalls and impressive returns. Initially, the hustle and bustle of acquiring and managing properties can […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 20:52:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ome’s $129 smart knob lets you turn off stove burners remotely</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/17/omes-smart-knob-lets-you-turn-off-stove-burners-remotely/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Quick confession: I take a picture of my stove before I leave on long trips. I’ve been living with OCD my entire life, and this is one of the little lifehacks I’ve created to silence that anxiety. In this case, it’s the very real and perfectly understandable concern that I’ve left the gas on and […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Domestic Abuse Survivor to Prison Pipeline</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/09/14/california-women-prison-domestic-abuse</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Researchers surveyed people who kill their abusers. They found several complicated reasons why survivors end up in prison because of abuse.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>7 Tips to Help You Find the Right Real Estate Market</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/tips-to-help-you-find-the-right-real-estate-market</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Learn how to find the best real estate markets to make smart investments.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 15:11:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hgen draws on lessons from Tesla and SpaceX to drive down the cost of hydrogen</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/17/hgen-draws-on-lessons-from-tesla-and-spacex-to-drive-down-the-cost-of-hydrogen/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>The startup focuses on optimizing the entire widget, from the electrolyzer’s electrodes to the tangle of pipes and pumps that support them. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Not ‘Mini-Adult Court’: Lawyers Lacking Qualifications Defended 1,200 Cuyahoga County Kids</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/09/12/cuyahoga-juvenile-courts-appointed-public-defender</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Juvenile Court judges will now track qualifications, but insist the state system creates barriers keeping experienced attorneys from defending kids.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>