<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from multiple RSS sources, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 06:59:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>3 Steps to Buying Your First (or Next) Small Multifamily Property</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-398</link><description>Small multifamily real estate investing can lead you to financial freedom faster than you think. Compared to traditional single-family rental properties, small multifamily properties often offer more cash flow, the […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 07:02:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Global Founders Capital will deploy Rocket Internet’s cash instead of raising a new fund</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/26/global-founders-capital-becomes-rocket-internets-venture-arm/</link><description>Global Founders Capital, the Berlin-based early stage VC firm with close ties to the German startup factory Rocket Internet, is going to become the venture arm of Rocket Internet. The VC previously raised two $1 billion funds and, just a few years ago, its name appeared in dozens of deals per year. But then, things […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 10:16:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Being Trans in Prison Is Really Like</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/26/trans-prison-voices-gender-essay</link><description>Amid a wave of anti-trans legislation, and the violence that often follows, four people share their experiences in the criminal justice system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 11:00:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A lot of children are about to be born in Ukraine. Will the war affect them for life?</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/children/features/fetal-programming-ukraine?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Some of the most horrific images from the war so far have come from a maternity hospital in Mariupol bombed by Russian troops in mid-March. The upheaval spurs a troubling question: Could the stress and condition of war affect a fetus?</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 10:32:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BiggerNews: Can’t Qualify for Another Mortgage? Try THESE Investor Loans w/Jeff Welgan</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-943</link><description>Want to scale your real estate portfolio faster? These investment property loans can help. Most real estate investors get stuck early on in their journey. They buy some properties and […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 07:02:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>xAI, Elon Musk’s OpenAI rival, is closing on $6B in funding and X, his social network, is already one of its shareholders</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/25/xai-elon-musks-openai-rival-is-closing-on-6b-in-funding-and-x-his-social-network-is-already-one-of-its-shareholders/</link><description>xAI, Elon Musk’s 10-month-old competitor to the AI phenom OpenAI, is raising $6 billion on a pre-money valuation of $18 billion, according to one trusted source close to the deal. The deal – which would give investors one quarter of the company –  is expected to close in the next few weeks unless the terms […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 05:41:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Enduring Use of Solitary, and New Proposed Limits That Will Likely Fail (Again)</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/20/solitary-confinement-reform-oklahoma-washington-florida</link><description>Isolation’s damaging effects are widely known. But many facilities confine people — even youth — virtually all day, sometimes in shower stalls.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Trans Health Care for Minors Really Means</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/sex/features/trans-access-to-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>The meaning of gender-affirming care for young people, and what it looks like on the ground, isn’t always clear. The cloud of politics surrounding it has obscured the medical reality of how and when trans youth can get the treatments they seek.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 10:32:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Americans Say THIS Is How Much You Need to Retire (More Than You’d Think)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-523</link><description>Is a six-figure salary enough to achieve FIRE? If you’re working towards financial independence, you know that any extra money at the end of the month can help propel you […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 07:01:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zomato’s quick commerce unit Blinkit eclipses core food business in value, says Goldman Sachs</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/25/zomato-quick-commerce-blinkit-eclipses-core-food-business-in-value-says-goldman-sachs/</link><description>Goldman Sachs said in a report late Thursday that Indian food delivery giant Zomato’s quick commerce arm Blinkit is now more valuable than its core food delivery business, as per the bank’s sum-of-the-parts analysis. The investment bank estimates Blinkit’s implied value at 119 Indian rupees per share ($1.43) or about $13 billion, while Zomato’s food […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 01:53:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Officials Failed to Act When COVID Hit Prisons. A New Study Shows the Deadly Cost.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/18/covid-prison-deaths-data</link><description>People in prison died at 3.4 times the rate of the free population, with the oldest hit hardest. New data holds lessons for preventing future deaths.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Get the Care You Need in a COVID-19 World</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/covid-senior-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>What to expect at the doctor’s office, hospitals, and long-term care facilities, the future of telemedicine, and how to get the best care during COVID-19.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 07:31:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The New Reform That Could Unlock $1B+ for Affordable Housing w/Sharon Cornelissen</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-211</link><description>America is in need of affordable housing; we’re all aware. Buying your first home has become increasingly challenging for everyday people. This is where housing subsidies come in. Federal housing […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 07:02:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The FTC’s ban on noncompete clauses could be good for startups. But it also might be struck down.</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/25/the-ftcs-ban-on-noncompete-clauses-could-be-good-for-startups-but-it-also-might-be-struck-down/</link><description>The Federal Trade Commission voted 3-2 to ban the use of most noncompete agreements on Tuesday. This ruling means companies can’t require employees who aren’t senior executives to wait a set amount of time before joining a competitor or launching their own company in the same category. While the FTC’s ruling will impact industries like […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 01:50:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Parents Paying for Their Children’s Crimes</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/13/michigan-school-shooting-parents</link><description>Experts warn about a wave of legal consequences for parents like the Crumbleys, while some states consider prosecutions for kids as young as 10.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What to Know About Your Health Insurer’s Formulary Drug List</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/health-insurance/features/formulary-list-medications?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>How do drug formularies work? Learn more about your health insurer's list of preferred drugs and how it can save you money.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 18:23:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sunbelt Surge: 15 Cities Dominating the Growth Charts</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/best-sunbelt-markets-for-growth</link><description>Simply investing in any metro Sunbelt market is not a recipe for success. To catch a cresting wave of appreciation and cash flow, you’ll need to dive deep into the metrics […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:48:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Norwest Venture Partners raises $3B for 17th vehicle, maintaining fund size despite market downturn</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/25/norwest-venture-partners-raises-3b-for-17th-vehicle-maintaining-fund-size-despite-market-downturn/</link><description>Norwest Venture Partners, a 65-year-old firm backed solely by Wells Fargo, has raised its 17th fund at $3 billion. That’s a noteworthy number, given that NVP last raised the same amount in December 2021. That was the peak of the venture boom, and at that time, the firm said it increased its capital pool by […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 00:24:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I Had a Tough Job at My Brooklyn Jail: Keeping Men From Taking Their Own Lives</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/12/brooklyn-jail-suicide-prevention-aide</link><description>As a suicide prevention aide, I had to make sure my fellow detainees didn’t harm themselves. It was surprisingly easy to get such a complex job.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shop Around to Save on Drug Prices</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/health-insurance/features/medication-shop-around?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Should you shop around for prescription drugs? Learn ways to compare drug prices to find more affordable options.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 18:21:54 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>