<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 07:09:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Where We’d Invest in Real Estate in 2024 if We Were Starting from Scratch</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-1007</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>New to real estate investing? In the beginning, you’re drowning in recommendations of where to invest in real estate, especially in 2024. Everyone is shouting different markets at you, “Cleveland! […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 10:00:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Skyfire lets AI agents spend your money</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/21/skyfire-lets-ai-agents-spend-your-money/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>There’s a lot of hype about the promise of AI agents today, but payments are a huge limiting factor. Today, an AI agent might be able to plan a vacation for you independently, but a human has to step in when it’s time to input your credit card information. Skyfire Systems wants to change that. […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Prosecutors Fight Exonerations</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/17/wrongful-conviction-innocence-claims-missouri-st-louis</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>As laws are passed to support the wrongfully convicted, some officials in the legal system push back.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Making $300K+ Profit Per Rental and Scaling FAST with “DADUs”</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-447</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Making a $300,000 profit from ONE rental?! Imagine how quickly you could reach financial freedom by raking in this amount of profit and reinvesting it into your real estate portfolio. […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 10:00:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WeTransfer’s expiry dates haven’t gone away, but you can at least extend them</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/21/wetransfers-expiry-dates-havent-gone-away-but-you-can-at-least-extend-them/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>WeTransfer’s expiry dates have been a major paint-point for users — especially creatives. Thing is, if you don’t download the files the moment you get the link or email you can easily forget to do so before the link expires. At which point you’ll have to ask for it to be resent. Which can get […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 11:27:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FAQ: How The Marshall Project Is Covering the 2024 Election</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/16/election-faq-crime-politics</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Learn more about who we are and how we choose what political stories to cover.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Commercial Brokerage JLL Takes $18 Million Loss In Loan Fraud Scheme</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/fraudelent-scheme-leaves-jll-with-a-18-million-dollar-loss</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>DOJ investigators discovered a multiyear scheme regarding fraudulent loans that led to an $18 million loss for JLL.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 21:32:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>India’s trade minister decries e-commerce growth, Amazon’s ‘predatory’ pricing</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/21/indias-trade-minister-decries-e-commerce-growth-amazons-predatory-pricing/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>India’s commerce minister Piyush Goyal on Wednesday expressed concern over the rapid growth of e-commerce in the country, warning of potential disruption to small retailers. Speaking at the launch of a report on the impact of e-commerce on employment and consumer welfare in India, Goyal said the projected dominance of online marketplaces in the coming […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 09:20:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Mother on a Mission for Full Police Transparency</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/16/police-beating-ulysses-wilkerson-mother-video</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Troy, Alabama, police severely beat Ulysses Wilkerson when he was 17. Seven years later, his mom, Angela Williams, is still fighting for answers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FIRE in 2024: What We’d Do Differently If We Started Over Today</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-556</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>2013 was a pivotal year for our hosts. Scott was fresh out of college and just beginning his journey to financial independence, while Mindy and her husband were well on […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 07:01:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SleekFlow snaps up $7M to tap the conversational AI opportunity across Asia</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/20/omnichannel-platform-sleekflow-gets-7m-to-propel-expansion-ai-capabilities/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>SleekFlow, a Singapore- and Hong Kong-headquartered social commerce platform that has built a conversational AI suite for customer engagement targeted to Asian markets, said Wednesday it had secured a further $7 million in funding. The money will be used to continue developing its AI, as well as penetrate deeper into Southeast Asia and the Middle […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 01:59:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How the 1968 DNC in Chicago Devolved into ‘Unrestrained and Indiscriminate Police Violence’</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/14/chicago-dnc-protests-police-reforms</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>As protesters prepare for the Democratic National Convention in Chicago next week, a half-century old report provides lessons for preventing chaos.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 11:00:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Does the President Have An Impact on Housing? Here’s What 30 Years of Data Says.</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/can-the-president-have-an-impact-on-the-housing-market</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>VP Harris just unveiled her economic plan, which included a number of items for supporting the housing market. But does history suggest executive policies make a difference?</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 19:06:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The banks that loaned Musk $13B to buy Twitter might be having regrets</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/20/the-banks-that-loaned-musk-13b-to-buy-twitter-might-be-having-regrets/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>X, formerly known as Twitter, looks like a pretty bad investment right about now. As readers might recall, Elon Musk borrowed $13 billion from Morgan Stanley, Bank of America and five other major banks to help finance its $44 billion acquisition. According to the WSJ, the deal has since become the worst merger-finance deal for […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 23:34:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aaron Sankin is The Marshall Project’s new Deputy Data Editor</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/13/aaron-sankin-is-the-marshall-projects-new-deputy-data-editor</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Sankin brings deep experience with ambitious data projects.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 20:00:24 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>