<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 06:48:33 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Madison Mallards unveil alternates IN A VAN DOWN BY THE RIVER</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/22/madison-mallards-unveil-alternates-in-a-van-down-by-the-river/baseball/</link><description>The collegiate summer level Madison Mallards unveiled an alternate identity today based on a classic Saturday Night Live sketch that featured the late, great Chris Farley over three decades ago in 1993. The logo and uniforms evoke Farley’s character Matt Foley, a down-on-his-luck motivational speaker who famously lives “in a</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 01:21:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Michael Jackson's Neverland Ranch Restored For Biopic Filming</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/22/michael-jackson-neverland-restored-biopic-filming-production/</link><description>Michael Jackson's infamous Neverland theme park is dusting off the cobwebs to film scenes for a new biopic about the late singer's life. As you can see in the aerial shots ... the film company behind the biopic has restored signature features from…</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 06:48:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Minnesota Vikings Alternate, New York Giants Throwback Jerseys Leak</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/22/minnesota-vikings-alternate-new-york-giants-throwback-jerseys-leak/football/</link><description>Former NFL wide receiver Antonio Brown's social media network leaked two more jerseys that will be worn this season, including a Minnesota Vikings alternate and New York Giants throwback design.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 21:24:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Designing Women' Star Delta Burke Tried Crystal Meth to Lose Weight</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/22/delta-burke-tried-crystal-meth-lose-weight-designing-women/</link><description>Delta Burke is revealing the shocking lengths to which she went just to drop a few pounds in her heyday -- using crystal meth as an appetite suppressant! The actress -- best known for playing Suzanne Sugarbaker on "Designing Women" -- stopped by…</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 06:48:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Denver Broncos Unveil New “Mile High” Uniforms, Revive Throwback Design</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/22/denver-broncos-unveil-new-mile-high-uniforms-tease-throwback/football/</link><description>Although a series of leaks ruined the surprise, the Denver Broncos officially unveiled new uniforms on Monday morning, marking the first significant overhaul of their look in 27 years.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 16:35:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jill Scott Defends Chris Brown After Quavo Diss, Fans War Amongst Themselves</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/22/jill-scott-quavo-chris-brown-weakest-link/</link><description>Jill Scott isn't going to let Chris Brown’s checkered past block her enjoyment of listening to him lyrically pummel Quavo, and she's been fending off critics who wished she didn't cape for Chris!!! The ripple effect from Chris' brutal "Weakest…</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 06:48:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nashville Sounds pay tribute to parent club, beer with new Brewskis cap</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/21/nashville-sounds-pay-tribute-to-parent-club-beer-with-new-brewskis-cap/baseball/</link><description>The Triple-A Nashville Sounds have been an affiliate of the Milwaukee Brewers since 2021, and before that from 2005 to 2014. The team is continuing a popular tribute to its parent club this season, playing as the Nashville Brewskis. The Sounds introduced the powder blue alternates designed by Brandon Lamarche</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 16:28:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Robert Kraft 'Deeply Saddened' Over Columbia, University Unrecognizable</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/22/robert-kraft-criticizes-columbia-university-pro-hamas-palestine-gaza-protestors/</link><description>Robert Kraft graduated from Columbia in '63, and has been a huge proponent of the school in every way, including financially ... but all that changed Monday when the billionaire Patriots owner made it clear he wasn't going to stand by and watch his…</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 06:48:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rumble Ponies to honor Rod Serling with Binghamton Creatures alternate</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/21/rumble-ponies-to-honor-rod-serling-with-binghamton-creatures-alternate/baseball/</link><description>The Double-A Binghamton Rumble Ponies will honor one of their hometown’s favorite sons, Twilight Zone creator Rod Serling, with an alternate identity based on the show. For one game this summer, the team will play as the Creatures, with a logo that derives from a Twilight Zone episode called “Nightmare</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 15:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kim Kardashian Loses 100K+ IG Followers, Swifties Flood Comment Section</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/22/kim-kardashian-loses-100k-ig-followers-swifties-flood-comment-section/</link><description>Kim Kardashian's social media profile is taking a hit in the wake of Taylor Swift dropping a new diss track about the reality TV star. ICYMI ... Taylor's new song, "thanK you aIMee," is a thinly veiled revenge anthem against Kim -- hence the…</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 06:48:33 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>