<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 06:52:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>How to Start Making Millions from These Overlooked RV Park Investments</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-988</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Heather Blankenship has made $10,000,000 alone from just one RV park investment. She got into it with no money and zero experience. While pregnant with her first child, Heather answered […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 07:02:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How VanMoof’s new owners plan to win over its old customers</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/15/how-vanmoofs-new-owners-plan-to-win-over-its-old-customers/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>When VanMoof declared bankruptcy last year, it left around 5,000 customers who had pre-ordered e-bikes in the lurch. Now VanMoof is up and running under new management, and the company’s current owners are courting those same customers by offering them a €1,000 discount off a new bike. It’s an audacious strategy, one that bets on […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How a Supreme Court Ruling Could Affect a Case Involving Police Abuse of Youth</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/13/supreme-court-bankruptcy-sackler-boy-scouts</link><description>Another court must now decide how the landmark ruling will impact the Boy Scouts abuse settlement, which involves victims of police sexual abuse.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Did We Just Find 2024’s Most “Under-the-Radar” Real Estate Market?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-234</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>We might have just found the most under-the-radar real estate market of 2024. It’s got jobs, appreciation potential, and affordable homes, and it’s growing…fast! The best part? We’re not sure […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 07:02:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mitti Labs aims to make rice farming less harmful to the climate, starting in India</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/14/mitti-labs-aims-to-make-rice-farming-less-harmful-to-the-climate-starting-in-india/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Mitti Labs aims to transform rice farming in India and other South Asian markets by reducing methane emissions by 50% and water consumption by 30%. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 05:30:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jackson, Mississippi, Wants Curfew Centers to Cut Crime. Here’s What Other Cities Learned.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/09/jackson-mississippi-youth-curfew-centers</link><description>After a teen’s murder, city officials hope a curfew and youth centers will get kids off the street. Young people are skeptical.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 11:00:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From Losing Her Health, Home, &amp; Marriage to Chasing Financial Freedom (5 Doors!)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-432</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Anyone can buy rentals, whether you have some money to deploy or very little to your name. With seemingly everything working against her, today’s guest managed to buy not one, […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 07:02:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to tell if your online accounts have been hacked</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/14/how-to-tell-if-your-online-accounts-have-been-hacked/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>This is a guide on how to check whether someone compromised your online accounts. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Love Beyond Bars: Miguel and Silvia</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/05/photo-essay-wrongful-conviction-love-story</link><description>While Miguel Solorio did 25 years for a crime he didn’t commit, his wife, Silvia, was right by his side. Here’s their California love story in pictures.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Slew of New Rental Laws Is Determining Who Landlords Can Rent To</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/slew-of-landlord-laws-are-going-to-determine-who-landlords-can-rent-to</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>New laws in California, New York, and elsewhere could eliminate the former red flags that landlords may have used to disqualify potential renters.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 20:47:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The AI financial results paradox</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/14/the-ai-financial-results-paradox/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>There is a general consensus today that generative AI is going to transform business in a profound way, and companies and individuals who don’t get on board will be quickly left in the dustbin of history. At the same time, as companies delve more deeply into this technology, they want proof, actual business metrics, that […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 19:36:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Crime Rates and the 2024 Election: What You Need to Know</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/27/trump-and-biden-spar-over-crime-rates-ahead-of-their-debate-what-do-we-really-know</link><description>As crime data again becomes a flashpoint in the presidential campaign, experts push for better national statistics.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Top 5 Alternative Investments for Real Estate Investors in 2024</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/best-alternative-investments-in-2024</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Good real estate investors know that diversification is important. These five alternative investments are great ways to diversify.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 18:28:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Google reportedly in talks to acquire cloud security company Wiz for $23B</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/14/google-reportedly-in-talks-to-acquire-cloud-security-company-wiz-for-23b/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Google’s parent company Alphabet might be on the verge of making its biggest acquisition ever. The Wall Street Journal reports that Alphabet is in advanced talks to acquire Wiz for around $23 billion. While the deal isn’t finalized, the WSJ says it could come together soon. Wiz offers an all-in-one approach to cloud security, ingesting […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 18:44:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Death Row Prisoner’s Parting Interview</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/24/texas-death-row-prisoner-final-interview</link><description>Days before his scheduled execution in Texas, Ramiro Gonzales speaks on faith, legacy — and apologizing to the family of his victim, Bridget Townsend.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>