<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 07:11:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Rookie Reply: House Hacking 101! Which Property to Buy &amp; How to Scale Fast</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-448</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>House hacking might be the easiest way to get into real estate. This beginner-friendly investing strategy involves little risk, works with several types of properties, and can cover your entire […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 10:00:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>360 One lifts its valuation of India’s National Stock Exchange to $29.9B</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/23/360-one-lifts-its-valuation-of-indias-national-stock-exchange-to-29-9b/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>360 One Asset, an investor in National Stock Exchange (NSE), has increased its valuation for India's top stock exchange to $29.9 billion. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 08:25:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Prosecutors Fight Exonerations</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/17/wrongful-conviction-innocence-claims-missouri-st-louis</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>As laws are passed to support the wrongfully convicted, some officials in the legal system push back.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BiggerNews: Have the Airbnb Bans Backfired on Big Cities?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-1008</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Are Airbnb bans actually hurting renters, homebuyers, and your local economy? The truth doesn’t seem so obvious, but new data shows the unintended consequences of banning Airbnbs and short-term rentals, […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 10:00:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Get in on the ground floor with Tesla’s humanoid by pretending to be one for pay</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/22/get-in-on-the-ground-floor-with-teslas-humanoid-by-pretending-to-be-one-for-pay/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Tesla is hiring individuals standing between 5’7 and 5’11 to carry up to 30 pounds for seven hours a day to train its Optimus robot. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 05:51:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FAQ: How The Marshall Project Is Covering the 2024 Election</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/16/election-faq-crime-politics</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Learn more about who we are and how we choose what political stories to cover.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Buying at the Peak, Surviving a Crash, and STILL Being Able to Quit at 38</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-557</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Have you ever made a poor financial decision? You’re not alone! But can a bad blunder disqualify you from FIRE? Today’s guest made a huge investment at the worst possible […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 07:01:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DeepMind workers sign letter in protest of Google’s defense contracts</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/22/deepmind-workers-sign-letter-in-protest-of-googles-defense-contracts/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>At least 200 workers at DeepMind, Google’s AI R&amp;D division, are displeased with Google’s reported defense contracts — and according to Time, they circulated a letter internally back in May to say as much. The letter, dated May 16, says the undersigned are concerned by “Google’s contracts with military organizations,” citing articles about the tech […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 23:15:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Mother on a Mission for Full Police Transparency</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/16/police-beating-ulysses-wilkerson-mother-video</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Troy, Alabama, police severely beat Ulysses Wilkerson when he was 17. Seven years later, his mom, Angela Williams, is still fighting for answers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>VP Harris Wants to Stop Wall Street Homebuying, But Will It Help Regular Buyers?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-245</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Kamala Harris has a plan to make it easier for first-time homebuyers to buy a house, but it comes at the expense of institutional investors. Eviction filings surge throughout the […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 10:00:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NASA to decide Saturday whether astronauts will ride Boeing’s Starliner home — or use SpaceX’s Dragon instead</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/22/nasa-to-decide-saturday-whether-astronauts-will-ride-boeings-starliner-home-or-use-spacexs-dragon-instead/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>NASA officials will announce their final decision on Saturday as to whether two NASA astronauts — Butch Wilmore and Sunita Williams — will return to Earth on Boeing’s Starliner spacecraft or hitch a ride home with SpaceX instead — a decision that could have a huge impact across the rapidly evolving space industry. Here’s the […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 23:14:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How the 1968 DNC in Chicago Devolved into ‘Unrestrained and Indiscriminate Police Violence’</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/14/chicago-dnc-protests-police-reforms</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>As protesters prepare for the Democratic National Convention in Chicago next week, a half-century old report provides lessons for preventing chaos.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 11:00:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rentals Cool—Here’s Where Concessions Are Picking Up</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rental-market-report-july-2024</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>The rental market has been on a downward trajectory for a while, but now a third of landlords are offering concessions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 15:54:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gimbal Space takes on legacy suppliers with fast-paced component supply chain</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/22/gimbal-space-takes-on-legacy-suppliers-with-fast-paced-component-supply-chain/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>America’s space industry seems mature, but the supply chain that provides all the parts and components for rockets, satellites, and other spacecraft is considerably less so. Gimbal Space is aiming to change that, starting with components in the crucial subsystem that enables a spacecraft to orient itself in space — but delivered cheaper and a whole […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 22:15:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aaron Sankin is The Marshall Project’s new Deputy Data Editor</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/13/aaron-sankin-is-the-marshall-projects-new-deputy-data-editor</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Sankin brings deep experience with ambitious data projects.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 20:00:24 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>