<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 01:05:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Premier League Away Kits Dominate Recent Unveilings From Around Europe</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/02/premier-league-away-kits-dominate-recent-unveilings-from-around-europe/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Clubs launching kits include Liverpool, Brighton, Fulham, Bournemouth, Nottingham Forest, Wolves, Le Havre, Stade de Reims, Montepellier, Roma, Parma, RB Leipzig, VFB Stuttgart, Girona</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 21:41:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sydney Calhoun Stuns In Black Swimsuit While Hanging Around The House</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/04/sydney-calhoun-black-swimsuit-hot-shots-miami/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>This week's hot shots are anything but chill ... because Sydney Calhoun makes plopping down on a couch in Miami look way better than your everyday hang around the house. When this fashion model peels herself off the furniture ... Sydney is on a…</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 01:05:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Carolina Panthers Add 30th Season Logo To Jerseys</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/02/carolina-panthers-add-30th-season-logo-to-jerseys/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Carolina Panthers will celebrate their 30th season this fall with a commemorative logo, which they quietly unveiled back in May and added to their jerseys ahead of Thursday's Fan Fest at Clemson's Memorial Stadium.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 17:02:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NBA Star Jaime Jaquez Jr. Raves Over Cooper Flagg's Game, 'Incredible Talent'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/04/jaime-jaquez-jr-cooper-flagg-game-incredible-talent-nba-duke/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>It's time to start buying into the Cooper Flagg hype if ya haven't already ... 'cause NBA star Jaime Jaquez Jr. tells TMZ Sports that after playing with the phenom this summer, he's the real deal. Flagg -- the No. 1-ranked H.S. player in the nation…</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 01:05:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Macon Some Changes: SPHL’s Mayhem Unveil New Suite of Logos</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/01/macon-some-changes-sphls-mayhem-unveil-new-suite-of-logos/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Primary logo once again depicts a Viking, only this time just the head with a red beard and eyebrows and wearing a shiny silver horned helmet</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 23:36:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Luann De Lesseps Says Bravo Should Add to 'RHONJ' Cast Instead of Total Reboot</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/04/luann-de-lesseps-real-housewives-new-york-jersey-add-cast-members/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Luann De Lesseps has advice for Bravo's "The Real Housewives of New Jersey" reboot ... rip the cast apart at your own peril! We caught up with "The Real Housewives of New York" alum in L.A. ... and, we had to ask her about 'RHONJ' going through a…</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 01:05:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Olympic Rings: Their Origin, History, and Meaning</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/01/the-olympic-rings-their-origin-history-and-meaning/other/olympics/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Olympic rings are synonymous with the peak of international sports achievement. Those five interlaced circles of equal size, each a different colour, absolutely dominate the sporting landscape around the globe for two straight weeks before vanishing as quickly as they appeared, hiding away until the next games, usually around</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 20:10:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zac Efron Hospitalized After Being Found in Swimming Pool in Distress</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/03/zac-efron-swimming-accident-hospital-ibiza/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>3:48 PM PT -- When asked why Efron was taken to the hospital for a minor incident, his rep once again reiterated it was purely a precautionary measure. However, the rep did not say what caused him to be in distress in the pool. 2:38 PM PT -- The…</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 01:05:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chicago Cubs to wear Motorola Ad on Uniform</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/01/chicago-cubs-to-wear-motorola-ad-on-uniform/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Chicago Cubs today became the 23rd Major League Baseball team to add an advertisement to their jersey sleeve, announcing that Motorola’s logo will live there for the foreseeable future. Chicago’s announcement comes just one day after the Philadelphia IBX Phillies announced their own jersey ad. The rather large patch</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 15:46:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Justin Bieber Shows Love for Very Pregnant Wife Hailey in New Photos</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/04/justin-bieber-hailey-pregnant-photos-love/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Justin Bieber is getting ready to be a dad and showing a lot of love for his baby mama, Hailey, who looks like she's about to burst! JB posted a series of photos to Instagram showing him with Hailey, whose stomach is very round and protruding in a…</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 01:05:05 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>