<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 06:47:43 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Book Review: Pause to Think</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/08/09/book-review-pause-to-think/</link><description>This book is direct, delightful, and articulate in suggesting that we take a slow rather than fast approach to getting things thoughtfully done. It touches the minds and hearts of investment professionals.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 12:59:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hurricane Debby remnants leave thousands of businesses and homes without power in the Northeast</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/08/12/hurricane-debby-remnants-thousands-businesses-homes-without-power-northeast/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/AP24222702773151-e1723458627974.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>After hitting Florida as a hurricane Aug. 5, the storm spent nearly a week unleashing tornadoes and flooding, damaging homes and taking lives along the East Coast.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 11:40:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is Illiquidity a Blessing in Disguise for Some Investors?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/08/07/is-illiquidity-a-blessing-in-disguise-for-some-investors/</link><description>Rather than running away from illiquidity, investment professionals, investors, and regulators alike should recognize its potential benefits and consider a more balanced approach.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 17:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Americans are refusing to keep paying high prices and that may be killing the U.S. inflation spike</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/08/12/americans-refusing-paying-high-prices-killing-us-inflation-spike/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/AP24222791492029-e1723457867970.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Some of America's largest companies, from Amazon to Disney to Yum Brands, say customers are seeking cheaper alternative products, searching for bargains or just avoiding items they deem too expensive.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 11:20:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scenario Planning, Foresight, and the Power of Imagination: Navigating an Uncertain Future</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/08/05/scenario-planning-foresight-and-the-power-of-imagination-navigating-an-uncertain-future/</link><description>By fostering resilience through the consideration of various outcomes, investment practitioners can better anticipate and manage the complexities and disruptions that characterize today's dynamic environment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 17:28:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paris Olympic dream struck a chord across France. Now Macron faces a fraught return to reality</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/08/12/paris-olympic-dream-struck-a-chord-across-france-now-macron-faces-a-fraught-return-to-reality/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/GettyImages-2166228110-e1723454459523.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>While the Games have lifted what was a morose mood in France, it is far from certain this will give a new impulse to the remaining three years of the unpopular president's mandate.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 10:43:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Private Equity: In Essence, Plunder?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/08/02/private-equity-in-essence-plunder/</link><description>To understand what private equity is at its worst is a call to action, personally and professionally.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 16:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Foreign investors pulled a record $15 billion out of China last quarter</title><link>https://fortune.com/asia/2024/08/12/foreign-investors-pull-record-15-billion-china-last-quarter/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/GettyImages-2163974888-e1723455675960.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The slowdown in the economy and rising geopolitical tensions has led some companies to reduce their exposure.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 10:43:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Small Caps, Large Caps, and Interest Rates</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/08/01/small-caps-large-caps-and-interest-rates/</link><description>The relationship between stocks and interest rates is not reliably stable. There are periods when equities are highly rate sensitive, and periods when they aren't.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 12:39:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>American tourists are flocking to boardwalks and piers to stick to their summer budgets</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/08/12/american-tourists-stick-to-summer-budgets/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/GettyImages-1610491988-e1723453477158.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>While the affluent are spending freely, lower-income vacationers are sticking to carefully planned-out budgets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 10:05:31 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>