<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 06:54:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>A World Without Airbnb &amp; Why “Sinking” Could Cause Your Insurance to Skyrocket</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-991</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Airbnb bans escalate, a “tsunami” could be coming for this real estate niche, and “sinking” cities lead to skyrocketing insurance prices. The housing market changes every week, so we’re here […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 07:02:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CrowdStrike update causes major IT outage, taking out banks, airlines and businesses across the world</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/19/banks-airlines-brokerage-houses-report-widespread-outages-across-the-globe/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Businesses across the world are reporting IT outages, including Windows “blue screen of death” errors on their computers, in what has already become one of the most widespread IT disruptions in recent years. The outage — linked to an update rolled out for widely used security software made by cybersecurity firm CrowdStrike early on Friday […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 08:40:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Love Beyond Bars: Jules and Samantha</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/19/photo-essay-werkheisers-wrongful-conviction</link><description>Jules and Samantha Werkheiser fought their wrongful convictions for over a decade. Here’s their journey of survival — and motherhood — in pictures.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rookie Reply: Buying Your NEXT Rental &amp; How to Save a Fortune on Renovations</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-434</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Home renovation projects aren’t cheap, and it’s easy to let your budget spiral out of control if you’re not careful. Fortunately, we have several tips, tricks, and hacks that will […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 07:02:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paytm loss widens and revenue shrinks as it grapples with regulatory clampdown</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/18/paytm-loss-widens-and-revenue-shrinks-following-regulatory-clampdown/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Indian fintech Paytm’s struggles won’t seem to end. The company on Friday reported that its revenue declined by 36% and its loss more than doubled in the first quarter as it continues to grapple with a regulatory clampdown that has significantly curtailed business at its payments bank subsidiary. Once the poster child of India’s startup […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 07:21:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meet the New Generation of Unarmed First Responders in this New Podcast Series.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/18/police-north-carolina-podcast-mental-health</link><description>“The Fifth Branch,” a podcast from The Marshall Project and Tradeoffs, examines new, alternative ways to respond to 911 crisis calls.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Using “ADUs” to Go From Firefighter to FIRE by His Late 30s</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-547</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>You could be missing out on the chance to earn passive income from your home (and other rentals!) with a “no-brainer” money move. This investing strategy is picking up steam […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 07:01:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fandango founder dies in fall from Manhattan skyscraper</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/18/fandango-founder-dies-in-fall-from-manhattan-skyscraper/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>J. Michael Cline, the co-founder of Fandango and multiple other startups over his multi-decade career, died after falling from a Manhattan hotel, New York’s Deputy Commissioner of Public Information tells TechCrunch. The New York Police Department responded to 911 calls from the Kimberly Hotel, a 30-story hotel on 50th street in midtown Manhattan on Tuesday […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 00:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What We Know About J.D. Vance’s Legislative Action on Criminal Justice</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/17/what-we-know-from-sen-j-d-vance-s-legislative-action-on-criminal-justice-issues</link><description>On immigration and more, Vance has defended and legislated former President Donald Trump’s policy goals.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 23:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Find, Evaluate, and Offer on Rental Properties in 2024</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-no-number-3</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Want financial freedom through real estate? Then, you’ll need to know how to buy a rental property. Don’t worry; even as a beginner, you can take three basic steps to […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 07:02:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple Vision Pro debuts immersive content featuring NBA players, The Weeknd and more</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/18/apple-immersive-video-new-content-vision-pro/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Apple on Thursday announced its upcoming lineup of immersive video content for the Vision Pro. The list includes behind-the-scenes footage of the 2024 NBA All-Star Weekend, an immersive performance by The Weeknd, new series, films, concerts and more. The headset launched in February with more than 150 3D movies and immersive titles. Apple is adding […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 21:14:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How a Supreme Court Ruling Could Affect a Case Involving Police Abuse of Youth</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/13/supreme-court-bankruptcy-sackler-boy-scouts</link><description>Another court must now decide how the landmark ruling will impact the Boy Scouts abuse settlement, which involves victims of police sexual abuse.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A World Without Airbnb &amp; Why “Sinking” Could Cause Your Insurance to Skyrocket</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-235</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Airbnb bans escalate, a “tsunami” could be coming for this real estate niche, and “sinking” cities lead to skyrocketing insurance prices. The housing market changes every week, so we’re here […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 07:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elon Musk is now a villain in Joe Biden’s presidential campaign</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/18/elon-musk-is-now-a-villain-in-joe-bidens-presidential-campaign/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Biden centering Musk in his campaign is a notable escalation, considering he spent most of his presidency seemingly pretending the billionaire didn't exist. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 21:03:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jackson, Mississippi, Wants Curfew Centers to Cut Crime. Here’s What Other Cities Learned.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/09/jackson-mississippi-youth-curfew-centers</link><description>After a teen’s murder, city officials hope a curfew and youth centers will get kids off the street. Young people are skeptical.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 11:00:57 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>