<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 22:03:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>2024 MLB All-Star Game, Workout Caps Released</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/21/2024-mlb-all-star-game-workout-caps-released/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The stars at night will be big and bright (emphasis on bright), deep in the heart of Texas next month at the 2024 Major League Baseball All-Star Game. SHOP: Get your 2024 MLB All-Star Game on-field cap right now, right here Today, the league, along with New Era, unveiled the</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 18:54:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kinks' Dave Davies Willing to Trade Guitar for Missing HOF Trophy Posted on eBay</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/21/kinks-rocker-dave-davies-willing-trade-guitar-missing-hall-of-fame-trophy-ebay/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Dave Davies is trying to get an important trophy he once had after it vanished and recently showed up for sale online ... but might have to give up another prized possession to do it. The Kinks rocker hopped on X this week to lament the fact that…</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 22:03:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Crystal Palace, Valencia Headline Recent Kit Launches From Around Europe</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/21/crystal-palace-valencia-headline-recent-kit-launches-from-around-europe/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Other clubs releasing 2024-25 kits recently include: Getafe CF, Borussia Mönchengladbach, Stade Rennais, RC Lens, FC Nantes, SL Benfica, FC Porto</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 15:16:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Southwest Fight Drops Dangerously Low Over Oklahoma Neighborhood</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/21/southwest-boeing-737-dives-below-500-feet-over-neighborhood-oklahoma-city/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>A Southwest Airlines plane dove to 500 feet over an Oklahoma neighborhood, leaving residents rattled ... and some are once again pointing the finger at Boeing. The commercial 737-800 jet was about 9 miles away from Will Rogers World Airport early…</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 22:03:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Washington Wizards Unveil 2024-25 Statement Edition Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/21/washington-wizards-unveil-2024-25-statement-edition-uniforms/basketball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Washington Wizards unveiled their 2024-25 Statement Edition uniforms early Friday morning, replacing the set they've worn since the 2019-20 season.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 14:55:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Harry Jowsey Not Dating Madeline Argy Despite Speculation in Cannes</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/21/harry-jowsey-not-dating-madeline-argy-despite-speculation-cannes/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Harry Jowsey and Madeline Argy had people thinking they may be banging after looking kinda cozy over in Cannes -- but as it turns out ... they're just content creator amigos. Here's the deal ... pics surfaced earlier this week of the 'DWTS' alum…</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 22:03:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>San Fransico Giants Add #24 Memorial Patch for Willie Mays</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/20/san-fransico-giants-add-24-memorial-patch-for-willie-mays/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The San Francisco Giants have added a memorial patch to the front of their uniform’s jersey in honour of the great Willie Mays. The patch shows Mays’ legendary number 24 in orange on a black circle, his name “MAYS” arched above in orange. There’s an additional orange outline around the</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 22:25:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Taylor Swift Extinguishes Fire In NYC Apartment Kitchen</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/21/taylor-swift-puts-out-fire-gracie-abrams/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>The legend of Taylor Swift grows -- she once extinguished a fire in her New York City apartment after flames erupted in her kitchen ... and now, we're seeing it all on video. TayTay's singer friend, Gracie Abrams, just shared footage of Taylor…</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 22:03:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Los Angeles Kings Unveil New Logos, Modernized Take on ’90s Classic</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/20/los-angeles-kings-unveil-new-logos-modernized-take-on-90s-classic/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Los Angeles Kings are goin’ back to the ’90s, kids! This morning, the Kings unveiled their new, old logo via their social media channels, one day after posting a teaser graphic simply showing the outline of the logo. It’s a throwback, mostly, to what the club wore from 1988</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 17:13:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Rust' Armorer Won't Be Forced To Testify In Alec Baldwin Manslaughter Trial</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/21/alec-baldwin-manslaughter-trial-rust-armorer-wont-be-forced-testify/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>The jury in Alec Baldwin's upcoming involuntary manslaughter trial likely won't hear from the movie's armorer ... because the judge overseeing the case won't force her to take the stand. Judge Mary Marlowe Sommer decided Friday Hannah…</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 22:03:27 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>