<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 06:47:24 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>10 Steamy Beach Reads to Spice Up Your Summer</title><link>https://bookriot.com/steamy-beach-reads-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Screenshot-2024-05-14-at-1.10.23 PM.png</image_url><description>What's your favorite genre to read at the beach?</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>19 thoughts about the 2024 Lexus LC: 2 editors, 2 versions, 2,300 miles apart</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/30/thoughts-lexus-lc-500h-500-convertible-review/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/29143655/LCLede.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Green , Lexus , Infotainment , Convertible , Coupe , Hybrid , Luxury , Performance , Road Tests Continue reading 19 thoughts about the 2024 Lexus LC: 2 editors, 2 versions, 2,300 miles apart 19 thoughts about the 2024 Lexus LC: 2 editors, 2 versions, 2,300 miles apart originally appeared on Autoblog on Thu, 30 May 2024 06:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fintech targeted by climate skeptics banks $37 million from likes of UBS, Commerzbank</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/30/ubs-backs-37-million-round-for-climate-fintech-startup-doconomy.html</link><description>Swedish climate fintech Doconomy told CNBC it's raised $36.9 million in a Series B round co-led by the venture arms of UBS and CommerzBank.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 11:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sharing Fun Facts About Yourself: 22 Examples &amp; Ideas</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/fun-facts-about-me/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fun-facts-about-me</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Asking to share some fun facts about yourself is a common icebreaker that’s used during job interviews. But the quality of your answer still matters. This guide will help you come up with some ideas for crafting a response that starts the interview on a good note. Table of contents Ideas for Sharing Fun Facts […] The post Sharing Fun Facts About Yourself: 22 Examples &amp; Ideas appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 15:26:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Becoming Confident in Parenting Abilities</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/confidence-in-parenting/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=confidence-in-parenting</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Parental self-efficacy (i.e., a parent’s confidence in their own ability to care for their infant and respond to the infant’s needs) is the first step to a good parent-child relationship. Research has explored the development of maternal self-efficacy beginning during pregnancy and continuing after childbirth. Mothers who have previous childbirth and […] The post Becoming Confident in Parenting Abilities appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 10:06:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ham and Cheese Croissant Casserole</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/ham-and-cheese-croissant-casserole/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>This Ham and Cheese Croissant Casserole is filled with comforting flavors of croissants, eggs, ham and plenty of melty cheese.…</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Best Air Purifying Plants</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/best-air-purifying-plants/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>We love any excuse to buy more plants, and you may have heard they can improve your home’s indoor air quality. But before you blow your paycheck in the name of a healthier home, let’s dive deeper into plants’ air purifying powers. We’ll share which plants we recommend and what benefits you can actually expect from them. We’ve heard for years about how plants act as natural air filters for your home. So let’s dive a little deeper, shall we? 7 Air Purifying Plants If you just came here for a list, our favorite air purifying houseplants are bulleted below. The best part is these are all beautiful, low-maintenance plants. Many also appear on our best low-light indoor plants list too! Dracaena (including Corn Plant ) Snake Plant Aglaonema English Ivy Pothos Bamboo Palm Spider Plant There are certainly more that could be included here, but we narrowed it to the ones that are most often cited by experts AND the plants that we think look best too. Continue reading Best Air Purifying Plants at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 14:15:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sea Star</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/sea-star/</link><description>Outfit Details: Sir Top, Zimmermann Skirt (love this similar dress too), Zara Necklace (similar here), Ciao Lucia Bag, Stella Kids Dress on M Living by the coast, we feel fortunate… The post Sea Star appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 21:15:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best Sentient Houses in Literature</title><link>https://bookriot.com/sentient-houses-in-literature/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/haunted-house.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>What would you add to this list?</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jeep Cherokee return announcement predicted this year</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/29/jeep-cherokee-return-announcement-predicted-this-year/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/29145017/2022_jeep_cherokee_0012.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Plants/Manufacturing , Rumormill , Jeep , SUV , Electric , Future Vehicles , Hybrid , Off-Road Vehicles Continue reading Jeep Cherokee return announcement predicted this year Jeep Cherokee return announcement predicted this year originally appeared on Autoblog on Wed, 29 May 2024 16:26:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 21:26:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Thursday's analyst calls: Nvidia price target increase, PayPal gets a big upgrade</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/30/analyst-calls-all-the-market-moving-wall-street-chatter-from-thursday.html</link><description>Nvidia and PayPal were among the stocks being talked about by analysts on Thursday.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 10:46:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 553</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-553/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-553</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Tools and technology change rapidly. Yet as wonderful as technology can be, it doesn’t replace the need for human connection through interactions. Keep this in mind as you are searching for a new job. It’s your human connections that often open doors! In this week’s collection of news and tips for job seekers, you’ll find: […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 553 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 12:19:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A case for public preschool: New study reveals preschool benefits to be longer-lasting and substantial</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/benefits-of-public-preschool/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=benefits-of-public-preschool</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Preschool lays a foundation for elementary school students to succeed. In the United States, as children approach kindergarten entry, it is increasingly common for 4-year-olds to be in non-parental group care and education, often in a center- or school-based setting where they can learn alongside peers. For children from low-income communities, […] The post A case for public preschool: New study reveals preschool benefits to be longer-lasting and substantial appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 08:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Strawberry Salsa (5 Ingredients)</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/strawberry-salsa/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Add a burst of fresh, fruity flavor to your table with this Strawberry Salsa. This quick and easy recipe combines…</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Weekend In New Orleans With Kids</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/new-orleans-with-kids/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Since our travel guides to Charleston with kids and Palm Springs with kids have elicited requests for more travel ideas with kids, we’re back with an overdue recap of our 3-night trip to New Orleans. We’d never been to The Big Easy before and were impressed by how family-friendly the city is. It’s not all booze, beads, and Bourbon Street! So here’s a look at where we stayed, what we did, and what we’re excited to do next time we go back – because we will definitely go back! The four of us (well, five if you count our chihuahua!) went to NOLA for 3 nights in November of 2022. At the time, our kids were 8 and 12 years old. So unfortunately we can’t vouch for our suggestions being a good fit for toddlers or younger children. Although I’m sure ours would’ve loved the Louisiana Children’s Museum and Storyland playground back in the day! Continue reading A Weekend In New Orleans With Kids at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 17:17:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>La Vie En Rose</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/la-vie-en-rose/</link><description>Outfit Details: Erdem Dress, JB x Jennifer Behr Necklace (worn as bracelet) &amp; Earrings, Larroude Sandals, Sea NY Dress on C… The post La Vie En Rose appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 05:00:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Reese’s YA Book Club is Back</title><link>https://bookriot.com/best-of-book-riot-may-29-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Twelfth-Knight.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>See the new pick, find your summer reading mood, get the deets on James Patterson's latest literary eruption, and more.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:13:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Top car colors for 2024? 'Colorful cars appear to be an endangered species'</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/article/top-car-colors-for-2024-colorful-cars-appear-to-be-an-endangered-species/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/29122718/Screenshot-2024-05-29-at-11.53.52.png</image_url><description>Filed under: Design/Style , Car Buying , Used Car Buying , Ownership Continue reading Top car colors for 2024? 'Colorful cars appear to be an endangered species' Top car colors for 2024? 'Colorful cars appear to be an endangered species' originally appeared on Autoblog on Wed, 29 May 2024 16:07:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 21:07:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>L’Oreal says it's working on a form of bioprinted skin that can actually ‘feel’</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/30/loreal-says-its-working-on-a-form-of-bioprinted-skin-that-can-feel.html</link><description>L'Oreal says it is working with start-ups and research institutions to develop bioprinted skin that can actually "feel."</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 10:17:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 552</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-552/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-552</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>When you are searching for a job, you will inevitably run into unexpected scenarios. You will have questions, experience self-doubt and even feel discouraged. You’ll also experience great wins, meet wonderful people and discover new things about yourself. That’s the roller-coaster of job search. Consider Summary Sunday your resource for getting questions answered and showing […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 552 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 11:37:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fathers’ views on family and work after COVID-19 lockdowns</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/fathers-views-on-family-and-work-after-covid-19-lockdowns/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fathers-views-on-family-and-work-after-covid-19-lockdowns</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Fathers often want to be present for their children and contribute to household tasks, but they can lack opportunities and confidence; they may see themselves as “helpers” instead of parents. Australian fathers in our small study reported that they spent more time with their children during the COVID-19 lockdowns, and they […] The post Fathers’ views on family and work after COVID-19 lockdowns appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zesty BBQ Chicken (5 Ingredients)</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/zesty-bbq-chicken/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>This zesty BBQ chicken is an easy crockpot recipe that only takes 5 ingredients to make! The slow-cooked tender pulled…</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>9 Easy Low-Light Indoor Plants</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/easy-low-light-indoor-plants/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>I used to think every houseplant needed a sunny corner or bright windowsill to thrive. But it turns out many of our favorite go-to houseplants do just fine in shady corners and low-light locations. So before you write off your house as too dark to sustain plant life, check out this list of the best indoor plants for low light. You might be surprised at how many good options there are! Our upstairs family room is the brightest room we’ve ever owned thanks to big unobstructed windows on all 4 sides. But most of our indoor plants live downstairs, where we get far less natural light. Luckily, that hasn’t stopped us from growing our collection of happy healthy houseplants. 9 Houseplants That Don’t Need A Lot Of Light Here are our favorite low-light indoor plants. We list a lot more info on them below, but here’s a quick list to bring on your next trip to the plant store: Snake Plant ZZ Plant Pothos Heartleaf Philodendron English Ivy Aglaonema Cast Iron Plant Monstera Parlor Palm Perhaps our favorite part of this list is that these aren’t ugly “consolation plants” that people begrudgingly buy for dark homes. Continue reading 9 Easy Low-Light Indoor Plants at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 14:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Print Mixing For Summer</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/print-mixing-for-summer/</link><description>Outfit Details: Bode Top, Zimmermann Skirt (longer version here &amp; dress version here), Prada Sandals, Chanel Bag (similar here), Marisa Klass Necklace I’ve always embraced the art of… The post Print Mixing For Summer appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 18:30:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best Book Club Books Out in June</title><link>https://bookriot.com/the-best-book-club-books-out-in-june/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/light-skinned-woman-reading-in-a-head-scarf.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>Which of these books are you looking forward to discussing with your book club?</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What is gap insurance?</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/article/what-is-gap-insurance-2/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/crop/5760x3240+0+122/resize/800x450!/format/jpg/quality/85/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2023/10/13153653/behind_the_wheel_gap_insurance-1.jpeg</image_url><description>Filed under: Car Buying , Insurance , Ownership Continue reading What is gap insurance? What is gap insurance? originally appeared on Autoblog on Wed, 29 May 2024 14:50:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>South Korean tech conglomerate SK Inc. surges 16% after chair's $1 billion divorce settlement</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/30/sk-inc-surges-16percent-after-chairs-1-billion-divorce-settlement.html</link><description>SK Inc. is one of Korea's largest conglomerates and is the holding firm for SK Hynix, one of the world's biggest memory chip firms.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 09:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>While a little competition in the workplace might help bring out the best in everyone involved, an atmosphere rooted in envy, fear, or jealousy can do the exact opposite. This post will help you recognize signs that your coworker is threatened by you, and help you navigate the situation. 1. They Don’t Want You Involved […] The post 10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:07:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Strong Latine Identity Supports U.S. Latine Children’s Well-Being</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/a-strong-latine-identity-supports-u-s-latine-childrens-well-being/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=a-strong-latine-identity-supports-u-s-latine-childrens-well-being</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key Takeaways for caregivers Children tend to have better health and well-being when they have a strong ethnic identity (affinity and adoption of ethnicity-based self-concept). A traditional Latine cultural value (familismo) that emphasizes family bonds is also associated with better developmental outcomes. Caregivers can support the development of U.S. Latine children (and possibly other children […] The post A Strong Latine Identity Supports U.S. Latine Children’s Well-Being appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 03:03:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Key Lime Pie Bars</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/key-lime-pie-bars/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key lime pie bars are classic key lime pie flavors baked into delightful little bars. They have a buttery graham…</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/how-to-remove-wallpaper/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Wallpaper has made a big comeback as a trendy home design choice. But despite its resurgence, there are still plenty of us dealing with dingy, dated, or downright ugly old wallpaper we don’t want. In our old home, we had to remove wallpaper in so many rooms: the kitchen, the dining room, the foyer, and two different bathrooms! As we traveled from room to room removing wallpaper, we tested 4 different methods, and today we’ll share what we learned. Removing wallpaper doesn’t require special tools or lots of money. It’s a totally doable project for any homeowner. However, it can be a tedious process that can take elbow grease and patience, depending on the size of your room and the stubbornness of your wallpaper. But having removed several rooms worth of decades-old wallpaper, we can confidently say it’s worth the effort! You can also check out more before and afters of our once-wallpapered rooms. Continue reading How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:21:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Week’s Favorites From Amazon</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/amazon-sundays-5-19-24/</link><description>Welcome to our latest favorites from Amazon that I’m especially excited to share! This week includes an array of colorful… The post This Week’s Favorites From Amazon appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 05:00:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Critics’ Most Anticipated Summer Reads</title><link>https://bookriot.com/today-in-books-may-29-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/beach-chairs-700-x-375.jpeg.optimal.jpeg</image_url><description>NPR critics reveal their summer TBRs, Reese brings back the YA book club, and the sexiest book of summer isn't a rom-com.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 17:17:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Donald Trump is reportedly considering an advisory role for Elon Musk</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/29/donald-trump-is-reportedly-considering-an-advisory-role-for-elon-musk/</link><image_url>https://o.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://media.zenfs.com/en/business_insider_articles_888/7d3e38a4f0e624a9796fb1f5c9bc3f6b</image_url><description>Filed under: Car Buying , Insurance , Ownership Continue reading Donald Trump is reportedly considering an advisory role for Elon Musk Donald Trump is reportedly considering an advisory role for Elon Musk originally appeared on Autoblog on Wed, 29 May 2024 13:56:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 18:56:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BlackRock-backed fintech Trustly says IPO still at least one year out even as profits jump 51%</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/30/trustly-posts-51percent-profit-jump-ceo-says-ipo-at-least-2-years-out.html</link><description>Johan Tjarnberg, CEO of Trustly, told CNBC his firm still needs time to prove the value of its open banking tech to investors before going public.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 08:59:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 551</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-551/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-551</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Job search requires writing and marketing skills. It also requires strong verbal communication. If these skills are not part of your normal work function, you’ll want some help. That’s what this week’s Summary Sunday is all about. There’s no doubt that LinkedIn is one of THE most powerful tools in your career toolbox. It contains […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 551 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 11:37:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Children caught between highly conflicted divorced parents at greater risk of mental health problems</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/children-caught-between-conflicted-divorced-parents/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=children-caught-between-conflicted-divorced-parents</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Interparental conflict after divorce escalates the risk of mental health problems in children and adolescents. Elevated levels of conflict between parents can also induce fear and worry in children about their future and whether they will be adequately taken care of. In turn, a greater fear of abandonment puts children at […] The post Children caught between highly conflicted divorced parents at greater risk of mental health problems appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 08:59:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Salmon Marinade</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/salmon-marinade/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>A great salmon marinade makes your fish flavorful, tender, and juicy! This recipe gives each filet the perfect balance of…</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aglaonema Plant – Complete Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/aglaonema-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Aglaonema, also called the Chinese Evergreen Plant, is an easy-care houseplant that lives happily in many lighting conditions – even a dark corner of our daughter’s room. There are dozens of different Aglaonema varieties, most with large tropical foliage and colors ranging from silvery-green, red, and even vibrant pink. They’re also tough to kill, so they’re a great option for forgetful plant owners or anyone looking for an easy win in the plant department. These truly have been very low maintenance for us. We purchased our two Aglaonemas (pronounced ag-lee-oh-neem-ah ) to put atop our daughter’s closet. It’s sometimes hard to distinguish different varieties, but we believe that’s an Aglaonema Silver (right) and either a Candy Cane or Princess Silver Queen (left). Aglaonema Quick Facts Here’s what you need to know about your Aglaonema at a glance: Latin name : Aglaonema is the genus under which there are 21 recognized species . Continue reading Aglaonema Plant – Complete Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:47:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Warm Weather Hair Care</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/warm-weather-hair-care/</link><description>Outfit Details: Cala de la Cruz Dress, Emme Parsons Sandals, Saint Laurent Sunglasses One of the essential parts of summer… The post Warm Weather Hair Care appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 05:00:31 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>