<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 07:24:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>FIRE in 2024: What We’d Do Differently If We Started Over Today</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-556</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>2013 was a pivotal year for our hosts. Scott was fresh out of college and just beginning his journey to financial independence, while Mindy and her husband were well on […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 07:01:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Starpath accelerates moon water mining plans with $12M seed funding</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/20/starpath-accelerates-moon-water-mining-plans-with-12m-seed-funding/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>NASA and the space industry are in agreement: if we want to establish a permanent human presence on the moon, we’ll need to make use of every native resource we can — and none are as important as water ice. Starpath Robotics is one of a handful of startups planning for this future. The startup […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Prosecutors Fight Exonerations</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/17/wrongful-conviction-innocence-claims-missouri-st-louis</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>As laws are passed to support the wrongfully convicted, some officials in the legal system push back.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Does the President Have An Impact on Housing? Here’s What 30 Years of Data Says.</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/can-the-president-have-an-impact-on-the-housing-market</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>VP Harris just unveiled her economic plan, which included a number of items for supporting the housing market. But does history suggest executive policies make a difference?</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 19:06:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Reliant’s paper-scouring AI takes on science’s data drudgery</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/20/reliant-ai/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>AI models have proven capable of many things, but what tasks do we actually want them doing? Preferably drudgery — and there’s plenty of that in research and academia. Reliant hopes to specialize in the kind of time-consuming data extraction work that’s currently a specialty of tired grad students and interns. “The best thing you […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 11:59:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FAQ: How The Marshall Project Is Covering the 2024 Election</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/16/election-faq-crime-politics</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Learn more about who we are and how we choose what political stories to cover.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>4 Properties in 4 Years and Saving $40K on ONE Deal by Doing This</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-446</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Can rookies find rental properties that cash flow in today’s housing market? Yes! But you may need to get creative. This investor made the numbers work by discovering extra income […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 10:00:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mike Lynch, recently acquitted in HP-Autonomy fraud case, is missing after yacht capsized off Sicily (updated)</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/20/mike-lynch-recently-acquitted-in-hp-autonomy-case-is-missing-after-yacht-capsized-off-sicily/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Update: Authorities have yet to access the inside of the sunken yacht, and Mike Lynch is still classified as missing. Other details have emerged in the interim. The accident appears to have been caused by a major storm and a resulting tornado-like water column that ensnared and damaged the yacht. Among the other six people […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 09:16:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Mother on a Mission for Full Police Transparency</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/16/police-beating-ulysses-wilkerson-mother-video</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Troy, Alabama, police severely beat Ulysses Wilkerson when he was 17. Seven years later, his mom, Angela Williams, is still fighting for answers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>50+ Rentals After Starting in Her 50s and How “Late Starters” Can Get Ahead</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-1006</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>With her retirement dreams on the line, Jill Forsythe had a few choices: return to work, start a business, or get into real estate investing. After trying out more “active […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 10:00:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>US tech giants fight Indian telcos’ bid to regulate internet services, pay for network usage</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/20/us-tech-giants-fight-indian-telcos-bid-to-regulate-internet-services/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Global technology giants are pushing back against attempts by India’s telecom networks to bring internet services under stricter regulation, rejecting arguments that such measures are necessary to create a “level playing field” and address national security concerns. The Asia Internet Coalition (AIC), a powerful industry body that represents Amazon, Apple, Google, Meta, Microsoft, Netflix and […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 09:12:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How the 1968 DNC in Chicago Devolved into ‘Unrestrained and Indiscriminate Police Violence’</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/14/chicago-dnc-protests-police-reforms</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>As protesters prepare for the Democratic National Convention in Chicago next week, a half-century old report provides lessons for preventing chaos.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 11:00:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tenants in Big Cities Could Save Thousands if “Broker Fee” Reform Passes</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-244</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>New “broker fee” reform could help tenants save thousands of dollars when finding their next apartment or home to rent, but it could come at a significant cost to landlords. […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 10:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pakistan’s PostEx to enter new markets, starting with Saudi Arabia</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/19/pakistans-postex-to-enter-new-markets-starting-with-saudi-arabia/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Pakistani startup PostEx is entering Saudi Arabia as first global market after hitting $21 million ARR in the South Asian nation. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aaron Sankin is The Marshall Project’s new Deputy Data Editor</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/13/aaron-sankin-is-the-marshall-projects-new-deputy-data-editor</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Sankin brings deep experience with ambitious data projects.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 20:00:24 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>