<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 15:42:52 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Book Review: Trailblazers, Heroes, and Crooks</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/26/book-review-trailblazers-heroes-and-crooks/</link><description>Stephen Foerster, CFA, extracts lessons from exceptional episodes in financial history that ordinary investors and seasoned professionals alike can put to profitable use. The bonus is that you'll be entertained from start to finish.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meta’s investors are worried about the billions it’s spending on AI—but its advertising empire makes it a positive, Deutsche Bank says</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/26/meta-ai-advertising-instagram-reels-facebook-zuckerberg/</link><description>Investors balk at $40 billion in spending, sending stock falling—but analysts say Meta’s advertising advantage is a perfect use case for AI.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 20:35:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Price Risk? Unpacking the Equity Risk Premium</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/24/what-price-risk-unpacking-the-equity-risk-premium/</link><description>Stocks are a good wager over the long term, on favorable odds. But stocks remain a bet, and investors must grasp how much returns can vary over long time horizons.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>With inflation still high and economic growth slowing sharply we could be heading toward stagflation, a scenario 'nobody is really prepared for,' UBS exec says</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/26/inflation-stagflation-ubs-economy-federal-reserve-jerome-powell-unemployment-recession/</link><description>After preparing for a recession, and hoping for a soft landing, the U.S. might end up in an unexpected bout of stagflation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 20:34:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Equity Income Investing Redux</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/22/equity-income-investing-redux/</link><description>No doubt the past year has been difficult for equity income investors. But history, inherent biases, mean reversion, and the current market backdrop point to a comeback.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 17:19:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Buffett-owned real estate brokerage pays $250 million to settle claims that agent commissions break antitrust law</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/26/homeservices-real-estate-commissions-lawsuit-settlement-warren-buffett/</link><description>HomeServices of America is the latest to settle a Missouri lawsuit filed on behalf of homebuyers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 19:52:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: Enrich Your Future</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/18/book-review-enrich-your-future/</link><description>This engaging book is simultaneously memorable and humorous. The numerous sports analogies will have you smiling as you absorb Larry Swedroe's unforgettable investment precepts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 18:07:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tesla’s Elon Musk speeds past Mark Zuckerberg on the billionaires list after Meta stock plummets on its cash-sucking AI plans</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/26/teslas-elon-musk-mark-zuckerberg-billionaire-meta/</link><description>Zuckerberg passed Musk on the list earlier this month.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 19:27:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CAPE Is High: Should You Care?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/17/cape-is-high-should-you-care/</link><description>A simple analysis shows that Robert Shiller's cyclically adjusted price-to-earnings ratio changed in the 1990s and that mean-reversion concerns may be misplaced. If CAPE changed three decades ago, however, there is nothing preventing it from doing so again.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 15:18:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>It’s still a golden age of homebuilding, according to one top real estate CEO. Here’s why</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/26/housing-market-golden-age-homebuilding-mortgage-rates-new-homes/</link><description>“It’s that unique confluence of strong demand, no supply because there’s no resale inventory, and large public builders with a meaningful advantage through those rate buydowns,” Howard Hughes’ chief executive said.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 19:25:06 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>