<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 06:57:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The Rental Property Toolkit: How to Build Your Buy Box and Source More Deals</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-453</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Struggling to land your next rental property? Even in today’s housing market, there’s a great deal out there with your name on it—you just need to know where to look. […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 10:00:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spotify launches its evolving playlist, daylist, globally</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/04/spotify-launches-its-evolving-playlist-daylist-globally/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Spotify is launching daylist globally. It’s a personalized playlist that evolves throughout the day depending on your listening habits. This rollout comes after the company introduced it first to English-speaking markets last year. The playlist will be available to both free and premium users. The company said it is also adding support for 14 additional […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Efforts to Cut Long Prison Sentences Have Stalled</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/31/wisconsin-california-sentence-prison</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Crime victim advocates and conservative groups are resisting moves to revisit “truth-in-sentencing” laws.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Real Estate Risk: How to Dodge It, When to Take It, and Using It to Build Wealth</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-1013</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Real estate risk can make you wealthy or cause your portfolio to come crashing down. Like any type of investing, real estate can be risky. However, the amount of risk […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 10:00:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Impact investors FMO and BlueOrchard back Ghana’s digital lender Fido in $30M Series B round</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/03/ghanas-digital-lender-fido-30m-series-b-round/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Digital lending platforms have become an easy and swift alternative source of credit for microenterprises and individuals overlooked by traditional banking institutions. These platforms have turned into a lifeline for millions of underbanked and demand will keep growing, pushing the value of the digital lending platform market in the Middle East and Africa to reach […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 04:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How a Massachusetts Cop Allegedly Groomed, Controlled and Killed Sandra Birchmore</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/30/police-explorer-sexual-abuse-massachusetts-birchmore</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Matthew Farwell met her in a police Explorer program. Prosecutors say he abused her for years before she became pregnant and he killed her.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dude ACTUALLY Withdraws From His 401(k) and Retires at 47</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-560</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Did you know you can use your 401(k) to retire early? Yep, it’s possible. And today’s guest, Eric Cooper, is doing it at age 47! Most FIRE chasers search for […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 07:01:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PharmEasy still 92% below its peak $5.6 billion valuation, investor estimates</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/03/pharmeasy-still-92-below-its-peak-5-6-billion-valuation-investor-estimates/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Indian online pharmacy startup PharmEasy, once valued at $5.6 billion, is still about 92% below its peak valuation, according to new estimates by its investor Janus Henderson. According to the British-American global asset firm, which disclosed how it values its shares in the Indian startup in a securities filing, PharmEasy’s implied valuation at the end […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 04:38:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>5 Things to Know About How Survivors Get Incarcerated for Their Abusers’ Crimes</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/28/accomplice-liability-laws-what-to-know</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Little-known laws allow people to be punished for crimes they didn’t directly commit. Survivors of domestic violence are especially vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>After Analyzing the Largest Rental Markets—Here’s Where Prices Could Fall</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rental-markets-where-prices-could-start-falling</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Which markets are currently seeing a decline in effective rents, and which are currently experiencing high vacancy?</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 18:09:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From their experiences at Uber and PayPal, Palm founders want to make moving cash easier for big companies</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/03/from-their-experiences-at-uber-and-paypal-palm-founders-want-to-make-moving-cash-easier-for-big-companies/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Palm launched in 2023 with the goal of making cash management for enterprise treasury teams easier. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How a Drop in Border Crossings May Change the Presidential Campaign</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/24/kamala-harris-dnc-border-donald-trump</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>The Democratic National Convention sought to address one of the party’s biggest weaknesses with voters.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>High Cash Flow and Low Risk by Turning Tenants into Homeowners (Rent-to-Own)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-1012</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Rent-to-own real estate can make you more cash flow, with less risk and fewer expenses, all while helping tenants become homeowners. But if it’s so good, why isn’t everyone doing […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:00:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Canva has increased prices for its Teams product</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/03/canva-has-increased-prices-for-its-teams-product/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Canva, the design platform, is increasing prices steeply for some customers. And it’s blaming the move in part on generative AI. In the U.S., some Canva Teams subscribers on older pricing plans are seeing the sticker price for a five-person plan jump from $119.99 per year to $500 per year (with a 40% discount for […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 01:45:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Prosecutors Fight Exonerations</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/17/wrongful-conviction-innocence-claims-missouri-st-louis</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>As laws are passed to support the wrongfully convicted, some officials in the legal system push back.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>