<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 07:21:22 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Rethinking Retirement Planning Amidst Aging Demographic Frontiers</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/28/rethinking-retirement-planning-amidst-aging-demographic-frontiers/</link><description>Forward-thinking approaches to policy and wealth management are needed to ensure a better financial future across generations and income brackets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 20:32:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Inflation's persistence is killing hope for a Fed rate cut in 2024</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/29/inflations-persistence-killing-hope-fed-reserve-interest-rate-cut-2024/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/AP24149743155138-e1716979098496.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The Fed's mandate is to strike a balance between keeping rates high enough to control inflation yet not so high as to damage the job market.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 12:06:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: The New World Economy in 5 Trends</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/24/book-review-the-new-world-economy-in-5-trends/</link><description>A diligent economist and an eclectic bookworm serve up an analysis of megatrends that will have the greatest impact on economies and investments: innovation, productivity, climate, multiglobalization, debt, and aging.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 12:22:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Russia-linked cyber attacks on Europe have doubled since 2023, top EU cybersecurity official says</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/29/russia-cyber-attacks-europe-doubled-since-2023-eu-cybersecurity-official/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2007336257-e1716978157711.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Juhan Lepassaar, head of the European Union Agency for Cybersecurity, said that attack methods — while mostly unsuccessful — were often tried out in Ukraine before being expanded to EU countries.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 11:50:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Factor Strategies Belong in Your Completion Portfolio Toolkit</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/23/factor-strategies-belong-in-your-completion-portfolio-toolkit/</link><description>Why wouldn't you include factor strategies in your completion portfolio? A review of the two commonly used approaches for managing institutional assets highlights their symbiotic nature.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 19:09:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Uber gears up for Paris Olympics by offering free cruises across the Seine and discounts to ease the load on public transport networks</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/29/uber-paris-olympics-free-cruises-seine-river-discounts-public-transport/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1602763816-e1716975585733.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Paris is expecting 30% more visitors this summer than usual—and Uber's support may help the city's public transport systems cope with the strain.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 11:39:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>For the Analyst: Peer Benchmarking Methods to Improve Earnings Forecasts</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/21/for-the-analyst-peer-benchmarking-methods-to-improve-earnings-forecasts/</link><description>Peer benchmarking is a vexing task for financial analysts but one that is critical for forecasting earnings. This straightforward measure can help find peers for relative performance, compensation, and valuation benchmarking.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 12:47:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ONS dealing with 20% staf exodus weeks after facing strikes over return to office orders</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/29/ons-stats-body-strike-remote-work-20-staff-exodus/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1308902643-e1716976967537.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Headcount has dipped at the ONS at the same time as the stats body fights with staff over office attendance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 11:23:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Building LLMs in the Open-Source Community: A Call to Action for Investment Professionals</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/20/building-llms-in-the-open-source-community-a-call-to-action-for-investment-professionals/</link><description>Large language models like ChatGPT are changing the way we think about investing and reshaping roles in the investment profession.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 16:26:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The future is a state of mind: What it takes to build a future-ready company</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/29/future-ready-company-leadership-traits-bcg/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2153485379-e1716499507886.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The best and most future-ready CEOs and leaders know how to balance prudence and patience with ambition and experimentation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 10:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>