<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 07:54:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Minor League Baseball teams, local indie bands team up on brands</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/14/minor-league-baseball-teams-local-indie-bands-team-up-on-brands/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Three affiliated Minor League Baseball teams will partner with local independent musicians to create the “Capsule Collection.” This collaboration is intended to do what minor league baseball branding specializes in: highlight connections between teams and their local community. In its just-announced initial stages, the Capsule Collection will combine design elements</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 18:30:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Masked Man Shoots at NYC Cab Driver After Not Being Able to Pay Fare</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/14/man-in-ski-mask-opens-fire-on-nyc-cab-driver-after-falling-out-of-moving-car/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>A masked man shot at a NYC taxi driver after he apparently couldn't pay his fare in full -- and now the cabbie's own ilk is telling its workforce how to avoid this situation. In the footage -- filmed from inside driver Eufelix Jiminian's cab…</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 07:54:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WNBA Expansion Team Golden State Valkyries Unveil Name, Logo</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/14/wnba-expansion-team-golden-state-valkyries-unveil-name-logo/basketball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Franchise name references warrior women from Norse mythology; logo depicts Bay Bridge between Oakland, where they'll train, and San Francisco, where they'll play home games</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 15:56:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zayn Malik Says He Got Kicked Off Tinder, No One Believed It Was Him</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/14/zayn-malik-kicked-off-tinder-accused-catfish-fake-profile-dating/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Dating apps aren't exactly the best for finding love among normies -- and celebs aren't having much luck on them either -- including Zayn Malik ... who tried (and failed) using Tinder. The One Direction heartthrob dished about his attempt to find…</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 07:54:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New York Giants Unveil 100th Season Logo, Uniform Patch</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/13/new-york-giants-unveil-100th-season-logo-uniform-patch/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The New York Giants kicked off their 100th season celebration on Monday morning by unveiling a commemorative logo, which will be worn as a patch on their uniforms this fall.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 02:05:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Brad Pitt Countersued in Winery Case, Allegedly Made It a Personal Piggy Bank</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/14/brad-pitt-countersued-sued-winery-case-angelina-jolie-misappropriate-funds/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>3:14 PM PT -- Sources with direct knowledge tell TMZ, Brad Pitt's side is scoffing at Tenute's countersuit -- as they feel they only tried getting into the Chateau Miraval biz because of his name-recognition and deep involvement with the company…</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 07:54:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>La Liga’s Real Betis Focus on Water With Newest Edition of ‘Forever Green’ Kits</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/13/la-ligas-real-betis-focus-on-water-with-newest-edition-of-forever-green-kits/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Club aims to raise awareness about the responsible use of water and the impact climate change is having on fields in Spain and all over the world</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 15:54:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Noah Cyrus Shares IG Tribute To Mom Tish Again, Family Feud Seemingly Over</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/14/noah-cyrus-another-tribute-post-mom-tish-birthday-family-feud-over/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Noah Cyrus is continuing to shout out her mom, Tish ... and it seems any inkling of love triangle drama is almost all but faded, and the newfound love is going both ways. Noah hit up her IG Stories Monday to wish her mom a happy birthday by sharing…</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 07:54:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Leak: Los Angeles Dodgers City Connect Jersey Spotted in Japan</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/13/leak-los-angeles-dodgers-city-connect-jersey-spotted-in-tokyo/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Los Angeles Dodgers’ new City Connect uniform was leaked this weekend. The jersey, spotted hanging up in a store in Japan, shows a vibrant pattern that departs from the traditional Dodgers’ style. The photo shows a white jersey speckled with tiny blue, red, and yellow dots, giving the feeling</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 15:25:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Angel Reese, Chicago Sky Still Flying Commercial Amid WNBA Charter Rollout</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/14/angel-reese-chicago-sky-fly-commercial-wnba-charter-rollout/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Not everybody in the WNBA is traveling in style just yet -- Angel Reese and her Chicago Sky teammates are still flying commercial to start the 2024 season ... as the league continues to smooth out its new charter flight program. Caitlin Clark's…</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 07:54:18 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>