<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 07:21:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Stay-at-Home Mom to “Accidental” Investor with a $600K/Year Business</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-412</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Want to invest but fear you don’t have enough money to get started? Building a profitable real estate business could be the answer. This strategy allowed today’s guest to not […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 07:02:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Clean Energy Ventures avoided the pandemic bubble and raised a $305M fund</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/29/how-clean-energy-ventures-avoided-the-pandemic-bubble-and-raised-a-305m-fund/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>When other firms were investing and raising eye-popping sums, Clean Energy Ventures took a different approach. It appears to be paying off. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Legal Doctrine That Shields Police From Many Lawsuits May Be Losing Support</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/25/police-mississippi-courts-judges-qualified-immunity</link><description>A federal judge in Mississippi joined other courts in recently rejecting police arguments that qualified immunity protected their actions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Federal Experts Talk Bird Flu ‘What Ifs’ in WebMD Live Event</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/cold-and-flu/news/20240516/federal-experts-talk-bird-flu-what-ifs?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>WebMD brought together experts from four federal agencies to talk prevention, monitoring, and what the “what ifs” of bird flu might look like.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:50:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Buy a Home (or Entire Neighborhood) With Your Friends and Family</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-962</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Imagine living in a home where your next-door neighbors are your best friends or family members. We know you’ve thought about it before—starting a compound with all the people you […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 07:02:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OpenAI signs 100K PwC workers to ChatGPT’s enterprise tier as PwC becomes its first resale partner</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/29/openai-signs-on-100k-pwc-workers-to-its-chatgpt-enterprise-tier-as-the-consultant-becomes-its-first-resale-partner/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>PwC, the management consulting giant, will become OpenAI’s biggest customer to date, covering 100,000 users. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 09:59:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Out of the Blue: The Rise and Fall of a Black Cop</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/23/black-police-officers-cleveland-black-shield</link><description>After Cleveland officer Vincent Montague shot a Black man, he got promoted. Then he allied with Black Lives Matter, and his life went off the rails.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What’s Next in Health Care for Older Adults: Questions and Answers With John Whyte, MD</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/blog-aging-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>As WebMD’s chief medical officer, John Whyte, MD, is in a unique position to see both the current state of medical care for America’s older adults and the way things are trending for the future. We asked him to share his insight on a few topics, along with a bit of advice.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:29:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Prepare Your Rental Property for Tenants</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/how-to-prepare-rental-property-for-tenants</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Rehabbing a home isn’t the same as preparing a home for rental, though. Not all homes require rehabbing, but all rental properties must be prepared for prospective renters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 04:59:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>72 hours left of the Disrupt early-bird sale</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/29/72-hours-left-disrupt-early-bird-sale/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Tech enthusiasts and entrepreneurs, the clock is ticking! With just 72 hours remaining until the early-bird ticket deadline for TechCrunch Disrupt 2024, now is the time to secure your spot and save big on this premier tech event. Don’t miss out on the opportunity to join us in San Francisco for an unforgettable experience filled […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Marshall Project Wins Prestigious Robert F. Kennedy Journalism Award for Criminal Justice</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/21/marshall-project-rfk-award</link><description>The award recognizes our 2023 investigation exposing lax prison discipline for abusive guards in New York state prisons.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Get the Care You Need in a COVID-19 World</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/covid-senior-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>What to expect at the doctor’s office, hospitals, and long-term care facilities, the future of telemedicine, and how to get the best care during COVID-19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 19:50:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>5 Insights on the Current State of Commercial Real Estate That Investors Must Know About</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/5-insights-on-the-current-state-of-commercial-real-estate-that-investors-must-know-about</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>This article is presented by Walker &amp; Dunlop. Read our editorial guidelines for more information. If you are, or thinking about, investing in commercial real estate, what should you know about the […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 20:36:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Avendus, India’s top venture advisor, confirms it’s looking to raise a $350 million fund</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/28/avendus-indias-top-venture-advisor-confirms-its-looking-to-raise-a-350-million-fund/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Avendus, the top investment bank for venture deals in India, confirmed on Wednesday it is looking to raise up to $350 million for its new private equity fund. The new fund, called Future Leaders Fund III, will enable the Mumbai-headquartered firm to write larger checks and maintain a meaningful position in the startups it backs, […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 03:03:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Police Tactics at Some Pro-Palestine Protests Ignore Past Lessons</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/18/police-israel-palestine-campus-protests</link><description>While some universities have sought peaceful approaches, others have used aggressive policing that bucks research from the protests following George Floyd’s murder.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Personal Shopper: A Savvy Black Entrepreneur Guides You to Eczema-Friendly Clothes, Creams, Cosmetics, and More</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/savvy-black-entrepreneur-guides-eczema-friendly-clothes-creams-cosmetics?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>A savvy black entrepreneur guides you on an eczema-friendly shopping spree.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:54:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seeing Greene: How to Avoid High Down Payments and When to BRRRR vs. Buy New</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-961</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>One of the biggest hurdles to rental property investing? High down payments. Most lenders want you to come to the table with twenty to thirty percent down, but with home […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 07:02:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>China’s $47B semiconductor fund puts chip sovereignty front and center</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/28/chinas-47b-semiconductor-fund-puts-chip-sovereignty-front-and-center/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>China has closed a third state-backed investment fund to bolster its semiconductor industry and reduce reliance on other nations, both for using and for manufacturing wafers — prioritizing what is called chip sovereignty. China’s National Integrated Circuit Industry Investment Fund, also known simply as ‘the Big Fund,’ had two previous vintages: Big Fund I (2014 […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 22:15:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Susan Chira to Step Down as The Marshall Project’s Editor-in-Chief in January</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/16/susan-chira-eic-step-down</link><description>Under her stewardship, the news nonprofit more than doubled in size, opened local newsrooms and won its second Pulitzer Prize.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Behind the Spike in Colorectal Cancer Among Young Americans</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/colorectal-cancer/news/20240515/behind-the-spike-in-colorectal-cancer-cases?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Colorectal cancer cases increased a whopping 333% among 15- to 19-year-olds and 185% among 20- to 24-year-olds from 1999 to 2020.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:59:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>