<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 18:02:32 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>What Price Risk? Unpacking the Equity Risk Premium</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/24/what-price-risk-unpacking-the-equity-risk-premium/</link><description>Stocks are a good wager over the long term, on favorable odds. But stocks remain a bet, and investors must grasp how much returns can vary over long time horizons.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fortune Future of Finance Livestream</title><link>https://fortune.com/article/fortune-future-of-finance-livestream-2024/</link><description>The summit will welcome to the stage everyone from senior Wall Street executives to next-generation finance leaders.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 22:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Equity Income Investing Redux</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/22/equity-income-investing-redux/</link><description>No doubt the past year has been difficult for equity income investors. But history, inherent biases, mean reversion, and the current market backdrop point to a comeback.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 17:19:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden's labor secretary touts auto union's win in the South: 'That choice belongs to the workers'</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/25/biden-uaw-union-election-chattanooga-julie-su/</link><description>Workers at a Chattanooga VW plant voted 3-to-1 to join the UAW, a choice Tennessee's governor called "a mistake."</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 22:39:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: Enrich Your Future</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/18/book-review-enrich-your-future/</link><description>This engaging book is simultaneously memorable and humorous. The numerous sports analogies will have you smiling as you absorb Larry Swedroe's unforgettable investment precepts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 18:07:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>British PM wants to reform the country’s disability benefits by ending ‘sick note culture’ that 'overmedicalizes everyday challenges’</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/25/rishi-sunak-uk-mental-health-work-welfare-reform/</link><description>In a speech proposing reforms to Britain’s welfare system prime minister Rishi Sunak said people with “less severe” mental health conditions should still be in the workforce.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 22:31:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CAPE Is High: Should You Care?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/17/cape-is-high-should-you-care/</link><description>A simple analysis shows that Robert Shiller's cyclically adjusted price-to-earnings ratio changed in the 1990s and that mean-reversion concerns may be misplaced. If CAPE changed three decades ago, however, there is nothing preventing it from doing so again.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 15:18:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hertz is done gambling with EVs: It took a first-quarter $195 million hit on Teslas that just keep losing value and can’t sell them fast enough</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/25/hertz-ev-electric-vehicles-tesla-elon-musk-recall-earnings-rental-cars/</link><description>Three years ago, investing in a fleet of 100,000 is what helped the car rental company emerge from bankruptcy.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 22:19:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI to the Rescue? Overhauling the US Power Grid on the Path to Net Zero</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/15/ai-to-the-rescue-overhauling-the-us-power-grid-on-the-path-to-net-zero/</link><description>Once known as secure and profitable investments, utilities are now viewed as enterprises fraught with financial risks. Investors should favor utilities that employ AI and other digital strategies to minimize damage from natural disasters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 21:24:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>USC cancels May graduation ceremony as concerns mount about pro-Palestinian protests on college campuses</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/25/usc-graduation-ceremony-protest-palestine/</link><description>USC announced the cancellation of the May 10 ceremony a day after more than 90 protesters were arrested on campus.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 22:12:49 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>