<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from multiple RSS sources, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 01:04:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Think Passive Real Estate Is Safe? Here Are 9 Hidden Risks That Could Cost You</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/passive-real-estate-investment-risks</link><description>You can’t eliminate all risk from investments. After all, the zombie apocalypse could strike tomorrow and probably wipe out your entire portfolio. But you can reduce risk, even among high-return […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 20:06:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TikTok faces a ban in the US, Tesla profits drop and healthcare data leaks</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/27/tiktok-faces-a-ban-in-the-us-tesla-profits-drop-and-healthcare-data-leaks/</link><description>Welcome, folks, to Week in Review (WiR), TechCrunch’s regular newsletter covering this week’s noteworthy happenings in tech. TikTok’s fate in the U.S. looks uncertain after President Joe Biden signed a bill that included a deadline for ByteDance, TikTok’s parent company, to divest itself of TikTok within nine months or face a ban on distributing it […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 21:15:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>They Killed Their Abusive Partners. Now Their Sentences Could Be Reconsidered.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/27/oklahoma-oregon-minnesota-domestic-violence</link><description>Oklahoma could re-examine how it punishes people whose crimes came after years of domestic abuse. Other states may follow.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>You Give Me (Spring) Fever</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/women/features/you-give-me-spring-fever?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>New Season Brings Boost of Energy, but Also Unplanned Pregnancies</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 16:57:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gen Z Is Dominating Their Parents in Homeownership—According to New Report</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/gen-z-homeownership-outpacing-parents</link><description>When it comes to homeownership, Gen Z might be ahead of the curve. According to data from real estate firm Redfin, more Gen Zers owned their home at 24 than their parents did (millennials and […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 19:59:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Will a TikTok ban impact creator economy startups? Not really, founders say</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/27/will-a-tiktok-ban-impact-creator-economy-startups-not-really-founders-say/</link><description>President Joe Biden signed a bill on Wednesday that could ban TikTok — for real this time. After so many false starts and stops, some creator economy founders and their clients are rolling their eyes. They’ve been through this before. “I think two years ago, this would have been devastating,” Karat Financial co-founder and co-CEO […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 21:15:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Being Trans in Prison Is Really Like</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/26/trans-prison-voices-gender-essay</link><description>Amid a wave of anti-trans legislation, and the violence that often follows, four people share their experiences in the criminal justice system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 11:00:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Older Adults: 9 Nutrients You May Be Missing</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/missing-nutrients?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>With age, your body doesn’t absorb nutrients well, so every calorie you consume must be packed with nutrition. Here are 9 nutrients older adults often need more of.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 16:57:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Economic Surge, Housing Plunge: Why Economic Growth Is Wrecking Real Estate Opportunities</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/a-robust-economy-is-wrecking-real-estate-opportunities</link><description>Mortgage rates recently rose above 7% for the first time this year, bringing an already glacial housing market to a standstill. The news has hit investors like a horror movie jump scare after […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 19:46:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Investors won’t give you the real reason they are passing on your startup</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/27/your-team-sucks/</link><description>“When an investor passes on you, they will not tell you the real reason,” said Tom Blomfield, group partner at Y Combinator. “At seed stage, frankly, no one knows what’s going to fucking happen. The future is so uncertain. All they’re judging is the perceived quality of the founder. When they pass, what they’re thinking […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 19:00:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Enduring Use of Solitary, and New Proposed Limits That Will Likely Fail (Again)</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/20/solitary-confinement-reform-oklahoma-washington-florida</link><description>Isolation’s damaging effects are widely known. But many facilities confine people — even youth — virtually all day, sometimes in shower stalls.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Immunity Challenge: How aging affects your immune system</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/seniors-boost-immunity?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>How does getting older affect your immune system? How can you keep those effects to a minimum? Your answers are here.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 16:57:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>3 Steps to Buying Your First (or Next) Small Multifamily Property</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-398</link><description>Small multifamily real estate investing can lead you to financial freedom faster than you think. Compared to traditional single-family rental properties, small multifamily properties often offer more cash flow, the […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 07:02:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deal Dive: Givebutter is turning a profit making tech for nonprofits</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/27/deal-dive-givebutter-is-turning-a-profit-making-tech-for-nonprofits/</link><description>Givebutter recently raised $50 million for its CRM platform for nonprofits as startups building tech for that industry gain momentum.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 17:00:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Officials Failed to Act When COVID Hit Prisons. A New Study Shows the Deadly Cost.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/18/covid-prison-deaths-data</link><description>People in prison died at 3.4 times the rate of the free population, with the oldest hit hardest. New data holds lessons for preventing future deaths.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Helps When It’s Hard to Chew and Swallow?</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/eating-problems?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Trouble chewing and swallowing? WebMD shares six ways to make everything go down a little easier.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 16:57:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BiggerNews: Can’t Qualify for Another Mortgage? Try THESE Investor Loans w/Jeff Welgan</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-943</link><description>Want to scale your real estate portfolio faster? These investment property loans can help. Most real estate investors get stuck early on in their journey. They buy some properties and […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 07:02:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The ‘valley of death’ for climate lies between early-stage funding and scaling up</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/27/climate-startup-valley-of-death/</link><description>It's easier for climate companies to get enough funding to get started. It's much harder once they need money to scale.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 16:00:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Parents Paying for Their Children’s Crimes</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/13/michigan-school-shooting-parents</link><description>Experts warn about a wave of legal consequences for parents like the Crumbleys, while some states consider prosecutions for kids as young as 10.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Foods to Keep You Healthy as You Age</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/longevity-foods?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Staying healthy as you enter your golden years has a lot to do with your diet. Here are some foods that are good for your heart, your brain, your bones, and your muscles.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 16:57:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>