<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 15:10:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>New Women’s 3-on-3 Basketball League Unveils  Logo</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/10/new-womens-3-on-3-basketball-league-unveils-logo/basketball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Unrivaled league will feature six teams of five players each playing compressed full-court 3-on-3 games in Miami starting in January 2025</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:10:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nicki Minaj's Fans Fuming Over Disaster Dublin Gig, Turns Up Late, Short Set</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/10/nicki-minaj-fans-refund-dublin-concert-late-costume-changes-curfew/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Nicki Minaj fans are pissed off -- this after they paid big bucks for tickets, only for her to show up over 90 minutes late for her Dublin gig ... leaving them stranded in the rain. The rapper was supposed to rock Malahide Castle at 8 PM Saturday…</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 15:10:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Boston Celtics Partner With Amica For New Jersey Patch</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/10/boston-celtics-partner-with-amica-for-new-jersey-patch/basketball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The reigning NBA champion Boston Celtics have announced a multi-year jersey patch partnership with Amica, a Rhode Island-based auto, home and life insurance company. “The Boston Celtics jersey is not only recognized all across New England, it’s recognized all across the world,” team president Rich Gotham said during a press</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 17:05:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wander Franco Formally Charged With Sexual Abuse Against A Minor</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/10/wander-franco-formally-charged-sexual-abuse-against-minor-dominican-republic-tampa-bay-rays/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Tampa Bay Rays star shortstop Wander Franco has been formally charged with sexual abuse and sexual exploitation against a minor in the Dominican Republic ... for a relationship he allegedly had with a 14-year-old girl. Franco, who's now 23, has…</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 15:10:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Winston-Salem Dash pay tribute to Windy City with Italian Beef alternate</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/10/winston-salem-dash-pay-tribute-to-windy-city-with-italian-beef-alternate/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Winston-Salem, North Carolina, is not exactly known for its Italian beef, but the High-A Winston-Salem Dash will wear jerseys featuring the sandwiches later this season. Italian beef sandwiches—made of slow roasted beef and giardiniera, an Italian relish of pickled vegetables—are a signature food item in Chicago, where the Dash’s parent</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 15:18:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>George Stephanopoulos Says Biden Can't Serve Another 4 Years</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/09/george-stephanopoulos-president-joe-biden-cant-serve-4-more-years-sidewalk-election/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>6:28 PM PT -- George Stephanopoulos tells TMZ in a statement from his rep, "Earlier today, I responded to a question from a passerby. I shouldn't have." An ABC spokesperson tells TMZ, "George expressed his own point of view and not the position of…</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 15:10:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lehigh Valley IronPigs City Connect series to highlight Bethlehem, PA</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/10/lehigh-valley-ironpigs-city-connect-series-to-highlight-bethlehem-pa/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Triple-A Lehigh Valley IronPigs’ “City Connect” series pays tribute to three Pennsylvania towns, Allentown, Bethlehem, and Easton, over the course of three seasons. Last year the first installment highlighted the famous strawberry pie at the Allentown department store Hess. This year the team will honor the “Christmas City” of</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 14:55:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Barron Trump Makes Debut at His Father's Rally for President</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/10/barron-trump-appearance-debut-rally-campaign-donald-biden-florida-doral/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Barron Trump made a surprise appearance at his father's campaign rally in Florida Tuesday night, and he quickly became the crowd favorite ... even briefly overshadowing The Donald. 18-year-old Barron was sitting in the front row near the stage…</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 15:10:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Portland Sea Dogs to play as Maine Lobster Bakes</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/10/portland-sea-dogs-to-play-as-maine-lobster-bakes/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Double-A Portland Sea Dogs will pay tribute to one of their home state’s oldest and largest industries when they play as the Maine Lobster Bakes later this season. Per the team, the state of Maine harvests more than 100 million pounds of lobster every year—roughly 90 percent of the</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 14:14:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Competitive Eater Nick Wehry Accused Of Cheating In Hot Dog Contest, Denies Claim</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/10/competitive-eater-nick-wehry-accused-cheating-hot-dog-contest-denies-claim/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Competitive eater Nick Wehry -- husband of women's champ Miki Sudo -- is facing bombshell allegations stemming from this year's hot dog contest ... being accused of cheating to increase his end result. This year's fourth-place finisher was…</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 15:10:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>