<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 06:36:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Is the 1% Rule Dead? + Why Building (NOT Buying) Could Make You More</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-953</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Could building houses make you more money than buying existing ones? When should someone use the 1% rule in real estate, and when does this metric point to a cash […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 07:02:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sona, a frontline workforce management platform, raises $27.5M with eyes on US expansion</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/14/sona-a-frontline-workforce-management-platform-raises-27-5m-with-eyes-on-us-expansion/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Sona, a workforce management platform for frontline employees, has raised $27.5 million in a Series A round of funding. More than two-thirds of the U.S. workforce are reportedly in frontline jobs, which might be anything from customer service and healthcare to retail environments and hospitality. But managing this vast workforce, ensuring roles are filled and […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When Bad Cops Become Private Security Guards</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/11/police-private-guard-florida-chicago</link><description>There’s growing evidence that former officers with troubling histories of abuse can easily find second careers in private security.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 7-Hour Itch: 3 Women With Eczema Describe the Ways They Combat Nighttime Flare-Ups</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/seven-hour-itch-women-eczema-combat-nighttime-flares?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Three women with eczema describe how they combat nighttime flare-ups.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 09:09:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Small Business Owner’s Guide to Taxes, LLCs, Deductions, &amp; Audit Risks</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-528</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Starting your first or next business? This episode is for you. Today, we’re bringing you everything you need to know about small business taxes for beginners. Whether you’re a solo […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 07:01:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Uber to acquire Foodpanda’s Taiwan unit from Delivery Hero for $950M in cash</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/14/uber-to-acquire-foodpandas-taiwan-unit-from-delivery-hero-for-950m-in-cash/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Uber Technologies announced Tuesday that it will buy the Taiwan unit of Delivery Hero’s Foodpanda for $950 million in cash. The deal is part of Uber Eats’ strategy to expand in Asia, specifically by strengthening its position in Taiwan. On the other hand, it also underscores Delivery Hero’s ongoing retreat from that same market: the sale […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 10:37:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Rare Bright Spot for a Canine Lover Doing Time: Raising Puppies to Become Service Dogs</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/10/service-dogs-training-prison-essay</link><description>Adam Roberts reflects on the highs and occasional lows of training Labrador retrievers for the Puppies Behind Bars program.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Mother’s Love: The Challenges of Parenting a Child With Eczema</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/mothers-love-challenges-parenting-child-eczema?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Two moms reveal the great lengths they went to in their determination to give their children relief and good health.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 09:18:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Exactly Does a Property Management Company Do?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/what-does-a-property-management-company-do</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>A property management company plays a vital role in overseeing the daily operations of rental properties to ensure efficient tenant management while maximizing profitability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 22:13:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paris-based VC firm Blisce launches climate tech fund with a target of $160M</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/14/paris-based-vc-firm-blisce-launches-climate-technology-fund/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Paris-based Blisce has become the latest VC firm to launch a fund dedicated to climate tech. It plans to raise as much as €150M (about $162M). © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 09:23:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Marshall Project Wins the Dart Award for “The Mercy Workers”</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/06/the-marshall-project-wins-the-dart-award-for-the-mercy-workers</link><description>Our feature on mitigation specialists who help save people from the death penalty was recognized for making “significant contributions to public understanding of trauma-related issues.”</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Working It Out: How to Minimize Eczema Flare-ups at the Gym and on the Job</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/minimize-eczema-flare-ups-gym-job?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Three keys to managing your eczema at the gym and then heading off to a productive and itch-free workday.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 07:30:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>21 Smart Ways to Save on College Tuition Costs and Keep Money For Other Investments</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/ways-to-save-on-college-tuition-costs</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Use these practical tips to make paying for college a bit easier for you and your family.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 14:41:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maad raises $3.2M seed amid B2B e-commerce sector turbulence in Africa</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/13/maad-raises-3-2-seed-fundin/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Maad, a B2B e-commerce startup based in Senegal, has secured $3.2 million debt-equity funding to bolster its growth in the western Africa country and to explore fresh opportunities in the wider Francophone region. The seed round was led by Ventures Platform, with participation from Seedstars International Ventures, Reflect Ventures, Oui Capital, Launch Africa, Voltron Capital […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 04:44:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weinstein Ruling Poses Quandary: Can #MeToo Coexist With Protections for Defendants?</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/04/sex-crimes-weinstein-me-too</link><description>Proving sex crimes often requires evidence that is generally excluded to protect the rights of the accused.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cows Are Potential Spreaders of Bird Flu to Humans</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/food-recipes/food-poisoning/news/20240510/cows-are-potential-spreaders-bird-flu-humans?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Cow udders have the same receptors for flu viruses as humans and birds, raising concerns that cows could become “mixing vessels” that help the bird flu virus spread between people.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 19:36:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Homeowners Are Slashing Prices In This Popular Region—Is There a Golden Opportunity For Investors?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/floridas-gulf-coast-homeowners-are-slashing-prices-according-to-report</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Inventory rose by a staggering 50% year over year in this popular state. Time to strike while the iron's hot?</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 14:10:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OpenAI Startup Fund raises additional $5M</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/13/openai-startup-fund-raises-additional-5m/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The fresh funds were raised from two investors who transferred the capital into a special purpose vehicle, a legal entity associated with the OpenAI Startup Fund. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 01:24:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mississippi Lawmakers Considered Modest Public Defense Reforms. They Rejected All of Them.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/02/mississippi-public-defense-legislative-reforms</link><description>With its refusal to impose oversight or consistent standards in local defense, Mississippi risks falling further behind rest of the U.S., critics say.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Age-Related Macular Degeneration: Putting a Hole in Our World</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/eye-health/news/20240510/age-related-macular-degeneration-putting-hole-our-world?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Estimates show that by 2040, age-related macular degeneration may affect nearly 300 million people worldwide. And we are very limited in our ability to treat or prevent it. Here's what to know.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 19:31:18 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>