<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 00:44:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Sustainability Reporting: Navigating Assurance Practices</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/17/sustainability-reporting-navigating-assurance-practices/</link><description>Don't be lulled into a false sense of security by the word "assurance" when evaluating sustainability reports. Assurance practices vary, and investors would be wise to learn more about the different levels of coverage.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 17:57:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Benny Gantz threatens to leave Israel’s war cabinet if Netanyahu doesn’t meet demands, warning against ‘path of fanatics’ that will lead to the ‘abyss’</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/18/benny-gantz-israel-war-cabinet-benjamin-netanyahu-gaza-hamas/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1419872476-e1716086880673.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>“Personal and political considerations began to penetrate the Holy of Holies — Israel’s security.”</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 04:04:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Power of Clicks, Likes, and Shares: Promote the Right Kind of Financial Content</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/16/the-power-of-clicks-likes-and-shares-promote-the-right-kind-of-financial-content/</link><description>Not all financial content creators on social media are created equal. A broad differentiation can be made between influencers, knowledge sharers, and aspiring thought leaders.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 14:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bankrupt crypto lender Genesis gets OK to return billions in tokens and cash to creditors, meaning parent firm DCG ‘is out of the money’</title><link>https://fortune.com/crypto/2024/05/18/bankrupt-crypto-lender-genesis-return-billions-bitcoin-tokens-creditors-dcg/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1475394879-e1716076256193.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>“Given the size of the creditor claims, DCG is out of the money as an equity holder by billions of dollars,” Judge Lane said.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 01:07:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why the New T+1 Settlement Cycle Matters: A Global Index Provider’s Perspective</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/14/why-the-new-t1-settlement-cycle-matters-a-global-index-providers-perspective/</link><description>Shorter settlement periods are meant to protect market participants. But the new T+1 settlement cycle for US equities may have undesirable knock-on effects for financial market participants around the world, including index fund managers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 16:54:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aging while exercising? Great. Just be sure to reevaluate your routine.</title><link>https://fortune.com/well/article/workout-as-you-age/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1254783748_4fe5fc-e1715964080270.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>“We need to think about changing the program to be effective and to be safe," notes one expert.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Leveraging AI to Identify and Predict Financial Crises</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/13/leveraging-ai-to-identify-and-predict-financial-crises/</link><description>Despite some current limitations, AI stands to offer significant advantages versus traditional approaches to identifying and predicting financial crises.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 14:39:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>An oil tanker going from Russia to China is hit by a Houthi missile in the Red Sea, U.S. military says</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/18/oil-tanker-russia-china-iran-houthi-rebels-missile-red-sea-israel-hamas/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2065827955-e1716073906569.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The strike Saturday on the Greek-owned M/T Wind caused flooding that knocked out its propulsion and steering, which the crew restored.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 00:23:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Your Portfolio Should Include Scarce Assets</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/10/why-your-portfolio-should-include-scarce-assets/</link><description>Portfolios that include both productive and scarce assets can deliver similar performance to the S&amp;P 500 with less risk than those that hold only productive assets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:34:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Some NYU students being disciplined for protests must reflect on a ‘Simpsons’ episode: ‘What, if anything, could Lisa have done or thought about to make better decisions?’</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/18/nyu-students-israel-gaza-hamas-protests-discipline-the-simpsons-lisa-simpson/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1074338030-e1716072038771.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>One workbook has a section based on an episode of “The Simpsons” in which Lisa uncharacteristically cheats on a test and is wracked by guilt.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 23:54:22 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>