<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 06:57:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>7 Exciting Film and TV Adaptations of Books Out this October!</title><link>https://bookriot.com/book-adaptations-out-this-october/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/tv-adaptations.png</image_url><description>Which of these will you be watching?</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>With shares at 10-year lows, Assassin's Creed maker Ubisoft faces questions over its future</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/10/01/assassins-creed-maker-ubisoft-ubi-faces-questions-over-its-future.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Gaming firm Ubisoft is facing questions over its future amid a lackluster games pipeline and pressure from an activist investor to sell itself and go private.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 11:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 565</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-565/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-565</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>The changing nature of the labor market mandates that job seekers adjust their strategies. Whether it be changes in technology used by recruiters (and job seekers), return to office, or the economy in general – adapt and adjust! In this week’s Summary you’ll learn about: If you enjoyed any of these articles, feel free to […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 565 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 11:57:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Power of Words: Benefits of Conversations with Toddlers for Self-Development</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/benefits-of-conversations-with-toddlers/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=benefits-of-conversations-with-toddlers</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Children learn a lot about themselves through daily conversations with caregivers. When caregivers talk to toddlers about their own bodies, thoughts, and feelings, they give them opportunities to attend to themselves. Mothers from Canada and Vanuatu differ in how they talk to their toddlers about these matters. These cultural differences may […] The post The Power of Words: Benefits of Conversations with Toddlers for Self-Development appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 09:37:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>No-Bake Pumpkin Cheesecake</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/no-bake-pumpkin-cheesecake/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Delicious no-bake pumpkin cheesecake topped off with whipped cream is the perfect fall dessert. It has a creamy cheesecake filling…</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Clean A Stainless Steel Sink</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/how-to-clean-a-stainless-steel-sink/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>This simple method for cleaning a stainless steel sink is quite literally my favorite household cleaning task. I am not exaggerating. It is SO easy, SO simple, and SO SO SO effective. It requires no special or harsh cleaners and will restore your sink to its original sparkle within minutes. Sherry tried this method first and we have both loved using it ever since. I even taught our kids how to do it. But honestly, it's so satisfying to do that I usually keep it to myself. Continue reading How To Clean A Stainless Steel Sink at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 16:26:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fall Discoveries At Walmart</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/10/fall-discoveries-at-walmart/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Thank you to Walmart for sponsoring this post. Embrace new fall discoveries at Walmart, featuring the latest selections perfectly timed… The post Fall Discoveries At Walmart appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 05:00:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>It’s Spooky (Mulder) Reading Season! 8 Exciting New SFF Books Out October 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/new-sci-fi-and-fantasy-books-october-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/off-center-collage-1.png</image_url><description>Which new SFF reads are you most excited about?</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PayPal CEO's first year praised by Wall Street — hard part begins for struggling payments company</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/10/01/paypal-ceo-alex-chriss-first-year-praised-by-wall-street-stock-pop-q3.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>PayPal CEO Alex Chriss just wrapped up his first year on the job, and his company's stock had its best quarterly performance since 2020.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 564</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-564/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-564</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>There are fewer jobs posted in most industries, but that doesn’t mean you should stop looking. Diversify your job search beyond the job boards! Be proactive, not reactive! Obviously, LinkedIn is a great place to start! In this week’s issue of Summary Sunday, you’ll find: There are some very talented and smart people writing and […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 564 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 14:02:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When Violence Hits a College Campus: How Parents Can Support Students, Even from Afar</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/when-violence-hits-a-college-campus/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=when-violence-hits-a-college-campus</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Although parents may try to shelter their children from collective tragedy, at some point, children of all ages will be exposed, personally or via peers, news, or family. Parents need to talk with their children (whether preschoolers, college-aged students, or somewhere in between) about such events and listen to their children’s […] The post When Violence Hits a College Campus: How Parents Can Support Students, Even from Afar appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 01:18:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Meal Plan #20</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/weekly-meal-plan-20/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>This week’s meal plan has a wide variety of meals and I made sure there was something for everyone! My…</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Refinishing Hardwood Floors 101</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/floor-refinishing-101/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>We’ve refinished hardwood floors in 5 of the 6 homes we’ve owned. That doesn’t make us professional floor refinishers, but as homeowners and DIYers, we’ve developed expertise for what to expect, what pitfalls to look out for, and how much refinishing your hardwood floors might cost. So in this post, we’ll answer all of your hardwood floor refinishing FAQs along with some before and after photos of our various projects! Continue reading Refinishing Hardwood Floors 101 at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 19:33:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shopbop Style Event Is On</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/09/shopbop-style-event-is-on/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Outfit Details: Veronica Beard Top, Levi’s Jeans, Rohe Jacket, Earrings &amp; Similar Heels Here &amp; Here The Shopbop Style Event is… The post Shopbop Style Event Is On appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 05:00:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Bestselling Books of the Week, According to All the Lists</title><link>https://bookriot.com/bestselling-books-september-30-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/tan-skinned-person-with-long-black-straight-hair-reading-a-book-in-front-of-a-book-stores-shelves.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>What's the last book you bought?</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 19:12:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NATO's new chief will have to confront threats outside the alliance — and within</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/10/01/mark-rutte-will-have-to-confront-threats-within-and-outside-nato.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>As Mark Rutte becomes NATO's new General Secretary, his leadership skills will be put to the test quickly as the bloc confronts external and internal threats.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 10:53:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 563</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-563/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-563</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Job Search requires multiple skills. From writing to interviewing to branding to strategizing. You can find a little bit of each of these in this week’s Summary Sunday. Here’s what you’ll find in this week’s Summary: There are really smart and talented people below! I highly encourage you to subscribe to their newsletters, and/or follow […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 563 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 13:11:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How parents can support math learning at home and through everyday activities</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/how-parents-can-support-math-learning-at-home/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=how-parents-can-support-math-learning-at-home</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Math skills at kindergarten entry predict children’s academic success in school. Young children usually enjoy learning math and can develop understanding about math in all the content areas they will encounter in school: number, patterns, shapes, spatial relations, and data. Parents can grow their young children’s math knowledge through playful activities […] The post How parents can support math learning at home and through everyday activities appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 23:18:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cowboy Chicken</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/cowboy-chicken/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>This cowboy chicken recipe is packed with bold flavors. The chicken is seared with lots of vibrant seasonings, surrounded by…</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2025 Color of the Year – Everything We Know So Far…</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/2025-color-of-the-year-guide/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Believe it or not, many companies have announced their 2025 Color of the Year! Since we love tracking and predicting these selections each year, we thought we’d start a post to keep track of each selection as they come out. This will be much easier to reference next year when we make our predictions instead of Googling around to find them all again. Will blue be big again like it was in 2024? Will any of our guesses even be remotely close? You can read below to follow along – and check back for updates as more COTY news rolls in. And just like we did in our 2024 Color of the Year round-up , we’ll compare each company’s past picks. That way you can see what’s trending for 2025, as well as how their color forecasts have evolved over time. So far things are shaping up to be pretty deep, moody, and muted… What is the 2025 Color of the Year? Continue reading 2025 Color of the Year – Everything We Know So Far… at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amazon Sundays</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/09/amazon-sundays-9-22-24/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Outfit Details: Amazon Top, Levi Jeans, Gucci Loafers Welcome to Amazon Sundays, where I’m sharing this week’s curated selection of finds for… The post Amazon Sundays appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 05:00:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meryl Streep Attached to Star in TV Adaptation of Franzen’s THE CORRECTIONS</title><link>https://bookriot.com/meryl-streep-attached-to-star-in-tv-adaptation-of-franzens-the-corrections/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/Untitled-8.png</image_url><description>Welcome to Today in Books, our daily round-up of literary headlines at the intersection of politics, culture, media, and more. ...</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 18:36:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tuesday's analyst calls: Ford Motor gets an upgrade, Alphabet to rally nearly 30%</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/10/01/analyst-calls-all-the-market-moving-wall-street-chatter-from-tuesday.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description></description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 10:48:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Start with A Plan to Grow Your Network</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/start-with-a-plan-to-grow-your-network/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=start-with-a-plan-to-grow-your-network</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>You’ve heard people tell you to network your way to a new job. But that seems easier said than done. You need a plan to grow your network. Maybe you don’t have a network or you don’t like to network or perhaps you don’t know how to network. Before you worry about any of this, […] The post Start with A Plan to Grow Your Network appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 20:32:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Do infants feel excluded? Early signs and why it matters</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/do-infants-feel-excluded/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=do-infants-feel-excluded</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Social exclusion harms individuals of all ages, leading to feelings of loneliness, decreased self-esteem, and even changes in brain activity. Humans’ ability to recognize and react to social exclusion emerges early, suggesting the importance of considering and addressing ostracism even when caring for very young children. Babies are sensitive to social […] The post Do infants feel excluded? Early signs and why it matters appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 01:37:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mozzarella Stuffed Meatballs</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/mozzarella-stuffed-meatballs/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Mozzarella Stuffed Meatballs take classic meatballs to the next level! Tender and juicy with melty cheese on the inside. Serve…</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Every Color of the Year 2024 – All In One Place!</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/2024-color-of-the-year-guide/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Guessing the Color of the Year is one of our favorite pastimes. We did it for years on our podcast and now we keep up the tradition on Instagram Stories . And every time the next COTY announcement season rolls aroun d , we like to see all of the previous picks in one easy place. So here’s a snapshot of not only every 2024 Color of the Year, but also how they compare to each company’s previous selections. Buckle up, fellow color nerds! As more and more companies jump on the color forecasting bandwagon, we’ve decided to focus on the major paint and color companies in the post. Many brands also release yearly palettes instead of one single color. For simplicity’s sake, we’ve omitted those as well. So apologies if we’ve missed your favorite niche paint brand below. Continue reading Every Color of the Year 2024 – All In One Place! at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 17:35:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Beautiful Bags</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/09/beautiful-bags/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Outfit Details: Dries Van Noten Dress, Miu Miu Heels (similar, less expensive here), Savette Bag, Hermes Bracelets (similar, less expensive here) As the leaves begin… The post Beautiful Bags appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 05:00:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Riot’s Deals of the Day for September 30, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/book-riots-deals-of-the-day-for-september-30-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/deals-93024.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>Here's a big batch of deals for your Monday morning, all for $4 or less</description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 17:42:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Euro zone inflation falls to 1.8% in September, below the European Central Bank's 2% target</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/10/01/euro-zone-inflation-september-2024.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Euro zone inflation fell to 1.8%, below the European Central Bank's target rate, in September, flash data from statistics agency Eurostat showed Tuesday.</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 10:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 562</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-562/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-562</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Artificial Intelligence is impacting the lives of recruiters and job seekers – in positive ways. However, at the end of the day, people hire people. Job seekers need current tech skills AND human skills. In this week’s Summary Sunday you’ll find: There are really smart and talented people below! I highly encourage you to subscribe […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 562 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 12:31:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10 Actions Parents Can Take to Help their Children Be More Resilient in a World of Adversity</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/10-actions-to-help-children-be-more-resilient/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=10-actions-to-help-children-be-more-resilient</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Decades of research points to specific ways parents can build resilience that can help protect children from the challenges of adverse experiences and stress. Strategies include parent-focused tips such as practicing self care, reflecting on one’s own past experiences, and developing emotional control. Additional strategies focus on ways to navigate relationships […] The post 10 Actions Parents Can Take to Help their Children Be More Resilient in a World of Adversity appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 02:36:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Louisiana Casserole</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/louisiana-casserole/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>This delicious Louisiana Casserole has become an instant favorite in our house! It has all of the delicious flavors of…</description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Get Rid Of Fruit Flies</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/how-to-get-rid-of-fruit-flies/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Got little bugs buzzing around your kitchen? Congratulations, you may have fruit flies! Don't fret. These annoying pests are pretty common but luckily, it doesn't take a lot of money, supplies, or effort to get rid of them. In fact, you can probably find everything you need in your cabinets! We recently had a fruit fly problem in our home (the first time in over four years here - we have no idea what brought them in). So I seized the opportunity to test 7 different methods of eliminating them. Yes, there were copious notes taken and even a spreadsheet. So today I'm sharing the best fruit fly traps and how to make them. Continue reading How To Get Rid Of Fruit Flies at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 16:08:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>All About Amazon Accessories</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/09/all-about-amazon-accessories/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>This season, embrace the rich palette and textures of fall with a curated selection of accessories from Amazon. These pieces… The post All About Amazon Accessories appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 05:00:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>