<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 06:57:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>New England Patriots Subtly Reveal New Secondary Logo</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/09/new-england-patriots-subtly-reveal-new-secondary-logo/football/</link><description>Following a recent visit to Gillette Stadium, former New England Patriots linebacker Brandon Spikes posted a photo of what appears to be the franchise’s new secondary logo prominently displayed inside the facility.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 20:58:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Glen 'Big Baby' Davis Cracks Jokes After Prison Sentence, Gonna Get In Shape!</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/09/glen-davis-big-baby-sentenced-fraud-months-prison-nba/</link><description>1:29 PM PT -- Glen "Big Baby" Davis isn't crying over his lengthy prison sentence ... going to Instagram Live to crack jokes at his own expense -- but also pointing out there are a few positives that'll come out of his time behind bars. Davis made…</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 06:57:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PWHL Announces Bauer as Jersey Partner for 2024-25</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/09/pwhl-announces-bauer-as-jersey-partner-for-2024-25/hockey-2/</link><description>The Professional Women’s Hockey League announced today that Bauer Hockey will serve as the PWHL’s exclusive jersey partner, supplying game and replica jerseys for all six teams in the league, beginning with the 2024-25 season. “Bauer is a leader in supporting the performance needs of the league and many of</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 17:40:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Real Housewives' Star Dorit Kemsley &amp; Husband PK Announce Split</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/09/real-housewives-beverly-hills-dorit-kemsley-husband-pk-split-separation/</link><description>3:20 PM PT -- We got PK Thursday in West Hollywood at The Henry right on the heels of the news of him and Dorit Kemsley separating -- and while we tried asking how he was feeling ... the guy wasn't in any mood to talk, beelining it for a restaurant…</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 06:57:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Utah NHL Team Releases 20 Possible Names, Fan Vote Begins</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/08/utah-nhl-team-releases-20-possible-names-fan-vote-begins/hockey-2/</link><description>Utah’s new NHL franchise has released its list of twenty team names it is considering for its inaugural 2024-25 season. Fans can vote for up to four of the twenty finalists on their ballot but can only cast one ballot. Voting starts tonight and will conclude after two weeks on</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 02:38:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Taylor Swift Makes Big Changes to 'Eras' Tour, Kicks Off European Leg</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/09/taylor-swift-makes-changes-eras-tour-kicks-off-european-leg-paris/</link><description>Taylor Swift is shaking things up for the start of the European leg of her 'Eras' tour ... introducing a slew of changes for the new shows, and her fans absolutely love it. The singer kicked off the new dates for her record-breaking tour with a…</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 06:57:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Burnley FC Leave Umbro, Sign Kit Deal With Castore</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/08/burnley-fc-leave-umbro-sign-kit-deal-with-castore/soccer/</link><description>Burnley currently in Premier League relegation zone; if they stay up, they'll be one of two clubs in England's top flight outfitted by Castore</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 17:46:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rapper Toosii Roasts Shaq For DMs to Baby Mom, Posts Receipts</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/09/rapper-toosii-roasts-shaq-for-dming-pregnant-baby-mom-posts-receipts/</link><description>Shaquille O'Neal's making waves for splashing around with his much younger GF ... which is his MO, according to "Favorite Song" rapper Toosii, who has a bone to pick with the NBA legend!!! Toosii must have gotten triggered by recent snaps of Shaq…</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 06:57:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Report: Brazil Could Ditch Nike as Kit Supplier After Receiving Massive Offer</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/07/report-brazil-could-ditch-nike-as-kit-supplier-after-receiving-massive-offer/soccer/</link><description>Brazilian news outlet reports CBF has received an offer worth more than five times what Nike currently pays them from either Adidas or Puma</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:29:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sydney Sweeney Can't Wait to Transform Her Body to Play Female Boxer</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/09/sydney-sweeney-cant-wait-transform-body-play-female-boxer-movie/</link><description>Sydney Sweeney is all set to play a famous female boxer -- something she says she can't wait to morph into ... so, get ready to see her way differently than what you're used to! The actress has been tapped to play brawler Christy Martin in a new…</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 06:57:18 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>