<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 06:53:32 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Real Estate Bookkeeping: A Crash Course for Getting Your Financials in Check</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-439</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Real estate bookkeeping is one of the tedious but necessary tasks that comes with owning a rental property. Unsurprisingly, it’s one of the things that can make or break your […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 07:02:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bumble and Hinge allowed stalkers to pinpoint users’ locations down to 2 meters, researchers say</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/31/bumble-and-hinge-allowed-stalkers-to-pinpoint-users-locations-down-to-2-meters-researchers-say/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>Badoo, Bumble, Grindr, happn, Hinge and Hily all had the same flaw that could have helped a malicious user to identify the near-exact location of another user. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What It Means to ‘Willie Horton’ a Political Candidate</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/31/willie-horton-donald-trump-kamala-harris</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>Donald Trump supporters run their version of the original dog-whistle attack ad against Kamala Harris. Here’s the history.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Create Multiple Streams of Income Through Real Estate Investing</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-998</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>If you know how to create multiple streams of income, you can build wealth FAST. Thankfully, real estate has dozens (if not hundreds) of ways to make money, and there’s […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 07:02:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tiger Global partner Alex Cook to leave firm, sources say</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/30/tiger-global-partner-alex-cook-to-leave-firm-sources-say/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>Alex Cook, a partner at Tiger Global who oversaw some of its largest fintech investments and India deals, is departing the firm after a tenure of nearly seven years, three people familiar with the matter told TechCrunch. Cook has briefed multiple people around him about his departure news in recent days, although he hasn’t explained […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 04:50:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Courts Cleared Jaleel Stallings. Trump’s Campaign Pulled Him Back Into the Political Muck.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/31/trump-election-kamala-harris-jaleel-stallings</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>Stallings was acquitted after an encounter with police during George Floyd protests in 2020, and one officer pleaded guilty to assaulting him.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seeing Greene: Keep or Sell? What to Do When Your Rental Doesn’t Cash Flow</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-997</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>Should you move to invest in real estate? Perhaps you’re stranded in a pricey market or an area with unfavorable landlord-tenant laws. Depending on your career, you could earn a […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:02:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OpenAI endorses Senate bills that could shape America’s AI policy</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/30/openai-endorses-senate-bills-that-could-shape-americas-ai-policy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>A lot of AI bills are flying around Congress these days, and OpenAI is throwing its weight behind some of them. OpenAI endorsed three Senate bills on Tuesday which could shape the federal government’s stance on artificial intelligence. One of the bills – the Future of AI Innovation Act – would formally authorize the United […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 04:43:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Company Promised to Improve Health Care in Jails. Dozens of Its Patients Have Died.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/30/oklahoma-jail-turn-key-health-deaths</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Turn Key Health Clinics has quickly expanded to jails in 10 states. Some of its policies and practices have endangered patients.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 11:00:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How My Home Makes Me an Extra $1,400/Month (EVEN In an Expensive Market)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-550</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>Wouldn’t it be nice if your home paid for itself? Every month, you throw a substantial sum of money towards your rent or mortgage payment, but what if you could […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 07:01:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lineaje raises $20M to help organizations combat software supply chain threats</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/30/lineaje-raises-20m-to-help-organizations-combat-software-supply-chain-threats/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>The software supply chain faces threats from all sides. A 2024 report by the Ponemon Institute found that over half of organizations have experienced a software supply chain attack, with 54% having experienced one within the past year. Supply chain attacks typically target services from third-party vendors or open source software that make up a […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 00:35:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What These Decisions Tell Us About Kamala Harris’ Approach to Criminal Justice</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/27/kamala-harris-prosecutor-california-police-election-crime</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>From the death penalty to school truancy and diversion programs, here are some key steps Harris took as a district attorney and attorney general.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>My First Big-Time Deal Failed. Here’s Why I’m Happy About It.</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/my-first-syndication-deal-failed-here-is-why-im-happy-about-it</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>I finally got my feet wet with a syndication deal, and it didn't go so well.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 20:44:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SEC charges BitClout founder Nader Al-Naji with fraud; says proceeds paid for L.A. mansion, gifts</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/30/sec-charged-crypto-founder-bitclout-startup-backed-by-a16z-sequoia/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>The founder of once-hyped crypto startup BitClout is facing trouble. On Tuesday, the SEC charged him with fraud and other offenses. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 20:56:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Love Beyond Bars: Raymond and Cassandra</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/26/photo-essay-raymond-flanks-wrongful-conviction</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>Raymond Flanks spent nearly 39 years in Louisiana lockups for a murder he didn’t commit. Luckily, he found love with an old friend, Cassandra Delpit.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 11:00:40 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>