<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 07:28:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The Million-Dollar Real Estate Business YOU Can Start Today with Just $150</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-433</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Starting a real estate business is one of the best ways to achieve financial freedom, replace your W2 income, and leave your nine-to-five. Why? Because you don’t need a ton […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 07:02:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kandji raises another $100M for Apple device management as valuation rises to $850M</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/17/kandji-raises-another-100m-for-apple-device-management-as-valuation-rises-to-850m/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>At a time when many startups have struggled to raise money and keep their heads above water, Kandji, an Apple device management platform, has been an exception. Founded in 2019, it has raced through its funding rounds like a precocious child, raising over $188 million along the way. Today it added to that total with […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How a Supreme Court Ruling Could Affect a Case Involving Police Abuse of Youth</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/13/supreme-court-bankruptcy-sackler-boy-scouts</link><description>Another court must now decide how the landmark ruling will impact the Boy Scouts abuse settlement, which involves victims of police sexual abuse.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2 Real Estate Markets We’re Investing in Now (Should You?)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-990</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>In this episode, we’re sharing two of the real estate markets we’re investing in NOW. One you may have heard of and one you probably haven’t. Both have strong long-term […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 07:02:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Matera raises $100M from Warburg Pincus to help the US catch up to Brazil in instant payments</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/17/matera-raises-100m-from-warburn-pincus-to-help-the-u-s-catch-up-to-brazil-in-instant-payments/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>To say that Pix, the instant payment system created by the Central Bank of Brazil, has been a resounding success is an understatement. With Pix, money moves directly between core banking systems of different financial institutions. Adoption has been widespread and ubiquitous. The country’s residents have the ability to even pay street vendors using the […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jackson, Mississippi, Wants Curfew Centers to Cut Crime. Here’s What Other Cities Learned.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/09/jackson-mississippi-youth-curfew-centers</link><description>After a teen’s murder, city officials hope a curfew and youth centers will get kids off the street. Young people are skeptical.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 11:00:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seeing Greene: Investing with High DTI, When to Refi, &amp; Getting Out of Debt</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-989</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Life happens, and you’ve accumulated some debt. You’re wondering how to buy real estate EVEN with a high DTI (debt-to-income) ratio. Whether it’s good debt, like rental property mortgages, or […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 07:02:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Local experience discovery startup, Bigfoot, adds GenAI to fast-track weekend planning</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/17/local-experience-discovery-startup-bigfoot-adds-genai-to-fast-track-weekend-planning/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Can generative AI substitute for having a social graph? California-based local experiences discovery startup Bigfoot is hoping the addition of a conversational interface to its weekend planner website — in the form of an AI chatbot it’s branding Littlefoot which launched last week — will give it a more personalized feel while making it easier […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 11:09:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Love Beyond Bars: Miguel and Silvia</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/05/photo-essay-wrongful-conviction-love-story</link><description>While Miguel Solorio did 25 years for a crime he didn’t commit, his wife, Silvia, was right by his side. Here’s their California love story in pictures.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From a Negative Net Worth to FI in Just 5 Years by Living Like a Stoic</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-546</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>The road to financial independence isn’t always linear, but stoicism might be the secret ingredient that keeps you on track. This ancient philosophy gets a bad rap, but with its […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 07:01:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tinder’s AI Photo Selector automatically picks the best photos for your dating profile</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/17/tinder-ai-photo-selection-feature-launches/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Tinder revealed last year that it was testing a photo-selection feature that uses AI to help users choose the best photos for their dating profiles. Now dubbed “Photo Selector,” the Match-owned dating app officially launched the feature on Wednesday. It’s now available to all users in the U.S. and will roll out to international markets […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Crime Rates and the 2024 Election: What You Need to Know</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/27/trump-and-biden-spar-over-crime-rates-ahead-of-their-debate-what-do-we-really-know</link><description>As crime data again becomes a flashpoint in the presidential campaign, experts push for better national statistics.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Resident Turnover Challenge: 5 Retention Strategies for Single-Family Rentals</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/strategies-for-better-single-family-rental-tenant-retention</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Every investor wants 100% retention, but it's not as easy as you'd wish. Here are the best strategies for getting as close as possible to it.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 22:06:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Korean prosecutors file warrant to arrest Kakao founder for stock manipulation</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/17/korean-prosecutors-file-warrant-to-arrest-kakao-founder-for-stock-manipulation/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The warrant is part of an investigation into alleged stock market manipulation related to a high-profile bidding war for music label, SM Entertainment. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 09:13:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Death Row Prisoner’s Parting Interview</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/24/texas-death-row-prisoner-final-interview</link><description>Days before his scheduled execution in Texas, Ramiro Gonzales speaks on faith, legacy — and apologizing to the family of his victim, Bridget Townsend.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>