<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 06:57:09 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Rookie Reply: Preparing for a Market Crash, Ending Leases, &amp; Building Teams</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-445</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>As a new investor, a strong real estate team is crucial to your success—especially when you’re looking to land your first deal, complete your first rehab project, or invest out-of-state. […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 10:00:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>UK neobank Revolut valued at $45B after secondary market sale</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/16/uk-neobank-revolut-valued-at-45b-after-secondary-market-sale/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Revolut has confirmed a new valuation of $45 billion via a secondary market share sale, shortly after the U.K.-based neobank secured its own banking license in the U.K. and in Mexico. The news positions Revolut as one of Europe’s most valuable private tech companies. Founded out of London in 2015, Revolut is one of numerous […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:47:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FAQ: How The Marshall Project Is Covering the 2024 Election</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/16/election-faq-crime-politics</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Learn more about who we are and how we choose what political stories to cover.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BiggerNews: What Happens if the Housing Market Crashes (&amp; What Will Cause It)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-1005</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Recession fears are increasing. The stock market has taken substantial hits, housing inventory is climbing, and bank account balances are starting to fall. So, with more economic turmoil, we have […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 10:00:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ben Horowitz Declares War on Michael Moritz</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/15/ben-horowitz-declares-war-on-michael-moritz/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>A social media spat between billionaire tech investors is raising questions about the journalistic independence of three-year-old news outfit SF Standard, after a reporter representing the outlet reached out to sources for a story about VC Ben Horowitz and his wife Felicia. The Standard’s sole backer is another longtime VC, Michael Moritz, and on Thursday […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 05:31:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Mother on a Mission for Full Police Transparency</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/16/police-beating-ulysses-wilkerson-mother-video</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Troy, Alabama, police severely beat Ulysses Wilkerson when he was 17. Seven years later, his mom, Angela Williams, is still fighting for answers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Retiring Early Before 30 and Why You DON’T Need Millions for FIRE</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-555</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>This might be the fastest path to FIRE we’ve ever seen. In just two years, Emily and James were able to retire early and travel the world full-time. They didn’t […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 07:01:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>California AI bill SB 1047 aims to prevent AI disasters, but Silicon Valley warns it will cause one</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/15/california-ai-bill-sb-1047-aims-to-prevent-ai-disasters-but-silicon-valley-warns-it-will-cause-one/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>SB 1047 has drawn the ire of Silicon Valley players large and small, including venture capitalists, big tech trade groups, researchers and startup founders. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 00:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How the 1968 DNC in Chicago Devolved into ‘Unrestrained and Indiscriminate Police Violence’</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/14/chicago-dnc-protests-police-reforms</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>As protesters prepare for the Democratic National Convention in Chicago next week, a half-century old report provides lessons for preventing chaos.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 11:00:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Should Investors Do if Insurance Prices Keep Rising?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-243</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>We’re currently in a home insurance crisis. Everyone (except for Henry, apparently) is feeling the sting of home insurance prices rising significantly year after year. Some investors have seen their […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 10:00:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>California weakens bill to prevent AI disasters before final vote, taking advice from Anthropic</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/15/california-weakens-bill-to-prevent-ai-disasters-before-final-vote-taking-advice-from-anthropic/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>California’s bill to prevent AI disasters, SB 1047, has faced significant opposition from many parties in Silicon Valley. Today, California lawmakers bent slightly to that pressure, adding in several amendments suggested by AI firm Anthropic and other opponents. On Thursday the bill passed through California’s Appropriations Committee, a major step toward becoming law, with several […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 23:11:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aaron Sankin is The Marshall Project’s new Deputy Data Editor</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/13/aaron-sankin-is-the-marshall-projects-new-deputy-data-editor</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Sankin brings deep experience with ambitious data projects.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 20:00:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>It’s Never Too Early (or Late) to Build a Team of Deal Finders. Here’s How To.</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/building-a-team-of-deal-finders-in-real-estate-investing</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Deal finding is one of the most important parts of real estate investing, yet a lot of investors struggle to put it together. Here's how you can form a stellar team of finders.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 21:15:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meta axed CrowdTangle, a tool for tracking disinformation. Critics claim its replacement has just ‘1% of the features’</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/15/meta-shut-down-crowdtangle-a-tool-for-tracking-disinformation-heres-how-its-replacement-compares/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Journalists, researchers and politicians are mourning Meta’s shutdown of CrowdTangle, which they used to track the spread of disinformation on Facebook and Instagram. In CrowdTangle’s place, Meta is offering its Content Library — but is limiting usage to people from “qualified academic or nonprofit institutions who are pursuing scientific or public interest research.” Many researchers […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 21:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘Deliberate Indifference’: Court Rulings Challenge Extreme Heat Conditions in Prisons</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/10/texas-heat-louisiana-prison</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>“If it’s 103 outside, it may be 107 to -8 inside of your cell,” said a man who worked in the fields while imprisoned in Texas.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>