<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 02:03:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>5 Growth Strategies To Unlock True Financial Freedom</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/strategies-to-unlock-true-financial-freedom</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Even in an uncertain market, these strategies can help you achieve your FIRE goals.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:50:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anthropic looks to fund a new, more comprehensive generation of AI benchmarks</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/01/anthropic-looks-to-fund-a-new-more-comprehensive-generation-of-ai-benchmarks/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Anthropic is launching a program to fund the development of new types of benchmarks capable of evaluating the performance and impact of AI models, including generative models like its own Claude. Unveiled on Monday, Anthropic’s program will dole out payments to third-party organizations that can, as the company puts it in a blog post, “effectively […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 00:45:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Crime Rates and the 2024 Election: What You Need to Know</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/27/trump-and-biden-spar-over-crime-rates-ahead-of-their-debate-what-do-we-really-know</link><description>As crime data again becomes a flashpoint in the presidential campaign, experts push for better national statistics.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Federal Experts Talk Bird Flu ‘What Ifs’ in WebMD Live Event</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/cold-and-flu/news/20240516/federal-experts-talk-bird-flu-what-ifs?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>WebMD brought together experts from four federal agencies to talk prevention, monitoring, and what the “what ifs” of bird flu might look like.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:50:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Can You Invest In Passive Real Estate Investments as a Non-Accredited Investor?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/can-you-invest-in-passive-real-estate-without-being-accredited</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Syndications typically require accreditation, but are there other ways to passively invest?</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 15:07:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Senators urge owners, partners, and VC backers of fintech Synapse to restore customers’ access to their money</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/01/senators-urge-synapses-owners-partners-and-vc-funders-to-restore-customers-access-to-their-money/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>A group of senators has banded together to urge Synapse’s owners and bank and fintech partners to “immediately restore customers’ access to their money.” As part of their demands, the senators implicated both the partners and investors of the company as being responsible for missing customer funds. In a letter shared publicly on Monday, U.S. […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 23:49:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Death Row Prisoner’s Parting Interview</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/24/texas-death-row-prisoner-final-interview</link><description>Days before his scheduled execution in Texas, Ramiro Gonzales speaks on faith, legacy — and apologizing to the family of his victim, Bridget Townsend.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What’s Next in Health Care for Older Adults: Questions and Answers With John Whyte, MD</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/blog-aging-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>As WebMD’s chief medical officer, John Whyte, MD, is in a unique position to see both the current state of medical care for America’s older adults and the way things are trending for the future. We asked him to share his insight on a few topics, along with a bit of advice.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:29:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A New California Law Just Increased Regulations On Home Flippers</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/california-law-changes-disclosures-for-home-flippers</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>The new bill changes what flippers will have to disclose when they move to sell the property.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:56:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TechCrunch Space: Star spangled</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/01/techcrunch-space-star-spangled/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Hello and welcome back to TechCrunch Space. I hope everyone has a fantastic July 4 this week. Go eat a hot dog. Read my story from last week on the causes of Starliner’s additional delay and what it might mean for Boeing’s Starliner program. Want to reach out with a tip? Email Aria at aria.techcrunch@gmail.com […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The New Battle Over an Old Institution: Forced Prison Labor</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/22/prison-slavery-forced-labor-lawsuits-bills</link><description>Inside the latest legal and legislative efforts to close state constitutional loopholes that allow slavery as punishment for a crime.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Get the Care You Need in a COVID-19 World</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/covid-senior-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>What to expect at the doctor’s office, hospitals, and long-term care facilities, the future of telemedicine, and how to get the best care during COVID-19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 19:50:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Migration Boom is Ending, But Here’s Where Movers Are Still Moving</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/migration-report-q2-2024</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>The pandemic-induced migration boom is coming to an end, but the holdouts are still on the go.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:45:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spotify tests emergency alerts in Sweden</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/01/spotify-tests-emergency-alerts-in-sweden/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Music, podcasts, audiobooks…emergency alerts? Spotify’s latest test has the streaming app venturing into new territory with a test of an emergency alerts system in its home market of Sweden. According to code references found within the Spotify app, the company is considering a system that would help distribute public announcements related to things like “accidents, […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 22:41:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mississippi Wants to Allow Some Votes From Jails and Prisons. Red Tape May Stop It.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/20/mississippi-voting-from-prison-and-jails</link><description>A new state law will allow more people in jails and prisons to cast absentee ballots, but many obstacles remain.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Personal Shopper: A Savvy Black Entrepreneur Guides You to Eczema-Friendly Clothes, Creams, Cosmetics, and More</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/savvy-black-entrepreneur-guides-eczema-friendly-clothes-creams-cosmetics?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>A savvy black entrepreneur guides you on an eczema-friendly shopping spree.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:54:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Post-Pandemic Demand Boomerangs Back to Cities, What Should Investors Do? w/Richard Barkham</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-230</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>“Super cities” are seeing a massive comeback in demand—one that most investors thought was impossible. With work-from-home being scaled back by many major companies, returning to downtown is a no-brainer […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 07:02:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>YouTube now lets you request removal of AI-generated content that simulates your face or voice</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/01/youtube-now-lets-you-request-removal-of-ai-generated-content-that-simulates-your-face-or-voice/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Simply submitting the request for a takedown doesn't necessarily mean the content will be removed, however. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 19:26:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Minneapolis Cop Who Beat Him Pleaded Guilty. He Still Fears the Department Won’t Change.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/16/police-minneapolis-beating-jaleel-stallings</link><description>Jaleel Stallings was swept up in the chaos of protests over George Floyd’s murder. The outcome changed his life.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Behind the Spike in Colorectal Cancer Among Young Americans</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/colorectal-cancer/news/20240515/behind-the-spike-in-colorectal-cancer-cases?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Colorectal cancer cases increased a whopping 333% among 15- to 19-year-olds and 185% among 20- to 24-year-olds from 1999 to 2020.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:59:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>