<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from multiple RSS sources, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 17:05:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The Investor’s Guide to a Single-Family Rental Emergency Fund</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/the-investors-guide-to-a-single-family-rental-emergency-fund</link><description>As real estate investors, your emergency funds are a critical line of defense against unexpected costs. It prevents you from dipping into your budget to handle them. But what should you really use an emergency fund […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 19:23:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tesla profits drop 55%, company says EV sales ‘under pressure’ from hybrids</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/23/tesla-profits-drop-55-company-says-ev-sales-under-pressure-from-hybrids/</link><description>Tesla profits fell 55% to $1.13 billion in the first quarter from the same year-ago period as a protracted EV price-cutting strategy and “numerous challenges” cut into the automaker’s bottom line. Tesla reported revenue of $21.3 billion in the first quarter, a 9% drop from the first quarter of 2023. Analysts polled by Yahoo Finance […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 21:23:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Enduring Use of Solitary, and New Proposed Limits That Will Likely Fail (Again)</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/20/solitary-confinement-reform-oklahoma-washington-florida</link><description>Isolation’s damaging effects are widely known. But many facilities confine people — even youth — virtually all day, sometimes in shower stalls.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Where Will the Legit Health Info Go If TikTok Goes Dark?</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/a-to-z-guides/news/20240423/what-happens-to-legit-health-info-if-tiktok-banned?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>If TikTok goes dark, it could render unavailable the work of those who have made the site a go-to for expert- and user-generated videos on topics that cover the spectrum of consumer health.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 19:21:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seeing Greene: Are Home Warranties Worth It &amp; When to Pay Off Debt vs. Invest?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-941</link><description>Should you pay off debt or invest? Many online financial gurus would tell you in a heartbeat that paying off debt is the number one priority…but is that always true? […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 07:02:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tesla launches new Model 3 Performance variant to rev up demand</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/23/tesla-model-3-performance-highland-price/</link><description>Tesla has officially revealed a new Performance variant of the recently refreshed Model 3 sedan as the company looks to fight off receding demand. The new version of the Model 3, which starts at $52,990, has a new active damping system and adaptive suspension for better handling and comfort, 296 miles of battery range and […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 17:53:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Officials Failed to Act When COVID Hit Prisons. A New Study Shows the Deadly Cost.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/18/covid-prison-deaths-data</link><description>People in prison died at 3.4 times the rate of the free population, with the oldest hit hardest. New data holds lessons for preventing future deaths.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are 'Man Vans' Coming to a Parking Lot Near You Soon?</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/prostate-cancer/news/20240422/prostate-cancer-screening-goes-mobile?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>"Game Changer Vehicles" – mobile medical units in a roving RV – are helping to bring cancer screening to where it's needed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 19:18:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Get PAID to Live in an Affordable City &amp; Fast-Track Financial Freedom</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-522</link><description>Moving is hard. But could relocating to a low-cost-of-living area help you lead a more fulfilling life and achieve financial freedom? As today’s guest came to find out, the benefits […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 07:01:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tesla earnings week spotlights EV price cuts, ‘balls to the wall’ autonomy push</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/23/tesla-earnings-week-spotlights-price-cuts-elons-balls-to-the-wall-autonomy-push/</link><description>Tesla investors, still digesting a 43% drop in share price since the beginning of the year, are gearing up for what will likely be unimpressive financial results for the first quarter and a shift in priorities for CEO Elon Musk, who is making more moves to go “balls to the wall for autonomy.” Tesla is expected to […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 17:33:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Parents Paying for Their Children’s Crimes</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/13/michigan-school-shooting-parents</link><description>Experts warn about a wave of legal consequences for parents like the Crumbleys, while some states consider prosecutions for kids as young as 10.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chronic Spontaneous Urticaria: What to Know</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/features/urticaria-chronic-spontaneous?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>What you should know about chronic spontaneous urticaria (CSU), including symptoms, triggers, treatment, and a link to autoimmune disease.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 14:35:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Don’t Overlook This When Buying an Investment Property—Learn From My Mistake</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/dont-overlook-this-when-buying-an-investment-property</link><description>Let’s get one thing straight: Real estate investing isn't a get-rich-quick scheme. If you think you can just waltz in and start raking in cash without a solid game plan, you're setting yourself up for a financial face-plant.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 04:28:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>X is launching a TV app for videos ‘soon’</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/23/x-is-launching-a-tv-app-for-videos-soon/</link><description>X, the company formerly known as Twitter, is launching a dedicated TV app for videos uploaded to the social network soon. X CEO Linda Yaccarino announced on Tuesday that the new app will bring “real-time, engaging content to your smart TVs.” The app’s interface looks quite similar to YouTube’s, as seen in a teaser video […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 17:17:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I Had a Tough Job at My Brooklyn Jail: Keeping Men From Taking Their Own Lives</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/12/brooklyn-jail-suicide-prevention-aide</link><description>As a suicide prevention aide, I had to make sure my fellow detainees didn’t harm themselves. It was surprisingly easy to get such a complex job.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CSU: What to Wear and What to Avoid</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/features/what-to-wear-with-csu?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Find out what’s best to wear to prevent and manage chronic spontaneous urticaria (CSU), also called chronic hives.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 14:35:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Should You Invest for Cash Flow or Appreciation? Let’s Reevaluate in an Era of High Interest Rates</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/invest-for-real-estate-cash-flow-or-appreciation-in-high-interest-rate-environment</link><description>For real estate investors, the question of cash flow versus appreciation is as old as time. However, in an era of high interest rates, buying properties for cash flow isn’t easy. That doesn’t mean investing should […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 20:32:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TechCrunch Minute: How HeadSpin’s founder fraudster almost got away with lying to investors</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/23/techcrunch-minute-how-headspins-founder-fraudster-almost-get-away-with-lying-to-investors/</link><description>News that the former founder of HeadSpin is headed to prison for fraud was further evidence that the last boom in the paired worlds of startup and venture capital led to more than just a little bit of fraud. Manish Lachwani, founder in question, is getting prison time and a massive fine for lying to […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 17:00:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Supreme Court Case on Homelessness May Limit Prisoner Rights and Expand Executions</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/10/supreme-court-homeless-grants-pass-originalism</link><description>In Grants Pass v. Johnson, a town in Oregon asks the court to reconsider what constitutes “cruel and unusual punishments.”</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Treatment Plan for Chronic Spontaneous Urticaria</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/features/csu-meds-lifestyle?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>The hives of CSU can be tricky to manage. You and your doctor can try medications to ease your symptoms. But other changes might make a difference, too.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 14:35:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>