<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from multiple RSS sources, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 17:28:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Trump May Consider Shaking Up the Federal Reserve If Elected—Here’s What That Could Look Like</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/trump-allies-draft-federal-reserve-changes-that-could-replace-powell</link><description>A group of former officials and other allies of Former President Donald Trump has drafted a document outlining suggested policy changes that would impact the authority and independence of the Federal Reserve. While […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:28:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple’s ‘Crush’ ad is disgusting</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/08/apples-crush-ad-is-disgusting/</link><description>The problem is not the media, but the message.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 22:15:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Marshall Project Wins the Dart Award for “The Mercy Workers”</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/06/the-marshall-project-wins-the-dart-award-for-the-mercy-workers</link><description>Our feature on mitigation specialists who help save people from the death penalty was recognized for making “significant contributions to public understanding of trauma-related issues.”</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Plant-Powered Sleep: Vegan, Vegetarian Diets Unlock Extra ZZZs</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/sleep-disorders/news/20240508/plant-powered-sleep-vegan-vegetarian-diet-unlocks-extra-zzzs?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Vegans and vegetarians sleep around 30 more minutes per night than average and up to 90% of them report good or excellent sleep quality, according to a new survey published by the Sleep Foundation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 19:12:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Avoid My Mistakes: Single-Family Renovation Lessons I Learned the Hard Way</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/single-family-renovation-lessons-i-learned-the-hard-way</link><description>I want to share a few tips and lessons (some are costly) so you don’t repeat my mistakes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OpenAI offers a peek behind the curtain of its AI’s secret instructions</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/08/openai-offers-a-peek-behind-the-curtain-of-its-ais-secret-instructions/</link><description>Ever wonder why conversational AI like ChatGPT says “Sorry, I can’t do that” or some other polite refusal? OpenAI is offering a limited look at the reasoning behind its own models’ rules of engagement, whether it’s sticking to brand guidelines or declining to make NSFW content. Large language models (LLMs) don’t have any naturally occurring […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 20:52:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weinstein Ruling Poses Quandary: Can #MeToo Coexist With Protections for Defendants?</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/04/sex-crimes-weinstein-me-too</link><description>Proving sex crimes often requires evidence that is generally excluded to protect the rights of the accused.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anorexia: The Body Neglected</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/mental-health/eating-disorders/anorexia-nervosa/features/anorexia-body-neglected?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>What, exactly, does anorexia nervosa do inside the human body? The heart and bones suffer the most.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Easiest Way to Invest in Real Estate in 2024</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-950</link><description>There’s one way to invest in real estate that’s cheaper, easier, and more efficient than almost any other strategy. It allows you to get the best mortgage rates with the […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 07:02:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>US Patent and Trademark Office confirms another leak of filers’ address data</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/08/us-patent-and-trademark-office-confirms-another-leak-of-filers-address-data/</link><description>The federal government agency responsible for granting patents and trademarks is alerting thousands of filers whose private addresses were exposed following a second data spill in as many years. The U.S. Patent and Trademark Office (USPTO) said in an email to affected trademark applicants this week that their private domicile address — which can include […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 20:44:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mississippi Lawmakers Considered Modest Public Defense Reforms. They Rejected All of Them.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/02/mississippi-public-defense-legislative-reforms</link><description>With its refusal to impose oversight or consistent standards in local defense, Mississippi risks falling further behind rest of the U.S., critics say.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Postpartum PTSD: Right Diagnosis Can Help Mothers and Babies</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/mental-health/news/20240506/postpartum-ptsd-right-diagnosis-can-help-mothers-and-babies?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Many new mothers aren’t aware that postpartum PTSD even exists, but it’s far from rare. Here's what to know.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:19:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>House Hacking Blunder to $2.7 Million in Small Multifamily by Doing THIS</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-403</link><description>Buying small multifamily properties is an easy way to build a portfolio, and with a little creativity, you don’t even need a ton of money! Despite a rocky start to […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 07:02:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Encrypted services Apple, Proton and Wire helped Spanish police identify activist</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/08/encrypted-services-apple-proton-and-wire-helped-spanish-police-identify-activist/</link><description>As part of an investigation into people involved in the pro-independence movement in Catalonia, the Spanish police obtained information from the encrypted services Wire and Proton, which helped the authorities identify a pseudonymous activist, according to court documents obtained by TechCrunch. Earlier this year, the Spanish police Guardia Civil sent legal requests through Swiss police […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 20:38:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In This Police Youth Program, a Trail of Sexual Abuse Across the U.S.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/01/police-explorer-sexual-abuse-boy-scouts</link><description>Explorer posts, overseen by the Boy Scouts, are supposed to foster an interest in policing. They have faced nearly 200 allegations of misconduct.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 18:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Living With Major Depressive Disorder</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/depression/features/live-with-mdd?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>See how one person manages the ups and downs of major depressive disorder -- and how her depression inspired her career as a therapist.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:45:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seeing Greene: Is Losing $800/Month in Cash Flow Worth $200K+ Equity?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-949</link><description>Would you buy a rental property that loses money every month? What if, in a few years, that one property could make you hundreds of thousands of dollars? Would the […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 07:02:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Match looks to Hinge as Tinder fails</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/08/match-looks-to-hinge-as-tinder-fails-q1-2024/</link><description>Match Group, the company that owns several dating apps, including Tinder and Hinge, released its first-quarter earnings report on Tuesday, which shows that Tinder’s paying user base has decreased for the sixth quarter in a row. On the other hand, Hinge has seen an increase in members who are willing to pay for the app. […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 20:14:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Campus Protests Could Shape the 2024 Elections — And Not Just the Presidency</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/30/campus-protests-gaza-arrests-prosecutors-elections</link><description>With hundreds of arrests and more campus standoffs looming, local law enforcement officials could face consequences at the ballot box.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 21:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Therapist’s Perspective</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/depression/features/mdd-therapists-perspective?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>A therapist talks about managing major depressive disorder (MDD): what to expect, strategies for dealing with setbacks, and when to talk to your therapist.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:45:03 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>