<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 16:32:41 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>West Virginia Mountaineers Unveil New Football Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/29/west-virginia-mountaineers-unveil-new-football-uniforms/college/</link><description>West Virginia unveiled new uniforms over the weekend that pay homage to different eras of Mountaineer football while maintaining a few modern touches.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 19:39:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Suge Knight Expresses Sympathy for Diddy Amid Legal Troubles</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/29/suge-knight-expresses-sympathy-diddy-legal-troubles-federal/</link><description>Diddy's legal troubles aren't anything to cheer about, says Suge Knight ... a shocking sentiment given the decades-long bad blood between the two, and he reveals his sentiments in a brand new documentary "TMZ Presents: The Downfall of Diddy." The…</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 16:32:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Grit and Glow: Tampa Bay Rays Unveil Skateboard-Inspired City Connect Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/29/grit-and-glow-tampa-bay-rays-unveil-skateboard-inspired-city-connect-uniforms/baseball/</link><description>The Tampa Bay Rays unveiled their new Nike MLB City Connect Series uniform today, taking inspiration from the region’s skateboarding culture while also mixing in a few fun little nods to the team’s history. These uniforms are set to make their on-field debut during a special weekend series from May</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 16:42:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Justin Bieber Shares Pictures of Himself Crying, Hailey Bieber Responds</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/28/justin-bieber-crying-share-himself-tears-instagram-hailey-bieber-response/</link><description>Justin Bieber's letting fans in on an emotional moment ... sharing pics of himself crying to Instagram -- and drawing a reaction from his wife. The beloved singer-songwriter shared the pics as part of a series of posts he shared Friday ... all of…</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 16:32:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jacksonville Jaguars Reveal 30th Season Logo Following Fan Vote</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/28/jacksonville-jaguars-reveal-30th-season-logo-following-fan-vote/football/</link><description>After asking fans to vote among four unique designs, the Jacksonville Jaguars officially unveiled their new 30th season logo during their 2024 NFL Draft party on Thursday evening.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 15:43:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jerry Seinfeld Goes After 'Extreme Left' Over Comedy Ahead of 70th Birthday</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/29/jerry-seinfeld-attacks-extreme-left-pc-culture-comedy-70th-birthday/</link><description>Jerry Seinfeld reflected on the state of comedy ahead of his 70th birthday -- and he thinks modern-day showbiz has lost its sense of humor ... all 'cause of politically correct culture. The legendary comedian was talking on the New Yorker's Radio…</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 16:32:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NFL Will Allow Players To Wear Guardian Caps In Games</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/28/nfl-will-allow-players-to-wear-guardian-caps-in-games/football/</link><description>The NFL announced it will now allow players to wear Guardian Caps, a 12-ounce soft shell that fits over their helmets, during regular-season games in an effort to reduce head injuries.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 15:25:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Bachelor' Nick Viall Marries Natalie Joy After Almost 4 Years Together</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/29/bachelor-nick-viall-natalie-joy-wedding-married/</link><description>Nick Viall is officially no longer a bachelor ... as the reality TV star-turned-podcaster wed fiancée Natalie Joy over the weekend. The Bachelor Nation alum and the surgical technologist said "I do" in an outdoor ceremony in Savannah, Georgia. The…</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 16:32:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Report: CFL’s Saskatchewan Roughriders to Add Fourth Uniform in 2024</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/27/report-cfls-saskatchewan-roughriders-to-add-fourth-uniform-in-2024/football/</link><description>Riders reportedly adding uniform that's predominantly a darker shade of green than usual; helmet to feature logo filed with Canadian trademark office in 2022</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 18:13:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mike Myers Debuts White Hair in First Public Appearance in Over a Year</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/29/mike-myers-new-look-white-hair-first-public-appearance-year-afi-award/</link><description>Mike Myers returned to the spotlight for a rare public appearance this weekend ... but folks had to do a double take, 'cause nobody could recognize him with his new hair color. The actor stepped out Saturday for the 49th AFI Life Achievement Award…</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 16:32:41 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>