<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 07:47:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The Bull Market is Officially Back</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/the-bull-market-is-officially-back/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, it's Ross Givens here with the Chart of the Day. Introducing the often-overlooked Russell 3000 index, encompassing 3,000 major U.S. stocks and serving as a comprehensive gauge of the U.S. market. Notably, it recently surged to new all-time highs, reflecting the overall robustness of the market. With this positive momentum, there's ample opportunity for savvy investors to capitalize on the market's strength. Stay tuned to unlock its potential. The post The Bull Market is Officially Back appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>REI Anniversary Sale 2024 is now live: Explore these deals through May 27, while supplies last</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/article/rei-anniversary-sale-2024-is-now-live-explore-these-deals-through-may-27-while-supplies-last/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/15115418/REI-Tents-copy.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Commerce Continue reading REI Anniversary Sale 2024 is now live: Explore these deals through May 27, while supplies last REI Anniversary Sale 2024 is now live: Explore these deals through May 27, while supplies last originally appeared on Autoblog on Fri, 17 May 2024 06:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stop Paying Someone Else’s Mortgage: Beginner Steps to Buy Your FIRST Home</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-407</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Are you tired of paying someone else’s mortgage? Then you’re in the right place. In today’s show, we’re sharing how to buy a home in 2024, even as a complete […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 07:02:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Do Book Challenge Forms Look Like?: Book Censorship News, May 17, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/book-challenge-forms/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/site-book-censorship-image.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>Take a look at five different book challenge forms to understand how little effort goes into attempting to ban books. That, plus this week's book censorship news.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sharing Fun Facts About Yourself: 22 Examples &amp; Ideas</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/fun-facts-about-me/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fun-facts-about-me</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Asking to share some fun facts about yourself is a common icebreaker that’s used during job interviews. But the quality of your answer still matters. This guide will help you come up with some ideas for crafting a response that starts the interview on a good note. Table of contents Ideas for Sharing Fun Facts […] The post Sharing Fun Facts About Yourself: 22 Examples &amp; Ideas appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 15:26:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GameStop shares fall after it files to sell securities, says first quarter sales declined</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/17/gamestop-shares-fall-after-it-files-to-sell-securities-says-first-quarter-sales-declined.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 12:33:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Ian Somerhalder and Nikki Reed Built a Life Away From Hollywood</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1391101/how-ian-somerhalder-and-nikki-reed-built-their-life-away-from-hollywood?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>No one needs to tell Ian Somerhalder and Nikki Reed that the Hollywood grind is way overrated. But getting their hands dirty is where it's at. "Things are busy," Reed told New Beauty last year of...</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Power of Clicks, Likes, and Shares: Promote the Right Kind of Financial Content</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/16/the-power-of-clicks-likes-and-shares-promote-the-right-kind-of-financial-content/</link><description>Not all financial content creators on social media are created equal. A broad differentiation can be made between influencers, knowledge sharers, and aspiring thought leaders.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 14:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump lawyers accuse former fixer Michael Cohen of lying to jury</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/17/trump-lawyers-fixer-michael-cohen-lying-jury-obsessed-jail/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/AP24137440205450-e1715945880204.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Whether the defense is successful in undermining Cohen's testimony could determine Trump's fate in the case.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 12:40:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Crop Tops</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/crop-tops/</link><description>Outfit Details: Kilentar Top (similar here), Emporior Sirenuse Skirt, Emme Parsons Sandals, Prada Bag The crop top has earned its place as one of… The post Crop Tops appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:30:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>They dont make anime like this anymore</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/a9yM6LZ</link><description>Tags: amazing 3121 points, 163 comments.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 12:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cannon Takes the Spotlight on Arsenal’s 2024-25 Home Kit</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/16/cannon-takes-the-spotlight-on-arsenals-2024-25-home-kit/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>New kit marks first time this version of cannon has been used on a home kit and first time Arsenal has used just a cannon as a home kit badge since 1989-90</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 16:24:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A US Trustee wants troubled fintech Synapse to be liquidated via Chapter 7 bankruptcy, cites ‘gross mismanagement’</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/16/a-us-trustee-wants-troubled-fintech-synapse-to-be-liquidated-via-chapter-7-bankruptcy-cites-gross-mismanagement/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The prospects for troubled banking-as-a-service startup Synapse have gone from bad to worse this week after a United States Trustee filed an emergency motion on Wednesday. The trustee is asking to convert the company’s debt reorganization Chapter 11 bankruptcy into a liquidation Chapter 7, according to court documents. The trustee wrote that the need for […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:01:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Susan Chira to Step Down as The Marshall Project’s Editor-in-Chief in January</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/16/susan-chira-eic-step-down</link><description>Under her stewardship, the news nonprofit more than doubled in size, opened local newsrooms and won its second Pulitzer Prize.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best Swedish Meatballs</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/the-best-swedish-meatballs/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>These Swedish Meatballs are smothered in the most amazing rich and creamy gravy and packed with such delicious flavor. You…</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chris Pratt's 'Guardians' Stunt Double Tony McFarr Dead at 47</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/16/chris-pratt-stunt-double-tony-mcfarr-dead-dies-guardians-of-the-galaxy/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>3:07 PM PT -- Chris just addressed Tony's passing, writing ... "Devastated to hear about the loss of my friend and former stunt double Tony McFarr. We did several movies together. We golfed, drank whiskey, smoked cigars, and spent endless hours on…</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 07:47:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Federal Experts Talk Bird Flu ‘What Ifs’ in WebMD Live Event</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/cold-and-flu/news/20240516/federal-experts-talk-bird-flu-what-ifs?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>WebMD brought together experts from four federal agencies to talk prevention, monitoring, and what the “what ifs” of bird flu might look like.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:50:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Easy Low-Light Indoor Plants</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/easy-low-light-indoor-plants/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>I used to think every houseplant needed a sunny corner or bright windowsill to thrive. But it turns out many of our favorite go-to houseplants do just fine in shady corners and low-light locations. So before you write off your house as too dark to sustain plant life, check out this list of the best indoor plants for low light. You might be surprised at how many good options there are! Our upstairs family room is the brightest room we’ve ever owned thanks to big unobstructed windows on all 4 sides. But most of our indoor plants live downstairs, where we get far less natural light. Luckily, that hasn’t stopped us from growing our collection of happy healthy houseplants. 9 Houseplants That Don’t Need A Lot Of Light Here are our favorite low-light indoor plants. We list a lot more info on them below, but here’s a quick list to bring on your next trip to the plant store: Snake Plant ZZ Plant Pothos Heartleaf Philodendron English Ivy Aglaonema Cast Iron Plant Monstera Parlor Palm Perhaps our favorite part of this list is that these aren’t ugly “consolation plants” that people begrudgingly buy for dark homes. Continue reading Easy Low-Light Indoor Plants at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 14:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Bull Flag Tells Me “Risk On”</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/this-bull-flag-tells-me-risk-on/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, it's Ross Givens here with the Chart of the Day. Presenting Bitcoin's price showcasing a classic "bull flag pattern," signaling a bullish market sentiment. While it's an opportune time to consider Bitcoin investments, the broader implication lies in the market's risk appetite. Despite the current subdued state, indications point towards an imminent surge, as evidenced by Bitcoin's pattern and recent meme stock activity. Stay tuned to harness potential opportunities arising from this evolving market sentiment. The post This Bull Flag Tells Me “Risk On” appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>7 better alternatives to the best-selling slime-like cleaning gel at Amazon</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/article/7-better-alternatives-to-the-best-selling-slime-like-cleaning-gel-at-amazon/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/16105912/goop-alts2_V1.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Commerce Continue reading 7 better alternatives to the best-selling slime-like cleaning gel at Amazon 7 better alternatives to the best-selling slime-like cleaning gel at Amazon originally appeared on Autoblog on Thu, 16 May 2024 17:30:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BiggerNews: Real Estate vs. Stocks, the Ultimate Wealth-Building Debate</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-955</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Which will make you richer: real estate vs. stocks? We brought the fine folks from The Motley Fool on the podcast to get into a serious debate over which asset […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 07:02:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>8 Cozy and Comforting Books About Bakeries</title><link>https://bookriot.com/cozy-books-about-bakeries/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/Cozy-Books-about-Bakeries.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>If the thought or smell of baked goods has you craving all things cozy, get your hands on these books.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 553</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-553/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-553</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Tools and technology change rapidly. Yet as wonderful as technology can be, it doesn’t replace the need for human connection through interactions. Keep this in mind as you are searching for a new job. It’s your human connections that often open doors! In this week’s collection of news and tips for job seekers, you’ll find: […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 553 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 12:19:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>5 things to know before the stock market opens Friday</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/17/5-things-to-know-before-the-stock-market-opens-friday-may-17.html</link><description>Here are the most important news items that investors need to start their trading day.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 12:26:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best Dishwasher-Safe Cookware for Effortless Cleanup</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1401786/the-best-dishwasher-safe-cookware-for-effortless-cleanup?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>We independently selected these deals and products because we love them, and we think you might like them at these prices. E! has affiliate relationships, so we may get a commission if you...</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why the New T+1 Settlement Cycle Matters: A Global Index Provider’s Perspective</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/14/why-the-new-t1-settlement-cycle-matters-a-global-index-providers-perspective/</link><description>Shorter settlement periods are meant to protect market participants. But the new T+1 settlement cycle for US equities may have undesirable knock-on effects for financial market participants around the world, including index fund managers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 16:54:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sir Richard Branson—who hates being called a billionaire—sees net worth fall back to 2000 levels</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/17/richard-branson-net-worth-falls-back-3-billion-year-2000-hates-being-called-billionaire/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1434426517-e1715943659708.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Branson took a $126 million hit to his fortune last year as he continued to fight several fires at his Virgin Group.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 12:39:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Punchy Prints</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/punchy-prints/</link><description>Outfit Details: Pucci Top &amp; Pants, Chanel Bag (similar, less expensive here), Dior Sandals (similar, less expensive here), Louis Abel Earrings (less expensive here) Punchy prints are a favorite of mine… The post Punchy Prints appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 05:00:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quite funny.</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/a1mZm4D</link><description>Tags: 1 , 2 , 3 8910 points, 67 comments.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 12:45:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Making the Connection: Manchester City Honors Roots With 2024-25 Home Kit</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/16/making-the-connection-manchester-city-honors-roots-with-2024-25-home-kit/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>0161 pattern woven into navy blue collar and sleeve cuffs represent Manchester dialling code and "a sense of location, no matter where you are in the world"</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 15:42:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seraphim’s latest space accelerator welcomes nine companies</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/16/seraphims-latest-space-accelerator-welcomes-nine-companies/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>U.K.-based Seraphim Space is spinning up its 13th accelerator program, with nine participating companies working on a range of tech from propulsion to in-space manufacturing and space situational awareness. The intense 12-week program is designed to get seed and Series A companies “investment ready,” the firm says, by providing specialist mentorship, networking opportunities and intensive […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 23:33:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When Bad Cops Become Private Security Guards</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/11/police-private-guard-florida-chicago</link><description>There’s growing evidence that former officers with troubling histories of abuse can easily find second careers in private security.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>No Bake Snickers Bar Pie</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/no-bake-snickers-bar-pie/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>No Bake Snickers Bar Pie is one of the easiest and most delicious no bake pies that you make. You…</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Airline Worker Falls From Plane After Coworkers Move Ladder</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/16/airline-worker-fall-plane-move-ladder-video/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>An airline worker plummeted several feet to the ground from an airplane ... this after his coworkers inadvertently screwed him. A ground staff member at the Jakarta airport in Indonesia is seen falling hard on the tarmac in this wild video making…</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 07:47:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What’s Next in Health Care for Older Adults: Questions and Answers With John Whyte, MD</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/blog-aging-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>As WebMD’s chief medical officer, John Whyte, MD, is in a unique position to see both the current state of medical care for America’s older adults and the way things are trending for the future. We asked him to share his insight on a few topics, along with a bit of advice.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:29:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/how-to-remove-wallpaper/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Wallpaper has made a big comeback as a trendy home design choice. But despite its resurgence, there are still plenty of us dealing with dingy, dated, or downright ugly old wallpaper we don’t want. In our old home, we had to remove wallpaper in so many rooms: the kitchen, the dining room, the foyer, and two different bathrooms! As we traveled from room to room removing wallpaper, we tested 4 different methods, and today we’ll share what we learned. Removing wallpaper doesn’t require special tools or lots of money. It’s a totally doable project for any homeowner. However, it can be a tedious process that can take elbow grease and patience, depending on the size of your room and the stubbornness of your wallpaper. But having removed several rooms worth of decades-old wallpaper, we can confidently say it’s worth the effort! You can also check out more before and afters of our once-wallpapered rooms. Continue reading How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:21:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Could This Derail the Recovery? (What to Do About It)</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/could-this-derail-the-recovery-what-to-do-about-it/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, it's Ross Givens here with the Chart of the Day. Diving into one of my top charts, the Equal-Weight S&amp;P 500 Index (RSP) paints a clearer picture of the market's health by eliminating the dominance of mega-cap tech stocks. Currently, RSP sits a mere 1.5% shy of its all-time highs, signaling a robust recovery from the April pullback. However, with the looming CPI report's potential impact, the market's trajectory remains uncertain. Stay ahead of the curve with my insight. The post Could This Derail the Recovery? (What to Do About It) appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mitsubishi off-road Delica van, outdoorsy Outlander variant planned for US market</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/16/mitsubishi-delica-off-road-van-outlander-variant-truck-future-product-plans/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/crop/1131x636+38+82/resize/800x450!/format/jpg/quality/85/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/16160957/mitsubishi-dx-delica-concept.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Green , Mitsubishi , Nissan , Truck , Crossover , Minivan/Van , Electric , Future Vehicles , Hybrid , Off-Road Vehicles Continue reading Mitsubishi off-road Delica van, outdoorsy Outlander variant planned for US market Mitsubishi off-road Delica van, outdoorsy Outlander variant planned for US market originally appeared on Autoblog on Thu, 16 May 2024 16:49:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 21:49:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FI by 25: How to Buy Time and Freedom with a Few Years of Frugal Living</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-529</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Financial independence by the age of twenty-five?! Today’s guest started working and saving money at a very early age, which allowed him to buy the time and freedom to do […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 07:01:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Watch the Trailer for IT ENDS WITH US, Adapted from the Colleen Hoover Novel</title><link>https://bookriot.com/it-ends-with-us-trailer/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/it-ends-with-us-trailer.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>Will you be watching?</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 19:20:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 552</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-552/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-552</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>When you are searching for a job, you will inevitably run into unexpected scenarios. You will have questions, experience self-doubt and even feel discouraged. You’ll also experience great wins, meet wonderful people and discover new things about yourself. That’s the roller-coaster of job search. Consider Summary Sunday your resource for getting questions answered and showing […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 552 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 11:37:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Microsoft's Mistral partnership avoids merger probe by British regulators</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/17/microsoft-mistral-partnership-avoids-merger-probe-by-uk-regulators.html</link><description>The U.K.'s Competition and Markets Authority cleared Microsoft's AI partnership with Mistral of regulatory concerns after previously inviting views on whether the arrangement qualified as a merger.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 12:17:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Enjoy Reuniting With These Saucy Beverly Hills, 90210 Secrets</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1401776/these-beverly-hills-90210-secrets-are-saucier-than-kissing-your-ex-at-your-best-friends-wedding?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>It's been 24 years since Donna Martin married David Silver. And how many years do you think it's been since their divorce? Not to say we weren't rooting for the happily-ever-after that Tori...</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Leveraging AI to Identify and Predict Financial Crises</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/13/leveraging-ai-to-identify-and-predict-financial-crises/</link><description>Despite some current limitations, AI stands to offer significant advantages versus traditional approaches to identifying and predicting financial crises.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 14:39:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A deepfake ‘CFO’ tricked the British design firm behind the Sydney Opera House in $25 million fraud</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/17/arup-deepfake-fraud-scam-victim-hong-kong-25-million-cfo/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1744769333-e1715942474314.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>“Our financial stability and business operations were not affected," an Arup spokesperson said.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 12:32:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bikini Edit</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/bikini-edit/</link><description>Outfit Details: Lspace Bikini, Janessa Leone Hat, Illestevsa Sunglasses With warm weather upon us, I’m excited to embrace bikinis perfect for… The post Bikini Edit appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Life Hack!</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/aRBgL22</link><description>Tags: wtf , random , savage , life hack , funny 6892 points, 293 comments.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 12:45:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New York Giants Unveil “Century Red” Throwback Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/16/new-york-giants-unveil-century-red-throwback-uniforms/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The New York Giants announced on Thursday morning they will celebrate their 100th season by wearing "Century Red" throwback uniforms in up to two games this fall.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 15:38:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OpenAI inks deal to train AI on Reddit data</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/16/openai-inks-deal-to-train-ai-on-reddit-data/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>OpenAI has reached a deal with Reddit to use the social news site’s data for training AI models. In a blog post on OpenAI’s press relations site, the company said that the Reddit partnership will provide it access to “real-time, structured and unique content” — e.g. posts and replies — from Reddit, allowing its tools […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 23:04:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Rare Bright Spot for a Canine Lover Doing Time: Raising Puppies to Become Service Dogs</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/10/service-dogs-training-prison-essay</link><description>Adam Roberts reflects on the highs and occasional lows of training Labrador retrievers for the Puppies Behind Bars program.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Easy Grilled Bourbon Chicken</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/grilled-bourbon-chicken/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>One bite of this grilled bourbon chicken and your tastebuds will be dancing with delight! It’s marinated in a flavorful…</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Whoopi Goldberg Defends Harrison Butker After Remarks, Right To Free Speech</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/16/whoopi-goldberg-defens-harrison-butker-right-free-speech/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Whoopi Goldberg is coming to Harrison Butker's defense following his controversial college address -- but she's not so much agreeing with what he said ... more so his right to say it. The TV star came out swinging on Thursday's episode of "The…</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 07:47:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Get the Care You Need in a COVID-19 World</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/covid-senior-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>What to expect at the doctor’s office, hospitals, and long-term care facilities, the future of telemedicine, and how to get the best care during COVID-19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 19:50:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aglaonema Plant – Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/aglaonema-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Aglaonema, also called the Chinese Evergreen Plant, is an easy-care houseplant that lives happily in many lighting conditions – even a dark corner of our daughter’s room. There are dozens of different Aglaonema varieties, most with large tropical foliage and colors ranging from silvery-green, red, and even vibrant pink. They’re also tough to kill, so they’re a great option for forgetful plant owners or anyone looking for an easy win in the plant department. These truly have been very low maintenance for us. We purchased our two Aglaonemas (pronounced ag-lee-oh-neem-ah ) to put atop our daughter’s closet. It’s sometimes hard to distinguish different varieties, but we believe that’s an Aglaonema Silver (right) and either a Candy Cane or Princess Silver Queen (left). Aglaonema Quick Facts Here’s what you need to know about your Aglaonema at a glance: Latin name : Aglaonema is the genus under which there are 21 recognized species . Continue reading Aglaonema Plant – Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:47:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bulls Back in Control (Do This Now)</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/bulls-back-in-control-do-this-now/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, it's Ross Givens here with the Chart of the Day. In a remarkable shift, my market health model swiftly transitioned from bearish to bullish within a week. This robust buying spree following the recent dip signifies significant strength and resilience in the market. The much-needed correction allowed for the consolidation of previous gains and the shedding of weak-handed sellers. While the overall market gears up for further upward movement, the dynamics for individual stocks present a nuanced scenario, as I delve into in today's Insight. The post Bulls Back in Control (Do This Now) appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Save a massive 42% off with this Amazon deal on a DeWalt cordless drill and impact driver kit</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/article/save-a-massive-42-off-with-this-amazon-deal-on-a-dewalt-cordless-drill-and-impact-driver-kit/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/16143927/drill-lead.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Commerce Continue reading Save a massive 42% off with this Amazon deal on a DeWalt cordless drill and impact driver kit Save a massive 42% off with this Amazon deal on a DeWalt cordless drill and impact driver kit originally appeared on Autoblog on Thu, 16 May 2024 16:12:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 21:12:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Economic Pessimism Peaks, So Why Are Investors Still Buying?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-217</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>The unemployment rate begins to rise as job growth slows in the latest jobs report, prompting many to wonder, “Will this finally lead to interest rate cuts?” With so many […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 07:02:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What are You Reading This Week — Read Harder, May 16, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/read-harder-updates-may-16-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/fair-skinned-Asian-woman-lying-on-her-stomach-and-reading-a-book-in-front-of-a-floor-length-mirror.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>Are you participating in any reading challenges this year?</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 18:30:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>While a little competition in the workplace might help bring out the best in everyone involved, an atmosphere rooted in envy, fear, or jealousy can do the exact opposite. This post will help you recognize signs that your coworker is threatened by you, and help you navigate the situation. 1. They Don’t Want You Involved […] The post 10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:07:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Dow tends to take a breather after surpassing big, round numbers</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/17/the-dow-tends-to-take-a-breather-after-surpassing-big-round-numbers.html</link><description>The Dow's rally to 40,000 could be followed by a pullback if historical performance is any guide.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 11:51:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TikToker Xandra Pohl Sparks Romance Rumors With This Chiefs NFL Player</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1401840/why-tiktoker-xandra-pohl-is-sparking-romance-rumors-with-kansas-city-chiefs-player-louis-rees-zamm?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>Xandra Pohl may have chosen a new first string. The TikTok star, who's best known for her viral "get ready with me" videos, was spotted enjoying the rides at the Worlds of Fun amusement park with...</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 03:33:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Your Portfolio Should Include Scarce Assets</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/10/why-your-portfolio-should-include-scarce-assets/</link><description>Portfolios that include both productive and scarce assets can deliver similar performance to the S&amp;P 500 with less risk than those that hold only productive assets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:34:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Taiwan is now exporting and investing more in the U.S. than China in major pivot away from Beijing</title><link>https://fortune.com/asia/2024/05/17/taiwan-exporting-investing-more-us-china-major-pivot-away-beijing/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/AP24135146409859-e1715943293440.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The U.S. displaced mainland China as the top destination for Taiwan’s exports in the first quarter of the year for the first time since the start of 2016, when comparable data became available.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 11:56:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>My Saks May Array</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/my-saks-may-array/</link><description>Outfit Details: Sandro Top, Erdem Skirt, Prada Bag, Sherman Fields Necklace Thank you to Saks Fifth Avenue for sponsoring this… The post My Saks May Array appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 05:00:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wishing all my fellow Norwegians a happy 17th of May! Drink responsibly.</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/aPAymnq</link><description>Tags: NORWAY , Idun Vollan , Bunad 2109 points, 249 comments.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 12:45:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Minor League Hockey Team in Athens, Georgia, Pays Tribute to B-52s with ‘Rock Lobsters’ Moniker</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/15/new-minor-league-hockey-team-in-athens-georgia-pays-tribute-to-b-52s-with-rock-lobsters-moniker/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>More than 8,000 people voted on new FPHL franchise's name; nod to one of the local band's best-known songs won by a margin of 565 votes</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 04:22:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>X pushes more users to Communities</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/16/x-pushes-more-users-to-communities/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>X users will now be able to discover posts from new Communities that are trending directly from an Explore tab within the section. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:50:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Marshall Project Wins the Dart Award for “The Mercy Workers”</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/06/the-marshall-project-wins-the-dart-award-for-the-mercy-workers</link><description>Our feature on mitigation specialists who help save people from the death penalty was recognized for making “significant contributions to public understanding of trauma-related issues.”</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wood-Fired Pizza Dough</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/wood-fired-pizza-dough/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>This is the perfect beginner’s guide for making wood-fired pizza dough! Pizza expert, Chef Brandon Price, taught me how to…</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lil Baby Music Video Shooting, 911 Audio Details Chaos</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/16/lil-baby-911-audio-call-music-video-shooting-atlanta/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Lil Baby and his music video crew got caught in the crossfire -- that's the early word from cops investigating the gunfire that erupted in the middle of his Atlanta music video shoot. TMZ Hip Hop obtained audio of the chaotic 911 call during the…</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 07:47:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Personal Shopper: A Savvy Black Entrepreneur Guides You to Eczema-Friendly Clothes, Creams, Cosmetics, and More</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/savvy-black-entrepreneur-guides-eczema-friendly-clothes-creams-cosmetics?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>A savvy black entrepreneur guides you on an eczema-friendly shopping spree.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:54:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Corn Plant – Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/corn-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Corn plants ( Dracaena fragrans ) are popular low-maintenance houseplants you’ve probably seen at the nursery, home improvement store, or doctor’s office. I even had one in my college dorm room! You can recognize them by their spear-shaped leaves and woody, cane-line trunks that can grow up to 6 feet tall indoors. But did you know there are several varieties of corn plants? We didn’t! Heck, we didn’t even realize some of our smaller houseplants were in the same corn plant family! Currently, we own two smaller varieties of corn plants, pictured above. The one on the left is a Dracaena Limelight ( Dracaena fragrans ‘Limelight’ ) and the taller plant is a Draecanea Dorado ( Dracaena fragrans ‘Dorado’ ). We actually have several limelights around because we love their vibrant color on shelves, tabletops, and windowsills. Corn Plant Quick Facts Latin name : Dracaena fragrans Common names : Corn plant, cornstalk plant, false palms Light : Bright, indirect light but can tolerate lower-light conditions Watering : Keep soil moist, but not soggy. Continue reading Corn Plant – Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 17:37:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bullish Breadth (Act Fast)</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/bullish-breadth-act-fast/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, it's Ross Givens here with the Chart of the Day. The percentage of stocks trading above their 50-day moving average, a key metric for medium-term momentum, has surged, signaling a potential continuation of the bull market. Nearly double the levels seen during the April pullback, it mirrors the market's upward trajectory observed from February to mid-March. This resurgence indicates an opportunity for swift action. Learn more about the implications in my detailed analysis below. The post Bullish Breadth (Act Fast) appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to protect your car from keyless vehicle thefts</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/16/how-to-prevent-keyless-car-theft-prevention-methods-techniques/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/http://s.aolcdn.com/commerce/blogcdn/www.autoblog.com/media/2012/03/29-2012-hyundai-equus.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Ownership , Technology Continue reading How to protect your car from keyless vehicle thefts How to protect your car from keyless vehicle thefts originally appeared on Autoblog on Thu, 16 May 2024 15:21:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:21:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meme Stocks Surged Again This Week—But I’m Not Buying the Hype</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/meme-stocks-are-surging-againbut-im-not-buying-the-hype</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Are they headed to the moon, or is this just a temporary blip?</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 21:08:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>7 Books for Better Mental Health</title><link>https://bookriot.com/books-for-better-mental-health/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/tengyart-DoqtEEn8SOo-unsplash.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>May is Mental Health Awareness Month, and we've got some book recommendations to help start or supplement your mental health journey.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 18:08:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 551</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-551/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-551</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Job search requires writing and marketing skills. It also requires strong verbal communication. If these skills are not part of your normal work function, you’ll want some help. That’s what this week’s Summary Sunday is all about. There’s no doubt that LinkedIn is one of THE most powerful tools in your career toolbox. It contains […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 551 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 11:37:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>China pledges $42 billion in a slew of measures to support the struggling property sector</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/17/china-pledges-billions-in-measures-to-support-struggling-property-sector.html</link><description>Chinese authorities on Friday pledged new support for state-owned enterprises to enable them to buy unsold apartments.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 11:49:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summer House's Jesse Solomon Shares Abnormal Cancer Scan Result</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1401749/summer-houses-jesse-solomon-shares-abnormal-results-of-testicular-cancer-scan?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>Jesse Solomon is facing another potential health scare. During Summer House's May 16 episode, the two-time testicular cancer survivor received some unsettling news during a routine doctor's...</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 03:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coiled Tight: Smaller Companies Are Primed for Outperformance</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/08/coiled-tight-smaller-companies-are-primed-for-outperformance/</link><description>Small-cap companies are poised for a rebound. The sector is best approached through an active investment strategy where expertise and a deep understanding of the individual businesses and their risk-and-reward characteristics are necessary for success.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:40:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nearly half of Gen Z and millennial workers have left a job, or plan to, because of climate concerns</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/17/gen-z-millennial-sustainability-jobs-climate-change-deloitte/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2042292838-e1715940128917.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Instead of sitting with their climate change anxiety, Gen Z and millennials are trying to save the planet by quitting jobs that aren’t eco-friendly.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 11:35:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Our Latest Favorites From Amazon</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/our-latest-favorites-from-amazon/</link><description>Outfit Details: Beaded Handmade Bag Welcome to our latest favorites from Amazon that I’m especially excited to share! This week… The post Our Latest Favorites From Amazon appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 05:00:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The new Assassin's Creed be like</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/aW40pEd</link><description>Tags: funny , assassins creed 7490 points, 276 comments.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 12:45:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MLS Launches Latest Version of ‘Love Unites’ Pre-Match Tops in Time for Pride Month</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/15/mls-launches-latest-version-of-love-unites-pre-match-tops-in-time-for-pride-month/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Jerseys were designed in collaboration with Brazilian drag queen and pop singer Pabllo Vittar and will be worn prior to matches throughout June</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 21:02:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mark Zuckerberg’s makeover: Midlife crisis or carefully crafted rebrand?</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/16/mark-zuckerbergs-makeover-midlife-crisis-or-carefully-crafted-rebrand/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>For Mark Zuckerberg’s 40th birthday, his wife got him a photoshoot. Zuckerberg gives the camera a sly smile as he sits amid a carefully crafted re-creation of his childhood bedroom. It’s appropriately childish — a lava lamp, a participation trophy, a white stuffed dog — yet the surroundings foreshadow the culture-shifting, technological force Zuckerberg would […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 19:58:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weinstein Ruling Poses Quandary: Can #MeToo Coexist With Protections for Defendants?</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/04/sex-crimes-weinstein-me-too</link><description>Proving sex crimes often requires evidence that is generally excluded to protect the rights of the accused.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blueberry Lemon Upside-Down Cake</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/blueberry-lemon-upside-cake/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Be prepared to fall in love with this blueberry lemon upside-down cake! A delicious and moist lemon sponge cake bursting…</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Riley Strain's Family Breaks Down in Tears While Accepting His Diploma</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/16/riley-strain-family-cries-breaks-down-tears-accepting-college-diploma/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Riley Strain's family experienced a bittersweet milestone on behalf of the late college student ... a moment that left them in tears, and with a diploma in hand. Riley's loved ones attended the University of Missouri's graduation Saturday ...…</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 07:47:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Behind the Spike in Colorectal Cancer Among Young Americans</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/colorectal-cancer/news/20240515/behind-the-spike-in-colorectal-cancer-cases?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Colorectal cancer cases increased a whopping 333% among 15- to 19-year-olds and 185% among 20- to 24-year-olds from 1999 to 2020.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:59:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Using Solid Stain In Our Outdoor Shower</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/solid-deck-stain-outdoor-shower/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>In all of our years of DIYing, I don’t think we’ve ever used a solid stain before. But we recently had a project that was *perfectly* suited for it and, well, solid stain quickly won us over. It was recommended by a professional house painter to us, specifically because he thought it would be great for our outdoor shower. And we found it easy to apply, it gave us great coverage, and we got an even-better-than-we-expected result (which is always the best kind!). So here’s a post that covers all the pros &amp; cons and hows &amp; whys of solid stain. As you can see, the “canvas” for this staining project was our outdoor shower. We gave it a mini-makeover right after moving in, but we knew it may need more attention and care down the line. Honestly, we dreaded the task of stripping and restaining it – so many nooks &amp; crannies! Continue reading Using Solid Stain In Our Outdoor Shower at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 17:46:51 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>