<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 02:11:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Our Chat with Cards’ President Bill DeWitt III About New City Connect Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/25/our-chat-with-cards-president-bill-dewitt-iii-about-new-city-connect-uniforms/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The St. Louis Cardinals brand new Nike MLB City Connect uniforms will be making their on-field début this afternoon. The red jerseys with “The Lou” scripted across the chest, inspired by the hit song from Nelly, were unveiled on Monday to an overall positive reaction from fans and media alike.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 17:17:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TMZ TV Hot Takes: Brawl at Cannes, 'Wheel of Fortune,' Jaelan Phillips</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/26/tmz-tv-hot-takes-sunday-cannes-travis-scott-brawl-alexander-edwards/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Another day, another chance to check out the best TMZ has to offer. Take a trip through our last week before the summer heat really kicks up. On "TMZ Live," Harvey and Charles break down the brawl between Travis Scott, Tyga, and Alexander "AE"…</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 02:11:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ligue 1’s Lille OSC Put Unique Spin on Traditional Chevron for 2024-25 Home Kits</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/24/ligue-1s-lille-osc-put-unique-spin-on-traditional-chevron-for-2024-25-home-kits/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Club's traditional chevron, which they've used in some form since the 1940s, appears on new kits made up of several tonal mini-chevrons</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 22:01:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jennifer Lopez -- Good Genes or Good Docs?!</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/26/jennifer-lopez-good-genes-or-good-docs/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Jennifer Lopez's love don't cost a thing ... but her looks are right on the money! Here is a 27-year-old version of the megastar glowing at the "Selena" Hollywood Premiere back in 1997 (left). This was J Lo's breakout role and shortly before her…</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 02:11:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Memorial Cup Host Saginaw Spirit Unveil Commemorative Jersey for Tourney Opener</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/24/memorial-cup-host-saginaw-spirit-unveil-commemorative-jersey-for-tourney-opener/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Like the Memorial Cup itself, Spirit jersey for Friday's opening game against the Moose Jaw Warriors honors fallen military personnel</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 15:34:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Byron Scott Unsure JJ Redick Good Fit For Lakers Job, Has No Experience!</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/26/byron-scott-jj-redick-lebron-james-mark-jackson-sam-cassell-lakers-coach-nba/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>JJ Redick is a legit candidate for the Lakers head -- despite never having spent a minute on the bench -- and Byron Scott isn't sold on the idea quite yet! The 3x NBA champ and former longtime NBA head coach talked to TMZ Sports this week about…</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 02:11:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Announcing Player 97: Our New Brand Vision, Research, Consulting Company</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/24/player-97-consulting-brand-vision-historical-research/misc/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Today, I’m excited to announce the official launch of Player 97, the new consulting, research, and branding company managed by the same friendly faces that have been running SportsLogos.Net. After many years of helping teams, leagues, designers, and other companies, I decided to finally make it official—folks, I am here</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 14:39:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Speed' Actor Joe Morton on Board for 3rd Film, if Vehicle is Right</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/26/speed-actor-joe-morton-on-board-third-film/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Joe Morton would love to reunite with Sandra Bullock and Keanu Reeves for a 3rd "Speed" movie ... but isn't yet sold on the plot, TMZ has learned. The actor tells TMZ ... he'd love to be a part of "Speed 3," after Sandra and Keanu both expressed an…</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 02:11:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Football in Their DNA: AC Milan Launches 2024-25 Home Kit</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/23/football-in-their-dna-ac-milan-launches-2024-25-home-kit/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Tonal segmented stripes inside red stripes are a visual representation of the human genome; patch on back collar celebrates club's 125th anniversary</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 16:11:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Priscilla Presley Celebrates 79th Birthday With Granddaughter Riley Keough</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/26/priscilla-presley-celebrates-birthday-riley-keough-elvis-graceland/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Priscilla Presley and her granddaughter, Riley Keough, presented a united front Saturday, celebrating the 79th birthday of Elvis' ex-wife. It's especially interesting in the wake of what looks like a fraudulent attempt to steal Graceland. Riley won…</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 02:11:29 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>