<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 06:45:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>BiggerNews: What Happens to The Housing Market if Mortgage Rates Stay High?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-979</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Mortgage rates were supposed to be going down by now, but what happened? Even in late 2023, many housing market experts predicted that we’d be seeing high to mid six […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 07:02:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Feather raises €6 million to go pan-European with its insurance platform for expats</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/28/feather-raises-e6-million-to-go-pan-european-with-its-insurance-platform-for-expats/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>As a foreigner, navigating health insurance systems can often be difficult. German startup Feather thinks it has a solution and raised €6 million to help some of the 40-plus million expats working and living in Europe. It is not that there are no options for foreign nationals to get insurance; there are plenty. But it […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump and Biden Spar Over Crime Rates Ahead of Their Debate. What Do We Really Know?</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/27/trump-and-biden-spar-over-crime-rates-ahead-of-their-debate-what-do-we-really-know</link><description>As crime data again becomes a flashpoint in the presidential campaign, experts push for better national statistics.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Federal Experts Talk Bird Flu ‘What Ifs’ in WebMD Live Event</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/cold-and-flu/news/20240516/federal-experts-talk-bird-flu-what-ifs?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>WebMD brought together experts from four federal agencies to talk prevention, monitoring, and what the “what ifs” of bird flu might look like.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:50:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rookie Reply: How to Pass Down Generational Wealth &amp; Top Airbnb Amenities</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-425</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>You’re working hard to build generational wealth. But have you thought about a succession plan for your growing real estate portfolio? Today, we’re going to show you several ways to […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 07:02:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rohlik rolls up $170M to expand in European grocery delivery and sell its tech to others</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/28/rohlik-rolls-up-170m-to-expand-european-grocery-delivery-and-sell-its-tech-to-others/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The salad days of fresh grocery delivery startups are over, but those that have stayed the course, and built businesses that are seeing gains, are still here and hungry for more growth. On Friday, one of those survivors, the Czech grocery delivery company Rohlik, announced $170 million in new funding. Rohlik – which means ‘baker’ […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 08:12:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Death Row Prisoner’s Parting Interview</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/24/texas-death-row-prisoner-final-interview</link><description>Days before his scheduled execution in Texas, Ramiro Gonzales speaks on faith, legacy — and apologizing to the family of his victim, Bridget Townsend.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What’s Next in Health Care for Older Adults: Questions and Answers With John Whyte, MD</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/blog-aging-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>As WebMD’s chief medical officer, John Whyte, MD, is in a unique position to see both the current state of medical care for America’s older adults and the way things are trending for the future. We asked him to share his insight on a few topics, along with a bit of advice.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:29:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Finance Friday: I’ve Got $150K Student Debt at 6.95%, Should I Invest?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-541</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Student loan debt can easily get in the way of financial independence, especially if there’s a high interest rate attached to your loans. But should you pay down this debt […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 07:01:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Robotics investments are gaining speed after post-pandemic slowdown</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/27/robotics-investments-are-gaining-speed-after-post-pandemic-slowdown/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The first six months of the year have seen $4.2 billion invested in robotics, putting this year well on track to beat 2023’s 12-month total of $6.8 billion. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 22:03:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The New Battle Over an Old Institution: Forced Prison Labor</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/22/prison-slavery-forced-labor-lawsuits-bills</link><description>Inside the latest legal and legislative efforts to close state constitutional loopholes that allow slavery as punishment for a crime.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Get the Care You Need in a COVID-19 World</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/covid-senior-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>What to expect at the doctor’s office, hospitals, and long-term care facilities, the future of telemedicine, and how to get the best care during COVID-19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 19:50:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When Will Home Prices Fall? + The Affordable Housing Solution We All Want</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-229</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>When will housing prices drop? Will real estate prices go down, or are we stuck with ever-worsening affordability as home prices continue to rise? What’s the solution to affordable housing, […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 07:02:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hebbia raises nearly $100M Series B for AI-powered document search led by Andreessen Horowitz</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/27/hebbia-raises-nearly-100m-seriesb-for-ai-powered-document-search-led-by-andreessen-horowitz/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Hebbia, a startup using generative AI to search large documents and return answers, has raised a nearly $100 million Series B led by Andreessen Horowitz, according to three people with knowledge of the matter. The round valued the company between $700 million and $800 million, although TechCrunch couldn’t verify whether that valuation is pre- or […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 21:20:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mississippi Wants to Allow Some Votes From Jails and Prisons. Red Tape May Stop It.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/20/mississippi-voting-from-prison-and-jails</link><description>A new state law will allow more people in jails and prisons to cast absentee ballots, but many obstacles remain.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Personal Shopper: A Savvy Black Entrepreneur Guides You to Eczema-Friendly Clothes, Creams, Cosmetics, and More</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/savvy-black-entrepreneur-guides-eczema-friendly-clothes-creams-cosmetics?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>A savvy black entrepreneur guides you on an eczema-friendly shopping spree.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:54:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Buy Your First, Second, or Third Rental Property!</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-no-number-2</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>“The stack” method is how to buy rental property faster than you thought possible. With so many real estate investing beginners wondering how to build a real estate portfolio, especially […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 07:02:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Agility’s humanoid robots are going to handle your Spanx</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/27/agilitys-humanoid-robots-are-set-to-handle-your-spanx/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Digit’s first job will be moving totes around a Connecticut Spanx factory — which is most definitely not a euphemism. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 21:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Minneapolis Cop Who Beat Him Pleaded Guilty. He Still Fears the Department Won’t Change.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/16/police-minneapolis-beating-jaleel-stallings</link><description>Jaleel Stallings was swept up in the chaos of protests over George Floyd’s murder. The outcome changed his life.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Behind the Spike in Colorectal Cancer Among Young Americans</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/colorectal-cancer/news/20240515/behind-the-spike-in-colorectal-cancer-cases?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Colorectal cancer cases increased a whopping 333% among 15- to 19-year-olds and 185% among 20- to 24-year-olds from 1999 to 2020.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:59:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>