<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:09:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Opportunities in the Evolving Cannabis Consumption Market</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/08/13/the-changing-nature-of-cannabis-consumption/</link><description>For investors in the space, the changing cannabis consumption landscape opens challenges and opportunities in product creation, marketing, and targeting new consumer groups.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:46:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rich people are going to Walmart more—and they’re a key reason for the company’s recent success</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/08/15/walmart-earnings-high-income-rich-consumer-spending-sales/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/GettyImages-2157161515-e1723739943773.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>CEO Doug McMillon told analysts upper-income shoppers account for most of Walmart’s sales gains.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:01:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From Sandpiles to Angel Investments</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/08/12/from-sandpiles-to-angel-investments/</link><description>The presence of power law returns in angel investing, with the potential for significant contributions from a handful of investments, has implications for portfolio construction, investment strategies, and diversification.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 13:19:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fellow Gen Xers: That retirement crisis you’re losing sleep over is a ‘rewirement’ opportunity</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/08/15/gen-x-retirement-crisis-rewirement-opportunity/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/Anne-Chow-gen-x-retirement-e1723739934883.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Rather than retire after corporate life, Anne Chow decided to “rewire,” completely reimagining her life’s next chapter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 17:45:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: Pause to Think</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/08/09/book-review-pause-to-think/</link><description>This book is direct, delightful, and articulate in suggesting that we take a slow rather than fast approach to getting things thoughtfully done. It touches the minds and hearts of investment professionals.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 12:59:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What is ketamine? Potential dangers of the drug responsible for ‘Friends’ star Matthew Perry’s death</title><link>https://fortune.com/well/article/what-is-ketamine-risks-dangers-matthew-perry/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/GettyImages-631611692-e1702682578182.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Ketamine, popularly known as the party drug Special K, has recently been hailed as a breakthrough treatment for major depression, but it's not without risks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 17:20:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is Illiquidity a Blessing in Disguise for Some Investors?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/08/07/is-illiquidity-a-blessing-in-disguise-for-some-investors/</link><description>Rather than running away from illiquidity, investment professionals, investors, and regulators alike should recognize its potential benefits and consider a more balanced approach.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 17:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Goldman Sachs’ CEO was rejected twice by the firm. He’s since led it to over $50 billion in revenue</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/08/15/goldman-sachs-ceo-career-rejected-twice-david-solomon/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/GettyImages-2165078133-e1723738351620.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>You’re less likely to get hired at Goldman Sachs than accepted into Harvard.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 17:19:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scenario Planning, Foresight, and the Power of Imagination: Navigating an Uncertain Future</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/08/05/scenario-planning-foresight-and-the-power-of-imagination-navigating-an-uncertain-future/</link><description>By fostering resilience through the consideration of various outcomes, investment practitioners can better anticipate and manage the complexities and disruptions that characterize today's dynamic environment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 17:28:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Toxic metals found in tampons have set off alarm bells—the kind I responded to 35 years ago when starting my company</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/08/15/toxic-metals-tampons-personal-health-women-period-care-menstruation-wellness/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/Natracare-CEO-Susie-Hewson-on-toxic-tampons-e1723735085150.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Regulators should demand greater transparency in period care products, says Natracare founder and CEO Susie Hewson.</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:34:09 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>