<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 23:36:07 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Brooklyn Nets Subtly Update Logos, Introduce New Secondary Mark For 2024-25 Season</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/07/brooklyn-nets-subtly-update-logos-introduce-new-secondary-mark-for-2024-25-season/basketball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Brooklyn Nets have made several changes to their logo set for the 2024-25 season, including introducing a new secondary logo that depicts a stylized net.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 19:12:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Slutty Vegan's Pinky Cole Calls Out Rival for Adding Meat to Menu</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/07/slutty-vegan-pinky-cole-calls-out-rival-adding-meat-to-menu/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Slutty Vegan founder Pinky Cole is weighing in on the controversy surrounding Sage Regenerative Kitchen &amp; Brewery ... calling out their vegan rival for adding meat and cheese to its menu. ICYMI ... earlier in June, protesters began picketing in…</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 23:36:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PSG Pay Homage to Eiffel Tower With New Away Kit – Plus More European Kit Launches</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/05/psg-pay-homage-to-eiffel-tower-with-new-away-kit-plus-more-european-kit-launches/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Other clubs unveiling 2024-25 kits include Napoli, Wolves, West Ham, Stade de Reims, Mallorca, Real Betis, Villarreal, Bochum, Stuttgart, Mainz 05 and Union Berlin</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 20:20:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cristina Pilo Stripes Down In Animal Print Bikini</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/07/cristina-pilo-stripes-down-in-animal-print-bikini/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>This week's Summer Hot Shots feature is coming from an exotic green patch on a Virginia Key beach ... where wellness coach and IG hottie Cristina Pilo went wild in an animal print bikini! When Cristina isn't sharing her natural beauty with the…</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 23:36:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Look at the New NHL Practice Jersey Design</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/04/a-look-at-the-new-nhl-practice-jersey-design/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Thanks to the Utah Hockey Club, we got ourselves a look at the new NHL practice jersey design. With the switch from Adidas to Fanatics for 2024-25, we knew there’d be some changes to the on-ice NHL uniform. We’ve already seen that each team’s jersey will now include the Fanatics</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 22:20:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Squaw Valley 1960 Winter Olympics Torch Up For Auction</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/07/squaw-valley-1960-winter-olympics-torch-for-sale-auction/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>There's a super cool piece of sports history going up for sale ... one of the rarest Olympic torches ever made is hitting the auction block. Get a load of this ... the official torch from the 1960 Winter Olympics in Squaw Valley, CA is going to be…</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 23:36:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MLB Teams Wearing USA-Themed Caps Today for Fourth of July</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/04/mlb-teams-wearing-usa-themed-caps-today-for-fourth-of-july/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>All 30 Major League Baseball teams will wear stars-and-stripes-themed caps on-field during today’s games in honour of Independence Day in the United States. This year, all 30 clubs will wear a cream-coloured crown, with teams again having the option of a red or navy blue visor and button. One more</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 16:34:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trey Parker's Ex-Wife Boogie's L.A. House Broken Into, $500k Stolen Goods</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/07/trey-parker-baby-ex-wife-house-boogie-home-burglarized/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Trey Parker's ex-wife, Boogie Parker, is the latest victim in a string of burglaries hitting L.A. Law enforcement sources tell TMZ ... two burglars broke into Boogie's home, where she lives with her and Trey's daughter Betty, just before 9 PM last…</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 23:36:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2024 MLB All-Star Game Uniforms Revealed</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/03/2024-mlb-all-star-game-uniforms-revealed/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Major League Baseball has officially unveiled the uniforms their best players will wear when they take the field at Globe Life Field in Arlington later this month. The uniforms, as you’d expect, incorporate some of that Texas style, with an Old West style typeface across the chest and again in</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 02:02:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BKFC In Talks W/ Bam Margera, Looking To Add Ex-'Jackass' Star To Commentary Team</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/07/bam-margera-bkfc-in-talks-negotiating-deal-commentary-team-bare-knuckle/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Get used to seeing Bam Margera ringside at BKFC ... we've learned the former 'Jackass' star is negotiating with the promotion, and the aim is to bring him on as a broadcaster! 44-year-old Margera has been in talks with Bare Knuckle Fighting…</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 23:36:07 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>