<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 06:59:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Investment Manager Selection Is Hotting Up. Are You Ready for the Tough Questions?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/25/investment-manager-selection-is-hotting-up-are-you-ready-for-the-tough-questions/</link><description>Investment managers are being caught off guard by tougher questions from an increasingly sophisticated allocator market. Are you prepared for your next beauty parade?</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 03:17:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hollywood video game performers are going on strike because they worry studios could train AI to copy them</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/07/26/hollywood-video-game-performers-strike-worry-studios-train-ai-copy-them/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/AP24207710279901-e1721990241364.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The move comes after nearly two years of negotiations with gaming giants, including divisions of Activision, Warner Bros. and Walt Disney, over a new interactive media agreement.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 11:41:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Measuring Corporate Impact: The Gold Is in the Details</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/24/measuring-corporate-impact-the-gold-is-in-the-details/</link><description>Do the products and services of the companies you invest in create negative or positive material outcomes?</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 12:09:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kamala Harris can rebuild the crypto bridges burned by Biden—but time is of the essence</title><link>https://fortune.com/crypto/2024/07/26/kamala-harris-can-rebuild-the-crypto-bridges-burned-by-biden-but-time-is-of-the-essence/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/GettyImages-2162425804_ed970e.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Two progressive Democrats have some advice for their party's soon-to-be Presidential nominee.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is Widespread Crypto Adoption Inevitable?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/22/is-widespread-crypto-adoption-inevitable/</link><description>New technologies always face resistance, but demographic shifts imply there is a fierce tailwind behind crypto adoption, politically, economically, and financially.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 12:38:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Unilever customers swallowing ‘carry-over pricing’ from historic inflation helped it generate $6.4 billion in profits so far this year</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/07/26/unilever-customers-carry-over-pricing-historic-inflation-profits-cost-of-living/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/GettyImages-1234069831-e1721988877466.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The Ben &amp; Jerry's owner says its starting to see negative pricing in some markets, but Europeans are still absorbing the group's rising costs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 11:24:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: Shocks, Crises, and False Alarms</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/19/book-review-shocks-crises-and-false-alarms/</link><description>Carlsson-Szlezak and Swartz attempt to add fresh thinking on framing macro shocks that may often prove to be false alarms. Any general reader will obtain some key fresh insights with this work, and CFA charterholders will be offered an alternative to the conventional Wall Street approach to macro discussions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 13:06:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spain poised to become Europe’s data center capital as Amazon and Meta invest billions to kickstart development</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/07/26/spain-poised-europe-data-center-capital-as-amazon-meta-invest-billions-microsoft/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/GettyImages-1341554748_8039c9-e1721988317751.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Developing more industries and businesses in emptier regions in Spain is a major common goal across the political aisle.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 11:17:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Preserving the Dollar: The Role of CBDCs in Securing Economic Stability for Future Generations</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/16/preserving-the-dollar-the-role-of-cbdcs-in-securing-economic-stability-for-future-generations/</link><description>As financial systems evolve, preserving the US dollar's dominance will require skillful policy management and the integration of cutting-edge technologies.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:24:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Empty nesters are sad to see their kids leave the house. They can be even more distressed when they return home</title><link>https://fortune.com/well/article/adult-child-moving-back-home-with-parents-tips-to-manage/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/GettyImages-1473895642-e1721932831123.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Why grown kids moving back home can be a big adjustment for parents.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>