<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 06:58:40 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Rookie Reply: Rent-Raising Renovations, the 1% Rule, &amp; Quitting Real Estate</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-440</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>Real estate investing offers a roadmap to financial freedom, but it’s far from easy. If you’re feeling the stress of ownership, whether it’s due to a difficult tenant or unforeseen […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 07:02:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Terraform Labs co-founder and crypto fugitive, Do Kwon, set for extradition to South Korea</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/02/terraform-labs-co-founder-and-crypto-fugitive-do-kwon-set-for-extradition-to-south-korea/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>The Appellate Court of Montenegro ruled on Thursday that Terraform Labs co-founder, Do Kwon, should be returned to his home country, South Korea. The ruling confirmed an earlier decision in April from the High Court of Podgorica which rejected a request to extradite the crypto fugitive to the U.S. The extradition date for Kwon to […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 09:54:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Facing Rollbacks, Criminal Justice Reformers Argue Policies Make People Safer</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/01/california-illinois-crime-public-safety-reform</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Advocates are refining their rebuttal to “tough on crime” messaging: Don’t focus on punishment, but on reforms that improve public safety.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BiggerNews: The Market Bets on Mortgage Rates Falling, More Homes for Sale</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-999</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>Mortgage rates are set to fall this year and well into 2025, all while housing inventory steadily increases. We’re in the best housing inventory position since before the pandemic, so […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 07:02:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meta’s Threads crosses 200 million active users</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/02/metas-threads-cross-200-million-active-users/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>A day after Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg talked about his newest social media experiment Threads reaching “almost” 200 million users on the company’s Q2 2024 earnings call, the platform has touched the milestone. Instagram head Adam Mosseri confirmed that the Twitter rival has reached 200M active users in a post on Threads. Meta has taken […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 09:40:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Drawing Attention</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/01/news-inside-issue-17</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>News Inside Issue 17 features the opinions of justice-affected people on Trump’s felonies, and a nonfiction comic about death penalty mitigation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Retired Early at 44 by Buying These “Boring” Investments</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-551</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>Todd retired early at age forty-four, just three years after discovering the FIRE movement. The most interesting part? He quit without reaching his FIRE number. That’s right. After realizing he […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 07:01:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Connect with Google Cloud, Aerospace, Qualcomm and more at Disrupt 2024</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/01/connect-with-google-cloud-aerospace-qualcomm-and-more-at-disrupt-2024/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>TechCrunch Disrupt 2024 will be in San Francisco on October 28–30, and we’re already excited! Disrupt brings innovation for every stage of your startup journey, and we could not bring you this world-class event without our world-class partners. Take advantage of the opportunity to leverage the expertise and resources of some of tech’s leading companies. Their participation […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>These Private Centers Lack Oversight. Cuyahoga County Judges Send Kids Anyway.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/01/juvenile-justice-detention-prison-youth-treatment-cuyahoga-county</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>Courts are increasingly sending children to private youth care centers, spending millions while detention center overcrowding persists.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>3 Steps to Buying Your First (or Next) Small Multifamily Property</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-no-number-4</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>Small multifamily real estate investing could be your quickest path to financial freedom. These properties, from duplexes to quadplexes, typically offer higher cash flow and scaling opportunities than traditional single-family […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 07:02:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A comprehensive list of 2024 tech layoffs</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/01/tech-layoffs-2024-list/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>The tech layoff wave is still going strong in 2024. Following significant workforce reductions in 2022 and 2023, this year has already seen 60,000 job cuts across 254 companies, according to independent layoffs tracker Layoffs.fyi. Companies like Tesla, Amazon, Google, TikTok, Snap and Microsoft have conducted sizable layoffs in the first months of 2024. Smaller-sized […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 00:10:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What It Means to ‘Willie Horton’ a Political Candidate</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/31/willie-horton-donald-trump-kamala-harris</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>Donald Trump supporters run their version of the original dog-whistle attack ad against Kamala Harris. Here’s the history.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>THE HUGE Downside of No-Income-Tax States and a Hidden Housing Market Threat</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-239</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>Why is everyone ignoring this one severe housing market trend, what does a 2008 crash predictor think will happen in 2025, and why are homes starting to sit longer on […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 07:02:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Intel to lay off 15,000 employees</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/01/intel-to-lay-off-15000-employees/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Intel announced it would layoff more than 15% of its staff, or 15,000 employees, in a memo to employees on Thursday. The massive headcount is part of a large plan to reduce spending by $10 billion in 2025, following a dismal second quarter earnings report and outlook. “Our revenues have not grown as expected – […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 00:05:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Courts Cleared Jaleel Stallings. Trump’s Campaign Pulled Him Back Into the Political Muck.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/31/trump-election-kamala-harris-jaleel-stallings</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>Stallings was acquitted after an encounter with police during George Floyd protests in 2020, and one officer pleaded guilty to assaulting him.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>