<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:17:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>My Rental Burned Down! What I Wish I Knew Before It Happened</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-430</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>You get a call one day from the fire department, telling you, “You’ve had a house fire that’s destroyed your rental property.” What do you do first? Check on the […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 07:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>As Microsoft leaves its observer seat, OpenAI says it won’t have any more observers</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/10/as-microsoft-leaves-its-observer-seat-openai-says-it-wont-have-any-more-observers/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Months after Microsoft gained an observer seat on OpenAI’s board, the company is leaving the position of the non-voting seat. In a letter sent to OpenAI on Tuesday, Microsoft said that the company has seen enough progress being made in the AI company and is confident in its direction, according to Axios. OpenAI said that […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jackson, Mississippi, Wants Curfew Centers to Cut Crime. Here’s What Other Cities Learned.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/09/jackson-mississippi-youth-curfew-centers</link><description>After a teen’s murder, city officials hope a curfew and youth centers will get kids off the street. Young people are skeptical.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 11:00:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Tiny Homes a Good Investment? How a $50,000 Home Pencils Out</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-986</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Are tiny homes a good investment? For just $50,000, you can get a brand new tiny home investment—not even fifteen percent of the average single-family home price in the United […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 07:02:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deep tech startups with very technical CEOs raise larger rounds, research finds</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/09/now-theres-a-deep-tech-hardware-napkin-with-concrete-advice-for-european-founders/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>SaaS founders trying to figure out what it takes to raise their next round can refer to Point Nine’s famous yearly SaaS Funding Napkin. (The term refers to “back of the napkin” plans or calculations.) Now, European hardware deep tech teams have a similar resource from First Momentum, a pre-seed fund investing in technical B2B […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 07:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Love Beyond Bars: Miguel and Silvia</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/05/photo-essay-wrongful-conviction-love-story</link><description>While Miguel Solorio did 25 years for a crime he didn’t commit, his wife, Silvia, was right by his side. Here’s their California love story in pictures.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seeing Greene: How to Use Home Equity to Retire, Buy Rentals, or House Hack</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-985</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Should you use a HELOC to buy investment property? Would we use home equity to retire? When is it time to sell a performing property and exchange it for a […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 07:02:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Iceland is dodging the VC doldrums as Frumtak Ventures lands $87 million for its fourth fund</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/09/frumtak-ventures-87-million-fund-confirms-icelands-global-ambitions/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Iceland’s startup scene is punching above its weight. That’s perhaps in part because it kept the 2021 hype in check, but mostly because its tech ecosystem is coming of age. Iceland attracted the most venture capital per capita of all Nordic countries in 2023, but that stat is somewhat skewed by its relatively small population […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Crime Rates and the 2024 Election: What You Need to Know</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/27/trump-and-biden-spar-over-crime-rates-ahead-of-their-debate-what-do-we-really-know</link><description>As crime data again becomes a flashpoint in the presidential campaign, experts push for better national statistics.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>80-Hour Workweeks to Lean FIRE in 8 Years through Real Estate</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-544</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Reaching financial independence and becoming a millionaire before the age of thirty?! While this path requires several years of ruthless saving, smart investing, and unwavering discipline, there’s no reason why […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 07:01:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Index Ventures raises $2.3 billion for new venture and growth funds</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/09/index-ventures-raises-23-billion-for-new-venture-and-growth-funds/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Index Ventures is announcing $2.3 billion in new funds to finance the next generation of tech startups globally. These new funds are spread across different stages with $800 million dedicated to venture investment and $1.5 billion set aside for growth and late-stage companies. How do these funds compare to the previous ones? In 2021, Index […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Death Row Prisoner’s Parting Interview</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/24/texas-death-row-prisoner-final-interview</link><description>Days before his scheduled execution in Texas, Ramiro Gonzales speaks on faith, legacy — and apologizing to the family of his victim, Bridget Townsend.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Revised Affordable Housing Law In Florida Takes Opportunities Away From Developers</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/revisions-to-florida-live-local-act-take-opportunities-from-developers</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>A revision to Florida's Live Local Act reduces incentives for developers and increases building restrictions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 21:42:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anthropic’s Claude adds a prompt playground to quickly improve your AI apps</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/09/anthropics-claude-adds-a-prompt-playground-to-quickly-improve-your-ai-apps/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Prompt engineering became a hot job last year in the AI industry, but it seems Anthropic is now developing tools to at least partially automate it. Anthropic released several new features on Tuesday to help developers create more useful applications with the startup’s language model, Claude, according to a company blog post. Developers can now […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 01:11:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The New Battle Over an Old Institution: Forced Prison Labor</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/22/prison-slavery-forced-labor-lawsuits-bills</link><description>Inside the latest legal and legislative efforts to close state constitutional loopholes that allow slavery as punishment for a crime.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>