<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:39:41 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Investment Returns Are NOT Random</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/07/investment-returns-are-not-random/</link><description>Are investment returns random across time as Burton Malkiel suggests in his book, A Random Walk Down Wall Street? There is notable disagreement on this topic. This research finds that practitioners may need to rethink their portfolio optimization routines.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:22:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Billionaire Stan Druckenmiller says he'd give Bidenomics an ‘F’ because inflation almost came down before the Fed 'fumbled on the five-yard line’</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/07/stan-druckenmiller-bidenomics-inflation-economy-federal-reserve-jerome-powell-biden/</link><description>The famed investor accused the Federal Reserve and the Biden administration of misdiagnosing the severity of the pandemic’s economic crisis.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:13:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Generational Wealth: Does the Apple Fall Far From the Tree?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/06/generational-wealth-does-the-apple-fall-far-from-the-tree/</link><description>There is strong evidence that most “rich families” will be poorer after several generations. Some of the reasons for this are systemic like taxes. But most factors that diminish a family’s wealth over generations are the choices that heirs make.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 12:37:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Boeing is such a mess it plans to 'celebrate' its latest whistleblower—even though two just suddenly died</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/07/boeing-celebrate-whistleblower-faa-probe-scott-stocker-joshua-dean-john-barnett/</link><description>“It’s critical that every one of us speak up,” Boeing VP Scott Stocker told employees in a memo.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:09:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>State Capitalism in Private Markets: Mission Creep</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/03/state-capitalism-in-private-markets-mission-creep/</link><description>Governments relish mingling in markets. Yet, if past policies are any guide, taxpayers are being shortchanged.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 12:30:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Job seekers—you shouldn't balk when a test is part of your interview</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/07/job-seekers-interview-test/</link><description>Employers look for “can do” attitudes exemplifying grit, ambition, and problem-solving—not the opposite.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 20:51:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Implementation Shortfalls Hamstring Factor Strategies</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/01/implementation-shortfalls-hamstring-factor-strategies/</link><description>Smart rebalancing rules help portfolio managers capture more of the return that is inherent in their factor strategies. Concentrating on “priority best” trading improves factor portfolio performance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 11:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>200-page report offers ‘sobering look’ inside toxic workplace at the government agency that regulates bankers, sources say</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/07/fdic-toxic-workplace-investigation-harassment/</link><description>The investigation was prompted by a Wall Street Journal article that reported female bank examiners had left the FDIC because of its “sexualized, boys’ club environment.”</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 20:21:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IFRS Accounting Standard Will Support Better Investment Decisions</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/30/ifrs-accounting-standard-will-support-better-investment-decisions/</link><description>IFRS 18 responds to investors' concerns about challenges in comparing companies' financial performance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 11:34:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Former Yahoo CEO Marissa Mayer was Google’s first female engineer—only because she tried to delete a recruiter email and accidentally opened it instead</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/07/marissa-mayer-google-first-female-engineer-email-accident-yahoo/</link><description>Mayer's career can be boiled down to a single wrong keystroke.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 20:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>