<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 06:47:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Rethinking Retirement Planning Amidst Aging Demographic Frontiers</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/28/rethinking-retirement-planning-amidst-aging-demographic-frontiers/</link><description>Forward-thinking approaches to policy and wealth management are needed to ensure a better financial future across generations and income brackets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 20:32:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Reality star Judge Judy says Gen Z are difficult to work with because they got too many trophies</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/30/judge-judy-gen-z-difficult-work-with-too-many-trophies/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-961806598-1-e1717062098963.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Judge Judy says pandering parents have set Gen Z up to fail in the corporate rat race.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 11:26:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: The New World Economy in 5 Trends</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/24/book-review-the-new-world-economy-in-5-trends/</link><description>A diligent economist and an eclectic bookworm serve up an analysis of megatrends that will have the greatest impact on economies and investments: innovation, productivity, climate, multiglobalization, debt, and aging.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 12:22:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Florida allows doctors to perform C-sections outside of hospitals</title><link>https://fortune.com/well/2024/05/30/florida-allows-c-sections-outside-hospitals/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1310443783-e1716990829719.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>It is the first state to allow this, siding with a private equity-owned physicians group.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Factor Strategies Belong in Your Completion Portfolio Toolkit</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/23/factor-strategies-belong-in-your-completion-portfolio-toolkit/</link><description>Why wouldn't you include factor strategies in your completion portfolio? A review of the two commonly used approaches for managing institutional assets highlights their symbiotic nature.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 19:09:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jamie Dimon is so over spectators questioning whether his possible move from CEO to chairman would be bad for JPMorgan: 'How the hell do they know? There's no magic to it'</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/30/jamie-dimon-jpmorgan-ceo-chairman-potential-move/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2152634568-e1717061010527.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>"The board should do the right thing—if the chairman is getting in the way of the new CEO they should go. If the chairman is helping the new CEO in a million different ways they should stay."</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 10:57:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>For the Analyst: Peer Benchmarking Methods to Improve Earnings Forecasts</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/21/for-the-analyst-peer-benchmarking-methods-to-improve-earnings-forecasts/</link><description>Peer benchmarking is a vexing task for financial analysts but one that is critical for forecasting earnings. This straightforward measure can help find peers for relative performance, compensation, and valuation benchmarking.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 12:47:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Massive ransomware network taken down by ‘Endgame’ international police operation</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/30/eurojust-ransomware-network-endgame-operation/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1192886558-e1717062226307.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Police arrested four “high value” suspects, took down more than 100 servers and seized control of over 2,000 internet domains.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 10:44:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Building LLMs in the Open-Source Community: A Call to Action for Investment Professionals</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/20/building-llms-in-the-open-source-community-a-call-to-action-for-investment-professionals/</link><description>Large language models like ChatGPT are changing the way we think about investing and reshaping roles in the investment profession.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 16:26:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Google promises $2 billion investment in Malaysia as Big Tech splurges on Southeast Asia spending</title><link>https://fortune.com/asia/2024/05/30/google-promises-2-billion-investment-malaysia-data-centers-cloud-southeast-asia/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2104711727-e1717052162852.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Google's pledge follows multi-billion dollar investment pledges from Microsoft and Amazon targeting Southeast Asia.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 10:25:41 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>