<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 16:01:12 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Seeing Greene: Should I Start Flipping Houses in My Market? (How to Know)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-993</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Should I pay off my rentals or scale to more doors? Should I start flipping houses in my local but expensive market or go long-distance? When is the time to […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 07:02:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OpenAI-backed legaltech startup Harvey raises $100M</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/23/openai-backed-legaltech-startup-harvey-raises-100m/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Harvey, a startup building what it describes as an AI-powered “copilot” for lawyers, has raised $100 million in a Series C round led by GV, Google’s corporate venture arm. The tranche, which also had participation from heavy-hitting angels and VCs OpenAI, Kleiner Perkins, Sequoia Capital, Elad Gil and SV Angel, brings Harvey’s total raised to […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 19:01:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Five Things to Know About Kamala Harris’ Criminal Justice Record</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/21/kamala-harris-criminal-justice-record</link><description>Here’s where Vice President Kamala Harris, a former prosecutor, stands on important criminal justice issues.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 19:09:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2 Money Moves We’re Making TODAY to Prepare for a Potential Recession</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-548</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Are we in a recession? Are we headed for a recession? No one knows for certain, but you can never be too prepared for an economic downturn. Are you saving […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 07:01:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Digital banking startup Mercury abruptly shuttered service for startups in Ukraine, Nigeria, other countries</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/23/mercury-bank-fintech-sanctions-ukraine-nigeria/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Digital banking startup Mercury informed some founders that it is no longer serving customers in certain countries, including Ukraine. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 18:19:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Project 2025 Plans for Trump to Have Unprecedented Power Over the Justice Department</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/20/trump-project-2025-crime-prosecutors</link><description>The policy plan for a second Trump term would turn the department against progressive local prosecutors.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Here’s Why Real Estate Investors Are Turning to ATMs For Diversification</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/why-investors-are-turning-to-atm-investments-for-diversification</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>As real estate conditions continue to tighten, investors are turning to ATMs for steady cash flow.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 20:21:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The next fintech to go public may not be the one you expected</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/23/the-next-fintech-to-go-public-may-not-be-the-one-you-expected/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Welcome to TechCrunch Fintech! This week, we’re looking at Human Interest’s path toward an IPO, fintech’s newest unicorn, a slew of new fundraises, and more. To get a roundup of TechCrunch’s biggest and most important fintech stories delivered to your inbox every Tuesday at 8:00 a.m. PT, subscribe here. The big story SMB-focused 401k provider […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 18:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Love Beyond Bars: Jules and Samantha</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/19/photo-essay-werkheisers-wrongful-conviction</link><description>Jules and Samantha Werkheiser fought their wrongful convictions for over a decade. Here’s their journey of survival — and motherhood — in pictures.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Month Seven of Our 1031 Exchange: We’re Investing in… Restaurants?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/1031-investor-journal-seven</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>With $975,000 to play with, we're looking at options outside of residential real estate.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 20:11:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Waymo-Zeekr robotaxi has come to San Francisco</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/23/the-waymo-zeekr-robotaxi-has-come-to-san-francisco/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Waymo has started testing a new robotaxi built by Chinese electric automaker Zeekr on public roads in San Francisco. Waymo has “less than a handful” of the Zeekr vehicles in San Francisco today and isn’t driving them autonomously yet. Still, the fact that Waymo has hit the roads with a roomier, custom-built robotaxi signals the […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 17:30:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meet the New Generation of Unarmed First Responders in This New Podcast Series</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/18/police-north-carolina-podcast-mental-health</link><description>“The Fifth Branch,” a podcast from The Marshall Project and Tradeoffs, examines new, alternative ways to respond to 911 crisis calls.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Department of Justice’s Next Target: Buyer Agents</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/department-of-justice-targets-buyer-agent-loopholes</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>The DOJ is planning further changes to agent commission structures, which could lead to a significant reduction in traditional commission rates.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 19:52:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TechCrunch Minute: Where Kamala Harris stands on tech issues</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/video/where-kamala-harris-stands-on-tech-issues/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>This weekend, President Biden announced that he would suspend his campaign for president, and he endorsed his vice president, Kamala Harris. We still don’t know if she will ultimately be the candidate that goes toe-to-toe with Donald Trump in November, but we do know that Silicon Valley has opinions. Like Trump’s VP pick J.D. Vance, […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What We Know About J.D. Vance’s Legislative Action on Criminal Justice</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/17/what-we-know-from-sen-j-d-vance-s-legislative-action-on-criminal-justice-issues</link><description>On immigration and more, Vance has defended and legislated former President Donald Trump’s policy goals.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 23:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>