<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:24:33 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Bowling Green Falcons Unveil New Throwback-Inspired Football Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/14/bowling-green-falcons-unveil-new-throwback-inspired-football-uniforms/college/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Bowling Green recently unveiled mockups of three new uniforms for this season that are reminiscent of the Falcons' look during the 1980s and 1990s.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 19:17:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Florida Gator Who Ate Homeless Woman Dissected, New Body Cam Video Shows Scene</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/13/florida-gator-who-ate-homeless-woman-dissected-bodycam-video-photos/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>The Florida alligator that ate a homeless woman last year got killed and cut open by officials once they discovered the grisly act -- and now ... we're seeing all the aftermath on tape. TMZ has obtained new photos/video from the Florida Fish and…</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:24:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Utah Hockey Club Unveils Logos, Uniforms, Colours, and Name for 2024-25</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/13/utah-hockey-club-unveils-logos-uniforms-colours-and-name-for-2024-25/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>It’s officially official: Utah has an NHL team… and a name, logo, colours, and uniform (even if those last four are just temporary). Today, the National Hockey League made it official by announcing the Utah Hockey Club would join the league in time for the 2024-25 season, absorbing the roster,</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 01:30:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bebe Rexha Rips G-Eazy as 'Stuck Up Ungrateful Loser'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/13/bebe-rexha-rips-g-eazy-ungrateful-loser/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Bebe Rexha is NOT interested in working with G-Eazy again ... blasting him as an "ungrateful loser" in a since-deleted social media post. The singer posted, then deleted a text message from a member of her team asking if Bebe had any interest…</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:24:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rising Tides: Halifax NSL Club Unveils Name, Crest</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/13/rising-tides-halifax-nsl-club-unveils-name-crest/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Nova Scotia-based club is third of Northern Super League's six teams for inaugural season in 2025 to unveil their visual identity system</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 00:28:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Young Girl Gets Slapped in the Face by Random Woman in Brazil, Video</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/14/young-girl-slapped-walking-street-brazil-video/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Random street attacks are not just an issue in the U.S. of A ... they're also a problem in South America -- with the latest victim being a child in Brazil and the incident was all caught on video. Check out the surveillance footage ... the girl was…</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:24:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MLB Releases Fourth of July Caps for 2024</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/13/mlb-releases-fourth-of-july-caps-for-2024/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Major League Baseball and New Era have unveiled the stars-and-stripes-themed caps that players, managers, coaches, and umpires will wear on-field for Independence Day in the United States on Thursday, July 4, 2024. This year, all 30 clubs will wear a cream-coloured crown, with teams again having the option of a</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 20:03:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pope Francis Meets With Hollywood's Biggest Comedians at Vatican</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/14/pope-francis-meets-comedians-whoopi-goldberg-fallon-colbert-vatican/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Pope Francis received a warm -- and very funny -- welcome at the Vatican from some of the biggest comedians in America, including Jimmy Fallon, Chris Rock and Whoopi Goldberg. The pontiff greeted a TON of famous jokesters Friday along with more…</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:24:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cardinals &amp; Giants Pay Tribute to Negro Leagues with Throwback Uniforms at Rickwood Field Next Week</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/12/cardinals-giants-pay-tribute-to-negro-leagues-with-throwback-uniforms-at-rickwood-field-next-week/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The special throwback uniforms for the Major League Baseball and Minor League Baseball games at Rickwood Field next week have been unveiled. The Major League game, officially known as “MLB at Rickwood Field,” will be played on June 20th. The San Francisco Giants and St. Louis Cardinals will wear uniforms</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 17:47:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bad Bunny Concert Targeted for Would-Be Race War Mass Shooting, Feds Say</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/14/bad-bunny-concert-targeted-race-war-mass-shooting-federal-indictment/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>An Arizona man allegedly tried to spark a race war ahead of the 2024 election by carrying out a mass shooting at a Bad Bunny concert ... so claim the feds, who stopped it. A new indictment alleges 58-year-old Mark Adams Prieto -- who's white --…</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:24:33 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>