<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 06:57:52 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Cincinnati Bengals Reveal Updated Turf Design</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/02/cincinnati-bengals-reveal-updated-turf-design/football/</link><description>The Cincinnati Bengals are in the process of installing new FieldTurf at Paycor Stadium and will have an updated design as a result.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 22:33:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Robert De Niro Did Not Shout at Pro-Palestinian Protesters, Rep Says</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/02/robert-de-niro-did-not-shout-pro-palestine-protesters-israel-hamas/</link><description>Robert De Niro did NOT yell at pro-Palestinian protesters in NYC ... this despite a video making the rounds online suggesting otherwise. The actor was filmed shouting at a group of individuals last week in NYC, accusing the crowd of "talking…</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 06:57:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Liverpool FC Pays Homage to Treble-Winning 1984 Squad With 2024-25 Home Kit</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/02/liverpool-fc-pays-homage-to-treble-winning-1984-squad-with-2024-25-home-kit/soccer/</link><description>Front and back of shirt feature yellow pinstripe pattern that spells out "YWNA" for club motto, "You'll Never Walk Alone"</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:19:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ryan Gosling Movie 'The Fall Guy' Criticized For Johnny Depp, Amber Heard Joke</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/02/fall-guy-movie-criticism-johnny-depp-amber-heard-joke/</link><description>Ryan Gosling's new action flick is stirring up controversy ... 'cause fans are pissed about a throwaway line in the final film -- and, it's all about Johnny Depp and Amber Heard. "The Fall Guy" -- which is out Friday, but seems to have been viewed…</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 06:57:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ope! Madison Mallards unveil another alternate</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/02/ope-madison-mallards-unveil-another-alternate/baseball/</link><description>There are a lot of theories about the origins of the quirky exclamation “Ope!”—none of which stand up to any real scrutiny. More onomatopoeia than actual word, the term has been likened to “oops” or “oh” plus the letter P, and associated with most anywhere human beings have made inadvertent</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 12:07:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mariah The Scientist Arrested for Brawl in Atlanta Lounge</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/02/mariah-the-scientist-arrested-brawl-assault-atlanta-fight/</link><description>Mariah The Scientist was arrested and booked in Atlanta Wednesday night ... after a woman told cops Mariah laid down a savage beating for no apparent reason According to a Fulton County police report, obtained by TMZ Hip Hop, a woman named…</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 06:57:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tri-City Chili Peppers to play “Cosmic Baseball” under black lights</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/01/tri-city-chili-peppers-to-play-cosmic-baseball-under-black-lights/baseball/</link><description>Nearly a century after the Negro Leagues’ Kansas City Monarchs became the first professional baseball team to host a baseball game under artificial lights, the Coastal Plain League’s Tri-City Chili Peppers are putting their own spin on that innovation. The team will play “Cosmic Baseball” under powerful black lights that</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 02:45:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Charles Barkley Trolled With Billboards After Galveston Diss</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/02/charles-barkley-trolled-with-billboards-after-galveston-diss/</link><description>Charles Barkley's feud with Galveston, Texas is far from over -- the NBA legend was just targeted with a bunch of billboards throughout the city after dissing it on national television!! As we previously reported, Chuck ruffled some feathers in the…</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 06:57:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rockford Rivets to rebrand as Screw City Sock Monkeys</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/01/rockford-rivets-to-rebrand-as-screw-city-sock-monkeys/baseball/</link><description>The collegiate summer level Rockford Rivets will pay tribute to their hometown’s textile and manufacturing heritage when they take to the field as the Screw City Sock Monkeys for two games this season. The Sock Monkeys nickname derives from Rockford, Illinois’s claim to “Home of the Sock Monkey”—a term the</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 02:03:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sia Legally Files to Change Her Name with Official Court Request</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/02/sia-files-legally-change-name-court-request-year-after-wedding/</link><description>Sia is switching up her name -- running to court to ask a judge to let her go by something different ... although, it's just the back half that's getting tweaked here. In new court docs, obtained by TMZ, the musician asks for her name to change…</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 06:57:52 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>