<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 07:25:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Bullish Breadth (Act Fast)</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/bullish-breadth-act-fast/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, it's Ross Givens here with the Chart of the Day. The percentage of stocks trading above their 50-day moving average, a key metric for medium-term momentum, has surged, signaling a potential continuation of the bull market. Nearly double the levels seen during the April pullback, it mirrors the market's upward trajectory observed from February to mid-March. This resurgence indicates an opportunity for swift action. Learn more about the implications in my detailed analysis below. The post Bullish Breadth (Act Fast) appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New hybrid-powered Porsche 911 is 8.7 seconds quicker around the 'Ring</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/13/porsche-911-hybrid-nurburgring-time/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/10174730/2025-Porsche-911-on-Nurburgring.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Porsche , Future Vehicles , Hybrid , Luxury , Performance Continue reading New hybrid-powered Porsche 911 is 8.7 seconds quicker around the 'Ring New hybrid-powered Porsche 911 is 8.7 seconds quicker around the 'Ring originally appeared on Autoblog on Mon, 13 May 2024 03:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Financial Freedom in 3 Years by Scaling with Small Multifamily</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-405</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>MANY people invest in real estate for financial freedom. Unfortunately, not all investors get there. The truth is that a little cash flow won’t allow you to quit your W2 […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 07:02:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Soak Up the Sunny Vibes With the Feel-Good Book of the Season</title><link>https://bookriot.com/read-this-book-may-13-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/funny-story.png</image_url><description>Have you read any Emily Henry books yet?</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 553</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-553/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-553</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Tools and technology change rapidly. Yet as wonderful as technology can be, it doesn’t replace the need for human connection through interactions. Keep this in mind as you are searching for a new job. It’s your human connections that often open doors! In this week’s collection of news and tips for job seekers, you’ll find: […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 553 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 12:19:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A case for public preschool: New study reveals preschool benefits to be longer-lasting and substantial</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/benefits-of-public-preschool/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=benefits-of-public-preschool</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Preschool lays a foundation for elementary school students to succeed. In the United States, as children approach kindergarten entry, it is increasingly common for 4-year-olds to be in non-parental group care and education, often in a center- or school-based setting where they can learn alongside peers. For children from low-income communities, […] The post A case for public preschool: New study reveals preschool benefits to be longer-lasting and substantial appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 08:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>5 things to know before the stock market opens Monday</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/13/5-things-to-know-before-the-stock-market-opens-monday-may-13.html</link><description>Here are the most important news items that investors need to start their trading day.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 12:23:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2023 NBA turnovers per game leaders</title><link>https://deadspin.com/2023-nba-turnovers-per-game-leaders-1851036203</link><description>This article is based on data from Sportradar. Read more...</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:10:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>These Amazon Beauty Deals Will Have You Glowing All Summer Long</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1401410/these-amazon-beauty-deals-will-have-you-glowing-all-summer-long-goop-cerave-rinna-beauty-more?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>We independently selected these deals and products because we love them, and we think you might like them at these prices. E! has affiliate relationships, so we may get a commission if you...</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Your Portfolio Should Include Scarce Assets</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/10/why-your-portfolio-should-include-scarce-assets/</link><description>Portfolios that include both productive and scarce assets can deliver similar performance to the S&amp;P 500 with less risk than those that hold only productive assets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:34:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ex-Peloton director says disclosing pregnancy hit job prospects: ‘100% of the companies I told went from scheduling interviews to declining to bring me in for a final round’</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/13/ex-peloton-director-kate-winick-disclosing-pregnancy-hit-job-prospects-scheduling-interviews-final-round/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1419239018-e1715597829752.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Kate Winick was reassured that "companies just want to hire the right people" after being laid off from her director role at Peleton last year while pregnant—she's still job hunting.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 12:23:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amazon Home Refresh Tips</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/amazon-home-refresh-tips/</link><description>Embrace the mid-spring refresh with Amazon and give your home a vibrant makeover for the season. Amazon makes it easy… The post Amazon Home Refresh Tips appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 05:00:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pakistani driver in Canada tells his passenger that if they were in Pakistan he would kidnap her just because she was a woman and alone. WTF!!!</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/a2vPmmD</link><description>Tags: islam , terrorist , disgusting , wtf , politics 6358 points, 466 comments.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 12:20:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>For the Land: Cleveland Guardians Unveil New City Connect Uniform Set</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/12/for-the-land-cleveland-guardians-unveil-new-city-connect-uniform-set/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>These uniforms are CLE-an. The Cleveland Guardians became the latest team to unveil their Nike MLB City Connect Uniform, doing so via a video posted to their social media accounts late Sunday night. Overall, the navy blue, red, and sandstone uniform draws most of its inspiration from the iconic Guardians</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 01:00:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Permira is taking Squarespace private in $6.6 billion deal</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/13/permira-is-taking-squarespace-private-in-6-6-billion-deal/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Website building software provider Squarespace is going private in an all-cash deal that values the company on equity basis at $6.6 billion, or a $6.9 billion enterprise valuation. The acquiring company is U.K.-based private equity firm Permira, which acquired a majority stake in Tel Aviv-based cybersecurity firm BioCatch just a couple of weeks ago. Founded in […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 12:15:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When Bad Cops Become Private Security Guards</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/11/police-private-guard-florida-chicago</link><description>There’s growing evidence that former officers with troubling histories of abuse can easily find second careers in private security.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cinnamon Roll Casserole</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/cinnamon-roll-casserole/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Get ready for a tasty treat with this easy cinnamon roll casserole! Using canned cinnamon rolls, this casserole is so…</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anita Baker Cancels ATL Show at Last Minute, Upends Mother's Day Gifts</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/12/anita-baker-cancels-last-minute-atlanta-mothers-day-concert/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Some Anita Baker fans are scrambling for Mother's Day gifts this morning after the singer had to pull the plug on her show in Atlanta just a few minutes before it was supposed to start. Anita's show at State Farm Arena was packed Saturday night, as…</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 07:25:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 7-Hour Itch: 3 Women With Eczema Describe the Ways They Combat Nighttime Flare-Ups</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/seven-hour-itch-women-eczema-combat-nighttime-flares?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Three women with eczema describe how they combat nighttime flare-ups.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 09:09:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/how-to-remove-wallpaper/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Wallpaper has made a big comeback as a trendy home design choice. But despite its resurgence, there are still plenty of us dealing with dingy, dated, or downright ugly old wallpaper we don’t want. In our old home, we had to remove wallpaper in so many rooms: the kitchen, the dining room, the foyer, and two different bathrooms! As we traveled from room to room removing wallpaper, we tested 4 different methods, and today we’ll share what we learned. Removing wallpaper doesn’t require special tools or lots of money. It’s a totally doable project for any homeowner. However, it can be a tedious process that can take elbow grease and patience, depending on the size of your room and the stubbornness of your wallpaper. But having removed several rooms worth of decades-old wallpaper, we can confidently say it’s worth the effort! You can also check out more before and afters of our once-wallpapered rooms. Continue reading How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:21:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Bull Market is Still Young</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/this-bull-market-is-still-young/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, it's Ross Givens here with the Chart of the Day. In analyzing historical data, it's evident that bull markets typically extend for years from the bear market bottom to the peak. Surprisingly, our current market cycle has seen a peak just 19 months post the last bear market bottom, contrasting with the typical 61-month duration. This insight suggests that the current bull market is still in its infancy, promising ample opportunities ahead. Stay tuned as I delve into the implications of this data in today's analysis. The post This Bull Market is Still Young appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2025 Aston Martin Vantage First Drive Review: Big changes, big big power</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/12/2025-aston-martin-vantage-first-drive/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/10181145/2025-Aston-Martin-Vantage-in-Cosmopolitan-Yellow-action-front.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Aston Martin , First Drives , Coupe , Luxury , Performance Continue reading 2025 Aston Martin Vantage First Drive Review: Big changes, big big power 2025 Aston Martin Vantage First Drive Review: Big changes, big big power originally appeared on Autoblog on Sun, 12 May 2024 19:01:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 00:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From Broke College Graduate to Financial Freedom While Living Abroad</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-952</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>You don’t have to race to financial independence to get there. Dave Meyer, VP of Market Intelligence at BiggerPockets, took his time building up passive income, and years later, it’s […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 07:02:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amazing Romance Novels by Asian North American Writers</title><link>https://bookriot.com/romance-by-asian-north-american-authors/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/romance-asian-north-american-authors.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>A Hollywood romance, wedding shenanigans, international foodie fun, and more await!</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 552</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-552/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-552</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>When you are searching for a job, you will inevitably run into unexpected scenarios. You will have questions, experience self-doubt and even feel discouraged. You’ll also experience great wins, meet wonderful people and discover new things about yourself. That’s the roller-coaster of job search. Consider Summary Sunday your resource for getting questions answered and showing […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 552 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 11:37:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fathers’ views on family and work after COVID-19 lockdowns</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/fathers-views-on-family-and-work-after-covid-19-lockdowns/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fathers-views-on-family-and-work-after-covid-19-lockdowns</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Fathers often want to be present for their children and contribute to household tasks, but they can lack opportunities and confidence; they may see themselves as “helpers” instead of parents. Australian fathers in our small study reported that they spent more time with their children during the COVID-19 lockdowns, and they […] The post Fathers’ views on family and work after COVID-19 lockdowns appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>U.S. sounds alarm as thousands in Georgia's capital protest 'Kremlin-style' foreign influence bill</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/13/thousands-in-georgias-capital-protest-russia-style-foreign-agents-law.html</link><description>White House national security advisor Jake Sullivan said over the weekend that the U.S. was "deeply alarmed" about democratic backsliding in Georgia.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 12:12:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2023 NHL goals against average leaders</title><link>https://deadspin.com/2023-nhl-goals-against-average-leaders-1851061822</link><description>This article is based on data from Sportradar. Read more...</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:10:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sink Your Teeth Into Robert Pattinson's Unforgettable Year</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1401256/sink-your-teeth-into-robert-pattinsons-unforgettable-year?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>Robert Pattinson has entered a new dawn. Because on May 13, the Twilight alum turned 38. And if you were to tell him on his birthday last year what 37 would bring, you might need to preface it...</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coiled Tight: Smaller Companies Are Primed for Outperformance</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/08/coiled-tight-smaller-companies-are-primed-for-outperformance/</link><description>Small-cap companies are poised for a rebound. The sector is best approached through an active investment strategy where expertise and a deep understanding of the individual businesses and their risk-and-reward characteristics are necessary for success.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:40:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Smartphone giant Xiaomi is making a new move on Tesla</title><link>https://fortune.com/asia/2024/05/13/smartphone-giant-xiaomi-tesla-selling-suv-model-y-2025/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2151868758-e1715597589665.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>An SUV would mark a big expansion of Xiaomi’s $10 billion EV endeavor, spearheaded personally by billionaire co-founder Lei Jun.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 11:55:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shell Season</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/shell-season/</link><description>Spring welcomes the captivating allure of shell season. As nature awakens and warmth spreads, ocean treasures inspire wardrobe choices. This… The post Shell Season appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:58:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>One reload for the cost of three</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/aAyVPDE</link><description>Tags: random 3006 points, 282 comments.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 12:20:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MLS’s Portland Timbers Introduce Tillamook as New Front-of-Shirt Sponsor</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/12/mlss-portland-timbers-introduce-tillamook-as-new-front-of-shirt-sponsor/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Oregon-based dairy farmers' cooperative takes over prime real estate on front of Timbers' shirts; previous sponsor dropped after only one game</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 23:40:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Buymeacoffee’s founder has built an AI-powered voice note app</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/13/buymeacoffees-founder-has-built-an-ai-powered-voice-note-app/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>AI-powered tools like OpenAI’s Whisper have enabled many apps to make transcription an integral part of their feature set for personal note-taking, and the space has quickly flourished as a result. Apps like AudioPen, Cleft Notes, and TalkNotes have proliferated across app stores and the Internet, but most offer a pretty limited feature set: They […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 08:51:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Rare Bright Spot for a Canine Lover Doing Time: Raising Puppies to Become Service Dogs</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/10/service-dogs-training-prison-essay</link><description>Adam Roberts reflects on the highs and occasional lows of training Labrador retrievers for the Puppies Behind Bars program.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Thai Chicken Salad</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/thai-chicken-salad/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Crunchy and bright, this Thai Chicken Salad with creamy peanut dressing is bursting with flavor, texture and deliciousness! Prep it in…</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tom Brady Sends Mother's Day Wish to Exes Gisele, Bridget After Roast Jokes</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/12/tom-brady-mothers-day-tribute-gisele-bundchen-pissed-roast-divorce-jokes/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Tom Brady's attempting, perhaps, his greatest comeback ever -- kicking off Mother's Day with warm words for the mothers of his children, one week after they took several stray shots during his roast. Tom posted several shots of his own mom, Galynn,…</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 07:25:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Mother’s Love: The Challenges of Parenting a Child With Eczema</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/mothers-love-challenges-parenting-child-eczema?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Two moms reveal the great lengths they went to in their determination to give their children relief and good health.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 09:18:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aglaonema Plant – Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/aglaonema-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Aglaonema, also called the Chinese Evergreen Plant, is an easy-care houseplant that lives happily in many lighting conditions – even a dark corner of our daughter’s room. There are dozens of different Aglaonema varieties, most with large tropical foliage and colors ranging from silvery-green, red, and even vibrant pink. They’re also tough to kill, so they’re a great option for forgetful plant owners or anyone looking for an easy win in the plant department. These truly have been very low maintenance for us. We purchased our two Aglaonemas (pronounced ag-lee-oh-neem-ah ) to put atop our daughter’s closet. It’s sometimes hard to distinguish different varieties, but we believe that’s an Aglaonema Silver (right) and either a Candy Cane or Princess Silver Queen (left). Aglaonema Quick Facts Here’s what you need to know about your Aglaonema at a glance: Latin name : Aglaonema is the genus under which there are 21 recognized species . Continue reading Aglaonema Plant – Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:47:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Earnings Divergence Opportunity</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/the-earnings-divergence-opportunity/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, it's Ross Givens here with the Chart of the Day. Amidst economic concerns, analysts have defied expectations by boosting their earnings estimates for S&amp;P 500 companies. This unexpected trend challenges prevailing pessimism about the market's trajectory. In today's analysis, I delve into what this shift means and why it's crucial not to let pessimism hinder your pursuit of current market opportunities. The post The Earnings Divergence Opportunity appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mercedes-AMG planning a 585-hp V8 for the AMG CLE 63</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/12/mercedes-amg-planning-a-585-hp-v8-for-the-amg-cle-63/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/12020438/2025_mercedes_amg_cle_53.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Mercedes-Benz , Convertible , Coupe , Future Vehicles , Luxury , Performance Continue reading Mercedes-AMG planning a 585-hp V8 for the AMG CLE 63 Mercedes-AMG planning a 585-hp V8 for the AMG CLE 63 originally appeared on Autoblog on Sun, 12 May 2024 13:01:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 18:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Squatters’ Rights: What Lawyers Want Landlords to Know in 2024 w/Denise Medina and Patrick MacQueen</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-216</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Squatters’ rights have been a serious subject of debate over the past few years. It seems that more and more investors and even one-off landlords are dealing with squatters staying […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 07:02:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10 Best New Fantasy Books by Asians and Pacific Islanders</title><link>https://bookriot.com/new-aapi-fantasy-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/aapi-fantasy-may-2024.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>Celebrate AAPI Heritage month with these exciting fantasy reads!</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>While a little competition in the workplace might help bring out the best in everyone involved, an atmosphere rooted in envy, fear, or jealousy can do the exact opposite. This post will help you recognize signs that your coworker is threatened by you, and help you navigate the situation. 1. They Don’t Want You Involved […] The post 10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:07:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Strong Latine Identity Supports U.S. Latine Children’s Well-Being</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/a-strong-latine-identity-supports-u-s-latine-childrens-well-being/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=a-strong-latine-identity-supports-u-s-latine-childrens-well-being</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key Takeaways for caregivers Children tend to have better health and well-being when they have a strong ethnic identity (affinity and adoption of ethnicity-based self-concept). A traditional Latine cultural value (familismo) that emphasizes family bonds is also associated with better developmental outcomes. Caregivers can support the development of U.S. Latine children (and possibly other children […] The post A Strong Latine Identity Supports U.S. Latine Children’s Well-Being appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 03:03:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GameStop shares jump 30% as trader 'Roaring Kitty' who drove meme craze posts again</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/13/gme-jumps-as-trader-roaring-kitty-who-drove-meme-craze-posts-again.html</link><description>GameStop shares rallied more than 21% in the premarket Monday after "Roaring Kitty" posted for the first time in roughly three years.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 12:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2023 NBA steals per game leaders</title><link>https://deadspin.com/2023-nba-steals-per-game-leaders-1851036198</link><description>This article is based on data from Sportradar. Read more...</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:10:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kate Gosselin Shares Rare Pic of 4 of Her and Jon's Sextuplets</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1401439/kate-gosselin-shares-rare-photo-of-4-of-her-and-jons-sextuplets-at-their-20th-birthday-celebration?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>Oops, you blinked and the Gosselin sextuplets turned 20. Kate Gosselin shared a rare photo of four out of the six of her and ex-husband Jon Gosselin's youngest children May 12, Mother's Day, two...</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 00:55:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Investment Returns Are NOT Random</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/07/investment-returns-are-not-random/</link><description>Are investment returns random across time as Burton Malkiel suggests in his book, A Random Walk Down Wall Street? There is notable disagreement on this topic. This research finds that practitioners may need to rethink their portfolio optimization routines.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:22:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Beijing narrowly escapes having to cover the debts of developer Country Garden</title><link>https://fortune.com/asia/2024/05/13/country-garden-makes-interest-payment-avoids-guarantor-paying-debt-china-real-estate-crisis/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2074404077-e1715592401291.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Last week, Country Garden revealed that it had missed an interest payment on onshore bonds guaranteed by a state-owned financial firm.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 11:45:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Discovering My Avaline Favorites</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/discovering-my-avaline-favorites/</link><description>Thank you to Avaline for sponsoring this post. Spring symbolizes fresh starts and cleaner living. In my quest to align… The post Discovering My Avaline Favorites appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:50:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Happy Endings, yay</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/ayNp8nq</link><description>Tags: funny , hol up 4832 points, 136 comments.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 12:20:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Serie A Players Honor Moms By Putting Their Names on Game Jerseys</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/12/serie-a-players-honor-moms-by-putting-their-names-on-game-jerseys/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Players on seven Serie A clubs wear mothers' first names or maiden names on the backs of their jerseys in matches held all weekend long</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 22:58:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Google partners with Airtel to offer cloud and genAI products to Indian businesses</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/13/google-partners-with-airtel-to-offer-cloud-and-genai-products-to-indian-businesses/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Airtel, India's second-largest telco, is partnering with Google Cloud to develop and deliver cloud and GenAI solutions to Indian businesses. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 08:49:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Marshall Project Wins the Dart Award for “The Mercy Workers”</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/06/the-marshall-project-wins-the-dart-award-for-the-mercy-workers</link><description>Our feature on mitigation specialists who help save people from the death penalty was recognized for making “significant contributions to public understanding of trauma-related issues.”</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Meal Plan #4</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/weekly-menu-plan-4/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Take advantage of this weekly meal plan that has all the favorite recipes that families love! It is so easy…</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Taylor Swift Fans Shocked by Baby Left on Floor During Paris Concert</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/12/taylor-swift-baby-floor-eras-tour-concert-paris/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Taylor Swift fans have bad blood with a fellow Swiftie who left their infant lying on the floor of the Paris arena where Taylor's performing. The shocking photo has gone viral, for obvious reasons, after it was posted by a woman who says she was at…</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 07:25:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Working It Out: How to Minimize Eczema Flare-ups at the Gym and on the Job</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/minimize-eczema-flare-ups-gym-job?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Three keys to managing your eczema at the gym and then heading off to a productive and itch-free workday.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 07:30:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Corn Plant – Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/corn-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Corn plants ( Dracaena fragrans ) are popular low-maintenance houseplants you’ve probably seen at the nursery, home improvement store, or doctor’s office. I even had one in my college dorm room! You can recognize them by their spear-shaped leaves and woody, cane-line trunks that can grow up to 6 feet tall indoors. But did you know there are several varieties of corn plants? We didn’t! Heck, we didn’t even realize some of our smaller houseplants were in the same corn plant family! Currently, we own two smaller varieties of corn plants, pictured above. The one on the left is a Dracaena Limelight ( Dracaena fragrans ‘Limelight’ ) and the taller plant is a Draecanea Dorado ( Dracaena fragrans ‘Dorado’ ). We actually have several limelights around because we love their vibrant color on shelves, tabletops, and windowsills. Corn Plant Quick Facts Latin name : Dracaena fragrans Common names : Corn plant, cornstalk plant, false palms Light : Bright, indirect light but can tolerate lower-light conditions Watering : Keep soil moist, but not soggy. Continue reading Corn Plant – Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 17:37:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Opportunity Window is Closing</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/the-opportunity-window-is-closing/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, it's Ross Givens here with the Chart of the Day. In market dynamics, volatility often mirrors market trends – as volatility rises, markets tend to dip, and as it falls, markets typically climb. Looking at historical data, this relationship holds true across various market conditions. Currently, with volatility showing signs of calming down, it suggests that the market might be on its way out of the recent pullback. Discover more insights on this intriguing correlation in today's analysis below. The post The Opportunity Window is Closing appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Junkyard Gem: 2007 Audi S8</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/12/junkyard-gem-2007-audi-s8/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/04/27122225/99-2007-Audi-S8-in-Colorado-junkyard-photo-by-Murilee-Martin.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Audi , Automotive History , Luxury , Special and Limited Editions , Performance , Classics , Sedan Continue reading Junkyard Gem: 2007 Audi S8 Junkyard Gem: 2007 Audi S8 originally appeared on Autoblog on Sun, 12 May 2024 12:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Florida Is the Perfect Rent-to-Own Market—Should You Take Advantage?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/why-florida-is-the-perfect-rent-to-own-market</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>The Sunshine State offers the exact combination of factors that make this investment option attractive.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 14:08:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Biggest and Comfiest Reading Chairs to Cozy Up In</title><link>https://bookriot.com/oversized-reading-chairs/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/chairs.png</image_url><description>What would your dream reading chair be? - Danika Ellis</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 551</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-551/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-551</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Job search requires writing and marketing skills. It also requires strong verbal communication. If these skills are not part of your normal work function, you’ll want some help. That’s what this week’s Summary Sunday is all about. There’s no doubt that LinkedIn is one of THE most powerful tools in your career toolbox. It contains […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 551 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 11:37:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Children caught between highly conflicted divorced parents at greater risk of mental health problems</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/children-caught-between-conflicted-divorced-parents/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=children-caught-between-conflicted-divorced-parents</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Interparental conflict after divorce escalates the risk of mental health problems in children and adolescents. Elevated levels of conflict between parents can also induce fear and worry in children about their future and whether they will be adequately taken care of. In turn, a greater fear of abandonment puts children at […] The post Children caught between highly conflicted divorced parents at greater risk of mental health problems appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 08:59:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shein's U.S. charm offensive and IPO could hinge on NRF membership. So far, it's been rejected</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/13/nrf-rejects-shein-membership-as-retailer-pursues-us-ipo.html</link><description>If Shein gets a stamp of approval from the NRF, it could help legitimize the retailer in the eyes of lawmakers and clear its path to a U.S. IPO.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2023 NBA free throws per game leaders</title><link>https://deadspin.com/2023-nba-free-throws-per-game-leaders-1851036206</link><description>This article is based on data from Sportradar. Read more...</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:09:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Olivia Munn Shares She Underwent a Hysterectomy Amid Cancer Battle</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1401437/olivia-munn-shares-she-underwent-a-hysterectomy-amid-cancer-battle?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>This Mother's Day, Olivia Munn is sharing a heartbreaking but hopeful personal update amid her recovery from breast cancer. The 43-year-old revealed that that in April, she made the decision to...</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 21:57:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Generational Wealth: Does the Apple Fall Far From the Tree?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/06/generational-wealth-does-the-apple-fall-far-from-the-tree/</link><description>There is strong evidence that most “rich families” will be poorer after several generations. Some of the reasons for this are systemic like taxes. But most factors that diminish a family’s wealth over generations are the choices that heirs make.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 12:37:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Global megarich are paying up to $2 million a week for superyacht rentals but smaller boat charters are down</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/13/super-yacht-rentals-megarich-smaller-charters/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-864197582-e1715591935495.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>IYC CEO Raphael Sauleau said he’s seeing more customers willing to pay a higher premium for the ultimate ocean experience.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 10:52:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spring Slumber</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/spring-slumber/</link><description>In the gentle embrace of mid-spring, there’s a delightful charm in refreshing my sleepwear collection. I tend to gravitate towards… The post Spring Slumber appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 20:00:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Almost 100 hours... And that's all he got?</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/aLnQMAx</link><description>Tags: wtf , not funny , work , scam , why 3592 points, 618 comments.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 12:20:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hub City Spartanburgers unveil new name, brand</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/12/hub-city-spartanburgers-unveil-new-name-brand/uncategorized/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The newest entry in the world of Minor League Baseball branding is the Hub City Spartanburgers, just unveiled yesterday. The Single-A affiliate of the Texas Rangers, newly relocated from Kinston, North Carolina, will play in Spartanburg, South Carolina. The town of Spartanburg earned the nickname Hub City because historically, it</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 19:51:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Women in AI: Rep. Dar’shun Kendrick wants to pass more AI legislation</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/12/women-in-ai-rep-darshun-kendrick-wants-to-pass-more-ai-legislation/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>To give AI-focused women academics and others their well-deserved — and overdue — time in the spotlight, TechCrunch has been publishing a series of interviews focused on remarkable women who’ve contributed to the AI revolution. We’re publishing these pieces throughout the year as the AI boom continues, highlighting key work that often goes unrecognized. Read more profiles here. […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weinstein Ruling Poses Quandary: Can #MeToo Coexist With Protections for Defendants?</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/04/sex-crimes-weinstein-me-too</link><description>Proving sex crimes often requires evidence that is generally excluded to protect the rights of the accused.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Garlic Balsamic Mushrooms</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/garlic-balsamic-mushrooms/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>The depth of flavors in these garlic balsamic mushrooms is next level! Sauteed mushrooms are coated in a sweet balsamic…</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cindy Crawford Says She Had Survivor’s Guilt After Brother’s Death</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/12/cindy-crawford-suffer-suvivors-guilt-brother-death-jeffrey-family-cancer/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Cindy Crawford’s getting real about her brother dying at a young age ... saying her dad wanted a boy, so she and her sisters felt like they should’ve died instead. The legendary supermodel opened up about her survivor’s guilt in a new episode…</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 07:25:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cows Are Potential Spreaders of Bird Flu to Humans</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/food-recipes/food-poisoning/news/20240510/cows-are-potential-spreaders-bird-flu-humans?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Cow udders have the same receptors for flu viruses as humans and birds, raising concerns that cows could become “mixing vessels” that help the bird flu virus spread between people.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 19:36:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Using Solid Stain In Our Outdoor Shower</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/solid-deck-stain-outdoor-shower/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>In all of our years of DIYing, I don’t think we’ve ever used a solid stain before. But we recently had a project that was *perfectly* suited for it and, well, solid stain quickly won us over. It was recommended by a professional house painter to us, specifically because he thought it would be great for our outdoor shower. And we found it easy to apply, it gave us great coverage, and we got an even-better-than-we-expected result (which is always the best kind!). So here’s a post that covers all the pros &amp; cons and hows &amp; whys of solid stain. As you can see, the “canvas” for this staining project was our outdoor shower. We gave it a mini-makeover right after moving in, but we knew it may need more attention and care down the line. Honestly, we dreaded the task of stripping and restaining it – so many nooks &amp; crannies! Continue reading Using Solid Stain In Our Outdoor Shower at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 17:46:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Keep Buying the Dips</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/how-to-keep-buying-the-dips/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, it's Ross Givens here with the Chart of the Day. In recent weeks, market movements have shifted to a more favorable pattern, oscillating within a consolidation range after a turbulent start to April. Now, signs suggest a potential breakout from this range, signaling a crucial turning point for traders. Learn how to navigate this evolving market landscape in today's Insight of the Day. The post How to Keep Buying the Dips appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gun thefts from cars have skyrocketed in the last decade</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/12/stolen-guns-cars/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/10164725/gun-safe.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Government/Legal , Safety Continue reading Gun thefts from cars have skyrocketed in the last decade Gun thefts from cars have skyrocketed in the last decade originally appeared on Autoblog on Sun, 12 May 2024 08:30:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 13:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What If We Replaced Income Taxes with Property and Sales Taxes? Would Real Estate Investing Even Work?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/should-the-us-eliminate-income-taxes-and-replace-it-with-sales-and-property-tax</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>A few reasons for—and against—this proposed shift in U.S. tax laws.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:15:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Riot’s Deals of the Day for May 12, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/book-riots-deals-of-the-day-for-may-12-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/deals-051224.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>A strange map with a deadly secret, the worst plagues in history, a fascinating community of apartment dwellers, and more of today's best book deals.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>15 Ways to Own Digital Terrain</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/15-ways-to-own-digital-terrain/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=15-ways-to-own-digital-terrain</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>It is now no longer optional…you must have an online presence! Your career stability and your job search demand it. Here are some tips to help you begin claiming digital terrain and brand it with your unique messaging! Why Should You Own Digital Terrain? You need to stake a claim by owning turf on the […] The post 15 Ways to Own Digital Terrain appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 15:56:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>“Why do they feel sad?” Shared book reading reveals how children learn about others’ emotions</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/shared-book-reading/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=shared-book-reading</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers: It is good for children to identify the emotions of others in conversations with caregivers because it scaffolds their ability to identify others’ emotions on their own. Children who use more emotion talk in parent-child conversations about emotions are more likely to have higher emotion knowledge one year later. Parents can […] The post “Why do they feel sad?” Shared book reading reveals how children learn about others’ emotions appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 08:19:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>No 'credible plan': U.S.' Blinken issues harshest criticism yet of Israel's Gaza operations</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/13/no-credible-plan-us-blinken-criticizes-israels-operations-in-gaza.html</link><description>The Biden administration opposes an Israeli invasion of Rafah, where more than 1.2 million displaced Palestinians are currently sheltering.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 10:47:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2023 NBA field goals per game leaders</title><link>https://deadspin.com/2023-nba-field-goals-per-game-leaders-1851036211</link><description>This article is based on data from Sportradar. Read more...</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:09:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Inside Nicole Richie's Private World as a Mom of 2 Teenagers</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1375519/inside-nicole-richies-private-world-as-a-mom-of-2-teenagers?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>Nicole Richie admittedly thought that The Simple Life would be a 30-day commitment. Little did the House of Harlow 1960 founder know that she and childhood BFF Paris Hilton would be the toast of...</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>State Capitalism in Private Markets: Mission Creep</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/03/state-capitalism-in-private-markets-mission-creep/</link><description>Governments relish mingling in markets. Yet, if past policies are any guide, taxpayers are being shortchanged.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 12:30:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Roger Corman: 'King of the Bs' who directed 'Little Shop of Horrors' has died at 98</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/13/roger-corman-little-shop-of-horrors-francis-ford-coppola-martin-scorsese-died-98/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/AP24133073798593-e1715593778656.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Starting in 1955, Corman helped create hundreds of B-movies as a producer and director, among them “Black Scorpion,” “Bucket of Blood” and “Bloody Mama.”</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 10:51:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coral Crush</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/coral-crush/</link><description>Outfit Details: Sir Top &amp; Skirt (also love the dress version), Loro Piana Hat, Prada Sunglasses Spring welcomes the delightful hue of coral, a color that perfectly… The post Coral Crush appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 05:00:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What an unexpected response :)</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/azxLVXj</link><description>Tags: wholesome 10790 points, 515 comments.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 12:20:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mother’s Day 2024: Pink Caps, Pink Ribbons as MLB Salutes Mom</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/11/mothers-day-2024-pink-caps-pink-ribbons-as-mlb-salutes-mom/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>It’s Mother’s Day here in North America, which means we’ll see pink-themed baseball caps and ribbons on the uniforms of Major League Baseball players, coaches, managers, and umpires during games played on Sunday, May 12th. SHOP: 2024 MLB Mother’s Day team caps available right now This will be the eighth</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:07:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A reckoning is coming for emerging venture funds, and that, VCs say, is a good thing</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/12/emerging-fund-venture-capital/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>We took the pulse of emerging fund managers about what it's been like for them during these post-ZERP, venture-capital-winter years. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mississippi Lawmakers Considered Modest Public Defense Reforms. They Rejected All of Them.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/02/mississippi-public-defense-legislative-reforms</link><description>With its refusal to impose oversight or consistent standards in local defense, Mississippi risks falling further behind rest of the U.S., critics say.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Creamy Cucumber Salad</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/creamy-cucumber-salad/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Creamy Cucumber Salad is a delicious and refreshing side dish. All it takes is a handful of fresh simple ingredients…</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rihanna, A$AP Rocky Celebrate RZA's 2nd Birthday, Adults Party Hard Too</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/12/rhianna-asap-rza-second-birthday-party/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Rihanna and A$AP Rocky aren't about to let their son RZA and his little friends have all the fun celebrating his birthday. The couple's firstborn will reach the ripe old age of 2 on Monday, but Mom and Dad threw a big party for him Saturday night…</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 07:25:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Age-Related Macular Degeneration: Putting a Hole in Our World</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/eye-health/news/20240510/age-related-macular-degeneration-putting-hole-our-world?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Estimates show that by 2040, age-related macular degeneration may affect nearly 300 million people worldwide. And we are very limited in our ability to treat or prevent it. Here's what to know.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 19:31:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ZZ Plant – Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/zz-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>The ZZ plant is another one of our favorite low-maintenance houseplants. They’re easy to care for, hard to kill, and always look full &amp; leafy. They’ve even earned the nickname “Eternity Plant” because they’re practically indestructible! That’s why they’re a top choice for commercial spaces, doctor’s offices, and busy homes like ours. Don’t you love a house plant you can forget about? ZZ plants are sold in a variety of sizes, meaning they’re great for shelves, tabletops, and small surfaces as well as larger statements on the floor. We have some that are over 3 feet tall with their pots! ZZ Plant Quick Facts Here’s what you need to know about your ZZ plant at a glance: Latin name : Zamioculcas zamiifolia Plant family : Araceae or Arums, which includes Philodendron , Alocasia, Aglaonema, Monstera , and Peace Lily Common name s: ZZ plant, Zanzibar Gem, Zuzu plant, Emerald Palm, Eternity plant Native to : East Africa Light : Medium indirect light, but is also low-light tolerant Watering : Every 2-3 weeks during its growing season Soil : Standard potting mix as long as it drains well Ideal Humidity : Average household humidity, ideally 40-50% Ideal Temperature : 65°F to 75°F Cold Hardiness : USDA Zones 9b-11 What Is A ZZ Plant? Continue reading ZZ Plant – Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 19:36:48 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>