<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 23:36:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The Biggest Literary News Stories of the Week</title><link>https://bookriot.com/today-in-books-july-7-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/typewriter-news.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>The popular SFF author accused of sexual assault, the most-anticipated most anticipated summer reading list, and more.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Junkyard Gem: 1985 Ford F-150 Explorer XL 4X4</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/07/07/junkyard-gem-1985-ford-f150-explorer/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/06/17120646/99-1985-Ford-F-150-in-Colorado-junkyard-photo-by-Murilee-Martin.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Ford , Automotive History , Truck , Classics Continue reading Junkyard Gem: 1985 Ford F-150 Explorer XL 4X4 Junkyard Gem: 1985 Ford F-150 Explorer XL 4X4 originally appeared on Autoblog on Sun, 7 Jul 2024 14:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Democratic power players are circulating a proposal for Biden to exit, launch 'blitz primary'</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/07/democratic-donors-staff-memo-biden-drop-out-blitz-primary.html</link><description>President Biden is facing escalating pressure to drop out of the 2024 race against Donald Trump, following his high-profile debate flop.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tater Tot Nachos</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/tater-tot-nachos/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Tater Tot Nachos (Totchos) are made with crispy golden tater tots, topped with seasoned beef, scoops of refried beans, corn,…</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Best Air Purifying Plants</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/best-air-purifying-plants/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>We love any excuse to buy more plants, and you may have heard they can improve your home’s indoor air quality. But before you blow your paycheck in the name of a healthier home, let’s dive deeper into plants’ air purifying powers. We’ll share which plants we recommend and what benefits you can actually expect from them. We’ve heard for years about how plants act as natural air filters for your home. So let’s dive a little deeper, shall we? 7 Air Purifying Plants If you just came here for a list, our favorite air purifying houseplants are bulleted below. The best part is these are all beautiful, low-maintenance plants. Many also appear on our best low-light indoor plants list too! Dracaena (including Corn Plant ) Snake Plant Aglaonema English Ivy Pothos Bamboo Palm Spider Plant There are certainly more that could be included here, but we narrowed it to the ones that are most often cited by experts AND the plants that we think look best too. Continue reading Best Air Purifying Plants at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 14:15:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Latest Finds From Amazon</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/07/amazon-sundays-6-30-24/</link><description>Outfit Details: Amazon The Drop Dress, Similar Bag Here, Similar Sunglasses Here Welcome to our latest finds from Amazon that… The post Latest Finds From Amazon appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 05:00:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Middle Grade Novels for Disability Pride Month and More Great Kids’ Books!</title><link>https://bookriot.com/middle-grade-novels-for-disability-pride-month/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/partial-cover-of-Majestica.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>Which of these new kids' releases are you adding to the TBR?</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hamilton holds off Verstappen's late charge for thrilling win at F1 British Grand Prix</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/07/07/hamilton-holds-off-verstappens-late-charge-for-thrilling-win-at-f1-british-grand-prix/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/crop/3378x1900+25+31/resize/1200x675/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/07/07123655/britain_f1_gp_auto_racing.jpeg</image_url><description>Filed under: Motorsports Continue reading Hamilton holds off Verstappen's late charge for thrilling win at F1 British Grand Prix Hamilton holds off Verstappen's late charge for thrilling win at F1 British Grand Prix originally appeared on Autoblog on Sun, 7 Jul 2024 12:38:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 17:38:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>French Prime Minister Gabriel Attal to tender resignation</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/07/french-prime-minister-gabriel-attal-to-tender-resignation.html</link><description>France now looks likely to be stranded in a hung-parliament scenario that divides it between three strongly represented parties that must broker alliances to gain absolute control.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 21:22:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Poke Sauce</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/poke-sauce/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>The best Poke Sauce is easy to make with just a handful of simple ingredients! Whether you are using salmon…</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Weekend In New Orleans With Kids</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/new-orleans-with-kids/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Since our travel guides to Charleston with kids and Palm Springs with kids have elicited requests for more travel ideas with kids, we’re back with an overdue recap of our 3-night trip to New Orleans. We’d never been to The Big Easy before and were impressed by how family-friendly the city is. It’s not all booze, beads, and Bourbon Street! So here’s a look at where we stayed, what we did, and what we’re excited to do next time we go back – because we will definitely go back! The four of us (well, five if you count our chihuahua!) went to NOLA for 3 nights in November of 2022. At the time, our kids were 8 and 12 years old. So unfortunately we can’t vouch for our suggestions being a good fit for toddlers or younger children. Although I’m sure ours would’ve loved the Louisiana Children’s Museum and Storyland playground back in the day! Continue reading A Weekend In New Orleans With Kids at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 17:17:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kid’s Camp</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/07/kids-camp/</link><description>Summer offers a great chance for children to explore the great outdoors and engage in exciting activities, including summer camps.… The post Kid’s Camp appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 05:00:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>500 New LGBTQ Book Releases Out In 2024 So Far</title><link>https://bookriot.com/new-lgbtq-books-of-2024-so-far/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/reading-on-couch.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>What's your favorite LGBTQ read of 2024 so far?</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aston Martin DBX707 AMR24 is an F1 medical car for the street</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/07/07/aston-martin-dbx707-amr24-is-an-f1-medical-car-for-the-street/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1200x675/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/07/04074219/aston_martin_dbx707_amr24_001.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Aston Martin , SUV , Luxury , Special and Limited Editions , Performance Continue reading Aston Martin DBX707 AMR24 is an F1 medical car for the street Aston Martin DBX707 AMR24 is an F1 medical car for the street originally appeared on Autoblog on Sun, 7 Jul 2024 12:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>France's left-wing coalition thwarts far right in parliamentary run-off vote</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/07/left-wing-new-popular-front-coalition-leads-in-french-parliamentary-run-off-vote-early-data-shows.html</link><description>A period of horse-trading and instability is now likely to take hold in France, as political alliances are forged with the aim of forming a government.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 19:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Philly Cheesesteak Foil Packs</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/philly-cheesesteak-foil-packs/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Try these delicious Philly Cheesesteak Foil Packs, a fun new way to enjoy the flavors of the classic Philly Cheesesteak.…</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>9 Easy Low-Light Indoor Plants</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/easy-low-light-indoor-plants/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>I used to think every houseplant needed a sunny corner or bright windowsill to thrive. But it turns out many of our favorite go-to houseplants do just fine in shady corners and low-light locations. So before you write off your house as too dark to sustain plant life, check out this list of the best indoor plants for low light. You might be surprised at how many good options there are! Our upstairs family room is the brightest room we’ve ever owned thanks to big unobstructed windows on all 4 sides. But most of our indoor plants live downstairs, where we get far less natural light. Luckily, that hasn’t stopped us from growing our collection of happy healthy houseplants. 9 Houseplants That Don’t Need A Lot Of Light Here are our favorite low-light indoor plants. We list a lot more info on them below, but here’s a quick list to bring on your next trip to the plant store: Snake Plant ZZ Plant Pothos Heartleaf Philodendron English Ivy Aglaonema Cast Iron Plant Monstera Parlor Palm Perhaps our favorite part of this list is that these aren’t ugly “consolation plants” that people begrudgingly buy for dark homes. Continue reading 9 Easy Low-Light Indoor Plants at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 14:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mesh Moment</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/07/mesh-moment/</link><description>Outfit Details: Frame Shirt, Bottega Veneta Skirt, Staud Flats (similar, less expensive here), Delvaux Bag, Prada Necklace I adore how exquisite mesh apparel instantly enhances my… The post Mesh Moment appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 05:00:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Riot’s Most Popular Stories of the Week</title><link>https://bookriot.com/best-of-book-riot-july-6-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/black-woman-reading-with-a-cup-of-coffee.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>If you’re in the U.S. and you don’t know what day of the week it is because a holiday on ...</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kimera K39 hill climb car aims for Pikes Peak in 2025</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/07/07/kimera-k39-reveal-pikes-peak-plans-hill-climb-car/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1200x675/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/06/30105031/kimera_k39_001.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Motorsports , Coupe , Racing Vehicles , Special and Limited Editions , Performance , Supercars Continue reading Kimera K39 hill climb car aims for Pikes Peak in 2025 Kimera K39 hill climb car aims for Pikes Peak in 2025 originally appeared on Autoblog on Sun, 7 Jul 2024 11:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden faces a 'vital week' to convince voters he can beat Trump, Sen. Murphy says</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/07/biden-vital-week-voters-beat-trump-chris-murphy.html</link><description>Five House Democrats so far have publicly called on President Biden to bow out of the 2024 race against Donald Trump.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 16:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tri Tip Marinade</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/tri-tip-marinade/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>This tasty tri tip marinade is the best way to infuse your tri-tip steak with delicious flavor and make it…</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/how-to-remove-wallpaper/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Wallpaper has made a big comeback as a trendy home design choice. But despite its resurgence, there are still plenty of us dealing with dingy, dated, or downright ugly old wallpaper we don’t want. In our old home, we had to remove wallpaper in so many rooms: the kitchen, the dining room, the foyer, and two different bathrooms! As we traveled from room to room removing wallpaper, we tested 4 different methods, and today we’ll share what we learned. Removing wallpaper doesn’t require special tools or lots of money. It’s a totally doable project for any homeowner. However, it can be a tedious process that can take elbow grease and patience, depending on the size of your room and the stubbornness of your wallpaper. But having removed several rooms worth of decades-old wallpaper, we can confidently say it’s worth the effort! You can also check out more before and afters of our once-wallpapered rooms. Continue reading How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:21:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wanderlust Seaside Style</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/07/wanderlust-seaside-style/</link><description>As we descend upon the sunlit shores of the Italian seaside, the expansive vistas of blue water and golden sands… The post Wanderlust Seaside Style appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 05:00:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>All the News Book Riot Covered This Week: July 6, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/today-in-books-july-6-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/laptop-with-notebook-and-coffee-cup.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>The bestselling books of the week, the indie bookstore shipping LGBTQ titles to states where they're banned, and more.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mercedes product plans keeping internal combustion around longer</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/07/07/mercedes-benz-adjusts-future-product-plans-keeps-internal-combustion/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1200x675/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/04/10161119/24C0152_008-copy.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Green , Mercedes-Benz , SUV , Electric , Future Vehicles , Hybrid , Luxury , Sedan Continue reading Mercedes product plans keeping internal combustion around longer Mercedes product plans keeping internal combustion around longer originally appeared on Autoblog on Sun, 7 Jul 2024 10:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Texas coastal residents told to expect power outages, flooding as Beryl moves closer to landfall</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/07/07/beryl-bears-down-on-texas-where-it-is-expected-to-hit-after-regaining-hurricane-strength.html</link><description>The earliest storm to develop into a Category 5 hurricane in the Atlantic, Beryl caused at least 11 deaths while tearing through the Caribbean.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Raspberry Fluff Salad</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/raspberry-fluff-salad/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Fresh and fruity Raspberry Fluff Salad is a sweet and creamy side or dessert with a mix of raspberries, vanilla…</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aglaonema Plant – Complete Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/aglaonema-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Aglaonema, also called the Chinese Evergreen Plant, is an easy-care houseplant that lives happily in many lighting conditions – even a dark corner of our daughter’s room. There are dozens of different Aglaonema varieties, most with large tropical foliage and colors ranging from silvery-green, red, and even vibrant pink. They’re also tough to kill, so they’re a great option for forgetful plant owners or anyone looking for an easy win in the plant department. These truly have been very low maintenance for us. We purchased our two Aglaonemas (pronounced ag-lee-oh-neem-ah ) to put atop our daughter’s closet. It’s sometimes hard to distinguish different varieties, but we believe that’s an Aglaonema Silver (right) and either a Candy Cane or Princess Silver Queen (left). Aglaonema Quick Facts Here’s what you need to know about your Aglaonema at a glance: Latin name : Aglaonema is the genus under which there are 21 recognized species . Continue reading Aglaonema Plant – Complete Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:47:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>12 Tops To Order For Summer</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/07/10-tops-to-order-for-summer/</link><description>Outfit Details: Loewe Top, Ulla Johnson Jeans, Delvaux Bag, Celine Sunglasses (similar here, less expensive here), Louis Abel Earrings Revamp your summer style with twelve… The post 12 Tops To Order For Summer appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 05:00:34 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>