<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 06:54:03 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Boomers Hoard Houses, Millennials Struggle to Buy, But Gen Z Gets Ahead w/Redfin’s Chen Zhao</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-222</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Millennials can’t afford homes, but somehow, their younger siblings, Gen Z, can. Even with over a decade more work experience than Gen Z, Millennials still feel priced out of the […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 07:02:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spotify to increase premium pricing in the US to $11.99 per month</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/03/spotify-to-increase-premium-pricing-in-the-us-to-11-99-per-month/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Spotify has announced that it’s hiking subscriptions for customers in the U.S., the second such price increase in the space of a year. The music-streaming giant reports that premium pricing will increase in July from $10.99 to $11.99, representing a near-10% rise. The Duo and Family plans will go up to $16.99 and $19.99, representing […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 11:47:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How We Reported on Homicide Investigations in St. Louis</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/03/st-louis-police-unsolved-murders-methods</link><description>Getting and interpreting homicide clearance data involved litigation, complex analysis and patience.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Federal Experts Talk Bird Flu ‘What Ifs’ in WebMD Live Event</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/cold-and-flu/news/20240516/federal-experts-talk-bird-flu-what-ifs?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>WebMD brought together experts from four federal agencies to talk prevention, monitoring, and what the “what ifs” of bird flu might look like.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:50:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Financial Independence at 29 by Quitting Rentals to Invest in THIS</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-414</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Do you dream of building a real estate empire and reaching financial independence but stop short due to the “tenants and toilets” problem? The irony wasn’t lost on twenty-nine-year-old Dillon […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 07:02:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>UK neobank Monzo reports first full (pre-tax) profit, prepares for EU expansion with Dublin hub</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/03/uk-neobank-monzo-reports-first-full-pre-tax-profit-prepares-for-eu-expansion-with-dublin-hub/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Monzo has announced its 2024 financial results, revealing its first full-year pre-tax profit. The company also confirmed that it’s in the early stages of expanding into the broader European market via a new base in Ireland. The news comes shortly after the U.K.-based neobank raised a couple of hefty tranches of funding, starting with $430 […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 11:34:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why 1,000 Homicides in St. Louis Remain Unsolved</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/03/st-louis-police-unsolved-murders</link><description>In one of America’s deadliest cities, police have struggled to solve killings due to staffing shortages, shoddy detective work and lack of community trust.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What’s Next in Health Care for Older Adults: Questions and Answers With John Whyte, MD</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/blog-aging-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>As WebMD’s chief medical officer, John Whyte, MD, is in a unique position to see both the current state of medical care for America’s older adults and the way things are trending for the future. We asked him to share his insight on a few topics, along with a bit of advice.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:29:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Retiring His Parents by Buying Unwanted, Overlooked Real Estate Deals</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-964</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>One investment property could change your life, especially if you buy the right one. Logan Koch, an investor in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, was buying investment properties for one specific goal: To […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 07:02:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Inside Apple’s efforts to build a better recycling robot</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/03/inside-apples-efforts-to-build-a-better-recycling-robot/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Last week, TechCrunch paid a visit to Apple’s Austin, Texas manufacturing facilities. Since 2013, the company has built its Mac Pro desktop about 20 minutes north of downtown. The 400,000 square foot facility sits in a maze of industry parks, a quick trip south from the company’s in-progress corporate campus. In recent years, the capital […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 10:23:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Abortion’s Legal Landscape Post-Roe is Causing Fear and Confusion</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/01/abortion-supreme-court-roe-dobbs</link><description>We spoke with seven reproductive rights organizations — here’s what we found.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Get the Care You Need in a COVID-19 World</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/covid-senior-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>What to expect at the doctor’s office, hospitals, and long-term care facilities, the future of telemedicine, and how to get the best care during COVID-19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 19:50:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>My Flip MUST Check These 5 Boxes—or I’m Walking Away From the Deal</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/my-flip-must-check-these-boxes</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>If something about the deal doesn't make financial sense, I'm not buying.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 16:54:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Binit is bringing AI to trash</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/03/binit-is-bringing-ai-to-trash/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Early attempts at making dedicated hardware to house artificial intelligence smarts have been criticized as, well, a bit rubbish. But here’s an AI gadget-in-the-making that’s all about rubbish, literally: Finnish startup Binit is applying large language models’ (LLMs) image processing capabilities to tracking household trash. AI for sorting the stuff we throw away to boost […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 09:00:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I Recorded a Whole Hip-Hop Album on a Death Row Telephone</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/31/north-carolina-death-row-rapper-book-excerpt</link><description>In this new book excerpt, incarcerated rapper Alim “RRome Alone” Braxton describes his early attempts to record vocals over a phone in the dayroom.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Personal Shopper: A Savvy Black Entrepreneur Guides You to Eczema-Friendly Clothes, Creams, Cosmetics, and More</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/savvy-black-entrepreneur-guides-eczema-friendly-clothes-creams-cosmetics?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>A savvy black entrepreneur guides you on an eczema-friendly shopping spree.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:54:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>No, Cash is Not King—You Can Do Way More and Way Better With Financing</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/cash-is-not-king-how-to-win-with-financed-offers</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>You hear it all the time on BiggerPockets Forums, podcasts, local meetups, from gurus, etc. It must be true if everyone says it is: “Cash is king.” The idea is […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 12:39:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Temasek, Fidelity buy $200M stake in Lenskart at $5B valuation</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/03/temasek-and-fidelity-buy-200-million-stake-in-indias-lenskart/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Temasek has previously invested in Lenskart, and this new funding follows a $500 million investment by the Abu Dhabi Investment Authority last year. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 08:31:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Legal Doctrine That Shields Police From Many Lawsuits May Be Losing Support</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/25/police-mississippi-courts-judges-qualified-immunity</link><description>A federal judge in Mississippi joined other courts in recently rejecting police arguments that qualified immunity protected their actions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Behind the Spike in Colorectal Cancer Among Young Americans</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/colorectal-cancer/news/20240515/behind-the-spike-in-colorectal-cancer-cases?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Colorectal cancer cases increased a whopping 333% among 15- to 19-year-olds and 185% among 20- to 24-year-olds from 1999 to 2020.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:59:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>