<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 06:47:44 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Notre Dame Unveils Shamrock Series Uniforms For Game Against Army At Yankee Stadium</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/24/notre-dame-unveils-shamrock-series-uniforms-for-game-against-army-at-yankee-stadium/college/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Notre Dame unveiled its latest Shamrock Series uniforms, which are inspired by the "Four Horsemen" and will be worn against Army at Yankee Stadium on Nov. 23.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 21:21:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pete Buttigieg Shares How He'd Campaign as Kamala Harris' VP</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/24/pete-buttigieg-shares-how-hed-go-about-vice-president-campaign/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Pete Buttigieg is fully onboard with getting Vice President Kamala Harris elected to the White House ... whether or not she selects him as her running mate. President Biden's Secretary of Transportation is among the leading candidates to jump on…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 06:47:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MLB All-Star Game Logos, Like Super Bowls, May Get a Templated Look Going Forward</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/23/mlb-all-star-game-logos-like-super-bowls-may-get-a-templated-look-going-forward/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Standardized sports logos are trending, from the Super Bowl to literally everything in the NBA. But what about Major League Baseball’s All-Star Game… Well, guess what? It looks like baseball’s annual Mid-Summer Classic is ready to join the club. “You might start to see some similarities in the format and</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 21:37:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NBA Strikes Media Rights Deal With Amazon Prime Video, TNT Not Giving Up</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/24/nba-strikes-media-rights-deal-amazon-prime-video-ending-tnt-partnership/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>2:45 PM PT -- TNT isn't going down without a fight ... saying it will take appropriate action after the league "grossly misinterpreted our contractual rights" regarding their relationship moving forward. "We have matched the Amazon offer, as we…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 06:47:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stellar Real Madrid Away Kit Headlines Recent Launches from Spain, Rest of Europe</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/23/stellar-real-madrid-away-kit-headlines-recent-launches-from-spain-and-rest-of-europe/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Inter Milan adds gold flourishes to home kit to celebrate 20th Serie A title; other clubs unveiling 24-25 kits include Aston Villa, Real Valladolid, Girona, Osasuna, Borussia Dortmund, Stade Rennais, Toulouse</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 17:27:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prosecutors Cite Alleged Diddy Hit on Tupac, Try to Block Keefe D's Release</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/24/diddy-claim-alleged-hit-offer-money-kill-tupac-keefe-d-bond-opposition/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>2:28 PM PT -- Law enforcement sources tell TMZ ... Diddy was never a suspect in the Tupac murder investigation, and that remains true today. In other words ... it's clear cops weren't buying what Keefe D was selling about Puff, and didn't deem his…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 06:47:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2025 MLB All-Star Game Logo Revealed; Hosted by Atlanta Braves</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/22/2025-mlb-all-star-game-logo-revealed-hosted-by-atlanta-braves/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Atlanta… You’re on the clock. Four years after they lost the game with just months to go, the Atlanta Braves are back and ready to host. Major League Baseball, along with the team, today unveiled the logo for the 2025 MLB All-Star Game, to be played at Truist Field on</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 00:18:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Dukes of Hazzard' Star John Schneider Marries Paul Sorvino's Widow Dee Dee</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/24/dukes-of-hazzard-john-schneider-paul-sorvino-widow-dee-dee/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>John Schneider has found a new Duchess of Hazzard -- tying the knot with Dee Dee Sorvino, widow of the late Paul Sorvino ... about two years after his own wife passed. The "Dukes of Hazzard" star and Dee Dee exchanged vows in Las Vegas Tuesday…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 06:47:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are The Kansas City Chiefs Considering Alternate Uniforms?</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/22/are-the-kansas-city-chiefs-considering-alternate-uniforms/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Don't expect the Kansas City Chiefs to get an alternate uniform anytime soon, though their owner appears to be warming up to the idea.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 22:23:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rockies Pitcher Ribs Reese McGuire Over Masturbation Arrest, Nearly Incites Brawl</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/24/rockies-pitcher-clowns-reese-mcguire-over-masturbation-bust-go-jack-off-in-a-parking-lot/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Rockies pitcher Cal Quantrill got so pissed at Reese McGuire during their game Wednesday, he shaded the Red Sox catcher for his past public masturbation arrest -- and his heated words nearly incited an all-out brawl. The incident went down after…</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 06:47:44 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>