<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 00:43:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Five Quotes from Financial History to Guide Trustees</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/31/five-quotes-from-financial-history-to-guide-trustees/</link><description>If you serve as a trustee of an institutional investment plan, these five quotes may help guide your decisions for the benefit of those who depend on your stewardship.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 13:59:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>5 best supplements to support your mental health, according to a psychiatrist</title><link>https://fortune.com/well/article/best-supplements-for-mental-health/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2025715909-e1717195240972.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Supplements may help you along your mental health journey; they are not a cure.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 01:41:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stocks for the Long Run? Setting the Record Straight</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/30/stocks-for-the-long-run-setting-the-record-straight/</link><description>Stocks are a good investment long-term, providing that you dial in your expectations. New historical findings provide a richer, more complete understanding of international returns.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 16:55:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Romance guild in upheaval following criticism over the way it handled an author who posted negative online comments about other writers</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/31/romance-guild-upheaval-bankruptcy/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2115097560-e1717201011392.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The group also faced criticism and withdrew an award for a book that included a sympathetic portrayal of a cavalry officer who participated in the slaughter of Lakota Indians.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 01:21:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rethinking Retirement Planning Amidst Aging Demographic Frontiers</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/28/rethinking-retirement-planning-amidst-aging-demographic-frontiers/</link><description>Forward-thinking approaches to policy and wealth management are needed to ensure a better financial future across generations and income brackets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 20:32:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A former tech CEO announced a fake offer to buy Getty Images in order to boost its stock price, authorities say</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/31/former-tech-ceo-fake-offer-getty/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1074277846-e1717200018656.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Robert Scott Murray, former chief executive of the networking-equipment maker 3Com, sold his Getty stock for about $1.5 million, officials said.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 01:01:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: The New World Economy in 5 Trends</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/24/book-review-the-new-world-economy-in-5-trends/</link><description>A diligent economist and an eclectic bookworm serve up an analysis of megatrends that will have the greatest impact on economies and investments: innovation, productivity, climate, multiglobalization, debt, and aging.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 12:22:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The best science-backed strategies for a strong mind as you age</title><link>https://fortune.com/well/2024/05/31/aging-sharp-mind-strategies/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-623192890-e1717186196542.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The lifelong learner is onto something.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Factor Strategies Belong in Your Completion Portfolio Toolkit</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/23/factor-strategies-belong-in-your-completion-portfolio-toolkit/</link><description>Why wouldn't you include factor strategies in your completion portfolio? A review of the two commonly used approaches for managing institutional assets highlights their symbiotic nature.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 19:09:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Billionaire Bill Ackman is about to get $4 billion richer as his hedge fund Pershing Square expects a funding round at a premium valuation</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/31/billionaire-bill-ackman-net-worth-pershing-square-funding-round-valuation-ipo/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1244132680-e1717189884278.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Pershing Square could go public as soon as 2025.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 23:25:47 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>