<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 01:49:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Our Chat with Cards’ President Bill DeWitt III About New City Connect Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/25/our-chat-with-cards-president-bill-dewitt-iii-about-new-city-connect-uniforms/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The St. Louis Cardinals brand new Nike MLB City Connect uniforms will be making their on-field début this afternoon. The red jerseys with “The Lou” scripted across the chest, inspired by the hit song from Nelly, were unveiled on Monday to an overall positive reaction from fans and media alike.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 17:17:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adam Silver Says NBA's Negotiations W/ TNT Not Dead Yet, 'We're All Still Talking'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/25/adam-silver-says-nbas-negotiations-w-tnt-not-dead-yet-we-re-all-still-talking/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Fill in the gravesite and call off the funeral ... Adam Silver says despite all the perception of doom and gloom surrounding the NBA's current negotiations with TNT -- the talks between the sides are NOT dead yet. The Association's commissioner…</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 01:49:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ligue 1’s Lille OSC Put Unique Spin on Traditional Chevron for 2024-25 Home Kits</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/24/ligue-1s-lille-osc-put-unique-spin-on-traditional-chevron-for-2024-25-home-kits/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Club's traditional chevron, which they've used in some form since the 1940s, appears on new kits made up of several tonal mini-chevrons</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 22:01:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Selling the OC' Sean Palmieri Fires Back at Ex-Castmates, Villain Label</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/25/sean-palmieri-selling-the-oc-fires-back-castmates-villian-label/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Former "Selling the OC" star Sean Palmieri's going scorched earth on his ex-colleagues ... firing off a barrage of critiques -- and, telling fans who think he's the villain to look at everyone else's behavior. We caught up with Palmieri on Rodeo…</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 01:49:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Memorial Cup Host Saginaw Spirit Unveil Commemorative Jersey for Tourney Opener</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/24/memorial-cup-host-saginaw-spirit-unveil-commemorative-jersey-for-tourney-opener/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Like the Memorial Cup itself, Spirit jersey for Friday's opening game against the Moose Jaw Warriors honors fallen military personnel</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 15:34:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Diddy's Walk of Fame Star Cannot Be Removed</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/25/diddy-no-discussion-remove-walk-of-fame-star-downfall/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Calls to remove Diddy's Hollywood Walk of Fame star are gaining traction amid his downfall -- but the team behind the honor has made no such move. A Hollywood Chamber of Commerce spokesperson tells TMZ ... they have not discussed it and the org is…</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 01:49:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Announcing Player 97: Our New Brand Vision, Research, Consulting Company</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/24/player-97-consulting-brand-vision-historical-research/misc/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Today, I’m excited to announce the official launch of Player 97, the new consulting, research, and branding company managed by the same friendly faces that have been running SportsLogos.Net. After many years of helping teams, leagues, designers, and other companies, I decided to finally make it official—folks, I am here</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 14:39:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Island Boys' Franky Venegas Arrested For Driving Offenses in Florida</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/25/island-boys-franky-venegas-florida-arrested-driving-offenses/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Franky Venegas – one half of the viral hip hop duo The Island Boys – has been busted in Florida for driving-related offenses. The tattooed TikTok star --who shares the limelight with his twin brother Alex – was arrested in Fort Lauderdale…</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 01:49:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Football in Their DNA: AC Milan Launches 2024-25 Home Kit</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/23/football-in-their-dna-ac-milan-launches-2024-25-home-kit/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Tonal segmented stripes inside red stripes are a visual representation of the human genome; patch on back collar celebrates club's 125th anniversary</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 16:11:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Millie Bobby Brown, Jake Bongiovi Flaunt Rings, First Pics Since Wedding</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/24/millie-bobby-brown-jake-bongiovi-seem-to-confirm-marriage-rings-new-photos/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Millie Bobby Brown and Jake Bongiovi are lookin' very newlywed ... tooling around the Hamptons and flashing their rings in the first shots of them since their reported secret wedding. The happy couple were out and about Friday doing some shopping…</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 01:49:35 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>