<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 22:36:10 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Five Quotes from Financial History to Guide Trustees</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/31/five-quotes-from-financial-history-to-guide-trustees/</link><description>If you serve as a trustee of an institutional investment plan, these five quotes may help guide your decisions for the benefit of those who depend on your stewardship.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 13:59:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Live Nation reveals ‘a criminal threat actor’ offered to sell Ticketmaster data on the dark web, while reports say hackers seek $500,000 for customer info</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/06/01/live-nation-ticketmaster-data-breach-hackers-dark-web-customer-info/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/GettyImages-2154676136-e1717283964535.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The data reportedly includes names, addresses, phone numbers and some credit card details of millions of Ticketmaster customers.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 00:27:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stocks for the Long Run? Setting the Record Straight</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/30/stocks-for-the-long-run-setting-the-record-straight/</link><description>Stocks are a good investment long-term, providing that you dial in your expectations. New historical findings provide a richer, more complete understanding of international returns.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 16:55:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The housing market is finally seeing more inventory, but buyers aren’t showing up as a ‘cold reality is settling down’</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/06/01/housing-market-crisis-inventory-buyer-demand-home-prices-mortgage-rates-fed-cuts/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/GettyImages-185222438-e1717283022247.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>“Without the rate cuts, a cold reality is settling down on the housing market,” Robert Frick, corporate economist for Navy Federal Credit Union, said.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 00:11:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rethinking Retirement Planning Amidst Aging Demographic Frontiers</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/28/rethinking-retirement-planning-amidst-aging-demographic-frontiers/</link><description>Forward-thinking approaches to policy and wealth management are needed to ensure a better financial future across generations and income brackets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 20:32:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The best-performing stock on the S&amp;P 500 is a ‘unicorn’ that joined the index less than a month ago and is beating Nvidia</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/06/01/best-sp500-stock-vistra-vst-nvidia-nvda-ai-data-center-power-nuclear-energy/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/GettyImages-1322819264-e1717281566167.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Vistra’s mix of gas and nuclear power plants make it “a unicorn,” according to Guggenheim’s Shahriar Pourreza.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 23:53:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: The New World Economy in 5 Trends</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/24/book-review-the-new-world-economy-in-5-trends/</link><description>A diligent economist and an eclectic bookworm serve up an analysis of megatrends that will have the greatest impact on economies and investments: innovation, productivity, climate, multiglobalization, debt, and aging.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 12:22:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The ANC party that freed South Africa from apartheid loses its 30-year majority, signaling first-ever coalition government to come</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/06/01/south-africa-election-african-national-congress-majority-coalition-government-cyril-ramaphosa/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/GettyImages-2155133582-e1717279826820.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>With more than 99% of votes counted, the once-dominant ANC had received just over 40% in Wednesday's election.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 23:21:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Factor Strategies Belong in Your Completion Portfolio Toolkit</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/23/factor-strategies-belong-in-your-completion-portfolio-toolkit/</link><description>Why wouldn't you include factor strategies in your completion portfolio? A review of the two commonly used approaches for managing institutional assets highlights their symbiotic nature.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 19:09:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jerome Powell's Federal Reserve is stuck in a self-defeating paradox that makes cutting rates more difficult, economist warns</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/06/01/jerome-powell-fed-rate-cut-outlook-financial-conditions-economic-growth-sp500-stock-market/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/GettyImages-2151818486-e1717274081541.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>"You can call this the Fed Cut Reflexivity Paradox: The more the Fed insists that the next move in interest rates is a cut, the more financial conditions will ease, making it more difficult for the Fed to cut."</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 22:55:32 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>