<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from multiple RSS sources, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 07:19:08 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Home Prices Stagnate in The South and America’s New #1 Housing Market</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-213</link><description>Texas and Florida are seeing stagnating home prices as housing inventory booms while demand slips away. Housing is still expensive, but with more inventory, why is it staying that way? […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 07:02:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Renda, which provides order fulfillment for businesses in Africa, takes in $1.9M</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/02/renda-which-provides-order-fulfillment-for-businesses-in-africa-takes-in-1-9m/</link><description>The logistics industry in Nigeria, like any informal sector, struggles with poor infrastructure and other inefficiencies, making it difficult for businesses — both large and small — to move and store goods. Many startups have tackled middle-mile and last-mile delivery challenges, but one untapped area is providing an end-to-end fulfillment solution. Renda, a three-year-old startup, […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 12:05:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mississippi Lawmakers Considered Modest Public Defense Reforms. They Rejected All of Them.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/02/mississippi-public-defense-legislative-reforms</link><description>With its refusal to impose oversight or consistent standards in local defense, Mississippi risks falling further behind rest of the U.S., critics say.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Truth or TV: Is Grey's Anatomy's Parkinson's 'Cure' Real?</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/parkinsons-disease/features/is-greys-anatomys-parkinsons-cure-real?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>How realistic is the Grey’s Anatomy episode that shows a Parkinson’s disease cure? A neurosurgery professor weighs in.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 08:17:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Contractor Nightmares: 5 Red Flags to Watch For and How to Escape a Bad Hire</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/red-flags-to-avoid-with-contractors-and-how-to-escape-a-bad-hire</link><description>What’s easier to find, a unicorn or a rock star contractor? If you asked most value-add real estate investors, the answer would be obvious: “Unicorns, of course.” We all know the inherent […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 17:18:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Digital fraud detection startup BioCatch hits $1.3B valuation as Permira buys majority stake</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/02/permira-to-acquire-digital-fraud-detection-company-biocatch-in-1-3b-deal/</link><description>Digital fraud detection company BioCatch has a new majority shareholder in the form of U.K private equity firm Permira.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:55:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In This Police Youth Program, a Trail of Sexual Abuse Across the U.S.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/01/police-explorer-sexual-abuse-boy-scouts</link><description>Explorer posts, overseen by the Boy Scouts, are supposed to foster an interest in policing. They have faced nearly 200 allegations of misconduct.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 18:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Easing Marijuana Laws Doesn’t Mean the Drug Is Safer</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/mental-health/addiction/news/20240501/reclassification-of-marijuana-doesnt-mean-its-safer?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>You shouldn’t draw major conclusions about the safety of marijuana amid the recent announcement that federal regulators may reclassify the drug, experts are cautioning.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 23:29:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Free Money? Can You Build a Real Estate Portfolio with Zero-Interest Credit Cards?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/can-you-build-a-real-estate-portfolio-with-zero-interest-credit-cards</link><description>Juggling 0% interest business credit cards is like juggling torches in a hay-covered barn. Drop one, and the whole place goes up in flames. However, if you are disciplined and […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 16:55:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ButcherBox acquires ‘Shark Tank’-featured startup Truffle Shuffle</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/02/butcherbox-acquires-truffle-shuffle/</link><description>Butcherbox is known for grinding its way forward, bootstrapping to more than $600,000 worth of revenue. The company hasn’t traditionally been on the M&amp;A path, but it today announced it is acquiring Truffle Shuffle – who you may remember from a Shark Tank episode back in 2021 (or, perhaps, The Goonies). The acquisition helps Butcher […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:00:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Campus Protests Could Shape the 2024 Elections — And Not Just the Presidency</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/30/campus-protests-gaza-arrests-prosecutors-elections</link><description>With hundreds of arrests and more campus standoffs looming, local law enforcement officials could face consequences at the ballot box.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 21:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Female Doctors Better? Here's What to Know</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/women/news/20240501/are-female-doctors-better-heres-what-to-know?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>A new study suggests female doctors may provide patients better care, especially when those patients are women. Here's what to know.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 18:11:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Solving the Housing Crisis: What Lawmakers Must Do to Support Investors and Boost Housing Supply</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/what-lawmakers-can-do-to-spur-housing-growth-and-help-investors</link><description>There’s a critical lack of affordable housing. This housing shortage began following the 2008 financial crisis and worsened during the pandemic, and now, not enough homes have been built to meet current […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 16:26:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Freshworks acquires Device42 for $230M, appoints Dennis Woodside new CEO</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/02/freshworks-acquires-device42-for-230m-appoints-dennis-woodside-new-ceo/</link><description>Freshworks, the publicly listed SaaS firm, is acquiring U.S.-based startup Device42 for $230 million, the company disclosed in an SEC filing. Alongside the acquisition disclosure, Freshworks revealed that founder Girish Mathrubootham has stepped down as CEO. Dennis Woodside, who joined Freshworks as president in September 2022 and previously served as CEO of Motorola Mobility, will […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 09:08:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>They Killed Their Abusive Partners. Now Their Sentences Could Be Reconsidered.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/27/oklahoma-oregon-minnesota-domestic-violence</link><description>Oklahoma could re-examine how it punishes people whose crimes came after years of domestic abuse. Other states may follow.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NIH’s Eliseo Pérez-Stable, MD, Talks Health Disparities, Biology, Behavior, and Culture</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/a-to-z-guides/features/nimhd-perez-stable-health-disparities?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Eliseo Pérez-Stable, MD, director of the National Institute on Minority Health and Health Disparities, talks about health disparities and how his studies aim to improve interventions in clinical settings and across communities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 22:06:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rookie Investor? Never Make This $40,000 Mistake</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-400</link><description>This episode could make you $40,000. Seriously, one property management mistake cost our own expert investor, Dave Meyer, anywhere from $30,000 to $40,000, BUT it’s easier to avoid than you […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 07:02:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TikTok gets Tay and Billie back with new UMG content licensing deal</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/02/tiktok-gets-tay-and-billie-back-with-new-umg-content-licensing-deal/</link><description>Users on TikTok can once again create music clips using tracks from UMG’s catalog, a list featuring some of the biggest names in music today: Taylor Swift, Billie Eilish, and Ariana Grande. That’s because, after months of fighting, the social media platform and Universal Music Group (UMG) have finally called a truce with a new […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 08:26:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Being Trans in Prison Is Really Like</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/26/trans-prison-voices-gender-essay</link><description>Amid a wave of anti-trans legislation, and the violence that often follows, four people share their experiences in the criminal justice system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 11:00:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New ‘FLiRT’ Variants Spark Summer COVID Surge Warning</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/covid/news/20240430/new-variant-sparks-summer-covid-surge-warning?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>A data scientist who has accurately predicted COVID waves since the beginning of the pandemic warns that a surge is on the horizon.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 18:16:30 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>