<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 06:59:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Moroccan Soccer Team Awarded Default Win After Kits Confiscated by Algerian Customs</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/25/moroccan-soccer-team-awarded-default-win-after-kits-confiscated-by-algerian-customs/soccer/</link><description>Kits feature map of Morocco on the chest that includes disputed Western Sahara territory</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 18:55:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chris Pine Channels 'Poolman' Character in Jorts, Long Blond Hair</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/25/chris-pine-channel-poolman-character-jorts-t-shirt-premiere-wig-blond-hair/</link><description>Chris Pine's got the California surfer look down ... a style he seemingly raided from the set of his new movie "Poolman," and seems comfortable keeping long after filming. The actor-director pulled up to the L.A. premiere of his new flick Wednesday…</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 06:59:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Glacier Range Riders, National Park Service Embroiled in Battle Over Arrowhead Logo</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/25/glacier-range-riders-national-park-service-embroiled-in-battle-over-arrowhead-logo/baseball/</link><description>NPS has filed protests with the U.S. Patent and Trademark Office over logo possible causing confusion that team is affiliated with service</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:56:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tiffany Haddish Says She Had Eight Miscarriages Due to Endometriosis</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/25/tiffany-haddish-eight-miscarriages-endometriosis-diagnosis/</link><description>Tiffany Haddish says she's had a lot of trouble with pregnancies over the years ... and it's all due to an ongoing battle with endometriosis. The comedian shared her struggles in a new interview with People ... which she also details in her new…</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 06:59:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New York Jets: Their Logos, Their Name, Their Colours</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/25/new-york-jets-their-logos-their-name-their-colours/football/</link><description>From their early-sixties inception as the Titans of New York to their modern, throwback-inspired green and white logo, the New York Jets have had several distinctive looks over their 60-plus year history. This team has found itself navigating through different eras, frequently alternating between two primary logos and uniform styles</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:34:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Johnny Depp's Director Walks Back Scary Claim, Says She Was Misunderstood</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/25/johnny-depp-director-maiwenn-walk-back-scary-claim-jeanne-du-barry/</link><description>French director Maïwenn is walking back her claim Johnny Depp "scared" her crew on the set of "Jeanne du Barry" ... saying she was misunderstood. Maïwenn hit back at The Independent after its headline suggested the actor was a terror while…</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 06:59:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Update on Utah’s NHL Team Name, Uniform Info, Tournament Coming?</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/24/update-on-utahs-nhl-team-name-uniform-info-tournament-coming/hockey-2/</link><description>Utah’s new National Hockey League team is starting to assemble their list of possible team names ahead of their inaugural (but not expansion) season this fall. DetroitHockey.Net’s Clark Rasmussen, the king of the trademark search, found two more names possibly trademarked by the group, bringing the total to nine that</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:51:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jeannie Mai Alleges Recklessness &amp; Abuse Against Jeezy, He Denies Claims</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/25/jeannie-mai-abuse-recklessness-jeezy-denies-claims-injury-photos/</link><description>Jeannie Mai has fired back at Jeezy in their bitter divorce -- asking a judge to deny him custody of their kid ... because she claims he's been reckless and abusive, but he calls BS. The talk show host filed new legal docs Thursday, obtained by…</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 06:59:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Liverpool FC Reportedly Ready to Return to Adidas in 2025</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/24/liverpool-fc-reportedly-ready-to-return-to-adidas-in-2025/soccer/</link><description>New deal with Liverpool reportedly part of an "aggressive push" by Adidas to win high-profile contracts after losing German national team deal</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 17:56:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Harvey Weinstein Cheerful, Tearful After NYC Rape Conviction Overturned</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/25/harvey-weinstein-cheerful-tearful-nyc-rape-conviction-overturned/</link><description>Harvey Weinstein's NYC rape conviction getting overturned has him so elated it's reduced him to tears as he sits in prison. Weinstein's rep Juda Engelmayer tells TMZ he chatted with his client twice today, and Harvey's over the moon about the news…</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 06:59:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>