<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 15:16:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>For the Analyst: Peer Benchmarking Methods to Improve Earnings Forecasts</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/21/for-the-analyst-peer-benchmarking-methods-to-improve-earnings-forecasts/</link><description>Peer benchmarking is a vexing task for financial analysts but one that is critical for forecasting earnings. This straightforward measure can help find peers for relative performance, compensation, and valuation benchmarking.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 12:47:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The starting salary for a new American Airlines flight attendant is low enough to qualify for food stamps in some states</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/21/american-airlines-flight-attendant-starting-salary-ceo-food-stamps-union/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1676723511-3-e1716317959418.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Legislation prevents workers from striking without permission from the government.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 20:11:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Building LLMs in the Open-Source Community: A Call to Action for Investment Professionals</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/20/building-llms-in-the-open-source-community-a-call-to-action-for-investment-professionals/</link><description>Large language models like ChatGPT are changing the way we think about investing and reshaping roles in the investment profession.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 16:26:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cyberattacks are soaring—and more lucrative for criminals than drugs. It's time to treat them as an 'act of war', health care exec warns</title><link>https://fortune.com/well/2024/05/21/health-care-cyberattacks-profits-stephen-gillett/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2021278717-e1716318047983.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Cybercrime profits now surpass "all of the illegal drug trafficking in the world combined," Verily CEO Stephen Gillett said at Fortune's Brainstorm Health conference.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 20:03:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sustainability Reporting: Navigating Assurance Practices</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/17/sustainability-reporting-navigating-assurance-practices/</link><description>Don't be lulled into a false sense of security by the word "assurance" when evaluating sustainability reports. Assurance practices vary, and investors would be wise to learn more about the different levels of coverage.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 17:57:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jamie Dimon shocks Wall Street, hinting at his retirement in the next five years and reciting a laundry list of red flags about the global economy</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/21/jamie-dimon-retirement-retiring-jpmorgan-ceo-successors-economy-inflation-investors/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2152634883-e1716315517551.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Dimon says he’s “cautiously pessimistic” about the future of inflation, spending, and the geopolitical landscape.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 19:36:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Power of Clicks, Likes, and Shares: Promote the Right Kind of Financial Content</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/16/the-power-of-clicks-likes-and-shares-promote-the-right-kind-of-financial-content/</link><description>Not all financial content creators on social media are created equal. A broad differentiation can be made between influencers, knowledge sharers, and aspiring thought leaders.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 14:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tech companies are voluntarily agreeing to an AI ‘kill switch’ to prevent Terminator-style risks as some regulators remain hesitant to flex their legal muscles</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/21/ai-regulation-guidelines-terminator-kill-switch-summit-bletchley-korea/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2152201119.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Developers and governments reach consensus, but “toothless” commitments fall short of formal global legal frameworks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 19:33:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why the New T+1 Settlement Cycle Matters: A Global Index Provider’s Perspective</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/14/why-the-new-t1-settlement-cycle-matters-a-global-index-providers-perspective/</link><description>Shorter settlement periods are meant to protect market participants. But the new T+1 settlement cycle for US equities may have undesirable knock-on effects for financial market participants around the world, including index fund managers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 16:54:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Health care workforce challenges must be addressed to support Black mothers</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/21/health-care-workforce-challenges-must-be-addressed-to-support-black-mothers/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Serena-Williams-GettyImages-1839224136.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>In order to serve Black mothers, the healthcare workforce must properly focus on diversity, equity, and inclusion.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>