<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 07:52:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Generational Wealth: Does the Apple Fall Far From the Tree?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/06/generational-wealth-does-the-apple-fall-far-from-the-tree/</link><description>There is strong evidence that most “rich families” will be poorer after several generations. Some of the reasons for this are systemic like taxes. But most factors that diminish a family’s wealth over generations are the choices that heirs make.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 12:37:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FDIC workplace probe finds bank regulator needs a ‘structural and cultural transformation’ to fix ‘sexualized, boys’ club environment’</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/07/fdic-workplace-probe-bank-regulator-structural-cultural-transformation-sexualized-boys-club-environment/</link><description>The findings also recommend changes to the agency’s performance review process, workplace conduct metrics, and that an internal monitor be installed to oversee the effort.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 12:37:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>State Capitalism in Private Markets: Mission Creep</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/03/state-capitalism-in-private-markets-mission-creep/</link><description>Governments relish mingling in markets. Yet, if past policies are any guide, taxpayers are being shortchanged.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 12:30:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Andreessen Horowitz partner says Google is an ‘amazing example’ of employing people in ‘BS jobs’: ‘Half the white-collar staff probably does no real work’</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/07/andreessen-horowitz-partner-david-ulevitch-google-bs-jobs-white-collar-staff-no-real-work/</link><description>"Those people aren't just being useless (and being coddled to think useless jobs actually matter—they don’t), but they are also taking money away from the rest of the workforce's retirement programs."</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 12:24:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Implementation Shortfalls Hamstring Factor Strategies</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/01/implementation-shortfalls-hamstring-factor-strategies/</link><description>Smart rebalancing rules help portfolio managers capture more of the return that is inherent in their factor strategies. Concentrating on “priority best” trading improves factor portfolio performance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 11:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wizz Air boss regrets laying off 20% of workforce during pandemic because it hit morale</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/07/wizz-air-ceo-jozset-varadi-125-million-bonus-regrets-firing-workforce-pandemic-hit-morale/</link><description>Wizz Air boss Jozsef Váradi told fatigued pilots to go "the extra mile" in 2022 as airline struggled with staff numbers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 12:16:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IFRS Accounting Standard Will Support Better Investment Decisions</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/30/ifrs-accounting-standard-will-support-better-investment-decisions/</link><description>IFRS 18 responds to investors' concerns about challenges in comparing companies' financial performance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 11:34:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kellogg’s is letting workers clock off at 12pm on Fridays—but only if they make up the hours during the week</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/07/kelloggs-workers-clock-off-noon-fridays-hours-during-week/</link><description>The $20.6 billion food manufacturer, Kellanova, said its research revealed that two-thirds of people would be willing to work harder during the rest of the week for Friday afternoons off.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 12:03:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meir Statman: Your State of Mind Influences Your Investing Success</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/29/meir-statman-your-state-of-mind-influences-your-investing-success/</link><description>Meir Statman shares his insights on the broader aspects of financial well-being and its interconnection with life satisfaction.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 12:58:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Americans need more exercise—and should be able to tap FSA and HSA funds to pay for gyms, studios, and sports leagues</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/07/health-fitness-phit-act-fsa-hsa-gyms-sports-equipment/</link><description>The PHIT Act aims to expand families' access to physical activity programs and equipment—for youth and adults alike.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>