<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 06:54:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>US Economic Outlook Significantly Stronger Than You’d Think</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-253</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>The US economy isn’t doing as well as you think—it’s doing even better. While mainstream media outlets and grocery prices may make you feel that the US economy is struggling, […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 10:00:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Phlair’s carbon sucking technology could lower direct air capture’s costs</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/19/phlairs-carbon-sucking-technology-could-lower-direct-air-captures-costs/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>The startup is taking a different approach to removing carbon dioxide from the air than most of its competitors. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How We Survived Extreme Heat in Prison</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/09/19/prison-journalists-how-to-survive-extreme-heat</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Incarcerated journalists detail the first signs of a heat wave in prison — and how they’ve coped with record-breaking temperatures.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What It Takes to Master Airbnb Accounting and Bookkeeping</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/mastering-airbnb-accounting-and-bookkeeping</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Accurate accounting and meticulous bookkeeping are vital to maintaining a profitable rental operation, especially when STRs are even more scrutinized than typical rentals.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 21:57:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>India weighs easing market share limits for UPI payment operators</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/18/india-weighs-easing-market-share-limits-for-upi-payment-operators/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>The governing body overseeing India's popular UPI payments rail is considering increasing its proposed market share cap for operators like Google Pay, PhonePe and Paytm. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 07:54:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Marshall Project to Host Inaugural Sing Sing Prison Film Festival</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/09/19/the-marshall-project-to-host-inaugural-sing-sing-prison-film-festival</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Incarcerated jury will choose best criminal justice documentary.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Federal Reserve Cuts Rates By 0.50%, a Bigger Cut Than Expected</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/federal-reserve-cuts-rates-for-first-time-since-2020</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>It finally happened: Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell announced that the Fed will, in fact, cut rates, ending months of speculation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 21:33:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Palmer Luckey returns to headsets as Anduril partners with Microsoft on U.S. military tech</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/18/palmer-luckey-back-in-the-headset-biz-as-anduril-partners-with-microsoft-on-u-s-military-system/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Palmer Luckey, the Hawaiian-shirt wearing founder who sold Oculus VR for $2 billion before co-founding the military tech company Anduril, is back in the headset business — in a sense. Anduril will soon embed its software into the Integrated Visual Augmentation System headset developed by Microsoft for the U.S. military in 2021. According to Wired, […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 05:47:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Robert Roberson’s Death Penalty Case Shows How Justice System Fails People With Autism</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/09/18/texas-autism-death-penalty-roberson</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>He was convicted in his daughter’s death. Those who believe he’s innocent argue his diagnosis helps explain how he ended up facing execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Don’t Do What I Did On Your Next Property…w/Craig Curelop</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-1019</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Can your mistakes make you a millionaire? If you’re like Craig Curelop and learn from what went wrong, then yes! Craig is now financially free, with millions of dollars in […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 10:00:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CEO of self-driving startup Motional is stepping down</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/18/ceo-of-self-driving-startup-motional-is-stepping-down/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Motional, the autonomous vehicle startup backed by Hyundai, is shaking up its leadership ranks. Karl Iagnemma, an early pioneer in the autonomous vehicle industry whose startup Nutonomy lies at the foundation of Motional, is stepping down as president and CEO. Iagnemma will move over to a senior strategy advisor role, while CTO Laura Major will […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 03:28:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Could People Facing the Death Penalty Lose the Right to Tell Juries Their Life Stories?</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/09/17/supreme-court-death-penalty-jury-overturn-precedent</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Some defense lawyers fear that a conservative Supreme Court could overturn that precedent.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 11:00:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Passive Investing 101: A Passive Path to Profit, Appreciation, &amp; Tax Benefits</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-459</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Visit PassivePockets, your resource for passive investing with syndications. Do you want to get into real estate without managing rentals and dealing with tenants? Passive real estate investing could be […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 10:00:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Craig Newmark pledges $100M to fight hacking by foreign governments</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/18/craig-newmark-pledges-100m-to-fight-hacking-by-foreign-governments/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Craigslist founder Craig Newmark plans to donate $100 million to further strengthen U.S. cybersecurity, addressing what he sees as a growing threat from foreign governments, he tells the WSJ. Half the funds will focus on protecting power grids and other infrastructure from cyberattacks; half will be earmarked to educate people about so-called cybersecurity hygiene. Newmark, […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 02:02:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>5 Things to Know About How the Parkland Shooter’s Life Was Spared</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/09/17/how-nikolas-cruz-avoided-death-penalty-takeaways</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways from our investigation into how Nikolas Cruz’s defense team convinced jurors not to impose the death penalty.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 11:00:22 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>