<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 12:08:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Book Riot’s Deals of the Day for April 23, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/book-riots-deals-of-the-day-for-april-23-2024/</link><description>Celebrate World Book Day with this megalist of ebook deals, all for $3.99 or less!</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 16:48:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Nissan Murano, Armada, and new Rogue trim will continue brand's rebound</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/04/23/new-nissan-murano-armada-and-new-rogue-trim-will-continue-brands-rebound/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/04/22224325/2023-Nissan-Pathfinder-Rock-Creek-361.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under:
					    Marketing/Advertising,Nissan,Crossover,SUV,Future Vehicles,Luxury
Continue reading New Nissan Murano, Armada, and new Rogue trim will continue brand's rebound
New Nissan Murano, Armada, and new Rogue trim will continue brand's rebound originally appeared on Autoblog on Tue, 23 Apr 2024 11:56:00 EDT.  Please see our terms for use of feeds.
Permalink | 
						Email this | 
					    Comments</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 16:56:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why this is perfect time to buy health care stocks, one financial advisor says</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/04/23/why-this-is-perfect-time-to-buy-health-care-stocks-one-financial-advisor-says.html</link><description>The market pro offered two names and one ETF to consider picking up.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 552</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-552/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-552</link><description>When you are searching for a job, you will inevitably run into unexpected scenarios. You will have questions, experience self-doubt and even feel discouraged. You’ll also experience great wins, meet wonderful people and discover new things about yourself. That’s the roller-coaster of job search. Consider Summary Sunday your resource for getting questions answered and showing […]
The post Summary Sunday: Issue 552 appeared first on Career Sherpa.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 11:37:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A case for public preschool: New study reveals preschool benefits to be longer-lasting and substantial</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/benefits-of-public-preschool/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=benefits-of-public-preschool</link><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Preschool lays a foundation for elementary school students to succeed. In the United States, as children approach kindergarten entry, it is increasingly common for 4-year-olds to be in non-parental group care and education, often in a center- or school-based setting where they can learn alongside peers. For children from low-income communities, […]
The post A case for public preschool: New study reveals preschool benefits to be longer-lasting and substantial appeared first on Child and Family Blog.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 08:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Properly Measure Baking Ingredients</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/how-to-measure-baking-ingredients/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/measuring-ingredients-.jpg</image_url><description>Whether you are a seasoned baker or just starting out, this informational post has all of my tips and tricks…</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Golden Pothos – Plant Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/golden-pothos-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2024/04/Golden-Pothos-Overhead-650x455.jpg</image_url><description>Pothos are easily our #1 favorite houseplant and the golden pothos is by far the most popular variety. They’re loved by beginners and plant experts alike because they’re affordable, attractive, and easy to care for. They’re quick-growing plants with beautiful trailing vines that add loads of life and color to any space. We have pothos in nearly EVERY room of our house!
There are over a dozen kinds of pothos (Epipremnum aureum), most of which share similar characteristics and care instructions as the golden pothos. You can read more about other varieties we love, like the marble queen pothos and neon pothos.
Golden Pothos Quick Facts
Here’s what you need to know about your golden pothos at a glance:

Latin name: Epipremnum aureum
Common names: Golden pothos, devil’s ivy, devil’s vine, hunter’s rove
Mistaken for: Neon pothos, marble queen pothos
Light: Prefers medium, indirect light but is low-light tolerant
Watering: Every 7-10 days during its growing season, or if the soil is dry &amp; leaves are drooping
Soil: Standard potting mix as long as it drains well
Ideal Humidity: Average household humidity, ideally 50-70%
Ideal Temperature: 65-85 degrees
Cold Hardiness: USDA Zones 10-12

What Is A Golden Pothos?
Continue reading Golden Pothos – Plant Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sandals For Littles</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/04/sandals-for-littles/</link><description>It’s the delightful little moments with my girls that bring the biggest smiles, especially when it comes to the simple…
The post Sandals For Littles appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 05:00:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PEN America Cancels Awards Following Writers’ Boycott Over Palestine</title><link>https://bookriot.com/pen-america-2024-awards-cancelled/</link><description>28 of the 61 writers nominated withdrew from consideration, including 9 of the 10 nominees for a $75,000 prize.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 15:40:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>These are the cars being discontinued for 2024 and beyond</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/article/cars-discontinued-for-2024-and-beyond/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2023/10/04145510/discontinued.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under:
					    Plants/Manufacturing,Audi,Chevrolet,Chrysler,Dodge,Ford,Genesis,Jeep,Maybach,Mazda,McLaren,Mercedes-Benz,Nissan,Subaru
Continue reading These are the cars being discontinued for 2024 and beyond
These are the cars being discontinued for 2024 and beyond originally appeared on Autoblog on Tue, 23 Apr 2024 11:53:00 EDT.  Please see our terms for use of feeds.
Permalink | 
						Email this | 
					    Comments</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 16:53:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tesla set to report first-quarter earnings after the bell</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/04/23/tesla-tsla-earnings-q1-2024-.html</link><description>Tesla releases first-quarter earnings on Tuesday following a dismal deliveries report earlier this month.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 17:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you</link><description>While a little competition in the workplace might help bring out the best in everyone involved, an atmosphere rooted in envy, fear, or jealousy can do the exact opposite. This post will help you recognize signs that your coworker is threatened by you, and help you navigate the situation. 1. They Don’t Want You Involved […]
The post 10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You appeared first on Career Sherpa.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:07:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fathers’ views on family and work after COVID-19 lockdowns</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/fathers-views-on-family-and-work-after-covid-19-lockdowns/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fathers-views-on-family-and-work-after-covid-19-lockdowns</link><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Fathers often want to be present for their children and contribute to household tasks, but they can lack opportunities and confidence; they may see themselves as “helpers” instead of parents. Australian fathers in our small study reported that they spent more time with their children during the COVID-19 lockdowns, and they […]
The post Fathers’ views on family and work after COVID-19 lockdowns appeared first on Child and Family Blog.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cookie Salad</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/cookie-salad/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/cookie-salad.jpg</image_url><description>Serve this fun and delicious cookie salad as a dessert or side dish! Everyone will love the sweet fluffy pudding…</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Neon Pothos – Plant Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/neon-pothos-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2024/04/Neon-Pothos-On-Floating-Shelf-Close-650x469.jpg</image_url><description>Our top recommendation for an easy, starter houseplant? Pothos, pothos, pothos! They’re low-stress, high-impact, and fast-growing vines that are great for both beginners and experts. The golden pothos may be the most common variety but don’t overlook its more vibrant cousin: the neon pothos. We’ve got several neon pothos in our home, and they’re beautiful and so easy! So here’s all you need to know before you get your own.
There are over a dozen varieties of pothos, most of which share similar care instructions to the neon pothos. You can read more about other pothos we love, like the golden pothos and marble queen pothos.
Neon Pothos Quick Facts
Here’s what you need to know about your neon pothos at a glance:

Latin name: Epipremnum aureum ‘Neon’ 
Common names: Neon pothos, neon devil’s ivy
Mistaken for: Golden pothos
Light: Prefers bright, indirect light but is low-light tolerant
Watering: Every 7-10 days during its growing season, or if the soil is dry &amp; leaves are drooping
Soil: Standard potting mix as long as it drains well
Ideal Humidity: Average household humidity, ideally 50-70%
Ideal Temperature: 65-85 degrees
Cold Hardiness: USDA Zones 10-12

What Is A Neon Pothos?
Continue reading Neon Pothos – Plant Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 19:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Saks April Spring Sale</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/04/saks-april-spring-sale/</link><description>Thank you to Saks Fifth Avenue for sponsoring this post. Step into the allure of the season with Saks Fifth…
The post Saks April Spring Sale appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 05:00:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>24 of the Best 2024 Book Covers So Far</title><link>https://bookriot.com/best-2024-book-covers-so-far/</link><description>What adult book covers have struck you as interesting, unique, or otherwise attention-grabbing so far this year?</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Smart #5 concept for Beijing shows how the small-car brand is thinking big</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/04/23/smart-5-concept-shows-how-the-small-car-brand-is-thinking-big/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/04/23090551/smartconcept5highres2.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under:
					    Beijing Motor Show,smart,Crossover,Concept Cars,Electric
Continue reading Smart #5 concept for Beijing shows how the small-car brand is thinking big
Smart #5 concept for Beijing shows how the small-car brand is thinking big originally appeared on Autoblog on Tue, 23 Apr 2024 11:28:00 EDT.  Please see our terms for use of feeds.
Permalink | 
						Email this | 
					    Comments</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 16:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Airbnb's new chief business officer shares his top priorities for hosts and travelers</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/04/23/airbnbs-new-chief-business-officer-shares-his-top-priorities-for-hosts-and-travelers.html</link><description>International stays and more guest experiences are crucial parts of Airbnb's top priorities for future growth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 17:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 551</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-551/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-551</link><description>Job search requires writing and marketing skills. It also requires strong verbal communication. If these skills are not part of your normal work function, you’ll want some help. That’s what this week’s Summary Sunday is all about. There’s no doubt that LinkedIn is one of THE most powerful tools in your career toolbox. It contains […]
The post Summary Sunday: Issue 551 appeared first on Career Sherpa.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 11:37:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Strong Latine Identity Supports U.S. Latine Children’s Well-Being</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/a-strong-latine-identity-supports-u-s-latine-childrens-well-being/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=a-strong-latine-identity-supports-u-s-latine-childrens-well-being</link><description>Key Takeaways for caregivers Children tend to have better health and well-being when they have a strong ethnic identity (affinity and adoption of ethnicity-based self-concept). A traditional Latine cultural value (familismo) that emphasizes family bonds is also associated with better developmental outcomes. Caregivers can support the development of U.S. Latine children (and possibly other children […]
The post A Strong Latine Identity Supports U.S. Latine Children’s Well-Being appeared first on Child and Family Blog.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 03:03:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Creamy Lemon Parmesan Chicken</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/creamy-lemon-parmesan-chicken/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/creamy-lemon-parmesan-chicken-2-4.jpg</image_url><description>Creamy Lemon Parmesan Chicken is an incredible restaurant-quality meal you can make in under 30 minutes. Tender, juicy chicken is…</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 13:00:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Marble Queen Pothos – Plant Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/marble-queen-pothos-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2024/04/Marble-Queen-Pothos-Close-Up-650x526.jpg</image_url><description>Even though the marble queen isn’t the most popular pothos variety, it’s one of our personal favorites! Like all pothos plants, they’re a perfect starter houseplant because they’re resilient, low-maintenance, and fast-growing. Plus, we think it has some of prettiest leaves of all.
There are over a dozen kinds of pothos, most of which share similar characteristics and care instructions as the marble queen. You can read more about other pothos we love, like the golden pothos and neon pothos.
Marble Queen Quick Facts
Here’s what you need to know about your marble queen pothos at a glance:

Latin name: Epipremnum aureum ‘Marble Queen’ 
Common names: Marble queen pothos, marble pothos, pothos marble
Mistaken for: Golden pothos, snow queen pothos
Light: Prefers medium, indirect light but is low-light tolerant
Watering: Every 7-10 days during its growing season, or if the soil is dry &amp; leaves are drooping
Soil: Standard potting mix as long as it drains well
Ideal Humidity: Average household humidity, ideally 50-70%
Ideal Temperature: 60-85 degrees
Cold Hardiness: USDA Zones 10-12

What Is A Marble Queen Pothos?
Continue reading Marble Queen Pothos – Plant Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 18:39:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Strapless For Spring</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/04/strapless-for-spring/</link><image_url>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240325-jb-the-wolf-gang-dress-1006813-1024x1536.jpg</image_url><description>Outfit Details: The Wolf Gang Dress, Dior Sandals, Prada Sunglasses, Gucci Bag (similar here and here) Strapless tops and dresses for spring are the season’s…
The post Strapless For Spring appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 05:00:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best New Book Releases Out April 23, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/best-new-book-releases-out-april-23-2024/</link><description>From nature writing to fake dating to space operas, this week's new releases have a little something for everyone. Which ones are you trying to get into?</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fox Factory Chevy Silverado is built to Baja</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/04/23/fox-factory-chevy-silverado-is-built-to-baja/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/04/22181835/fox_factory_chevy_silverado_01.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under:
					    Chevrolet,Truck,Luxury,Off-Road Vehicles,Performance
Continue reading Fox Factory Chevy Silverado is built to Baja
Fox Factory Chevy Silverado is built to Baja originally appeared on Autoblog on Tue, 23 Apr 2024 10:25:00 EDT.  Please see our terms for use of feeds.
Permalink | 
						Email this | 
					    Comments</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 15:25:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Healthy Returns: Biotech IPOs ramped up to start 2024, but market hasn't fully recovered just yet</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/04/23/healthy-returns-biotech-ipos-heated-up-but-havent-fully-recovered.html</link><description>Biotech IPOs surged at the start of 2024, but the rest of the year will depend on Fed rate cuts. Meanwhile, doctors using VR and AI to hone their skills.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>15 Ways to Own Digital Terrain</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/15-ways-to-own-digital-terrain/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=15-ways-to-own-digital-terrain</link><description>It is now no longer optional…you must have an online presence! Your career stability and your job search demand it. Here are some tips to help you begin claiming digital terrain and brand it with your unique messaging!   Why Should You Own Digital Terrain? You need to stake a claim by owning turf on the […]
The post 15 Ways to Own Digital Terrain appeared first on Career Sherpa.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 15:56:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Children caught between highly conflicted divorced parents at greater risk of mental health problems</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/children-caught-between-conflicted-divorced-parents/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=children-caught-between-conflicted-divorced-parents</link><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Interparental conflict after divorce escalates the risk of mental health problems in children and adolescents. Elevated levels of conflict between parents can also induce fear and worry in children about their future and whether they will be adequately taken care of. In turn, a greater fear of abandonment puts children at […]
The post Children caught between highly conflicted divorced parents at greater risk of mental health problems appeared first on Child and Family Blog.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 08:59:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Swiss Meringue Buttercream</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/swiss-meringue-buttercream/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Meringue-Buttercream-2.jpg</image_url><description>The most delicious Swiss Meringue Buttercream is easy to make with just 5 simple ingredients! It whips up deliciously light…</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Snake Plant – Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/snake-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2024/04/Snake-Plant-By-Stairs-Closer-650x505.jpg</image_url><description>If you’re someone who thinks you can’t keep a plant alive – this plant will prove you wrong! In fact, you’ve probably seen one at a doctor’s office, home improvement store, or hotel lobby because they’re so low maintenance. Thanks to being so easy to care for and widely liked, they’re a great option for anyone who wants a low-effort plant. So today we’ll share why serial plant-killers and seasoned plant lovers all love this spear-shaped beauty.
There are dozens of varieties of snake plants, but today we’ll mainly be talking about the most popular variety: Dracaena trifasciata ‘Laurentii.’ The Laurentii refers to the specific variant of this species seen in these photos. They’re identifiable by their stiff, sword-like leaves with bright yellow edges.
Snake Plant: Quick Facts
Here’s what you need to know about your snake plant at a glance:

Latin name: Dracaena Trifasciata (formerly Sansevieria Trifasciata)
Common names: Snake Plant, Mother-in-Law’s Tongue, Devil’s Tongue, Saint George’s Sword, Vipers Bowstring Hemp, Spear Plant
Native to: West Africa 
Light: Prefers medium, indirect light
Watering: About every 2 weeks or whenever the soil is dry
Soil: Well-drained soil such as a cactus, palm, or succulent mix
Ideal Humidity: Average household humidity
Ideal Temperature: 70-90 degrees
Cold Hardiness: USDA Zones 9-11

Benefits Of A Snake Plant
Beyond being attractive and low maintenance, snake plants are also popular houseplants for their health benefits.
Continue reading Snake Plant – Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 00:41:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Art Of Date Night Dressing</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/04/j-mclaughlin/</link><image_url>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240412-jb-jmclaughlin-1001997-1024x1536.jpg</image_url><description>Outfit Details: J.McLaughlin Top, Pants &amp; Bag Thank you to J.McLaughlin for sponsoring this post. Spring is the perfect season…
The post The Art Of Date Night Dressing appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:00:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best and Buzziest LGBTQ Fantasy Books of 2024 (So Far)</title><link>https://bookriot.com/lgbtq-fantasy-books-of-2024-so-far/</link><description>What's your favorite fantasy book of the year so far?</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The best jumper cables of 2024</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/article/best-jumper-cables/</link><image_url>https://o.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.yimg.com/os/creatr-uploaded-images/2023-07/bf1a6c20-1f62-11ee-ae67-e0557717005d</image_url><description>Filed under:
					    Commerce,Parts and Accessories
Continue reading The best jumper cables of 2024
The best jumper cables of 2024 originally appeared on Autoblog on Tue, 23 Apr 2024 10:15:00 EDT.  Please see our terms for use of feeds.
Permalink | 
						Email this | 
					    Comments</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 15:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Market veteran Howard Marks says Fed is 'not going back' to ultra-low rates</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/04/23/market-veteran-howard-marks-says-fed-is-not-going-back-to-ultra-low-rates.html</link><description>That means credit can provide a "very solid foundation" to an investment portfolio, the Oaktree Capital Management co-founder told CNBC.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 15:53:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 550</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-550/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-550</link><description>Job search strategies change based on the economy, the level and type of work you are looking for, and your personal situation. In other words, there’s no absolute right way for everyone. However, there are best practices you should know about. In this week’s Summary Sunday, you’ll learn about: I carefully curate these articles and […]
The post Summary Sunday: Issue 550 appeared first on Career Sherpa.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 10:44:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>“Why do they feel sad?” Shared book reading reveals how children learn about others’ emotions</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/shared-book-reading/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=shared-book-reading</link><description>Key takeaways for caregivers: It is good for children to identify the emotions of others in conversations with caregivers because it scaffolds their ability to identify others’ emotions on their own. Children who use more emotion talk in parent-child conversations about emotions are more likely to have higher emotion knowledge one year later. Parents can […]
The post “Why do they feel sad?” Shared book reading reveals how children learn about others’ emotions appeared first on Child and Family Blog.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 08:19:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Meal Plan #1</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/weekly-menu-plan-1/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/Meal-Plan-Collage-1-No-Numbers-1-1.jpg</image_url><description>It’s week one of meal planning! Here you will find a free weekly menu plan with a printable shopping list.…</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Weekend In Palm Springs With Kids</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/palm-springs-with-kids/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2024/03/Palm-Springs-Cabazon-Dinosaur-Pink-Brontosaurus-650x507.jpg</image_url><description>Palm Springs, California may not scream “kid-friendly destination” but we recently had THE BEST vacation there with our family (our kids are 9 and 13). So here’s a quick rundown of our favorite must-see attractions in Palm Springs as well as info about where we stayed, what we ate, and what we’re excited to check out next time. Because we definitely will be back!
Did I mention we also brought our nine-pound chihuahua with us? So most of our suggestions are dog-friendly too!
Why Vacation With Kids In Palm Springs?
We chose Palm Springs for a lot of reasons. First, our East Coast-born kids had never been to California! Of course, there are lots of options for California vacations. But we wanted to avoid the hustle of a bigger city like Los Angeles or San Francisco, and we liked the idea of introducing them to the unfamiliar desert geography.
Continue reading A Weekend In Palm Springs With Kids at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 18:51:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Warmer Days Of Spring</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/04/warmer-days-of-spring/</link><image_url>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240416-jb-nordstrom-1002639-1024x1536.jpg</image_url><description>Outfit Details: Erdem Dress Thank you to Nordstrom for sponsoring this post. My wardrobe is fully embracing the warmth of…
The post Warmer Days Of Spring appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 05:00:48 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>