<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 07:43:43 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>MLB Jersey Ads by Team</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/31/mlb-jersey-ads-by-team/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>On April 1, 2022, Major League Baseball announced its teams would be permitted to wear advertisements on their in-game uniforms starting with Opening Day in 2023. As of July 31, 2024, twenty-two (73%) of the thirty MLB teams have advertisements on their uniforms. These ad patches can only be worn</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 20:58:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elon Musk Accepts Fight Challenge From Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/31/elon-musk-accepts-challenge-venezuelan-president-nicolas-maduro/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Elon Musk's talking tough once again ... accepting Venezuelan President Nicolás Maduro's invitation to brawl -- one year after he vowed he'd fight Mark Zuckerberg. President Maduro called out Musk on national television this morning ...…</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 07:43:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seeing Red: AHL’s Milwaukee Admirals Add Second Fauxback Jersey to Rotation</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/31/seeing-red-ahls-milwaukee-admirals-add-second-fauxback-jersey-to-rotation/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Red fauxback jersey is based on cream-colored sweater team introduced back in 2021, and features full body Admiral logo in style of 1950s and ’60s</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 18:36:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Donald Trump Says He's the Best President for Black People Since Lincoln</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/31/donald-trump-best-president-black-people-since-lincoln-nabj/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Donald Trump is in the hot seat right now, as he's being put to task for his controversial past ... though, he thinks his record is pretty impressive -- comparing himself to one of history's most famous U.S. presidents. Trump was at the National…</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 07:43:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Philadelphia Phillies Add IBX Advertisement Patch to Jersey Sleeves</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/31/philadelphia-phillies-add-ibx-advertisement-patch-to-jersey-sleeves/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Philadelphia Phillies have announced they will begin wearing an advertisement for Independence Blue Cross (IBX) on their jersey sleeve beginning with their home game against the New York Yankees on Wednesday, July 31. The patch shows IBX in large blue letters with Independence above placed within a white rounded</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 17:56:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rihanna Dissed By Young Soccer Fan, Asked Her To Take Pic Of Him And Pulisic</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/31/rihanna-christian-pulisic-jack-grealish-yunus-musah-fan/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>History has been made ('cause surely this has never happened before) ... a young soccer fan completely blew off Rihanna, asking the superstar singer to TAKE a photo of him with Christian Pulisic, instead of including RiRi in the pic! Talk about…</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 07:43:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Toronto Raptors Unveil 30th Season Logo</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/30/toronto-raptors-unveil-30th-season-logo/basketball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Toronto Raptors will celebrate their 30th season in 2024-25 with a commemorative logo, which was unveiled on Tuesday morning.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 22:14:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Power Rangers' Star Hector David Jr. Facing Battery Charge</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/31/green-power-ranger-hector-david-jr-battery-charge-police/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Hector David Jr. -- an actor best known for his role on "Power Rangers" -- is a suspect in a misdemeanor battery case ... and we're told he's wanted by Idaho police. Nampa PD in Idaho tells TMZ ... cops are looking for the former Green Power Ranger…</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 07:43:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2024-25 NFL Alternate, Throwback Uniform Schedule</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/30/2024-25-nfl-alternate-throwback-uniform-schedule/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>We've compiled a schedule of when every alternate and throwback uniform will be worn this season, and we'll continue to update as teams make it known what they'll wear and when.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 20:47:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mark Curry Vouches For Tyler Perry's Comedy, Billion-Dollar Bank Account</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/31/mark-curry-supports-tyler-perry-divorce-movie/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Tyler Perry recently fended off critics of his low-rated new film -- but Mark Curry says he need not argue with these folks ... 'cause the man's legacy and earnings speak for themself. We caught up with the veteran comedian out in NYC this week --…</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 07:43:43 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>