<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 15:17:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The Best Books of the 21st Century (So Far)</title><link>https://bookriot.com/today-in-books-may-3-2024/</link><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 17:33:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tesla layoffs, new safety mandates, and a bumper crop of V12s! | Autoblog Podcast #830</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/03/tesla-layoffs-new-safety-mandates-and-a-bumper-crop-of-v12s-autoblog-podcast-830/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/03134805/cast-830.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under:
					    Government/Legal,Green,Podcasts,Aston Martin,Ferrari,Hyundai,Land Rover,Subaru,Tesla,Convertible,Coupe,Crossover,SUV,Electric,Performance,Sedan
					    Plus, we drive some EVs and the updated Range Rover EvoqueContinue reading Tesla layoffs, new safety mandates, and a bumper crop of V12s! | Autoblog Podcast #830
Tesla layoffs, new safety mandates, and a bumper crop of V12s! | Autoblog Podcast #830 originally appeared on Autoblog on Fri, 3 May 2024 14:41:00 EDT.  Please see our terms for use of feeds.
Permalink | 
						Email this | 
					    Comments</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 19:41:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>These 4 stocks have earnings momentum into their reports next week</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/03/these-4-stocks-have-earnings-momentum-into-their-reports-next-week.html</link><description>Watch this collection of stocks for a potential bounce after quarterly results.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 18:33:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 553</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-553/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-553</link><description>Tools and technology change rapidly. Yet as wonderful as technology can be, it doesn’t replace the need for human connection through interactions. Keep this in mind as you are searching for a new job. It’s your human connections that often open doors! In this week’s collection of news and tips for job seekers, you’ll find: […]
The post Summary Sunday: Issue 553 appeared first on Career Sherpa.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 12:19:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A case for public preschool: New study reveals preschool benefits to be longer-lasting and substantial</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/benefits-of-public-preschool/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=benefits-of-public-preschool</link><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Preschool lays a foundation for elementary school students to succeed. In the United States, as children approach kindergarten entry, it is increasingly common for 4-year-olds to be in non-parental group care and education, often in a center- or school-based setting where they can learn alongside peers. For children from low-income communities, […]
The post A case for public preschool: New study reveals preschool benefits to be longer-lasting and substantial appeared first on Child and Family Blog.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 08:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Meal Plan #3</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/weekly-menu-plan-3/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/Week-3-Meal-Plan-No-Numbers.jpg</image_url><description>When I made this Week 3 Meal Plan, I kept your busy schedule in mind! These quick and easy meals…</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Corn Plant – Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/corn-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2024/04/Corn-Plants-On-Bench-Together-650x443.jpg</image_url><description>Corn plants (Dracaena fragrans) are popular low-maintenance houseplants you’ve probably seen at the nursery, home improvement store, or doctor’s office. I even had one in my college dorm room! You can recognize them by their spear-shaped leaves and woody, cane-line trunks that can grow up to 6 feet tall indoors. But did you know there are several varieties of corn plants? We didn’t! Heck, we didn’t even realize some of our smaller houseplants were in the same corn plant family!
Currently, we own two smaller varieties of corn plants, pictured above. The one on the left is a Dracaena Limelight (Dracaena fragrans ‘Limelight’) and the taller plant is a Draecanea Dorado (Dracaena fragrans ‘Dorado’). We actually have several limelights around because we love their vibrant color on shelves, tabletops, and windowsills. 
Corn Plant Quick Facts

Latin name: Dracaena fragrans
Common names: Corn plant, cornstalk plant, false palms
Light: Bright, indirect light but can tolerate lower-light conditions
Watering: Keep soil moist, but not soggy.

Continue reading Corn Plant – Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 17:37:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Travel Essentials</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/travel-essentials/</link><description>As travel season rolls in, promising fresh adventures and revisits to beloved spots, we’re all set with our go-to travel…
The post Travel Essentials appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 05:00:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Riot’s Deals of the Day for May 3, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/book-riots-deals-of-the-day-for-may-3-2024/</link><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 15:34:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Max Verstappen fastest in 2024 Miami GP practice, Leclerc spins</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/03/miami-gp-practice-one-results/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/03135902/auto-prix-f1-usa-practice.jpeg</image_url><description>Filed under:
					    Motorsports,Racing Vehicles
Continue reading Max Verstappen fastest in 2024 Miami GP practice, Leclerc spins
Max Verstappen fastest in 2024 Miami GP practice, Leclerc spins originally appeared on Autoblog on Fri, 3 May 2024 14:09:00 EDT.  Please see our terms for use of feeds.
Permalink | 
						Email this | 
					    Comments</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 19:09:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stocks making the biggest moves midday: Apple, Expedia, Block, Live Nation and more</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/03/stocks-making-the-biggest-moves-midday-aapl-expe-sq-lyv-and-more.html</link><description>These are the stocks posting the largest moves in midday trading.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 18:09:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 552</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-552/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-552</link><description>When you are searching for a job, you will inevitably run into unexpected scenarios. You will have questions, experience self-doubt and even feel discouraged. You’ll also experience great wins, meet wonderful people and discover new things about yourself. That’s the roller-coaster of job search. Consider Summary Sunday your resource for getting questions answered and showing […]
The post Summary Sunday: Issue 552 appeared first on Career Sherpa.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 11:37:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fathers’ views on family and work after COVID-19 lockdowns</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/fathers-views-on-family-and-work-after-covid-19-lockdowns/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fathers-views-on-family-and-work-after-covid-19-lockdowns</link><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Fathers often want to be present for their children and contribute to household tasks, but they can lack opportunities and confidence; they may see themselves as “helpers” instead of parents. Australian fathers in our small study reported that they spent more time with their children during the COVID-19 lockdowns, and they […]
The post Fathers’ views on family and work after COVID-19 lockdowns appeared first on Child and Family Blog.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Slow Cooker Ranch Chicken Tacos</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/slow-cooker-ranch-tacos/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/slow-cooker-ranch-chicken-tacos-1-2.jpg</image_url><description>Switch up taco night with these 4-ingredient slow cooker ranch tacos! The chicken shreds perfectly and is packed with flavor.…</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Using Solid Stain In Our Outdoor Shower</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/solid-deck-stain-outdoor-shower/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2024/04/Sherry-In-Outdoor-Shower-Featured-Image-650x542.jpg</image_url><description>In all of our years of DIYing, I don’t think we’ve ever used a solid stain before. But we recently had a project that was *perfectly* suited for it and, well, solid stain quickly won us over. It was recommended by a professional house painter to us, specifically because he thought it would be great for our outdoor shower. And we found it easy to apply, it gave us great coverage, and we got an even-better-than-we-expected result (which is always the best kind!). So here’s a post that covers all the pros &amp; cons and hows &amp; whys of solid stain. 
As you can see, the “canvas” for this staining project was our outdoor shower. We gave it a mini-makeover right after moving in, but we knew it may need more attention and care down the line. Honestly, we dreaded the task of stripping and restaining it – so many nooks &amp; crannies!
Continue reading Using Solid Stain In Our Outdoor Shower at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 17:46:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spring Clean &amp; Organize</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/spring-clean-organize/</link><description>In our household, spring cleaning is more than a seasonal task; it’s about embracing a system that keeps our home…
The post Spring Clean &amp; Organize appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 05:00:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Here Are The 2024 Edgar Award Winners for Best Mysteries</title><link>https://bookriot.com/here-are-the-2024-edgar-award-winners-for-best-mysteries/</link><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 13:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Salsa Notch 160 Deore 12 eBike: Electric mountain bike built for adventure riding</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/article/salsa-notch-160-deore-12-ebike-electric-mountain-bike-built-for-adventure-riding/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/03123150/59a5f262-c134-4620-858d-51205f7c.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under:
					    Commerce
Continue reading Salsa Notch 160 Deore 12 eBike: Electric mountain bike built for adventure riding
Salsa Notch 160 Deore 12 eBike: Electric mountain bike built for adventure riding originally appeared on Autoblog on Fri, 3 May 2024 14:05:00 EDT.  Please see our terms for use of feeds.
Permalink | 
						Email this | 
					    Comments</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 19:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>These big, well-known stocks are forming the dreaded death cross chart pattern</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/03/these-big-well-known-stocks-are-forming-the-dreaded-death-cross-chart-pattern.html</link><description>A death cross forms when a stock's 50-day moving average slips below its 200-day moving average, lending a signal that investors are bearish on a stock.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 17:51:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you</link><description>While a little competition in the workplace might help bring out the best in everyone involved, an atmosphere rooted in envy, fear, or jealousy can do the exact opposite. This post will help you recognize signs that your coworker is threatened by you, and help you navigate the situation. 1. They Don’t Want You Involved […]
The post 10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You appeared first on Career Sherpa.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:07:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Strong Latine Identity Supports U.S. Latine Children’s Well-Being</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/a-strong-latine-identity-supports-u-s-latine-childrens-well-being/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=a-strong-latine-identity-supports-u-s-latine-childrens-well-being</link><description>Key Takeaways for caregivers Children tend to have better health and well-being when they have a strong ethnic identity (affinity and adoption of ethnicity-based self-concept). A traditional Latine cultural value (familismo) that emphasizes family bonds is also associated with better developmental outcomes. Caregivers can support the development of U.S. Latine children (and possibly other children […]
The post A Strong Latine Identity Supports U.S. Latine Children’s Well-Being appeared first on Child and Family Blog.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 03:03:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Addicting Bean Dip</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/bean-dip/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/cheesiest_bean_dip.jpg</image_url><description>Bring out the chips and start dipping because this is the most addicting bean dip you will ever have! It’s…</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ZZ Plant – Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/zz-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2024/04/ZZ-Plant-Close-Up-Horiztonal-650x475.jpg</image_url><description>The ZZ plant is another one of our favorite low-maintenance houseplants. They’re easy to care for, hard to kill, and always look full &amp; leafy. They’ve even earned the nickname “Eternity Plant” because they’re practically indestructible! That’s why they’re a top choice for commercial spaces, doctor’s offices, and busy homes like ours. Don’t you love a house plant you can forget about?
ZZ plants are sold in a variety of sizes, meaning they’re great for shelves, tabletops, and small surfaces as well as larger statements on the floor. We have some that are over 3 feet tall with their pots!
ZZ Plant Quick Facts
Here’s what you need to know about your ZZ plant at a glance:

Latin name: Zamioculcas zamiifolia
Plant family: Araceae or Arums, which includes Philodendron, Alocasia, Aglaonema, Monstera, and Peace Lily
Common names: ZZ plant, Zanzibar Gem, Zuzu plant, Emerald Palm, Eternity plant
Native to: East Africa
Light: Medium indirect light, but is also low-light tolerant
Watering: Every 2-3 weeks during its growing season
Soil: Standard potting mix as long as it drains well
Ideal Humidity: Average household humidity, ideally 40-50%
Ideal Temperature: 65°F to 75°F
Cold Hardiness: USDA Zones 9b-11

What Is A ZZ Plant?
Continue reading ZZ Plant – Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 19:36:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Introducing the JB x Jennifer Behr Collection</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/04/introducing-the-jb-x-jennifer-behr-collection/</link><image_url>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240312-julia-berolzheimer-jennifer-behr-turquoisenecklace-greenskirt-1002614-1024x1536.jpg</image_url><description>Image Details: JB x Jennifer Behr Necklace &amp; Earrings, Goop Top, Aje Skirt (similar here), Chanel Sandals (similar here), I…
The post Introducing the JB x Jennifer Behr Collection appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 15:00:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Most Read Books on Goodreads This Week</title><link>https://bookriot.com/most-read-books-on-goodreads-may-3-2024/</link><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 10 cheapest cars to drive per mile in 2024</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/article/the-10-cheapest-cars-to-drive-per-mile-in-2024/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2021/10/26143036/Honda-Insight.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under:
					    Green,Driving,Gas Prices,Ownership,Hybrid
Continue reading The 10 cheapest cars to drive per mile in 2024
The 10 cheapest cars to drive per mile in 2024 originally appeared on Autoblog on Fri, 3 May 2024 13:47:00 EDT.  Please see our terms for use of feeds.
Permalink | 
						Email this | 
					    Comments</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 18:47:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>First Berkshire Hathaway annual meeting without Charlie Munger: What to expect from Warren Buffett</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/03/berkshire-hathaways-2024-meeting-is-saturday-heres-how-to-watch.html</link><description>The absence of Charlie Munger will be on everyone's mind when Berkshire Hathaway's annual shareholder meeting kicks off Saturday in Omaha.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 551</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-551/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-551</link><description>Job search requires writing and marketing skills. It also requires strong verbal communication. If these skills are not part of your normal work function, you’ll want some help. That’s what this week’s Summary Sunday is all about. There’s no doubt that LinkedIn is one of THE most powerful tools in your career toolbox. It contains […]
The post Summary Sunday: Issue 551 appeared first on Career Sherpa.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 11:37:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Children caught between highly conflicted divorced parents at greater risk of mental health problems</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/children-caught-between-conflicted-divorced-parents/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=children-caught-between-conflicted-divorced-parents</link><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Interparental conflict after divorce escalates the risk of mental health problems in children and adolescents. Elevated levels of conflict between parents can also induce fear and worry in children about their future and whether they will be adequately taken care of. In turn, a greater fear of abandonment puts children at […]
The post Children caught between highly conflicted divorced parents at greater risk of mental health problems appeared first on Child and Family Blog.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 08:59:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Monster Cookies</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/monster-cookies/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/05/monster-cookies-4.jpg</image_url><description>Monster cookies are slightly crisp on the outside, and soft and chewy in the center. They are loaded with peanut…</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Star Jasmine – Plant Growing &amp; Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/star-jasmine-plant-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2024/04/Star-Jasmine-Flower-Close-Up-650x488.jpg</image_url><description>Star jasmine is a fast-growing and fragrant evergreen vine that not only gives you great coverage &amp; privacy as a climbing or creeping vine, it also bursts into blooms with incredible-smelling flowers in the spring. The plant is native to Asia, but is incredibly popular in the Southeastern United States and areas of California. In warm environments like these, star jasmine is also super easy to care for and grow. Just another reason we love it!
Star jasmine can grow as a dense ground cover, but we prefer to use it as a climbing vine. This does require a trellis, pergola, stakes, or some other structure for it to grow up. Those are easy to make and we have DIY tutorials for a wire trellis on a wall as well as a freestanding privacy trellis. 
Star Jasmine Quick Facts
Here’s what you need to know about star jasmine at a glance:

Latin name: Trachelospermum jasminoides
Plant type: Evergreen climbing vine
Flowers: White star-shaped blooms in late spring &amp; early summer
Sun exposure: Full sun to part shade
Growth rate: Fast-growing (3 to 6 feet per year)
Mature size: Up to 20 feet
Soil: Well-draining loamy soil.

Continue reading Star Jasmine – Plant Growing &amp; Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:02:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Workout Refresh</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/04/workout-refresh/</link><image_url>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240429-jb-workoutrefresh-1-1024x1280.jpg</image_url><description>Outfit Details: Beyond Yoga Sports Bra &amp; Leggings, Marni Bag, Hermes Sandals As spring unfolds, my commitment to working out…
The post Workout Refresh appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 05:00:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Librarians Criminals? These Bills Would Make Them So: Book Censorship News, May 3, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/librarian-criminalization-bills/</link><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>U.S. loosens battery rules, potentially making more cars eligible for EV tax credits</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/03/u-s-loosens-battery-rules-potentially-making-more-cars-eligible-for-ev-tax-credits/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/03124425/composition_of_a_battery.jpeg</image_url><description>Filed under:
					    Government/Legal,Green,Plants/Manufacturing,Electric
Continue reading U.S. loosens battery rules, potentially making more cars eligible for EV tax credits
U.S. loosens battery rules, potentially making more cars eligible for EV tax credits originally appeared on Autoblog on Fri, 3 May 2024 12:45:00 EDT.  Please see our terms for use of feeds.
Permalink | 
						Email this | 
					    Comments</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 17:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Here's where the jobs are for April 2024 — in one chart</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/03/heres-where-the-jobs-are-for-april-2024-in-one-chart.html</link><description>Health care and social assistance led the way, while construction hiring slowed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 15:53:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>15 Ways to Own Digital Terrain</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/15-ways-to-own-digital-terrain/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=15-ways-to-own-digital-terrain</link><description>It is now no longer optional…you must have an online presence! Your career stability and your job search demand it. Here are some tips to help you begin claiming digital terrain and brand it with your unique messaging!   Why Should You Own Digital Terrain? You need to stake a claim by owning turf on the […]
The post 15 Ways to Own Digital Terrain appeared first on Career Sherpa.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 15:56:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>“Why do they feel sad?” Shared book reading reveals how children learn about others’ emotions</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/shared-book-reading/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=shared-book-reading</link><description>Key takeaways for caregivers: It is good for children to identify the emotions of others in conversations with caregivers because it scaffolds their ability to identify others’ emotions on their own. Children who use more emotion talk in parent-child conversations about emotions are more likely to have higher emotion knowledge one year later. Parents can […]
The post “Why do they feel sad?” Shared book reading reveals how children learn about others’ emotions appeared first on Child and Family Blog.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 08:19:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Bake with Yeast</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/how-to-bake-with-yeast/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/how-to-bake-with-yeast-1.jpg</image_url><description>You asked for help with yeast, so I have created a “How to Bake with Yeast” guide just for you!…</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best Greige Paint Colors (According To Experts)</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/best-greige-paint-colors/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2024/04/Best-Greige-Paint-Square-Graphic-650x614.jpg</image_url><description>“Greige” is that sweet spot between gray &amp; beige, and it’s a paint color that’s both trendy and timeless. In fact, we’ve been on the greige bandwagon for nearly 20 years – well before we’d even heard that term! But finding the perfect greige can be daunting. There are 100s of neutral paint colors that could be considered greige, so we’ve waded through dozens of expert round-ups to see what colors come up over and over again. (Yes, I made a spreadsheet. And yes, I liked it). 
We weren’t surprised to see our favorite greige paint show up on this Iist, but the color that ranked #1 was a bit of a shock to us! 
What Is Greige?
Greige is an umbrella term for any color that dances the line between gray and beige (gray + beige = greige).
Continue reading The Best Greige Paint Colors (According To Experts) at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 17:43:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amazon Sundays</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/04/amazon-sundays-4-21-24/</link><description>Outfit Details: My Swimsuit, Girls’ Swimsuits, Goggles Welcome to Amazon Sundays, filled with the latest from Amazon that I’m especially…
The post Amazon Sundays appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 05:00:43 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>