<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 07:10:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Book Review: The New World Economy in 5 Trends</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/24/book-review-the-new-world-economy-in-5-trends/</link><description>A diligent economist and an eclectic bookworm serve up an analysis of megatrends that will have the greatest impact on economies and investments: innovation, productivity, climate, multiglobalization, debt, and aging.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 12:22:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bill Gates said he wished he learned this lesson from Warren Buffett sooner: The power of an 'intentionally light' calendar</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/28/bill-gates-warren-buffett-calendar-lesson/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2151357685-e1716892204682.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>"In hindsight, it’s a lesson I could have learned a lot sooner had I taken more peeks at Warren Buffett’s intentionally light calendar."</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 11:40:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Factor Strategies Belong in Your Completion Portfolio Toolkit</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/23/factor-strategies-belong-in-your-completion-portfolio-toolkit/</link><description>Why wouldn't you include factor strategies in your completion portfolio? A review of the two commonly used approaches for managing institutional assets highlights their symbiotic nature.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 19:09:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>While American companies go quiet on climate change, Europeans keep banging the drum</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/28/american-companies-quiet-climate-change-europeans-keep-banging-drum/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Danone-CEO-GettyImages-2149552913-e1716890807828.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>One-pager: Concerns over culture wars and ESG investment backlash are stronger factors in the U.S. than Europe, which may lead to further divergence on net zero trajectories.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 11:37:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>For the Analyst: Peer Benchmarking Methods to Improve Earnings Forecasts</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/21/for-the-analyst-peer-benchmarking-methods-to-improve-earnings-forecasts/</link><description>Peer benchmarking is a vexing task for financial analysts but one that is critical for forecasting earnings. This straightforward measure can help find peers for relative performance, compensation, and valuation benchmarking.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 12:47:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Rational' monetary policies are back, says Turkey's finance chief, as he seeks to stabilize inflation-ridden economy</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/28/rational-monetary-policies-back-turkey-finance-chief-stabilize-inflation-ridden-economy/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Mehmet-Simsek-Turkey-Christopher-Pike-Bloomberg-GettyImages-2152489250-e1716887426958.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Turkey had kept interest rates low amid soaring inflation, against conventional wisdom, leading investors to desert its bond market.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 11:33:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Building LLMs in the Open-Source Community: A Call to Action for Investment Professionals</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/20/building-llms-in-the-open-source-community-a-call-to-action-for-investment-professionals/</link><description>Large language models like ChatGPT are changing the way we think about investing and reshaping roles in the investment profession.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 16:26:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>American company tells Mexico president that his $385m offer to buy its Caribbean property for ecotourism 'substantially undervalues' its crocodile-filled quarries</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/28/vulcan-materials-mexico-president-amlo-385m-offer-caribbean-property-undervalues-crocodile-quarries/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/AP24148663080590-e1716891186418.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Mexican President Andrés Manuel López Obrador has threatened to expropriate the property, claiming the pits it has dug to extract crushed limestone have damaged the area's fragile system of underground rivers and caves.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 11:22:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sustainability Reporting: Navigating Assurance Practices</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/17/sustainability-reporting-navigating-assurance-practices/</link><description>Don't be lulled into a false sense of security by the word "assurance" when evaluating sustainability reports. Assurance practices vary, and investors would be wise to learn more about the different levels of coverage.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 17:57:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wisconsin law that banned collective bargaining for most public employees back in court</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/28/wisconsin-law-ban-collective-bargaining-most-public-employeescourt-unions-sue/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/AP24142556347932-e1716890809474.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The court is controlled 4-3 by liberals, a flip from when it upheld the law a decade ago under 5-2 conservative control.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 11:09:04 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>