<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 06:52:12 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>My Tenant Was Airbnbing Their Apartment Without Me Knowing. It Happens More Than You Think.</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/my-tenants-were-airbnbing-my-apartment-without-me-knowing</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Renting has its horror stories, and sometimes it gets out of control. Jeff gives us an inside look at what happened when one of his tenants rented out his property without him knowing, plus stories from other landlords.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 21:24:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stripe acquires payment processing startup Lemon Squeezy</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/26/stripe-acquires-payment-processing-startup-lemon-squeezy/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Payments giant Stripe has acquired a four-year-old competitor, Lemon Squeezy, the latter company announced Friday. Terms of the deal were not disclosed. As a merchant of record, Lemon Squeezy calculates and pays global sales tax for digital products, handling legal processing and fees in every country. It primarily serves SaaS and software businesses. In a […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 21:55:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Love Beyond Bars: Raymond and Cassandra</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/26/photo-essay-raymond-flanks-wrongful-conviction</link><description>Raymond Flanks spent nearly 39 years in Louisiana lockups for a murder he didn’t commit. Luckily, he found love with an old friend, Cassandra Delpit.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 11:00:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mortgage Rate Gaps: Tracking the States With the Tightest Lock-In Effects</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/states-with-the-tightest-lock-in-effects</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>With higher interest rates, the lock-in effect has created a low inventory environment. Homeowners in these states are the most locked-in.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 21:05:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple reports iCloud Private Relay global outages for some users</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/26/apples-icloud-private-relay-hit-by-outages-for-some-users/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>iCloud Private Relay has not been working for some Apple users across major markets, including the U.S., Europe, India and Japan. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 20:55:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Problem With Labeling Trump a ‘Felon’</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/25/donald-trump-felon-election24</link><description>Here’s why language used to describe any person convicted of crimes matters, and affects more than the former president.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 23:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BiggerNews: Multifamily Market Update + Where to Find Deals NOW</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-995</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Multifamily real estate is still offering some significant opportunities to investors—you just need to know where to look! Although the past two years have been rough for multifamily, with falling […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 07:02:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Legal tech, VC brawls and saying no to big offers</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/26/legal-tech-vc-brawls-and-saying-no-to-big-offers/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Welcome to Startups Weekly — your weekly recap of everything you can’t miss from the world of startups. To get Startups Weekly in your inbox every Friday, sign up here. This week we are talking about Wiz’s bold decision, VC’s public feud, legal tech’s new capital and a16z’s close call. Let’s go! Most interesting startup stories […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 20:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Photos: Three Years of a Family’s Grief and Healing After a Fatal Police Shooting</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/25/family-photos-cleveland-police-shooting-belmonte</link><description>Photographer Michael Indriolo documents an East Cleveland family’s search for peace after the 2021 police shooting of their 19-year-old brother.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 11:00:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rookie Reply: What EVERY Rookie Must Learn Before Investing in Real Estate</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-437</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Not quite ready to invest in real estate? Maybe you’re still getting your finances in check or saving for a bigger down payment. In any case, don’t sit on your […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 07:02:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple signs the White House’s commitment to AI safety</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/26/apple-signs-the-white-houses-commitment-to-ai-safety/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Apple joins 15 other tech companies — including Google, Meta, Microsoft and OpenAI — that committed to the White House's rules for developing generative AI. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 18:45:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sending Unarmed Responders Instead of Police: What We’ve Learned</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/25/police-mental-health-alternative-911</link><description>There are more than 100 response teams nationwide, but experts say more research on their impact is needed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 11:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is FIRE Dead? No, But Here’s Why Most WON’T Achieve It</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-549</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Is the FIRE movement dead? In 2024, more people are catching on to the huge downsides of pursuing financial independence, retire early. Strict frugality, massive sacrifice, working harder than ever…is […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 07:01:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Privacy watchdog says it’s ‘surprised’ by Elon Musk opting user data into Grok AI training</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/26/privacy-watchdog-says-its-surprised-by-elon-musk-opting-user-data-into-grok-ai-training/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The language is ambiguous, so it's not clear whether X is helping itself to all user data for training Grok or whether this processing refers only to user interactions with the chatbot. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 18:34:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Marshall Project Launches Investigate This!</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/25/the-marshall-project-launches-investigate-this</link><description>Our toolkits will offer data, storytelling and engagement resources to empower more criminal justice reporting in local communities</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>