<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 07:19:08 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Seeing Greene: Investing with High DTI, When to Refi, &amp; Getting Out of Debt</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-989</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Life happens, and you’ve accumulated some debt. You’re wondering how to buy real estate EVEN with a high DTI (debt-to-income) ratio. Whether it’s good debt, like rental property mortgages, or […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 07:02:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ultrahuman’s smart ring gets FDA-approved AFib detection</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/16/ultrahumans-smart-ring-gets-fda-approved-afib-detection/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The smart ring has long played second fiddle to the smart watch. While tech giants like Apple and Google duked it out over wrists for years, the ring has been significantly quieter, a space where plucky startups have a chance to make their mark. Things are quickly changing, however. Samsung will debut its first finger-worn […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How a Supreme Court Ruling Could Affect a Case Involving Police Abuse of Youth</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/13/supreme-court-bankruptcy-sackler-boy-scouts</link><description>Another court must now decide how the landmark ruling will impact the Boy Scouts abuse settlement, which involves victims of police sexual abuse.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From a Negative Net Worth to FI in Just 5 Years by Living Like a Stoic</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-546</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>The road to financial independence isn’t always linear, but stoicism might be the secret ingredient that keeps you on track. This ancient philosophy gets a bad rap, but with its […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 07:01:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Byju’s, once valued at $22 billion, faces insolvency proceedings</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/16/byjus-once-valued-at-22-billion-faces-insolvency-proceedings/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>An Indian tribunal court initiated insolvency proceedings for Byju’s, once India’s most valuable startup, on Tuesday in response to a petition from the country’s powerful cricket board. The Tuesday ruling installs an interim resolution professional to manage the company’s operations, pushing the once-billionaire founder out in a dramatic turn for a firm that was valued […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 11:25:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jackson, Mississippi, Wants Curfew Centers to Cut Crime. Here’s What Other Cities Learned.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/09/jackson-mississippi-youth-curfew-centers</link><description>After a teen’s murder, city officials hope a curfew and youth centers will get kids off the street. Young people are skeptical.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 11:00:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Resident Turnover Challenge: 5 Retention Strategies for Single-Family Rentals</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/strategies-for-better-single-family-rental-tenant-retention</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Every investor wants 100% retention, but it's not as easy as you'd wish. Here are the best strategies for getting as close as possible to it.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 22:06:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Uber just added a way to search for rides in other cities— here’s how to use it</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/16/uber-feature-search-for-rides-in-other-cities/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>As Uber gears up for the summer travel season, the company announced Tuesday a new feature to ease the planning process for riders. The feature offers a convenient way for users to search for destinations in another city and reserve rides in advance before their plane even lands. Uber’s new feature addresses the surge in […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Love Beyond Bars: Miguel and Silvia</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/05/photo-essay-wrongful-conviction-love-story</link><description>While Miguel Solorio did 25 years for a crime he didn’t commit, his wife, Silvia, was right by his side. Here’s their California love story in pictures.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Millions of Americans Should Keep Their Homes as Rentals, Not Sell. Here’s Why.</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/americans-should-keep-their-homes-not-sell-in-2024</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>The higher interest rate environment has changed the answer to the “sell vs. keep” question, and every homeowner needs to run the math before selling.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 21:32:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Toddle wants to ‘change how we build software’ with a collaborative visual web app builder</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/16/toddle-wants-to-change-how-we-build-software-with-a-collaborative-visual-web-app-builder/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Danish startup Toddle has launched a no-code web app builder that's designed as a full-featured alternative to Javascript frameworks. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 10:42:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Crime Rates and the 2024 Election: What You Need to Know</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/27/trump-and-biden-spar-over-crime-rates-ahead-of-their-debate-what-do-we-really-know</link><description>As crime data again becomes a flashpoint in the presidential campaign, experts push for better national statistics.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Large Apartment Buildings Remain at Risk of Catastrophic Losses</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/large-apartment-buildings-set-for-further-losses</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>After two years of multifamily decline, the end is still not in sight.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 20:19:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Presti is using GenAI to replace costly furniture industry photo shoots</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/15/presti-uses-generative-ai-to-improve-product-photography-in-the-furniture-industry/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>If you’ve ever bought a sofa online, have you thought about the homes you can see in the background of the product shots? When it’s time to release a new collection, furniture brands usually spend a small fortune on photo shoots. It’s a cumbersome and expensive process as it’s not easy to move furniture around. […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 07:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Death Row Prisoner’s Parting Interview</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/24/texas-death-row-prisoner-final-interview</link><description>Days before his scheduled execution in Texas, Ramiro Gonzales speaks on faith, legacy — and apologizing to the family of his victim, Bridget Townsend.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>