<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 09:51:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The Fed Finally Cuts Rates, but Will It Even Matter?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-255</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>The Fed’s recent rate cut signaled something clear about the US economy, but what are they trying to say? With a bolder rate cut than many of us expected, homebuyers, […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 10:00:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>After is a new dating app that tries to tackle ghosting</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/26/after-is-a-new-dating-app-that-tries-to-tackle-ghosting/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>A new female-founded dating app called After is launching in Austin, Texas on Thursday with the mission of tackling ghosting and holding people accountable. What sets the app apart from the rest of the dating app scene is that After requires users to share why they have unmatched a person before they are allowed to […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Wisconsin Board Says the Real Victim of Police Misconduct Is … the Government</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/09/25/kenosha-wisconsin-police-crime</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Michael Bell says Kenosha police killed his son and covered up the truth. A victims rights board had a different takeaway.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why I Continue to Buy REITs Instead of Rental Properties</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/why-im-buying-reits-instead-of-rental-properties</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Last year, Jussi Askola explained why he believes REITs are better investment vehicles than rental properties. This year, he explains why nothing has changed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 21:44:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Tor Project merges with Tails, a Linux-based portable OS focused on privacy</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/26/the-tor-project-merges-with-tails-a-linux-based-portable-os-focused-on-privacy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>The Tor Project is merging operations with Tails, a portable Linux-based operating system focused on preserving user privacy and anonymity. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 13:19:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Inside Story Season 2 to Premiere Soon</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/09/24/criminal-justice-inside-story-trailer</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>The video series, developed by formerly incarcerated people, about the criminal justice system returns for another season.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 20:00:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>One Month After the NAR Rule Changes, These Agents Told Us How Their Business Has Changed</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/one-month-after-nar-changes-this-is-how-some-agents-have-changed-their-business</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>It’s been a little over a month since the groundbreaking rules regarding agent commissions stipulated in a $418 million settlement between the DOJ and NAR (National Association of Realtors) took […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 20:24:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prepared, which wants to ‘revolutionize’ emergency 911 calls, raises $27M</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/26/prepared-which-lets-911-dispatchers-text-and-video-chat-with-callers-raises-27m/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>A company that claims its tech can “revolutionize” emergency calls has raised $27 million in a Series B round led by Andreessen Horowitz. The company, Prepared, enables 911 dispatchers to get a caller’s real-time GPS location if their phone supports it. Via Prepared, dispatchers can also receive and respond to texts and images, and — […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 13:00:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mississippi Court Candidates Tell You Why They Should Be Elected</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/09/24/mississippi-court-candidates-tell-you-why-they-should-be-elected</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>The Marshall Project - Jackson and Mississippi Today asked the candidates to explain why people should vote for them. Here’s who responded.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What to Invest in When You’re NOT Buying Real Estate</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-1022</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Struggling to pick what to invest in, especially when real estate prices and mortgage rates are still so high? Many investors are sitting on the sidelines, saving cash for their […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 10:00:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>As war rages in Ukraine, investment in European defense and dual-use tech skyrockets</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/26/as-war-rages-in-ukraine-investment-in-european-defense-and-dual-use-tech-skyrockets/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>A new Dealroom report shows that VC investment in defense-related tech is outpacing any other type of investment across NATO member states and allies. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 12:07:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meet the People Running for Mississippi’s Supreme Court and Other Courts</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/09/24/mississippi-judge-guide-supreme-court-appeals-hinds-county</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>We profiled candidates for two state Supreme Court seats and other courts, and asked each to tell you in their own words why they should be elected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>7 Properties in 10 Years by Turning 1 Home’s Equity Into an Entire Portfolio</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-462</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>This assistant principal slowly and steadily used home equity to invest, helping him acquire seven properties in just over ten years. These properties have now seen sizable appreciation, and he […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 10:00:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Peak XV has reaped $1.2B in the year since it split from Sequoia</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/25/peak-xv-has-reaped-1-2b-in-the-year-since-it-split-from-sequoia/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Peak XV Partners, the largest India-focused venture fund, has realized about $1.2 billion in exits since it separated from Sequoia last year. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 07:39:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How We Survived Extreme Heat in Prison</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/09/19/prison-journalists-how-to-survive-extreme-heat</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Incarcerated journalists detail the first signs of a heat wave in prison — and how they’ve coped with record-breaking temperatures.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>