<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from multiple RSS sources, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 06:58:52 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The New Reform That Could Unlock $1B+ for Affordable Housing w/Sharon Cornelissen</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-211</link><description>America is in need of affordable housing; we’re all aware. Buying your first home has become increasingly challenging for everyday people. This is where housing subsidies come in. Federal housing […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 07:02:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TikTok pulls feature from Lite app in EU over addiction concerns</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/25/tiktok-lite-rewards-feature-suspended-eu/</link><description>TikTok suspended a gamification feature in the European Union following an intervention by the bloc. With attention on TikTok’s growing pile of US legal woes, the announcement went mostly unnoticed when it occurred late local time Wednesday. TikTok’s move came just two days after the EU opened an investigation into a so-called “task and reward” […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 09:46:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Enduring Use of Solitary, and New Proposed Limits That Will Likely Fail (Again)</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/20/solitary-confinement-reform-oklahoma-washington-florida</link><description>Isolation’s damaging effects are widely known. But many facilities confine people — even youth — virtually all day, sometimes in shower stalls.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rise and Shine: A Carefully Considered Morning Ritual That Can Brighten Your Day</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/rise-shine-carefully-considered-morning-ritual-brighten-your-day?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Strategies for getting ready to be at your best each morning</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 10:31:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sunbelt Surge: 15 Cities Dominating the Growth Charts</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/best-sunbelt-markets-for-growth</link><description>Simply investing in any metro Sunbelt market is not a recipe for success. To catch a cresting wave of appreciation and cash flow, you’ll need to dive deep into the metrics […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:48:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Playruo lets you try game demos from your web browser</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/25/playruo-lets-you-try-game-demos-from-your-web-browser/</link><description>It’s still unclear whether cloud gaming will ever become the next big thing. The appeal is clear: The game you’re playing runs in a data center near you, and the video output is directly streamed to your local device. When you interact with the game, everything is relayed back to the data center. When it […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Officials Failed to Act When COVID Hit Prisons. A New Study Shows the Deadly Cost.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/18/covid-prison-deaths-data</link><description>People in prison died at 3.4 times the rate of the free population, with the oldest hit hardest. New data holds lessons for preventing future deaths.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Considering a Clinical Trial When You Have COPD</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/lung/copd/features/clinical-trials-copd?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Thinking about joining a clinical trial to help your COPD? Jean Rommes shares some of what to expect.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 22:21:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Warning: These States and Cities Are Becoming Uninvestable Due to Politics</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/how-politics-is-making-these-states-and-cities-uninvestable</link><description>Taxes and regulations impact your bottom line as an investor—and not always in direct or obvious ways. Unfortunately, as soon as you start talking about either one, the average person closes their […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:27:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Edonia grabs €2M to turn microalgae into less bitter-tasting ground meat alternative</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/24/edonia-2m-microalgae-ground-meat-alternative/</link><description>The company produces plant-based ingredients from raw microalgae biomass, generated from spirulina or chlorella, that it claims is more nutritious than meat.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 07:00:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Parents Paying for Their Children’s Crimes</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/13/michigan-school-shooting-parents</link><description>Experts warn about a wave of legal consequences for parents like the Crumbleys, while some states consider prosecutions for kids as young as 10.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Treating and Managing Mild COPD</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/lung/copd/features/treat-mild-copd?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Learn how to treat and manage mild COPD.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 22:07:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The BEST Ways to Protect Your Rental Property and Keep Your Tenants Safe</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-397</link><description>If you own a rental property, it’s YOUR responsibility to provide a safe environment for tenants. This starts with things like tenant screening, security upgrades, and most importantly, acting swiftly […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:02:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Swiggy, the Indian food delivery giant, seeks $1.25 billion in IPO after receiving shareholder approval</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/24/india-swiggy-secures-shareholder-approval-for-1-2-billion-ipo/</link><description>Swiggy, an Indian food delivery and instant commerce startup, plans to raise $1.25 billion in an initial public offering and has secured approval from its shareholders. The company disclosed its IPO plans in a filing to the local regulator. The Bengaluru-headquartered startup plans to raise $450 million through the issuance of new shares and offer […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 06:28:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I Had a Tough Job at My Brooklyn Jail: Keeping Men From Taking Their Own Lives</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/12/brooklyn-jail-suicide-prevention-aide</link><description>As a suicide prevention aide, I had to make sure my fellow detainees didn’t harm themselves. It was surprisingly easy to get such a complex job.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Manage Your COPD Flares</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/lung/copd/features/manage-copd-episodes?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>If you have chronic obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD), you’re probably no stranger to flares. If you take steps to address symptoms early and find ways to minimize triggers, you can dramatically lower your risk of flares.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 21:54:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Building Wealth with OLD Homes and How to Keep Tenants for Longer</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-942</link><description>How do you find investment properties nobody else is looking for—the ones with cash flow potential, equity upside, and wealth-building qualities all the other investors overlook? Simple: buy what nobody […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:02:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mark Zuckerberg says Threads has 150 million monthly active users</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/24/mark-zuckerberg-says-threads-has-150-million-monthly-active-users/</link><description>Threads, the Twitter/X rival from Meta, is growing at a stable pace. The social network now has more than 150 million monthly active users — up from 130 million in February — Mark Zuckerberg mentioned during the company’s Q1 2024 earnings call. Since the last quarterly earnings call, Threads has notably taken steps towards integrating […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 05:01:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Supreme Court Case on Homelessness May Limit Prisoner Rights and Expand Executions</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/10/supreme-court-homeless-grants-pass-originalism</link><description>In Grants Pass v. Johnson, a town in Oregon asks the court to reconsider what constitutes “cruel and unusual punishments.”</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Lifestyle Changes Helped Minimize My COPD Episodes</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/lung/copd/features/copd-lifestyle-changes?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Edi Mesa  made these lifestyle changes in order to keep COPD episodes to a minimum.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 21:51:41 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>