<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:24:32 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>4 Unconventional Signals That Show Me Untapped Potential in a Real Estate Market</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/unconventional-signals-i-look-for-to-find-potential-in-a-real-estate-market</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>We all know the basics for market analysis, but these less conventional signals can be game changers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 17:30:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Startups Weekly: Clash of the AI titans, and Europe is firing on all cylinders</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/14/startups-weekly-clash-of-the-ai-titans-and-europe-is-firing-on-all-cylinders/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Welcome to Startups Weekly — Haje’s weekly recap of everything you can’t miss from the world of startups. Sign up here to get it in your inbox every Friday. Hold on to your Apple Watches, folks! At WWDC 2024, Apple finally decided to give Siri a brain transplant with something they’re calling “Apple Intelligence” (AI—get […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 20:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Criminal Justice Journalist Wrestles With Doubts in the Jury Box</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/14/journalist-serves-on-jury-criminal-trial</link><description>A longtime journalist serving on a jury must weigh the flaws of the system against the holes in the gun and drug case he heard.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Fed Stalls as High Rates Cause More Pain—What Is Powell Doing?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/federal-reserve-stalls-as-inflation-numbers-improve-may-2024</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>As far as real estate investors are concerned, there’s more bad news than good from the latest Federal Reserve meeting. The bad news is that interest rates will remain the […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 17:06:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pitch Deck Teardown: Kinnect’s $250K angel deck</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/14/pitch-deck-teardown-kinnects-250k-angel-deck/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>How well did the company do telling its own story in the form of its angel pitch deck? Let's take a look. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Serving Time for Their Abusers’ Crimes</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/13/abuse-domestic-violence-survivors-liability-prison</link><description>The Marshall Project found nearly 100 people who were punished for the actions of their abusers under little-known laws like “accomplice liability.”</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Airbnb Is Pairing Up With Mom-and-Pop Investors to Win Its War—but Is It Too Late?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/airbnb-partners-with-mom-and-pop-investors-to-win-its-legislative-war</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>When New York City banned short-term rentals (under 30 days) under Local Law 18 in September 2023, 15,000 landlords suddenly found themselves without income, many struggling to pay their mortgages. […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 16:58:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Arc now features a live calendar button to help you stay punctual for meetings</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/14/arc-browser-new-live-calendar-button-feature/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The Browser Company’s Arc, a web browser that aims to have a less cluttered user interface, launched a “Live Calendar” feature to ensure you never miss a call or run late to a meeting. The feature rolled out yesterday on Mac and is available in the latest Arc update with version 1.47.1. The new feature […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 16:41:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Behind the Black Shield: The History of a Cleveland Institution</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/13/black-shield-history-police-cleveland</link><description>How one of the oldest Black policing organizations in the country shaped law enforcement in Cleveland.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Market Your Rental Property (8 Tips for Landlords)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/how-to-market-your-rental-property</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>There’s no right or wrong way to market your rental property, but there are some tips you can follow to increase the likelihood of quickly finding a quality tenant.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 16:03:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meta pauses plans to train AI using European users’ data, bowing to regulatory pressure</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/14/meta-pauses-plans-to-train-ai-using-european-users-data-bowing-to-regulatory-pressure/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Meta has confirmed that it will pause plans to start training its AI systems using data from its users in the European Union and U.K. The move follows pushback from the Irish Data Protection Commission (DPC), Meta’s lead regulator in the EU, which is acting on behalf of several data protection authorities across the bloc. […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 16:33:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>5 Takeaways From Our Series on St. Louis Homicide Investigations</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/10/st-louis-police-unsolved-murders-takeaways</link><description>The police department has struggled to solve homicides, partly due to shoddy detective work, staffing shortages and eroding community trust.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Show a Rental Property (6 Simple Steps)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/how-to-show-a-rental-property</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>When you know how to show a rental property, you'd better position yourself to find a tenant in short order. Here are the six steps you must take to show a rental property to prospective tenants.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:10:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Brave integrates its own search results with its Leo AI assistant</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/14/brave-integrates-its-own-search-results-with-its-leo-ai-assistant/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Privacy-focused search engine and web browser company Brave Software is integrating search results into its Leo chatbot. Search results are based on the Brave Search API and Leo is integrated into the company’s browser. The company said that this integration will help users find more up-to-date information. People can use this integration to fetch information […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 11:10:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>They Were in a Mental Health Crisis at a Hospital. This Is How They Landed in Jail.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/09/seattle-arrest-assault-mental-illness</link><description>Washington, like most states, has a law intended to protect health care workers. Instead, it’s led to prosecutions of people with severe mental illness.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>