<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 07:47:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>BiggerNews: 2024 Housing Market Update (Home Prices, Mortgage Rate Predictions)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-1002</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>Where will the housing market be by 2025? We’ve got some of the top 2024 housing market predictions to share today as we run through what could happen with home […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 10:00:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ola Electric surges 20% in India’s biggest listing in two years</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/08/ola-electric-surges-in-indias-biggest-listing-in-two-years/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>Ola Electric, India’s largest electric two-wheeler maker, surged by 20% on its public debut on Friday, making it the biggest listing among Indian firms in two years. Shares of the Bengaluru-based firm, which counts SoftBank and Temasek among its backers, jumped to ₹91.20 (about $1.1) after starting to trade at ₹76, the higher end of […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 05:48:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tim Walz on Criminal Justice: 5 Things to Know</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/06/tim-walz-kamala-harris-vp-criminal-justice</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Where Minnesota Gov. Tim Walz, Vice President Kamala Harris’ running mate, stands on policing, guns, prison reform and other issues.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rookie Reply: How to Screen Tenants for Free &amp; When to Cash-Out Refinance</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-442</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>Screening tenants is a necessary but expensive part of real estate investing. In some cases, property managers charge as much as one month’s rent to place a tenant. What if […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 10:00:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rocket Lab’s sunny outlook bodes well for future constellation plans</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/08/rocket-labs-sunny-outlook-bodes-well-for-future-constellation-plans/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Rocket Lab surpassed $100 million in quarterly revenue for the first time, a 71% increase from the same quarter of last year. This is just one of several shiny accomplishments executives showed off to investors on Thursday — and a good omen for the space company’s medium-term ambitious plans. Executives continued to tease plans for […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 00:33:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>They Exposed Police Misconduct. Now They’re Paying a Steep Price.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/03/police-congress-corruption-whistleblower</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Whistleblower laws have advanced in public and private sectors, but protections for police who report illegal or unethical behavior lag far behind.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>$100K by 23, Coast FI by 27 Thanks to One Smart Money Challenge</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-553</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Once you hit Coast FI, you don’t need to worry about retirement. While traditional FIRE may take a bit more extra work, Coast FI allows you to let your foot […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 07:01:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CloudPay, a payroll services provider, lands $120M in new funding</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/08/cloudpay-a-payroll-services-provider-lands-120m-in-new-funding/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>In 1996, two companies, Patersons HR and Payroll Solutions, formed a venture called CloudPay to provide payroll and payments services to enterprise clients. CloudPay grew quietly over the next several decades, adding workflow automation features to maintain pace with upstart rivals. It’s still growing, CFO Andy Thomson assures TechCrunch. Thomson claims that CloudPay is handling […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 23:20:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Drawing Attention</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/01/news-inside-issue-17</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>News Inside Issue 17 features the opinions of justice-affected people on Trump’s felonies, and a nonfiction comic about death penalty mitigation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Developers Are Ditching This State as Regulations Rise</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-241</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>Why are developers ditching California NOW? Is commercial real estate still struggling, and what’s up with all those empty office buildings all over town? Does it seem like everyone is […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 10:00:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Security bugs in ransomware leak sites helped save six companies from paying hefty ransoms</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/08/security-bugs-in-ransomware-leak-sites-helped-save-six-companies-from-paying-hefty-ransoms/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>The vulnerabilities allowed one security researcher to peek inside the leak sites without having to log in. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 23:20:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>These Private Centers Lack Oversight. Cuyahoga County Judges Send Kids Anyway.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/01/juvenile-justice-detention-prison-youth-treatment-cuyahoga-county</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>Courts are increasingly sending children to private youth care centers, spending millions while detention center overcrowding persists.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Half of America’s Homes Are Equity-Rich—And These States Have the Most</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/half-of-american-homes-are-considered-equity-rich-q2-2024</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>According to Q2 data, about half of U.S. households are "equity-rich," with the biggest gains in the South and Midwest.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 21:49:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A comprehensive list of 2024 tech layoffs</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/08/tech-layoffs-2024-list/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>The tech layoff wave is still going strong in 2024. Following significant workforce reductions in 2022 and 2023, this year has already seen 60,000 job cuts across 254 companies, according to independent layoffs tracker Layoffs.fyi. Companies like Tesla, Amazon, Google, TikTok, Snap and Microsoft have conducted sizable layoffs in the first months of 2024. Smaller-sized […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Facing Rollbacks, Criminal Justice Reformers Argue Policies Make People Safer</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/01/california-illinois-crime-public-safety-reform</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Advocates are refining their rebuttal to “tough on crime” messaging: Don’t focus on punishment, but on reforms that improve public safety.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>