<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from multiple RSS sources, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 12:44:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Free Money? Can You Build a Real Estate Portfolio with Zero-Interest Credit Cards?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/can-you-build-a-real-estate-portfolio-with-zero-interest-credit-cards</link><description>Juggling 0% interest business credit cards is like juggling torches in a hay-covered barn. Drop one, and the whole place goes up in flames. However, if you are disciplined and […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 16:55:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Microsoft taps Sanctuary AI for general-purpose robot research</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/01/microsoft-taps-sanctuary-ai-for-general-purpose-robot-research/</link><description>Microsoft, it seems, is hedging its bets when it comes to general-purpose robotics AI. At the end of February, the Windows maker spearheaded a massive $675 million Series B in Bay Area-based Figure. Today, the tech giant announced a collaboration with Figure competitor Sanctuary AI, best known for its humanoid robot, Phoenix. The Sanctuary partnership […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 17:00:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Campus Protests Could Shape the 2024 Elections — And Not Just the Presidency</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/30/campus-protests-gaza-arrests-prosecutors-elections</link><description>With hundreds of arrests and more campus standoffs looming, local law enforcement officials could face consequences at the ballot box.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 21:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Female Doctors Better? Here's What to Know</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/women/news/20240501/are-female-doctors-better-heres-what-to-know?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>A new study suggests female doctors may provide patients better care, especially when those patients are women. Here's what to know.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 18:11:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Solving the Housing Crisis: What Lawmakers Must Do to Support Investors and Boost Housing Supply</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/what-lawmakers-can-do-to-spur-housing-growth-and-help-investors</link><description>There’s a critical lack of affordable housing. This housing shortage began following the 2008 financial crisis and worsened during the pandemic, and now, not enough homes have been built to meet current […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 16:26:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Substack now lets writers paywall their ‘Chat’ discussion spaces</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/01/substack-now-lets-writers-paywall-their-chat-discussion-spaces/</link><description>Substack is launching the ability for writers to paywall their entire Chat or specific threads to paid or founding members only, the company announced on Wednesday. The rollout of the new feature comes 18 months after Substack launched Chat as a way for writers to communicate directly with their loyal readers. The company believes paywalled […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 17:00:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>They Killed Their Abusive Partners. Now Their Sentences Could Be Reconsidered.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/27/oklahoma-oregon-minnesota-domestic-violence</link><description>Oklahoma could re-examine how it punishes people whose crimes came after years of domestic abuse. Other states may follow.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NIH’s Eliseo Pérez-Stable, MD, Talks Health Disparities, Biology, Behavior, and Culture</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/a-to-z-guides/features/nimhd-perez-stable-health-disparities?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Eliseo Pérez-Stable, MD, director of the National Institute on Minority Health and Health Disparities, talks about health disparities and how his studies aim to improve interventions in clinical settings and across communities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 22:06:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rookie Investor? Never Make This $40,000 Mistake</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-400</link><description>This episode could make you $40,000. Seriously, one property management mistake cost our own expert investor, Dave Meyer, anywhere from $30,000 to $40,000, BUT it’s easier to avoid than you […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 07:02:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Atlassian launches Rovo, its new AI teammate</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/01/atlassian-launches-rovo-its-new-ai-teammate/</link><description>During its Team ’24 conference in Las Vegas, Atlassian today launched Rovo, its new AI assistant. Rovo can take data from first- and third-party tools and make it easily accessible through a new AI-powered search tool and other integrations into Atlassian’s products. The most interesting part, though, may be the new Rovo Agents, which can […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 17:00:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Being Trans in Prison Is Really Like</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/26/trans-prison-voices-gender-essay</link><description>Amid a wave of anti-trans legislation, and the violence that often follows, four people share their experiences in the criminal justice system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 11:00:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New ‘FLiRT’ Variants Spark Summer COVID Surge Warning</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/covid/news/20240430/new-variant-sparks-summer-covid-surge-warning?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>A data scientist who has accurately predicted COVID waves since the beginning of the pandemic warns that a surge is on the horizon.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 18:16:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Supplement Your Income with Real Estate (So You Can Do What You Love)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-946</link><description>Why are rock stars turning to real estate side hustles to pay their bills? During the lockdowns, many musicians, gig workers, and creatives saw their income streams dwindle. There were no […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 07:02:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TechCrunch Minute: Razer’s Zephyr mask lands them in regulatory hot water</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/01/techcrunch-minute-razers-zephyr-mask-lands-them-in-regulatory-hot-water/</link><description>Razer is in trouble with the FTC over masks it made and sold during the COVID pandemic. The matter is going to cost it around $1.1 million, and some bad press. Yeah, masks. Not what comes to mind when you think of the word “Razer,” right? You probably associate the brand with gaming keyboards and […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 17:00:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Enduring Use of Solitary, and New Proposed Limits That Will Likely Fail (Again)</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/20/solitary-confinement-reform-oklahoma-washington-florida</link><description>Isolation’s damaging effects are widely known. But many facilities confine people — even youth — virtually all day, sometimes in shower stalls.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>You Give Me (Spring) Fever</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/women/features/you-give-me-spring-fever?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>New Season Brings Boost of Energy, but Also Unplanned Pregnancies</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 16:57:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seeing Greene: Stolen Properties and Why Your Rate Doesn’t (Really) Matter</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-945</link><description>There’s a silent threat out there that most real estate investors have no idea about. It’s a threat that could take away all your cash flow, ruin your real estate […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 07:02:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Atlassian combines Jira Software and Work Management tools</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/01/jira-software-and-jira-work-management-become-one/</link><description>At its Team ’24 event in Las Vegas, Atlassian today announced that it is combining Jira Software with Jira Service Management into a single product under the ‘Jira’ brand. The origins of Jira, Atlassian’s flagship project management tool, are in software development and issue tracking for developers, but throughout the past few years, the company […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 17:00:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Officials Failed to Act When COVID Hit Prisons. A New Study Shows the Deadly Cost.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/18/covid-prison-deaths-data</link><description>People in prison died at 3.4 times the rate of the free population, with the oldest hit hardest. New data holds lessons for preventing future deaths.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Older Adults: 9 Nutrients You May Be Missing</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/missing-nutrients?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>With age, your body doesn’t absorb nutrients well, so every calorie you consume must be packed with nutrition. Here are 9 nutrients older adults often need more of.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 16:57:26 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>