<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 07:52:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>USL’s Orange County SC Try to Capture Some Magic With New Cup Kit</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/06/usls-orange-county-sc-try-to-capture-some-magic-with-new-cup-kit/soccer/</link><description>Kit is inspired by designs worn in 1910s, when U.S. Open Cup started, and will be worn when OCSC takes on Loudoun United in Round of 32 on Tuesday, May 7</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 03:31:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Simone Biles Says She Blacked Out from Drinking at Her Wedding Party</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/06/simone-biles-blacked-out-drinking-wedding-party-cabo-jonathan-owens/</link><description>Simone Biles says she had one too many at a pre-wedding party down in Cabo last year before she tied the knot with Jonathan Owens ... and she's got the proof on camera. The Olympian posted a bunch of never-before-seen photos ahead of her 1-year…</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 07:52:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Panamanian Football Federation Unveils New National Team Crest</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/06/panamanian-football-federation-unveils-new-national-team-crest/soccer/</link><description>Crest depicts a harpy eagle — the national bird of Panama — with each feather representing one of the country's 10 provinces</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Richard Simmons Posts Audio Message, First Time We've Heard Voice in Years</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/06/richard-simmons-posts-inspirational-audio-message-first-time-voice-years/</link><description>Richard Simmons seems to be poking his head out from where he's been hiding for about a decade now -- 'cause he just let the world hear his voice anew ... and he hasn't changed. The legendary fitness instructor threw up an audio clip Monday to his…</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 07:52:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Snoop Dogg’s Gin &amp; Juice Brand Becomes Presenting Sponsor Of Arizona Bowl</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/06/snoop-doggs-gin-juice-brand-becomes-presenting-sponsor-of-arizona-bowl/college/</link><description>The Arizona Bowl announced a multi-year partnership with 17-time Grammy Award winning artist Snoop Dogg that makes his alcohol brand, Gin &amp; Juice by Dre and Snoop, the game’s presenting sponsor.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 21:55:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Akademiks Says Kendrick Lamar Is Winning, But Drake Still Alive in Rap Beef</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/06/akademiks-kendrick-lamar-rap-beef-not-like-us-the-heart-pt-6/</link><description>Drake and Kendrick Lamar's historic battle is over, with K. Dot emerging victorious, so says a large consensus of the hip-hop community -- but DJ Akademiks says a comeback is still possible. The #1 rap media maven joined us Monday on "TMZ Live,"…</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 07:52:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bayern Munich Goes All In On Red With 2024-25 Home Kits</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/06/bayern-munich-goes-all-in-on-red-with-2024-25-home-kits/soccer/</link><description>Sponsor logo on left sleeve contains QR code that fans can scan to participate in exclusive promotions throughout the 2024-25 season</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:48:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jennifer Lopez Arrives to the Met Gala Solo, Ben Affleck Filming in L.A.</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/06/jennifer-lopez-arrives-solo-met-gala-ben-affleck-filming-los-angeles/</link><description>Jennifer Lopez just showed up to the Met Gala -- and while she was rolling solo ... we know it's only because Ben Affleck is hard at work on the West Coast, where he's on set. The actress/singer made a big entrance Monday at the Metropolitan Museum…</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 07:52:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Detroit Tigers Get Their Motor Runnin’, Unveil City Connect Uniform</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/06/detroit-tigers-get-their-motor-runnin-unveil-city-connect-uniform/baseball/</link><description>The Detroit Tigers today joined the Nike Cool Kids Club™ with the official unveiling of their new City Connect uniform, the 24th of the 30 Major League Baseball teams to release one thus far. As expected, the uniform leans into Detroit’s “Motor City” heritage and its ties to the automobile</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 15:08:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jeff Ross Says Tom Brady Wasn't Actually Mad About Robert Kraft Joke</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/06/jeff-ross-tom-brady-not-mad-robert-kraft-massage-joke-netflix-roast/</link><description>Jeff Ross appeared to get scolded (for realsies) by Tom Brady at his Netflix roast after Robert Kraft became the butt of a joke ... but as it turns out, it was really no big deal at all. The legendary comedian -- and bona fide roast master -- went…</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 07:52:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>