<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:48:37 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Premier League Away Kits Dominate Recent Unveilings From Around Europe</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/02/premier-league-away-kits-dominate-recent-unveilings-from-around-europe/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Clubs launching kits include Liverpool, Brighton, Fulham, Bournemouth, Nottingham Forest, Wolves, Le Havre, Stade de Reims, Montepellier, Roma, Parma, RB Leipzig, VFB Stuttgart, Girona</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 21:41:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TMZ TV Hot Takes: Britney Spears Biopic, Bianca Censori, Bronny James</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/03/tmz-tv-hot-takes-saturday/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Britney Spears is getting a movie made about her life, Bianca Censori is not covering up and Bronny James is getting the video game treatment ... all this on today's TMZ hot takes. First up on "TMZ Live," Harvey and Elex break down Britney's…</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:48:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Carolina Panthers Add 30th Season Logo To Jerseys</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/02/carolina-panthers-add-30th-season-logo-to-jerseys/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Carolina Panthers will celebrate their 30th season this fall with a commemorative logo, which they quietly unveiled back in May and added to their jerseys ahead of Thursday's Fan Fest at Clemson's Memorial Stadium.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 17:02:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OG Dr. Doom Tells Fans to Chill With RDJ Casting Trash Talk</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/03/original-dr-doom-actor-tells-fans-stop-trash-talk-robert-downey-jr/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Robert Downey Jr. returning to the Marvel Cinematic Universe as Dr. Doom has some fans already bitching ... but one fellow actor who's worn the villain's iron mask is all in. Here's the deal ... RDJ made a jaw-dropping appearance at Comic-Con where…</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:48:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Macon Some Changes: SPHL’s Mayhem Unveil New Suite of Logos</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/01/macon-some-changes-sphls-mayhem-unveil-new-suite-of-logos/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Primary logo once again depicts a Viking, only this time just the head with a red beard and eyebrows and wearing a shiny silver horned helmet</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 23:36:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What's The Big Frigin' Difference?!</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/03/whats-the-big-frigin-difference/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Whatcha' lookin' at Snoop Dogg?! The Snoop D.O. Double G has definitely made his rounds in Paris, sporting Team USA merch and rockin' those iconic Olympic rings! See if you can put your finger on the minor switch-ups in these two dope pics! Snoop's…</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:48:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Olympic Rings: Their Origin, History, and Meaning</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/01/the-olympic-rings-their-origin-history-and-meaning/other/olympics/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Olympic rings are synonymous with the peak of international sports achievement. Those five interlaced circles of equal size, each a different colour, absolutely dominate the sporting landscape around the globe for two straight weeks before vanishing as quickly as they appeared, hiding away until the next games, usually around</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 20:10:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bud Crawford Has No Regrets Missing Olympics, Gold Medal Wasn't My Dream!</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/03/terence-crawford-medal-olympics-israil-madrimov-boxing/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Terence Crawford's career is far from over and he's achieved more than just about any active professional boxer ... there's just one thing he's missing, an Olympic medal. But, Bud ain't sweatin' it! TMZ Sports spoke with the undefeated champ as the…</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:48:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chicago Cubs to wear Motorola Ad on Uniform</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/01/chicago-cubs-to-wear-motorola-ad-on-uniform/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Chicago Cubs today became the 23rd Major League Baseball team to add an advertisement to their jersey sleeve, announcing that Motorola’s logo will live there for the foreseeable future. Chicago’s announcement comes just one day after the Philadelphia IBX Phillies announced their own jersey ad. The rather large patch</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 15:46:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Larsa Pippen Unbothered by Ex-BF Marcus Jordan's New Girl, Seeing Reality Star</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/03/larsa-pippen-does-not-care-marcus-jordan-dating-new-woman/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Larsa Pippen is not sweating Marcus Jordan's new arm candy ... and she's moving on with her dating life too ... namely, with a reality TV star. Sources with direct knowledge tell TMZ ... Larsa doesn't care her ex-boyfriend is on vacation with an IG…</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:48:37 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>