<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 02:04:30 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The Affordable Housing Crisis is About More Than Interest Rates. It Started Decades Ago With NIMBYism.</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/how-the-nimby-movement-helped-create-the-affordable-housing-crisis</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>NIMBYs, YIMBYs, and the struggle that's resulted in a housing crisis unlike we've ever seen. The real story of today's housing market goes back several decades.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 19:15:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How the theft of 40M UK voter register records was entirely preventable</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/02/how-the-theft-of-40-million-uk-voter-register-records-was-entirely-preventable/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>A scathing rebuke by the U.K. data protection watchdog reveals what led to the compromise of tens of millions of U.K. voters' information. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Facing Rollbacks, Criminal Justice Reformers Argue Policies Make People Safer</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/01/california-illinois-crime-public-safety-reform</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>Advocates are refining their rebuttal to “tough on crime” messaging: Don’t focus on punishment, but on reforms that improve public safety.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Senator Warren’s New Bill Includes Estate Tax Hikes, Private Equity Crackdowns, and Incentives</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/senator-warrens-new-bill-targets-private-equity-and-looks-to-incentivize-affordable-housing-development</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>The American Housing and Mobility Act would use estate tax increases to incentivize development. Private equity, lenders, and homeowners are caught in the crossfire.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 15:57:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Self-driving truck startup Aurora Innovation raises $483M in share sale ahead of commercial launch</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/02/self-driving-truck-startup-aurora-innovation-raises-483m-commercial-launch/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Self-driving technology company Aurora Innovation was hoping to raise hundreds of millions in additional capital as it races toward a driverless commercial launch by the end of 2024. The company, which had arranged to sell up to $420 million worth of shares, exceeded its goal and raised $483 million. The newly raised funds come a little […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 00:38:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Drawing Attention</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/01/news-inside-issue-17</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>News Inside Issue 17 features the opinions of justice-affected people on Trump’s felonies, and a nonfiction comic about death penalty mitigation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maximizing Your Rental Income: Four Tips From My House-Hacking Experience</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/tips-from-my-house-hacking-experience</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>Follow this advice to get your REI journey off on the right foot.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 13:47:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FTC and Justice Department sue TikTok over alleged child privacy violations</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/02/ftc-and-justice-department-sue-tiktok-over-alleged-child-privacy-violations/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>The U.S. Federal Trade Commission and the Justice Department are suing TikTok and ByteDance, TikTok’s parent company, with violating the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). The law requires digital platforms to notify and obtain parents’ consent before collecting and using personal data from children under the age of 13. In a press release issued […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 21:12:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>These Private Centers Lack Oversight. Cuyahoga County Judges Send Kids Anyway.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/01/juvenile-justice-detention-prison-youth-treatment-cuyahoga-county</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Courts are increasingly sending children to private youth care centers, spending millions while detention center overcrowding persists.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rookie Reply: Rent-Raising Renovations, the 1% Rule, &amp; Quitting Real Estate</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-440</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Real estate investing offers a roadmap to financial freedom, but it’s far from easy. If you’re feeling the stress of ownership, whether it’s due to a difficult tenant or unforeseen […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 07:02:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Acquiring AI talent wholesale</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/02/acquiring-ai-talent-wholesale/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>Welcome to Startups Weekly — your weekly recap of everything you can’t miss from the world of startups. This week we are looking at acquisitions of small startups, two new unicorns, wearable AI devices, and VCs who are supporting Kamala Harris. Let’s get into it. Most interesting startup stories from the week With the IPO […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 19:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What It Means to ‘Willie Horton’ a Political Candidate</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/31/willie-horton-donald-trump-kamala-harris</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Donald Trump supporters run their version of the original dog-whistle attack ad against Kamala Harris. Here’s the history.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BiggerNews: The Market Bets on Mortgage Rates Falling, More Homes for Sale</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-999</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>Mortgage rates are set to fall this year and well into 2025, all while housing inventory steadily increases. We’re in the best housing inventory position since before the pandemic, so […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 07:02:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Character.AI CEO Noam Shazeer returns to Google</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/02/character-ai-ceo-noam-shazeer-returns-to-google/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>In a big move, Character.AI co-founder and CEO Noam Shazeer is returning to Google after leaving the company in October 2021 to found the a16z-backed chatbot startup. In his previous stint, Shazeer spearheaded the team of researchers that built LaMDA (Language Model for Dialogue Applications), a language model that was used for conversational AI tools. Character.AI co-founder Daniel […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 18:52:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Courts Cleared Jaleel Stallings. Trump’s Campaign Pulled Him Back Into the Political Muck.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/31/trump-election-kamala-harris-jaleel-stallings</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>Stallings was acquitted after an encounter with police during George Floyd protests in 2020, and one officer pleaded guilty to assaulting him.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>