<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 03:16:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Denver Broncos’ New Helmet Design Leaks On NFL Draft Prop</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/20/denver-broncos-new-helmet-design-leaks-on-nfl-draft-prop/football/</link><description>The design of the Denver Broncos' new helmets were leaked by former NFL wide receiver Antonio Brown, who shared a photo on social media of an oversized helmet that will be on display at next week's draft.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 17:20:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>O.J. Simpson Bank of America Credit Card Hits Auction Block After Death</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/20/oj-simpson-bank-america-credit-card-auction-dead-dies/</link><description>O.J. Simpson's Bank of America credit card has hit the auction block ... and let's just say the seller is banking on it raking in some serious cash. Jonathan Lepore is selling the business account card over at Goldin Auctions ... telling TMZ he…</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 03:16:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nike Releases New Rebel Edition Jerseys for 6 WNBA Teams</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/19/nike-releases-new-rebel-edition-jerseys-for-6-wnba-teams/basketball/</link><description>Teams receiving new Rebel Edition alternate jerseys include Chicago Sky, Connecticut Sun, Las Vegas Aces, Los Angeles Sparks, Phoenix Mercury, Seattle Storm</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:38:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Taylor Swift Blasted For Saying She Wants to Live in 1830s in New Song</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/19/taylor-swift-backlash-lyrics-new-song-live-1830s-tortured-poets-album/</link><description>Taylor Swift's new album's already causing some controversy ... and, it ain't about an ex either -- it's all got to do with T-Swift's view of American history, including the ugly part. 😬 The singer dropped "The Tortured Poet's Department" Friday…</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 03:16:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New York Mets Unveil City Connect Uniforms Inspired by Subways, Bridges, and Concrete</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/19/new-york-mets-unveil-city-connect-uniforms-inspired-by-subways-bridges-and-concrete/baseball/</link><description>“If you know New York, you know.” That’s the idea behind the New York Mets‘ brand new Nike MLB City Connect uniform, which the club unveiled this morning. The Mets are the second of nine teams scheduled to do so during the 2024 season. They’ll debut April 27 and then</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 15:00:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NYC Restaurateur Gets Rat Problem Amid Bezos-Sanchez Beef</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/20/rats-restaurant-jeff-bezos-lauren-sanchez-keith-mcnally-balthazar/</link><description>The beef between NYC restaurateur Keith McNally and Jeff Bezos and his fiancée, Lauren Sanchez, just took an odd turn ... and it involves a dirty rat! McNally – the owner of Manhattan's famed Balthazar bistro – jumped on Instagram Friday to…</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 03:16:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Denver Broncos, Houston Texans’ Jerseys Leaked By Antonio Brown’s Social Media Network</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/19/denver-broncos-houston-texans-jerseys-leaked-by-antonio-browns-social-media-network/football/</link><description>Although they won't be unveiled until Monday and Tuesday, respectively, former NFL wide receiver Antonio Brown's social media network leaked the Denver Broncos and Houston Texans' new jerseys late Thursday evening.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 12:43:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bill Maher Says Nickelodeon, Disney, Gender Ed Puts Kids at Risk</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/20/bill-maher-disney-nickelodeon-kids-gender-drag-queen-story-hour/</link><description>Bill Maher has no kids, but he was all about them Friday night as he RAILED on Hollywood and others for putting them at risk. The 'Real Time' host began with 'Quiet on the Set,' lambasting Nickelodeon for putting child actors in highly-charged,…</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 03:16:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indianapolis Indians pay tribute to Pittsburgh with Young Bucs alternate</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/18/indianapolis-indians-pay-tribute-to-pittsburgh-with-young-bucs-alternate/baseball/</link><description>For six games this season, the Triple-A Indianapolis Indians will represent the colors of their parent club of 19 years, the Pittsburgh Pirates. The Indians will wear specialty “Young Bucs” jerseys and caps for Prospects Weekends in May and June. The Pittsburgh Pirates are often referred to as the Bucs,</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 04:32:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Florida Man Who Set Himself on Fire Outside Trump Trial Has Died</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/20/florida-man-set-fire-donald-trump-trial-dead-dies-max-azzarello/</link><description>The man who lit himself ablaze outside the Trump trial courthouse in NYC has died. Max Azzarello was rushed in critical condition to a hospital Friday after he doused himself with a flammable liquid and set himself on fire outside Manhattan…</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 03:16:06 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>