<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 06:50:07 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Seeing Greene: How to Use Home Equity to Retire, Buy Rentals, or House Hack</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-985</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Should you use a HELOC to buy investment property? Would we use home equity to retire? When is it time to sell a performing property and exchange it for a […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 07:02:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nala to use $40M Series A to build B2B payments platform, scale remittance services</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/09/nala-series-a/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Nala, a remittance startup that is now widening its portfolio through a new B2B payments platform, has raised $40 million equity in a rare deal that becomes one of the largest Series A transactions in Africa. The oversubscribed round was led by San Francisco-based VC firm Acrew Capital, with participation from DST Global, Norrsken22, HOF Capital, […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 09:04:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jackson, Mississippi, Wants Curfew Centers to Cut Crime. Here’s What Other Cities Learned.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/09/jackson-mississippi-youth-curfew-centers</link><description>After a teen’s murder, city officials hope a curfew and youth centers will get kids off the street. Young people are skeptical.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 11:00:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>80-Hour Workweeks to Lean FIRE in 8 Years through Real Estate</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-544</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Reaching financial independence and becoming a millionaire before the age of thirty?! While this path requires several years of ruthless saving, smart investing, and unwavering discipline, there’s no reason why […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 07:01:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Byway is using AI to help travelers slow down and take the scenic route</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/09/byway-is-using-ai-to-help-travellers-slow-down-and-take-the-scenic-route/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Solo founder Cat Jones took the plunge on setting up a travel business right around the time the pandemic was hitting Europe in March 2020. Fast forward to summer 2024 and her curated package tour business, Byway, is announcing close of an oversubscribed £5.04 million Series A round (around $6.4M at current exchange rates). Jones’ […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Love Beyond Bars: Miguel and Silvia</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/05/photo-essay-wrongful-conviction-love-story</link><description>While Miguel Solorio did 25 years for a crime he didn’t commit, his wife, Silvia, was right by his side. Here’s their California love story in pictures.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Revised Affordable Housing Law In Florida Takes Opportunities Away From Developers</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/revisions-to-florida-live-local-act-take-opportunities-from-developers</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>A revision to Florida's Live Local Act reduces incentives for developers and increases building restrictions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 21:42:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Microsoft-owned adtech Xandr accused of EU privacy breaches</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/08/microsoft-owned-adtech-xandr-accused-of-eu-privacy-breaches/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>An adtech business owned by Microsoft is the target of a complaint backed by European privacy advocacy group, noyb — a nonprofit that punches far above its weight when it comes to chalking up strikes against data protection-infringing tech giants. For its latest action, noyb is supporting an unnamed individual in Italy to lodge a […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Crime Rates and the 2024 Election: What You Need to Know</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/27/trump-and-biden-spar-over-crime-rates-ahead-of-their-debate-what-do-we-really-know</link><description>As crime data again becomes a flashpoint in the presidential campaign, experts push for better national statistics.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Airbnb Bans Only Make Tourism More Expensive. Just Ask New York.</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/short-term-rental-bans-in-new-york-only-made-hotels-more-expensive</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>New data from New York City shows that short-term rental bans haven't moved the needle on housing at all.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 20:41:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quora’s Poe now lets users create and share web apps</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/08/quoras-poe-now-lets-users-create-and-share-web-apps/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Poe, Quora’s subscription-based, cross-platform aggregator for AI-powered chatbots like Anthropic’s Claude and OpenAI’s GPT-4o, has launched a feature called Previews that lets users create interactive apps directly in chats with chatbots. Previews allows Poe users to build data visualizations, games and even drum machines by typing things like “Analyze the information in this report and […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 05:40:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Death Row Prisoner’s Parting Interview</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/24/texas-death-row-prisoner-final-interview</link><description>Days before his scheduled execution in Texas, Ramiro Gonzales speaks on faith, legacy — and apologizing to the family of his victim, Bridget Townsend.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>5 Ways to Find Off-Market Real Estate Deals Like a Pro</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/ways-to-find-off-market-deals-in-2024</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Off-market deals can be a huge source of great deals, if you can find them.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 20:34:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian game firms want to distance themselves from fantasy sports</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/08/indian-game-firms-want-to-distance-themselves-from-fantasy-sports/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>For over a decade, real-money gaming companies and fantasy sports startups have marketed themselves as video game companies. But as these businesses face increasing regulatory scrutiny, a coalition of more than 70 video game companies in India is urging the government to create a clear distinction between their industries. In a letter to Prime Minister […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 04:32:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The New Battle Over an Old Institution: Forced Prison Labor</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/22/prison-slavery-forced-labor-lawsuits-bills</link><description>Inside the latest legal and legislative efforts to close state constitutional loopholes that allow slavery as punishment for a crime.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>