<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 07:47:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>What Do Book Challenge Forms Look Like?: Book Censorship News, May 17, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/book-challenge-forms/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/site-book-censorship-image.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>Take a look at five different book challenge forms to understand how little effort goes into attempting to ban books. That, plus this week's book censorship news.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>REI Anniversary Sale 2024 is now live: Explore these deals through May 27, while supplies last</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/article/rei-anniversary-sale-2024-is-now-live-explore-these-deals-through-may-27-while-supplies-last/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/15115418/REI-Tents-copy.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Commerce Continue reading REI Anniversary Sale 2024 is now live: Explore these deals through May 27, while supplies last REI Anniversary Sale 2024 is now live: Explore these deals through May 27, while supplies last originally appeared on Autoblog on Fri, 17 May 2024 06:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GameStop shares fall after it files to sell securities, says first quarter sales declined</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/17/gamestop-shares-fall-after-it-files-to-sell-securities-says-first-quarter-sales-declined.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 12:33:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sharing Fun Facts About Yourself: 22 Examples &amp; Ideas</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/fun-facts-about-me/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fun-facts-about-me</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Asking to share some fun facts about yourself is a common icebreaker that’s used during job interviews. But the quality of your answer still matters. This guide will help you come up with some ideas for crafting a response that starts the interview on a good note. Table of contents Ideas for Sharing Fun Facts […] The post Sharing Fun Facts About Yourself: 22 Examples &amp; Ideas appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 15:26:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best Swedish Meatballs</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/the-best-swedish-meatballs/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>These Swedish Meatballs are smothered in the most amazing rich and creamy gravy and packed with such delicious flavor. You…</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Easy Low-Light Indoor Plants</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/easy-low-light-indoor-plants/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>I used to think every houseplant needed a sunny corner or bright windowsill to thrive. But it turns out many of our favorite go-to houseplants do just fine in shady corners and low-light locations. So before you write off your house as too dark to sustain plant life, check out this list of the best indoor plants for low light. You might be surprised at how many good options there are! Our upstairs family room is the brightest room we’ve ever owned thanks to big unobstructed windows on all 4 sides. But most of our indoor plants live downstairs, where we get far less natural light. Luckily, that hasn’t stopped us from growing our collection of happy healthy houseplants. 9 Houseplants That Don’t Need A Lot Of Light Here are our favorite low-light indoor plants. We list a lot more info on them below, but here’s a quick list to bring on your next trip to the plant store: Snake Plant ZZ Plant Pothos Heartleaf Philodendron English Ivy Aglaonema Cast Iron Plant Monstera Parlor Palm Perhaps our favorite part of this list is that these aren’t ugly “consolation plants” that people begrudgingly buy for dark homes. Continue reading Easy Low-Light Indoor Plants at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 14:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Crop Tops</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/crop-tops/</link><description>Outfit Details: Kilentar Top (similar here), Emporior Sirenuse Skirt, Emme Parsons Sandals, Prada Bag The crop top has earned its place as one of… The post Crop Tops appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:30:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>8 Cozy and Comforting Books About Bakeries</title><link>https://bookriot.com/cozy-books-about-bakeries/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/Cozy-Books-about-Bakeries.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>If the thought or smell of baked goods has you craving all things cozy, get your hands on these books.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>7 better alternatives to the best-selling slime-like cleaning gel at Amazon</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/article/7-better-alternatives-to-the-best-selling-slime-like-cleaning-gel-at-amazon/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/16105912/goop-alts2_V1.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Commerce Continue reading 7 better alternatives to the best-selling slime-like cleaning gel at Amazon 7 better alternatives to the best-selling slime-like cleaning gel at Amazon originally appeared on Autoblog on Thu, 16 May 2024 17:30:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>5 things to know before the stock market opens Friday</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/17/5-things-to-know-before-the-stock-market-opens-friday-may-17.html</link><description>Here are the most important news items that investors need to start their trading day.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 12:26:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 553</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-553/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-553</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Tools and technology change rapidly. Yet as wonderful as technology can be, it doesn’t replace the need for human connection through interactions. Keep this in mind as you are searching for a new job. It’s your human connections that often open doors! In this week’s collection of news and tips for job seekers, you’ll find: […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 553 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 12:19:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>No Bake Snickers Bar Pie</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/no-bake-snickers-bar-pie/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>No Bake Snickers Bar Pie is one of the easiest and most delicious no bake pies that you make. You…</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/how-to-remove-wallpaper/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Wallpaper has made a big comeback as a trendy home design choice. But despite its resurgence, there are still plenty of us dealing with dingy, dated, or downright ugly old wallpaper we don’t want. In our old home, we had to remove wallpaper in so many rooms: the kitchen, the dining room, the foyer, and two different bathrooms! As we traveled from room to room removing wallpaper, we tested 4 different methods, and today we’ll share what we learned. Removing wallpaper doesn’t require special tools or lots of money. It’s a totally doable project for any homeowner. However, it can be a tedious process that can take elbow grease and patience, depending on the size of your room and the stubbornness of your wallpaper. But having removed several rooms worth of decades-old wallpaper, we can confidently say it’s worth the effort! You can also check out more before and afters of our once-wallpapered rooms. Continue reading How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:21:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Punchy Prints</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/punchy-prints/</link><description>Outfit Details: Pucci Top &amp; Pants, Chanel Bag (similar, less expensive here), Dior Sandals (similar, less expensive here), Louis Abel Earrings (less expensive here) Punchy prints are a favorite of mine… The post Punchy Prints appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 05:00:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Watch the Trailer for IT ENDS WITH US, Adapted from the Colleen Hoover Novel</title><link>https://bookriot.com/it-ends-with-us-trailer/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/it-ends-with-us-trailer.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>Will you be watching?</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 19:20:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mitsubishi off-road Delica van, outdoorsy Outlander variant planned for US market</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/16/mitsubishi-delica-off-road-van-outlander-variant-truck-future-product-plans/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/crop/1131x636+38+82/resize/800x450!/format/jpg/quality/85/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/16160957/mitsubishi-dx-delica-concept.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Green , Mitsubishi , Nissan , Truck , Crossover , Minivan/Van , Electric , Future Vehicles , Hybrid , Off-Road Vehicles Continue reading Mitsubishi off-road Delica van, outdoorsy Outlander variant planned for US market Mitsubishi off-road Delica van, outdoorsy Outlander variant planned for US market originally appeared on Autoblog on Thu, 16 May 2024 16:49:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 21:49:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Microsoft's Mistral partnership avoids merger probe by British regulators</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/17/microsoft-mistral-partnership-avoids-merger-probe-by-uk-regulators.html</link><description>The U.K.'s Competition and Markets Authority cleared Microsoft's AI partnership with Mistral of regulatory concerns after previously inviting views on whether the arrangement qualified as a merger.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 12:17:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 552</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-552/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-552</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>When you are searching for a job, you will inevitably run into unexpected scenarios. You will have questions, experience self-doubt and even feel discouraged. You’ll also experience great wins, meet wonderful people and discover new things about yourself. That’s the roller-coaster of job search. Consider Summary Sunday your resource for getting questions answered and showing […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 552 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 11:37:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Easy Grilled Bourbon Chicken</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/grilled-bourbon-chicken/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>One bite of this grilled bourbon chicken and your tastebuds will be dancing with delight! It’s marinated in a flavorful…</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aglaonema Plant – Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/aglaonema-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Aglaonema, also called the Chinese Evergreen Plant, is an easy-care houseplant that lives happily in many lighting conditions – even a dark corner of our daughter’s room. There are dozens of different Aglaonema varieties, most with large tropical foliage and colors ranging from silvery-green, red, and even vibrant pink. They’re also tough to kill, so they’re a great option for forgetful plant owners or anyone looking for an easy win in the plant department. These truly have been very low maintenance for us. We purchased our two Aglaonemas (pronounced ag-lee-oh-neem-ah ) to put atop our daughter’s closet. It’s sometimes hard to distinguish different varieties, but we believe that’s an Aglaonema Silver (right) and either a Candy Cane or Princess Silver Queen (left). Aglaonema Quick Facts Here’s what you need to know about your Aglaonema at a glance: Latin name : Aglaonema is the genus under which there are 21 recognized species . Continue reading Aglaonema Plant – Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:47:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bikini Edit</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/bikini-edit/</link><description>Outfit Details: Lspace Bikini, Janessa Leone Hat, Illestevsa Sunglasses With warm weather upon us, I’m excited to embrace bikinis perfect for… The post Bikini Edit appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What are You Reading This Week — Read Harder, May 16, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/read-harder-updates-may-16-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/fair-skinned-Asian-woman-lying-on-her-stomach-and-reading-a-book-in-front-of-a-floor-length-mirror.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>Are you participating in any reading challenges this year?</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 18:30:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Save a massive 42% off with this Amazon deal on a DeWalt cordless drill and impact driver kit</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/article/save-a-massive-42-off-with-this-amazon-deal-on-a-dewalt-cordless-drill-and-impact-driver-kit/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/16143927/drill-lead.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Commerce Continue reading Save a massive 42% off with this Amazon deal on a DeWalt cordless drill and impact driver kit Save a massive 42% off with this Amazon deal on a DeWalt cordless drill and impact driver kit originally appeared on Autoblog on Thu, 16 May 2024 16:12:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 21:12:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Dow tends to take a breather after surpassing big, round numbers</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/17/the-dow-tends-to-take-a-breather-after-surpassing-big-round-numbers.html</link><description>The Dow's rally to 40,000 could be followed by a pullback if historical performance is any guide.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 11:51:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>While a little competition in the workplace might help bring out the best in everyone involved, an atmosphere rooted in envy, fear, or jealousy can do the exact opposite. This post will help you recognize signs that your coworker is threatened by you, and help you navigate the situation. 1. They Don’t Want You Involved […] The post 10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:07:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wood-Fired Pizza Dough</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/wood-fired-pizza-dough/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>This is the perfect beginner’s guide for making wood-fired pizza dough! Pizza expert, Chef Brandon Price, taught me how to…</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Corn Plant – Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/corn-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Corn plants ( Dracaena fragrans ) are popular low-maintenance houseplants you’ve probably seen at the nursery, home improvement store, or doctor’s office. I even had one in my college dorm room! You can recognize them by their spear-shaped leaves and woody, cane-line trunks that can grow up to 6 feet tall indoors. But did you know there are several varieties of corn plants? We didn’t! Heck, we didn’t even realize some of our smaller houseplants were in the same corn plant family! Currently, we own two smaller varieties of corn plants, pictured above. The one on the left is a Dracaena Limelight ( Dracaena fragrans ‘Limelight’ ) and the taller plant is a Draecanea Dorado ( Dracaena fragrans ‘Dorado’ ). We actually have several limelights around because we love their vibrant color on shelves, tabletops, and windowsills. Corn Plant Quick Facts Latin name : Dracaena fragrans Common names : Corn plant, cornstalk plant, false palms Light : Bright, indirect light but can tolerate lower-light conditions Watering : Keep soil moist, but not soggy. Continue reading Corn Plant – Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 17:37:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>My Saks May Array</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/my-saks-may-array/</link><description>Outfit Details: Sandro Top, Erdem Skirt, Prada Bag, Sherman Fields Necklace Thank you to Saks Fifth Avenue for sponsoring this… The post My Saks May Array appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 05:00:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>7 Books for Better Mental Health</title><link>https://bookriot.com/books-for-better-mental-health/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/tengyart-DoqtEEn8SOo-unsplash.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>May is Mental Health Awareness Month, and we've got some book recommendations to help start or supplement your mental health journey.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 18:08:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to protect your car from keyless vehicle thefts</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/16/how-to-prevent-keyless-car-theft-prevention-methods-techniques/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/http://s.aolcdn.com/commerce/blogcdn/www.autoblog.com/media/2012/03/29-2012-hyundai-equus.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Ownership , Technology Continue reading How to protect your car from keyless vehicle thefts How to protect your car from keyless vehicle thefts originally appeared on Autoblog on Thu, 16 May 2024 15:21:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:21:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>China pledges $42 billion in a slew of measures to support the struggling property sector</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/17/china-pledges-billions-in-measures-to-support-struggling-property-sector.html</link><description>Chinese authorities on Friday pledged new support for state-owned enterprises to enable them to buy unsold apartments.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 11:49:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 551</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-551/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-551</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Job search requires writing and marketing skills. It also requires strong verbal communication. If these skills are not part of your normal work function, you’ll want some help. That’s what this week’s Summary Sunday is all about. There’s no doubt that LinkedIn is one of THE most powerful tools in your career toolbox. It contains […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 551 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 11:37:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blueberry Lemon Upside-Down Cake</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/blueberry-lemon-upside-cake/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Be prepared to fall in love with this blueberry lemon upside-down cake! A delicious and moist lemon sponge cake bursting…</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Using Solid Stain In Our Outdoor Shower</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/solid-deck-stain-outdoor-shower/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>In all of our years of DIYing, I don’t think we’ve ever used a solid stain before. But we recently had a project that was *perfectly* suited for it and, well, solid stain quickly won us over. It was recommended by a professional house painter to us, specifically because he thought it would be great for our outdoor shower. And we found it easy to apply, it gave us great coverage, and we got an even-better-than-we-expected result (which is always the best kind!). So here’s a post that covers all the pros &amp; cons and hows &amp; whys of solid stain. As you can see, the “canvas” for this staining project was our outdoor shower. We gave it a mini-makeover right after moving in, but we knew it may need more attention and care down the line. Honestly, we dreaded the task of stripping and restaining it – so many nooks &amp; crannies! Continue reading Using Solid Stain In Our Outdoor Shower at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 17:46:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Our Latest Favorites From Amazon</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/our-latest-favorites-from-amazon/</link><description>Outfit Details: Beaded Handmade Bag Welcome to our latest favorites from Amazon that I’m especially excited to share! This week… The post Our Latest Favorites From Amazon appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 05:00:13 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>