<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 14:06:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Seeing Greene: Investing with High DTI, When to Refi, &amp; Getting Out of Debt</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-989</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Life happens, and you’ve accumulated some debt. You’re wondering how to buy real estate EVEN with a high DTI (debt-to-income) ratio. Whether it’s good debt, like rental property mortgages, or […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 07:02:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hacked, leaked, exposed: Why you should never use stalkerware apps</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/16/hacked-leaked-exposed-why-you-should-stop-using-stalkerware-apps/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Using stalkerware is creepy, unethical, potentially illegal, and puts your data and that of your loved ones in danger. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 18:27:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How a Supreme Court Ruling Could Affect a Case Involving Police Abuse of Youth</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/13/supreme-court-bankruptcy-sackler-boy-scouts</link><description>Another court must now decide how the landmark ruling will impact the Boy Scouts abuse settlement, which involves victims of police sexual abuse.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From a Negative Net Worth to FI in Just 5 Years by Living Like a Stoic</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-546</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>The road to financial independence isn’t always linear, but stoicism might be the secret ingredient that keeps you on track. This ancient philosophy gets a bad rap, but with its […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 07:01:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sequoia bets big on Stripe, LatAm fintechs clean up and one African startup’s outsized Series A</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/16/sequoia-bets-big-on-stripe-latam-fintechs-clean-up-and-one-african-startups-outsized-series-a/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Welcome to TechCrunch Fintech! This week, we’re looking at Sequoia Capital’s effort to give its LPs liquidity on the firm’s investments in Stripe, how LatAm fintechs are still catching investors’ attention, a sizable Series A from an African startup, and more. To get a roundup of TechCrunch’s biggest and most important fintech stories delivered to […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 18:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jackson, Mississippi, Wants Curfew Centers to Cut Crime. Here’s What Other Cities Learned.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/09/jackson-mississippi-youth-curfew-centers</link><description>After a teen’s murder, city officials hope a curfew and youth centers will get kids off the street. Young people are skeptical.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 11:00:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Resident Turnover Challenge: 5 Retention Strategies for Single-Family Rentals</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/strategies-for-better-single-family-rental-tenant-retention</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Every investor wants 100% retention, but it's not as easy as you'd wish. Here are the best strategies for getting as close as possible to it.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 22:06:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anthropic releases Claude app for Android</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/16/anthropic-releases-claude-app-for-android/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Anthropic launched its Claude Android app on Tuesday to bring its AI chatbot to more users. This is Anthropic’s latest effort to convince users to ditch ChatGPT by making Claude available in more places. The Claude Android app will work just like the iOS version released in May, including free access to Anthropic’s best AI […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 17:02:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Love Beyond Bars: Miguel and Silvia</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/05/photo-essay-wrongful-conviction-love-story</link><description>While Miguel Solorio did 25 years for a crime he didn’t commit, his wife, Silvia, was right by his side. Here’s their California love story in pictures.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Millions of Americans Should Keep Their Homes as Rentals, Not Sell. Here’s Why.</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/americans-should-keep-their-homes-not-sell-in-2024</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>The higher interest rate environment has changed the answer to the “sell vs. keep” question, and every homeowner needs to run the math before selling.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 21:32:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TechCrunch Minute: Whistleblowers say OpenAI employs ‘illegally restrictive’ NDAs</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/video/techcrunch-minute-whistleblowers-say-openai-employs-illegally-restrictive-ndas/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Trouble could be on the horizon for OpenAI. A group of whistleblowers accused OpenAI of requiring its employees to sign illegally restrictive non-disclosure agreements, or NDAs. The lawyers representing these whistleblowers sent a letter to SEC chair Gary Gensler, alleging that OpenAI’s contracts with current and former employees could illegally prevent them from alerting government […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Crime Rates and the 2024 Election: What You Need to Know</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/27/trump-and-biden-spar-over-crime-rates-ahead-of-their-debate-what-do-we-really-know</link><description>As crime data again becomes a flashpoint in the presidential campaign, experts push for better national statistics.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Large Apartment Buildings Remain at Risk of Catastrophic Losses</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/large-apartment-buildings-set-for-further-losses</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>After two years of multifamily decline, the end is still not in sight.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 20:19:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>VC David Sacks delivers a fire-and-brimstone speech at the Republican National Convention</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/16/vc-david-sacks-delivers-a-fire-and-brimstone-speech-at-the-republican-national-convention/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>On the first night of the RNC, venture capitalist David Sacks took the stage to warn Republicans of “a world on fire.” © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 16:45:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Death Row Prisoner’s Parting Interview</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/24/texas-death-row-prisoner-final-interview</link><description>Days before his scheduled execution in Texas, Ramiro Gonzales speaks on faith, legacy — and apologizing to the family of his victim, Bridget Townsend.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>