<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from multiple RSS sources, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 17:17:12 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>How “Switching Costs” Hold the Housing Market in Limbo w/Lance Lambert</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-215</link><description>The housing market has seen unprecedented home price growth in the 2020s. Already, we’ve almost beat the past three decades, and we aren’t even halfway through our own. And now, […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 07:02:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Infighting among fintech players has caused TabaPay to ‘pull out’ from buying bankrupt Synapse</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/09/tabapay-ends-plans-synapse-mercury-evolve/</link><description>A dust-up between Evolve Bank &amp; Trust, Mercury and Synapse has led TabaPay to abandon its acquisition plans of troubled banking-as-a-service startup Synapse.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:59:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Marshall Project Wins the Dart Award for “The Mercy Workers”</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/06/the-marshall-project-wins-the-dart-award-for-the-mercy-workers</link><description>Our feature on mitigation specialists who help save people from the death penalty was recognized for making “significant contributions to public understanding of trauma-related issues.”</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Healthy Lifestyle Can Add Years to Life, Despite 'Bad' Genes</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/balance/news/20240509/defeat-bad-genes-with-healthy-lifestyle?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Turn around those bad family genes with four lifestyle changes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 19:47:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best Appliances to Boost Your Rental Property’s Value—and Bonus Tips For Saving Money</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/best-appliances-to-raise-property-value</link><description>Rental properties come in all shapes, sizes, and prices, as do many of the appliances that go in them. Assuming, however, that your rental is not a sprawling Beverly Hills […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:55:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple’s ‘Crush’ ad is disgusting</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/09/apples-crush-ad-is-disgusting/</link><description>The problem is not the media, but the message.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:58:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weinstein Ruling Poses Quandary: Can #MeToo Coexist With Protections for Defendants?</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/04/sex-crimes-weinstein-me-too</link><description>Proving sex crimes often requires evidence that is generally excluded to protect the rights of the accused.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Taking Racism out of the Kidney Disease Equation</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/a-to-z-guides/features/end-of-racist-kidney-math?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Kidney care in the U.S. is at a watershed moment of moving past a deeply entrenched, institutionally racist equation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 04:17:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Before You Buy: 3 Key Strategies for Investing in Turnkey Properties</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/three-tips-for-turnkey-property-analysis</link><description>Turnkey investing is one of the more controversial forms of investing in real estate. Depending on who you ask, you may hear that turnkey is one of the best forms of […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:50:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Google built some of the first social apps for Android, including Twitter and others</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/09/google-built-some-of-the-first-social-apps-for-android-including-twitter-and-others/</link><description>The Twitter for Android client was "a demo app that Google had created and gave to us," says Particle co-founder and ex-Twitter employee Sara Beykpour.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 20:35:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mississippi Lawmakers Considered Modest Public Defense Reforms. They Rejected All of Them.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/02/mississippi-public-defense-legislative-reforms</link><description>With its refusal to impose oversight or consistent standards in local defense, Mississippi risks falling further behind rest of the U.S., critics say.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Plant-Powered Sleep: Vegan, Vegetarian Diets Unlock Extra ZZZs</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/sleep-disorders/news/20240508/plant-powered-sleep-vegan-vegetarian-diet-unlocks-extra-zzzs?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Vegans and vegetarians sleep around 30 more minutes per night than average and up to 90% of them report good or excellent sleep quality, according to a new survey published by the Sleep Foundation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 19:12:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump May Consider Shaking Up the Federal Reserve If Elected—Here’s What That Could Look Like</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/trump-allies-draft-federal-reserve-changes-that-could-replace-powell</link><description>A group of former officials and other allies of Former President Donald Trump has drafted a document outlining suggested policy changes that would impact the authority and independence of the Federal Reserve. While […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:28:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WhatsApp’s latest update streamlines navigation and adds a ‘darker dark mode’</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/09/whatsapp-streamlining-navigation-darker-dark-mode/</link><description>WhatsApp is updating its mobile apps for a fresh and more streamlined look, while also introducing a new “darker dark mode,” the company announced on Thursday. The messaging app says that over the years, it has primarily focused on adding utility to the app and that while the product continues to grow, its design needs […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In This Police Youth Program, a Trail of Sexual Abuse Across the U.S.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/01/police-explorer-sexual-abuse-boy-scouts</link><description>Explorer posts, overseen by the Boy Scouts, are supposed to foster an interest in policing. They have faced nearly 200 allegations of misconduct.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 18:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anorexia: The Body Neglected</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/mental-health/eating-disorders/anorexia-nervosa/features/anorexia-body-neglected?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>What, exactly, does anorexia nervosa do inside the human body? The heart and bones suffer the most.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Avoid My Mistakes: Single-Family Renovation Lessons I Learned the Hard Way</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/single-family-renovation-lessons-i-learned-the-hard-way</link><description>I want to share a few tips and lessons (some are costly) so you don’t repeat my mistakes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Plinky is an app for you to collect and organize links easily</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/09/plinky-is-an-app-for-you-to-collect-links/</link><description>Plinky lets you solve the problem of saving and organizing links from anywhere with a focus on simplicity and customization.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Campus Protests Could Shape the 2024 Elections — And Not Just the Presidency</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/30/campus-protests-gaza-arrests-prosecutors-elections</link><description>With hundreds of arrests and more campus standoffs looming, local law enforcement officials could face consequences at the ballot box.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 21:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Postpartum PTSD: Right Diagnosis Can Help Mothers and Babies</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/mental-health/news/20240506/postpartum-ptsd-right-diagnosis-can-help-mothers-and-babies?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Many new mothers aren’t aware that postpartum PTSD even exists, but it’s far from rare. Here's what to know.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:19:10 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>