<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 06:59:07 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>St Louis Cardinals Unveil New “The Lou” City Connect Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/20/st-louis-cardinals-unveil-new-the-lou-city-connect-uniforms/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>They’re from “The Lou,” and they’re proud. This morning, the St. Louis Cardinals became the 26th team to unveil their new Nike MLB City Connect uniform, doing so with the help of Grammy Award-winning hip-hop artist Nelly, a St. Louis native. It’s the first time in franchise history that the</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 13:59:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kid Rock Allegedly Waves Gun at Rolling Stone Writer, Says N-Word</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/20/kid-rock-allegedly-waves-gun-say-n-word-rolling-stone-interview/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Kid Rock is pushing his provocative persona to erratic new levels -- at least according to a new feature by Rolling Stone ... which claims he waved a gun around and said the n-word. The outlet dropped a fresh piece that chronicled an interview with…</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 06:59:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chicago Bears Add George S. Halas’ Initials To 1936 Throwback Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/18/chicago-bears-add-george-s-halas-initials-to-1936-throwback-uniforms/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Chicago Bears have subtly added the initials of late founder, owner and coach George S. Halas to the left sleeve of their 1936 throwback uniforms, matching their navy blue home, white road and orange alternate jerseys.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 22:34:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Prison Break' Star Sarah Wayne Callies Claims Male Costar Spat in Her Face</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/20/prison-break-sarah-wayne-callies-male-costar-actor-spit-face/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Sarah Wayne Callies claims one of her male costars on "Prison Break" spat in her face -- just one example, she says, of the rampant misogyny she had to deal with as the only gal. The actress went on the 'Broad Ideas' podcast Monday, with SWC…</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 06:59:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fanatics and NFLPA Reveal 2024 NFL Rookie Jerseys</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/18/fanatics-and-nflpa-reveal-2024-nfl-rookie-jerseys/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Last night, Fanatics and the NFLPA held a special “Jersey Reveal” event in Los Angeles to unveil the official game jerseys for 39 NFL rookies during the NFLPA Rookie Premiere. Several high-profile 2024 NFL Draft picks and rookies attended the event, including Caleb Williams and Rome Odunze of the Chicago</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 17:58:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zac Brown Estranged Wife Kelly Yazdi Says She Won't Be Silenced After TRO</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/20/zac-brown-estranged-wife-kelly-yazdi-divorce-restraining-order-lawsuit/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Zac Brown's estranged wife is addressing the fact he's asking a court to muzzle her Instagram posts ... which she says is just him trying to play victim and silence her. Kelly Yazdi hopped on IG Sunday to speak her piece on Zac's lawsuit from last…</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 06:59:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Carolina Disco Turkeys to play as Camel City Humps</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/18/carolina-disco-turkeys-to-play-as-camel-city-humps/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The town of Winston-Salem, North Carolina, is called “Camel City” because since 1875 it has been home to the R.J. Reynolds Tobacco Company, which produces Camel brand cigarettes. The town of Winston-Salem is also home to the collegiate summer level Carolina Disco Turkeys, who will put a new twist on</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 17:29:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tom Hanks' Son Chet Explains Kendrick &amp; Drake Beef To Him Over Text</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/20/tom-hanks-son-chet-explains-kendrick-lamar-drake-beef-dad-over-text/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Tom Hanks doesn't need Genius annotations to get the play-by-play on the Drake and Kendrick Lamar battle ... 'cause his son Chet can break it down ... and he did just that. Chet -- who's moonlighted as a rapper/reggae artist in the past, and has a…</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 06:59:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>All MLB Teams are Wearing Black Camo Caps Today</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/17/all-mlb-teams-are-wearing-black-camo-caps-today/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Why are all the Major League Baseball teams wearing black and green camouflage hats today? Well, that’s because MLB and New Era are in the midst of their annual Armed Forces Day ballcap celebration; here in 2024, the caps will be worn across the league over the May 17-18-19 weekend.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 23:44:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Diddy Legally Could Not Say Cassie's Name in Video Apology</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/20/diddy-legal-not-say-cassie-name-apology-video-nda-lawsuit-settlement/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>There are lots of reasons to drag Diddy over his video apology -- the public outrage is still fresh over what he did to Cassie -- but when it comes to him not saying her name in the mea culpa ... there's a legal reason he couldn't. As you know,…</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 06:59:07 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>