<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 06:57:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>CAPE Is High: Should You Care?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/17/cape-is-high-should-you-care/</link><description>A simple analysis shows that Robert Shiller's cyclically adjusted price-to-earnings ratio changed in the 1990s and that mean-reversion concerns may be misplaced. If CAPE changed three decades ago, however, there is nothing preventing it from doing so again.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 15:18:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Some interns at Big Tech and consulting giants are already earning six-figure salaries</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/18/best-paid-internships-2024-glassdoor-bain-company-roblox-amazon/</link><description>The $23 billion gaming giant Roblox is said to be paying fresh-faced interns over $10,000 a month, according to Glassdoor.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 11:39:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI to the Rescue? Overhauling the US Power Grid on the Path to Net Zero</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/15/ai-to-the-rescue-overhauling-the-us-power-grid-on-the-path-to-net-zero/</link><description>Once known as secure and profitable investments, utilities are now viewed as enterprises fraught with financial risks. Investors should favor utilities that employ AI and other digital strategies to minimize damage from natural disasters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 21:24:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jamie Dimon confronted Bill Gates after the Microsoft founder said banks were dinosaurs: 'Obviously he was dead wrong, he'd probably agree with that'</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/18/jamie-dimon-confronted-bill-gates-over-dinosaur-banks-comment/</link><description>But Dimon did agree with Gates on the wider point that "technology changes everything"—even if that hadn't meant banks becoming redundant.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 11:17:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Does a Stock’s Price Influence Its Risk Profile?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/12/does-a-stocks-price-influence-its-risk-profile/</link><description>As a stock falls in value, it becomes more sensitive to market movements and its total volatility increases.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deliveroo returns to order growth with a 2% increase but for rival Just Eat Takeaway, it's not looking as rosy</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/04/18/deliveroo-returns-to-order-growth-with-a-2-increase-but-for-rival-just-eat-its-not-looking-as-rosy/</link><description>Orders were up 4% in the international division and Deliveroo reported flat order growth in the UK and Ireland.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 10:57:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Managing Regret Risk: The Role of Asset Allocation</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/10/managing-regret-risk-the-role-of-asset-allocation/</link><description>Regret risk is a quantifiable phenomenon. The answer for some clients may be equally weighted portfolios.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 13:04:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI deepfakes could decide U.S election, experts warn</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/18/ai-deepfake-biden-trump-election-disinformation/</link><description>Political strategists warn of a 'race to the bottom' as AI supercharges the spread of fake news.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 10:50:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Art and Science of DC Plan Investment Design</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/08/the-art-and-science-of-dc-plan-investment-design/</link><description>Defined contribution plan sponsors need to take a disciplined approach to investment menu construction.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden administration agrees to provide $6.1bn for Micron Technology to produce advanced memory chips in New York and Idaho</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/18/biden-administration-6-billion-micron-technology-advanced-memory-chips-new-york-idaho/</link><description>Senate Majority Leader Chuck Schumer, D-N.Y., personally courted Micron to build what would ultimately be a set of four chip factories near Syracuse in the town of Clay.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 10:36:22 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>