<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 00:44:01 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>This Indicator Tells Me NOW is the Time to Strike</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/this-indicator-tells-me-now-is-the-time-to-strike/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Markets dipped slightly yesterday after a strong Wednesday, and I'm closely watching the 10-year U.S. Treasury yield. This yield typically moves opposite the stock market and has been falling steadily since May. Now, it's hit technical support, temporarily halting its decline. If it breaks this support, we could see a market surge. Until then, we have a narrow opportunity window. Tomorrow at 11 a.m. Eastern, I’m hosting a special masterclass to show you how to target stocks poised to surge. Don't miss out – secure your spot now and join me for this essential session! The post This Indicator Tells Me NOW is the Time to Strike appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 14:26:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Junkyard Gem: 1994 Volvo 850 Turbo Wagon</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/18/junkyard-gem-1994-volvo-850-turbo-wagon/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/12122534/99-1994-Volvo-850-Turbo-in-Colorado-junkyard-photo-by-Murilee-Martin.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Volvo , Automotive History , Wagon , Performance , Classics Continue reading Junkyard Gem: 1994 Volvo 850 Turbo Wagon Junkyard Gem: 1994 Volvo 850 Turbo Wagon originally appeared on Autoblog on Sat, 18 May 2024 16:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>We’re in a Home Construction Golden Age—Here’s How Investors Would Benefit From Building</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/why-investors-should-be-flocking-to-new-construction</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>This may be the best time ever to invest in new construction.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 16:01:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Most Popular Book Riot Stories of the Week</title><link>https://bookriot.com/best-of-book-riot-may-18-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/black-woman-reading-with-a-cup-of-coffee.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>Grab your coffee, kick up your feet, and dive into our best stuff from another eventful week in the world ...</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sharing Fun Facts About Yourself: 22 Examples &amp; Ideas</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/fun-facts-about-me/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fun-facts-about-me</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Asking to share some fun facts about yourself is a common icebreaker that’s used during job interviews. But the quality of your answer still matters. This guide will help you come up with some ideas for crafting a response that starts the interview on a good note. Table of contents Ideas for Sharing Fun Facts […] The post Sharing Fun Facts About Yourself: 22 Examples &amp; Ideas appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 15:26:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A case for public preschool: New study reveals preschool benefits to be longer-lasting and substantial</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/benefits-of-public-preschool/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=benefits-of-public-preschool</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Preschool lays a foundation for elementary school students to succeed. In the United States, as children approach kindergarten entry, it is increasingly common for 4-year-olds to be in non-parental group care and education, often in a center- or school-based setting where they can learn alongside peers. For children from low-income communities, […] The post A case for public preschool: New study reveals preschool benefits to be longer-lasting and substantial appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 08:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>No ‘cop on the beat’: Why the SEC may deny new ether ETFs this month</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/18/crypto-fraud-and-poor-regulation-may-jeopardize-ether-etf-approval.html</link><description>The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission is expected to make a key decision on approving ether ETFs.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>13 Travel-Approved Loungewear Sets That Amazon Reviewers Swear By</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1396104/13-travel-approved-loungewear-sets-that-amazon-reviewers-swear-by?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>We independently selected these deals and products because we love them, and we think you might like them at these prices. E! has affiliate relationships, so we may get a commission if you...</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 02:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sustainability Reporting: Navigating Assurance Practices</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/17/sustainability-reporting-navigating-assurance-practices/</link><description>Don't be lulled into a false sense of security by the word "assurance" when evaluating sustainability reports. Assurance practices vary, and investors would be wise to learn more about the different levels of coverage.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 17:57:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Benny Gantz threatens to leave Israel’s war cabinet if Netanyahu doesn’t meet demands, warning against ‘path of fanatics’ that will lead to the ‘abyss’</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/18/benny-gantz-israel-war-cabinet-benjamin-netanyahu-gaza-hamas/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1419872476-e1716086880673.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>“Personal and political considerations began to penetrate the Holy of Holies — Israel’s security.”</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 04:04:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wedding Guest Edit</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/wedding-guest-edit/</link><description>Outfit Details: Siedres Dress, JB x Jennifer Behr Necklace, Sherman Fields Necklace, Prada Bag, Hermes Bangles (similar, less expensive here) Wedding season… The post Wedding Guest Edit appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 05:00:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wait\u2026 I\u2019m the president!</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/aGyVMnZ</link><description>Tags: President 5973 points, 327 comments.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 05:40:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chicago Bears Add George S. Halas’ Initials To 1936 Throwback Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/18/chicago-bears-add-george-s-halas-initials-to-1936-throwback-uniforms/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Chicago Bears have subtly added the initials of late founder, owner and coach George S. Halas to the left sleeve of their 1936 throwback uniforms, matching their navy blue home, white road and orange alternate jerseys.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 22:34:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OpenAI and Google lay out their competing AI visions</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/18/openai-and-google-lay-out-their-competing-ai-visions/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Welcome back to TechCrunch’s Week in Review. This week had two major events from OpenAI and Google. OpenAI’s spring update event saw the reveal of its new model, GPT-4o, which has voice and vision capabilities that can turn ChatGPT into a virtual assistant seemingly aspiring to be “Her.” Hot off OpenAI’s tail, Google’s I/O conference […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 21:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Police Tactics at Some Pro-Palestine Protests Ignore Past Lessons</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/18/police-israel-palestine-campus-protests</link><description>While some universities have sought peaceful approaches, others have used aggressive policing that bucks research from the protests following George Floyd’s murder.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>California Burrito</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/california-burrito/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>This delicious California Burrito is filled with well-seasoned grilled steak, pepper jack cheese, French fries, pico de Gallo, sour cream…</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gayle King Embraces WW &amp; Exercise For Weight Loss, Unlike Pal Oprah</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/18/gayle-king-embrace-weightwatchers-exercise-sports-illustrated-oprah-weight-loss-drugs/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Gayle King is dishing on how she got cover ready for her photo shoot with Sports Illustrated ... giving cred to the very company her pal Oprah Winfrey just ditched, at least professionally. We caught up with Gayle in NYC, where the CBS News anchor…</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 00:44:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Federal Experts Talk Bird Flu ‘What Ifs’ in WebMD Live Event</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/cold-and-flu/news/20240516/federal-experts-talk-bird-flu-what-ifs?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>WebMD brought together experts from four federal agencies to talk prevention, monitoring, and what the “what ifs” of bird flu might look like.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:50:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Weekend In New Orleans With Kids</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/new-orleans-with-kids/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Since our travel guides to Charleston with kids and Palm Springs with kids have elicited requests for more travel ideas with kids, we’re back with an overdue recap of our 3-night trip to New Orleans. We’d never been to The Big Easy before and were impressed by how family-friendly the city is. It’s not all booze, beads, and Bourbon Street! So here’s a look at where we stayed, what we did, and what we’re excited to do next time we go back – because we will definitely go back! The four of us (well, five if you count our chihuahua!) went to NOLA for 3 nights in November of 2022. At the time, our kids were 8 and 12 years old. So unfortunately we can’t vouch for our suggestions being a good fit for toddlers or younger children. Although I’m sure ours would’ve loved the Louisiana Children’s Museum and Storyland playground back in the day! Continue reading A Weekend In New Orleans With Kids at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 17:17:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Bull Market is Officially Back</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/the-bull-market-is-officially-back/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, it's Ross Givens here with the Chart of the Day. Introducing the often-overlooked Russell 3000 index, encompassing 3,000 major U.S. stocks and serving as a comprehensive gauge of the U.S. market. Notably, it recently surged to new all-time highs, reflecting the overall robustness of the market. With this positive momentum, there's ample opportunity for savvy investors to capitalize on the market's strength. Stay tuned to unlock its potential. The post The Bull Market is Officially Back appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Morocco’s automotive industry shifts gears to prep for electric vehicle era</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/18/moroccos-automotive-industry-shifts-gears-to-prep-for-electric-vehicle-era/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/17133232/morocco_car_industry.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Earnings/Financials , Government/Legal , Plants/Manufacturing , Green Automakers , Electric , Future Vehicles , Hybrid Continue reading Morocco’s automotive industry shifts gears to prep for electric vehicle era Morocco’s automotive industry shifts gears to prep for electric vehicle era originally appeared on Autoblog on Sat, 18 May 2024 14:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>5 Ways to Capitalize on Public Investments in Tax Increment Financing (TIF) Districts</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/ways-to-capitalize-on-public-investments-in-tax-increment-financing-districts</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>These smart strategies make the most of community investments while increasing your profitability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Riot’s YA Book Deals of the Day: May 18, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/book-riots-ya-book-deals-of-the-day-may-18-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Untitled-design-56.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>A dozen YA books across an array of genres, all coming in at under $3 today!</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 553</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-553/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-553</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Tools and technology change rapidly. Yet as wonderful as technology can be, it doesn’t replace the need for human connection through interactions. Keep this in mind as you are searching for a new job. It’s your human connections that often open doors! In this week’s collection of news and tips for job seekers, you’ll find: […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 553 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 12:19:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fathers’ views on family and work after COVID-19 lockdowns</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/fathers-views-on-family-and-work-after-covid-19-lockdowns/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fathers-views-on-family-and-work-after-covid-19-lockdowns</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Fathers often want to be present for their children and contribute to household tasks, but they can lack opportunities and confidence; they may see themselves as “helpers” instead of parents. Australian fathers in our small study reported that they spent more time with their children during the COVID-19 lockdowns, and they […] The post Fathers’ views on family and work after COVID-19 lockdowns appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Study links talc use to ovarian cancer, adding a potential boon for lawsuits against J&amp;J</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/18/study-links-talc-to-ovarian-cancer-with-implications-for-jj-.html</link><description>The analysis, released Wednesday in the Journal of Clinical Oncology, found that applying talc powder to the genitals was associated with ovarian cancer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 15:29:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>John Stamos Shares Full House Reunion Pic With Olsen Twins</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1401926/john-stamos-shares-never-before-seen-full-house-reunion-photo-with-mary-kate-and-ashley-olsen?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>Have mercy. You may get emotional seeing John Stamos' newly posted never-before-seen photo of the cast of Full House reuniting for a bittersweet reason: To attend costar Bob Saget's funeral back...</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 01:10:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Power of Clicks, Likes, and Shares: Promote the Right Kind of Financial Content</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/16/the-power-of-clicks-likes-and-shares-promote-the-right-kind-of-financial-content/</link><description>Not all financial content creators on social media are created equal. A broad differentiation can be made between influencers, knowledge sharers, and aspiring thought leaders.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 14:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bankrupt crypto lender Genesis gets OK to return billions in tokens and cash to creditors, meaning parent firm DCG ‘is out of the money’</title><link>https://fortune.com/crypto/2024/05/18/bankrupt-crypto-lender-genesis-return-billions-bitcoin-tokens-creditors-dcg/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1475394879-e1716076256193.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>“Given the size of the creditor claims, DCG is out of the money as an equity holder by billions of dollars,” Judge Lane said.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 01:07:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pastel Palette Picks</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/pastel-palette-picks/</link><description>Outfit Details: Pucci Swimsuit, Janessa Leone Hat, Prada Sunglasses One of the joys of embracing spring and early summer in Charleston is… The post Pastel Palette Picks appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 21:30:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blue Just now</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/aGyVA1G</link><description>Tags: aliens 2159 points, 147 comments.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 05:40:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fanatics and NFLPA Reveal 2024 NFL Rookie Jerseys</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/18/fanatics-and-nflpa-reveal-2024-nfl-rookie-jerseys/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Last night, Fanatics and the NFLPA held a special “Jersey Reveal” event in Los Angeles to unveil the official game jerseys for 39 NFL rookies during the NFLPA Rookie Premiere. Several high-profile 2024 NFL Draft picks and rookies attended the event, including Caleb Williams and Rome Odunze of the Chicago</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 17:58:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Expedia says two execs dismissed after ‘violation of company policy’</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/18/expedia-says-two-execs-dismissed-after-violation-of-company-policy/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Expedia says Rathi Murthy and Sreenivas Rachamadugu, respectively its CTO and senior vice president of core services product &amp; engineering, are no longer employed at the travel booking company. In a statement shared with Bloomberg and elsewhere, Expedia said Murthy and Rachamadugu are “no longer employed at Expedia Group” due to an unspecified “violation of […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 19:05:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Susan Chira to Step Down as The Marshall Project’s Editor-in-Chief in January</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/16/susan-chira-eic-step-down</link><description>Under her stewardship, the news nonprofit more than doubled in size, opened local newsrooms and won its second Pulitzer Prize.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Meal Plan #5</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/weekly-menu-plan-5/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Weekly meal plan #5 is made up of delicious comfort meals the whole family will love. I specifically included a…</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kanye West and Bianca Censori Dine at Denny's Amid Major Yeezy Changes</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/18/kanye-west-bianca-censori-dennys-yeezy-mass-exodus-employees/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Kanye West and Bianca Censori chowing down at America's Diner isn't something you'd expect, but their affordable meal comes as a major shakeup goes down at Ye's company. New video obtained by TMZ shows Kanye -- with a white hoodie tight around his…</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 00:44:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What’s Next in Health Care for Older Adults: Questions and Answers With John Whyte, MD</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/blog-aging-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>As WebMD’s chief medical officer, John Whyte, MD, is in a unique position to see both the current state of medical care for America’s older adults and the way things are trending for the future. We asked him to share his insight on a few topics, along with a bit of advice.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:29:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Easy Low-Light Indoor Plants</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/easy-low-light-indoor-plants/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>I used to think every houseplant needed a sunny corner or bright windowsill to thrive. But it turns out many of our favorite go-to houseplants do just fine in shady corners and low-light locations. So before you write off your house as too dark to sustain plant life, check out this list of the best indoor plants for low light. You might be surprised at how many good options there are! Our upstairs family room is the brightest room we’ve ever owned thanks to big unobstructed windows on all 4 sides. But most of our indoor plants live downstairs, where we get far less natural light. Luckily, that hasn’t stopped us from growing our collection of happy healthy houseplants. 9 Houseplants That Don’t Need A Lot Of Light Here are our favorite low-light indoor plants. We list a lot more info on them below, but here’s a quick list to bring on your next trip to the plant store: Snake Plant ZZ Plant Pothos Heartleaf Philodendron English Ivy Aglaonema Cast Iron Plant Monstera Parlor Palm Perhaps our favorite part of this list is that these aren’t ugly “consolation plants” that people begrudgingly buy for dark homes. Continue reading Easy Low-Light Indoor Plants at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 14:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Bull Flag Tells Me “Risk On”</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/this-bull-flag-tells-me-risk-on/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, it's Ross Givens here with the Chart of the Day. Presenting Bitcoin's price showcasing a classic "bull flag pattern," signaling a bullish market sentiment. While it's an opportune time to consider Bitcoin investments, the broader implication lies in the market's risk appetite. Despite the current subdued state, indications point towards an imminent surge, as evidenced by Bitcoin's pattern and recent meme stock activity. Stay tuned to harness potential opportunities arising from this evolving market sentiment. The post This Bull Flag Tells Me “Risk On” appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indy 500: When it starts, how to watch, betting odds for 'The Greatest Spectacle in Racing'</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/18/indy-500-when-it-starts-how-to-watch-betting-odds-for-the-greatest-spectacle-in-racing/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/17131047/indycar_indy_500_auto_racing.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Motorsports , Racing Vehicles Continue reading Indy 500: When it starts, how to watch, betting odds for 'The Greatest Spectacle in Racing' Indy 500: When it starts, how to watch, betting odds for 'The Greatest Spectacle in Racing' originally appeared on Autoblog on Sat, 18 May 2024 12:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adventures in Property Management: 5 Lessons Learned from My Years of Self-Managing Single Family Rentals</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/lessons-learned-from-years-of-self-managing-single-family-rentals</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Use my tips to be a better self-managing landlord.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Riot’s Deals of the Day for May 18, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/book-riots-deals-of-the-day-for-may-18-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/deals-051824.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>A teen-created Satanic panic, a bruja with ever-growing magical abilities, and more of today's best book deals.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 552</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-552/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-552</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>When you are searching for a job, you will inevitably run into unexpected scenarios. You will have questions, experience self-doubt and even feel discouraged. You’ll also experience great wins, meet wonderful people and discover new things about yourself. That’s the roller-coaster of job search. Consider Summary Sunday your resource for getting questions answered and showing […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 552 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 11:37:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Strong Latine Identity Supports U.S. Latine Children’s Well-Being</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/a-strong-latine-identity-supports-u-s-latine-childrens-well-being/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=a-strong-latine-identity-supports-u-s-latine-childrens-well-being</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key Takeaways for caregivers Children tend to have better health and well-being when they have a strong ethnic identity (affinity and adoption of ethnicity-based self-concept). A traditional Latine cultural value (familismo) that emphasizes family bonds is also associated with better developmental outcomes. Caregivers can support the development of U.S. Latine children (and possibly other children […] The post A Strong Latine Identity Supports U.S. Latine Children’s Well-Being appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 03:03:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Activist Corvex could take an amicable approach to help create value at Vestis. How it may unfold</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/18/corvex-could-take-an-amicable-approach-to-help-create-value-at-vestis.html</link><description>Corvex reveals a stake in uniform supplier Vestis. The firm is suggesting that it’s here for the long term.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Teen Mom's Jenelle Evans Gets Restraining Order Against Ex</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1401924/teen-moms-jenelle-evans-reportedly-obtains-restraining-order-against-ex-david-eason?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>Jenelle Evans has been granted a restraining order against her ex David Eason months after their breakup, according to multiple reports. On May 16, the Teen Mom star obtained a six-month domestic...</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 00:12:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why the New T+1 Settlement Cycle Matters: A Global Index Provider’s Perspective</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/14/why-the-new-t1-settlement-cycle-matters-a-global-index-providers-perspective/</link><description>Shorter settlement periods are meant to protect market participants. But the new T+1 settlement cycle for US equities may have undesirable knock-on effects for financial market participants around the world, including index fund managers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 16:54:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aging while exercising? Great. Just be sure to reevaluate your routine.</title><link>https://fortune.com/well/article/workout-as-you-age/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1254783748_4fe5fc-e1715964080270.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>“We need to think about changing the program to be effective and to be safe," notes one expert.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jet Set Ready With Net-A-Porter</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/jet-set-ready-with-net-a-porter/</link><description>Thank you to NET-A-PORTER for sponsoring this post. Jet Set Ready With Net-A-Porter emerges as your essential guide to traveling… The post Jet Set Ready With Net-A-Porter appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 05:00:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Smart people and their wrong predictions</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/aD2w8qZ</link><description>Tags: random 5014 points, 664 comments.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 05:40:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Carolina Disco Turkeys to play as Camel City Humps</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/18/carolina-disco-turkeys-to-play-as-camel-city-humps/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The town of Winston-Salem, North Carolina, is called “Camel City” because since 1875 it has been home to the R.J. Reynolds Tobacco Company, which produces Camel brand cigarettes. The town of Winston-Salem is also home to the collegiate summer level Carolina Disco Turkeys, who will put a new twist on</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 17:29:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>With AI startups booming, nap pods and Silicon Valley hustle culture are back</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/18/ai-startups-nap-pods-silicon-valley-hustle-culture/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>When Jeffrey Wang posted to X asking if anyone wanted to go in on an order of fancy-but-affordable office nap pods, he didn’t expect the post to go viral. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When Bad Cops Become Private Security Guards</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/11/police-private-guard-florida-chicago</link><description>There’s growing evidence that former officers with troubling histories of abuse can easily find second careers in private security.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best Swedish Meatballs</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/the-best-swedish-meatballs/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>These Swedish Meatballs are smothered in the most amazing rich and creamy gravy and packed with such delicious flavor. You…</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Billionaire Juices Speech with $1,000 to Each UMass Dartmouth Graduate</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/18/billionaire-robert-hale-jr-speech-1000-dollars-umass-dartmouth-graduation/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Oprah Winfrey's got nothing on Robert Hale Jr., a telecom billionaire, who didn't hand out car keys to UMass Dartmouth grads ... but, instead, handed them cold hard cash -- for themselves and others. You could say Hale spiced up his commencement…</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 00:44:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Get the Care You Need in a COVID-19 World</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/covid-senior-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>What to expect at the doctor’s office, hospitals, and long-term care facilities, the future of telemedicine, and how to get the best care during COVID-19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 19:50:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/how-to-remove-wallpaper/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Wallpaper has made a big comeback as a trendy home design choice. But despite its resurgence, there are still plenty of us dealing with dingy, dated, or downright ugly old wallpaper we don’t want. In our old home, we had to remove wallpaper in so many rooms: the kitchen, the dining room, the foyer, and two different bathrooms! As we traveled from room to room removing wallpaper, we tested 4 different methods, and today we’ll share what we learned. Removing wallpaper doesn’t require special tools or lots of money. It’s a totally doable project for any homeowner. However, it can be a tedious process that can take elbow grease and patience, depending on the size of your room and the stubbornness of your wallpaper. But having removed several rooms worth of decades-old wallpaper, we can confidently say it’s worth the effort! You can also check out more before and afters of our once-wallpapered rooms. Continue reading How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:21:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Could This Derail the Recovery? (What to Do About It)</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/could-this-derail-the-recovery-what-to-do-about-it/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, it's Ross Givens here with the Chart of the Day. Diving into one of my top charts, the Equal-Weight S&amp;P 500 Index (RSP) paints a clearer picture of the market's health by eliminating the dominance of mega-cap tech stocks. Currently, RSP sits a mere 1.5% shy of its all-time highs, signaling a robust recovery from the April pullback. However, with the looming CPI report's potential impact, the market's trajectory remains uncertain. Stay ahead of the curve with my insight. The post Could This Derail the Recovery? (What to Do About It) appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Yeti coolers, drinkware and more are 20% off at REI's Anniversary Sale</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/article/yeti-coolers-drinkware-and-more-are-20-off-at-reis-anniversary-sale/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/15122608/61301101-b2fb-453b-a87b-72f150f81.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Commerce Continue reading Yeti coolers, drinkware and more are 20% off at REI's Anniversary Sale Yeti coolers, drinkware and more are 20% off at REI's Anniversary Sale originally appeared on Autoblog on Sat, 18 May 2024 11:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A New South Carolina Law Would Severely Crack Down on Wholesaling</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/new-south-carolina-law-would-severely-crack-down-on-wholesaling</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>The bill could be a precursor of what's to come across the country.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Riot’s Deals of the Day for May 17, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/book-riots-deals-of-the-day-for-may-17-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/deals-051724.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>Another mega-list of deals for you today - grab 'em while you can!</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 19:09:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>While a little competition in the workplace might help bring out the best in everyone involved, an atmosphere rooted in envy, fear, or jealousy can do the exact opposite. This post will help you recognize signs that your coworker is threatened by you, and help you navigate the situation. 1. They Don’t Want You Involved […] The post 10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:07:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Children caught between highly conflicted divorced parents at greater risk of mental health problems</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/children-caught-between-conflicted-divorced-parents/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=children-caught-between-conflicted-divorced-parents</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Interparental conflict after divorce escalates the risk of mental health problems in children and adolescents. Elevated levels of conflict between parents can also induce fear and worry in children about their future and whether they will be adequately taken care of. In turn, a greater fear of abandonment puts children at […] The post Children caught between highly conflicted divorced parents at greater risk of mental health problems appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 08:59:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Some consumers are punting big purchases like pools and mattresses</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/18/some-consumers-are-punting-big-purchases-like-pools-and-mattresses.html</link><description>There are some signs that shoppers are holding off on big-ticket buys, the latest signal of the economy contracting at the hands of tighter monetary policy.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 14:22:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kendall Jenner Attends Ex Bad Bunny's Show After Met Gala After-Par</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1401917/kendall-jenner-spotted-at-ex-bad-bunnys-concert-following-met-gala-after-party-reunion?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>Kendall Jenner remains one of ex Bad Bunny's biggest fans. The model was spotted attending the rapper's concert at Kia Center in Orlando, Fla. May 17, more than a week after they reunited at a...</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 21:32:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Leveraging AI to Identify and Predict Financial Crises</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/13/leveraging-ai-to-identify-and-predict-financial-crises/</link><description>Despite some current limitations, AI stands to offer significant advantages versus traditional approaches to identifying and predicting financial crises.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 14:39:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>An oil tanker going from Russia to China is hit by a Houthi missile in the Red Sea, U.S. military says</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/18/oil-tanker-russia-china-iran-houthi-rebels-missile-red-sea-israel-hamas/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2065827955-e1716073906569.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The strike Saturday on the Greek-owned M/T Wind caused flooding that knocked out its propulsion and steering, which the crew restored.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 00:23:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Crop Tops</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/crop-tops/</link><description>Outfit Details: Kilentar Top (similar here), Emporior Sirenuse Skirt, Emme Parsons Sandals, Prada Bag The crop top has earned its place as one of… The post Crop Tops appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:30:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A god does not care about the opinion of an ant. Mike Tyson owning whatshisface by doing nothing.</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/a9yMvgj</link><description>Tags: dark humor , mike tyson , jake paul 5865 points, 759 comments.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 05:40:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>All MLB Teams are Wearing Black Camo Caps Today</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/17/all-mlb-teams-are-wearing-black-camo-caps-today/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Why are all the Major League Baseball teams wearing black and green camouflage hats today? Well, that’s because MLB and New Era are in the midst of their annual Armed Forces Day ballcap celebration; here in 2024, the caps will be worn across the league over the May 17-18-19 weekend.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 23:44:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OpenAI created a team to control ‘superintelligent’ AI — then let it wither, source says</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/18/openai-created-a-team-to-control-superintelligent-ai-then-let-it-wither-source-says/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>OpenAI’s Superalignment team, responsible for developing ways to govern and steer “superintelligent” AI systems, was promised 20% of the company’s compute resources, according to a person from that team. But requests for a fraction of that compute were often denied, blocking the team from doing their work. That issue, among others, pushed several team members […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 17:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Rare Bright Spot for a Canine Lover Doing Time: Raising Puppies to Become Service Dogs</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/10/service-dogs-training-prison-essay</link><description>Adam Roberts reflects on the highs and occasional lows of training Labrador retrievers for the Puppies Behind Bars program.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>No Bake Snickers Bar Pie</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/no-bake-snickers-bar-pie/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>No Bake Snickers Bar Pie is one of the easiest and most delicious no bake pies that you make. You…</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jennifer Lopez, Ben Affleck's Separate Lives, Not Together on Mother's Day</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/18/jennifer-lopez-ben-affleck-separate-lives-mothers-day/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Jennifer Lopez and Ben Affleck are living such separate lives right now, they reportedly did not celebrate Mother's Day together. As we reported, Ben has moved out of their Beverly Hills mansion, and into a home he's renting in Brentwood -- not far…</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 00:44:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Personal Shopper: A Savvy Black Entrepreneur Guides You to Eczema-Friendly Clothes, Creams, Cosmetics, and More</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/savvy-black-entrepreneur-guides-eczema-friendly-clothes-creams-cosmetics?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>A savvy black entrepreneur guides you on an eczema-friendly shopping spree.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:54:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aglaonema Plant – Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/aglaonema-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Aglaonema, also called the Chinese Evergreen Plant, is an easy-care houseplant that lives happily in many lighting conditions – even a dark corner of our daughter’s room. There are dozens of different Aglaonema varieties, most with large tropical foliage and colors ranging from silvery-green, red, and even vibrant pink. They’re also tough to kill, so they’re a great option for forgetful plant owners or anyone looking for an easy win in the plant department. These truly have been very low maintenance for us. We purchased our two Aglaonemas (pronounced ag-lee-oh-neem-ah ) to put atop our daughter’s closet. It’s sometimes hard to distinguish different varieties, but we believe that’s an Aglaonema Silver (right) and either a Candy Cane or Princess Silver Queen (left). Aglaonema Quick Facts Here’s what you need to know about your Aglaonema at a glance: Latin name : Aglaonema is the genus under which there are 21 recognized species . Continue reading Aglaonema Plant – Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:47:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bulls Back in Control (Do This Now)</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/bulls-back-in-control-do-this-now/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, it's Ross Givens here with the Chart of the Day. In a remarkable shift, my market health model swiftly transitioned from bearish to bullish within a week. This robust buying spree following the recent dip signifies significant strength and resilience in the market. The much-needed correction allowed for the consolidation of previous gains and the shedding of weak-handed sellers. While the overall market gears up for further upward movement, the dynamics for individual stocks present a nuanced scenario, as I delve into in today's Insight. The post Bulls Back in Control (Do This Now) appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>UAW loss in Alabama won't kill national organizing effort, analysts say</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/18/uaw-loss-in-alabama-wont-kill-national-organizing-effort-analysts-say/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/crop/3800x2138+0+81/resize/800x450!/format/jpg/quality/85/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/18095258/the_exterior_of_the_visitors_center_at_the_mercedes-benz__suv_manufacturing_plant_in_vance_.jpeg</image_url><description>Filed under: Plants/Manufacturing , UAW/Unions , Mercedes-Benz Continue reading UAW loss in Alabama won't kill national organizing effort, analysts say UAW loss in Alabama won't kill national organizing effort, analysts say originally appeared on Autoblog on Sat, 18 May 2024 10:30:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Only One Major Market is Seeing Housing Prices Decline Right Now</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/home-prices-declining-in-only-one-major-metro-area</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Supply is up and demand is down, so why aren't more cities seeing price decreases?</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 13:56:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best Sci-Fi, Fantasy, and Horror Books of the Summer</title><link>https://bookriot.com/best-of-book-riot-may-17-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/nebula.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>Here’s to wrapping up the week with a big serving of bookish goodness! 🍿 Less than a month until It ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 551</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-551/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-551</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Job search requires writing and marketing skills. It also requires strong verbal communication. If these skills are not part of your normal work function, you’ll want some help. That’s what this week’s Summary Sunday is all about. There’s no doubt that LinkedIn is one of THE most powerful tools in your career toolbox. It contains […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 551 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 11:37:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>“Why do they feel sad?” Shared book reading reveals how children learn about others’ emotions</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/shared-book-reading/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=shared-book-reading</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers: It is good for children to identify the emotions of others in conversations with caregivers because it scaffolds their ability to identify others’ emotions on their own. Children who use more emotion talk in parent-child conversations about emotions are more likely to have higher emotion knowledge one year later. Parents can […] The post “Why do they feel sad?” Shared book reading reveals how children learn about others’ emotions appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 08:19:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>These stocks and ETFs could benefit from AI's voracious appetite for energy</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/18/stocks-and-etfs-that-could-benefit-from-ais-insatiable-need-for-energy.html</link><description>The power required to operate large artificial intelligence programs could help these investments outside of technology, according to Bank of America.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 14:17:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Matthew Stafford's Wife Kelly Weighs in on Harrison Butker Controversy</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1401920/kelly-stafford-wife-of-nfls-matthew-stanford-weighs-in-on-harrison-butker-controversy?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>Kelly Stafford, the wife of Los Angeles Rams quarterback Matthew Stafford, has joined the chat about Harrison Butker's controversial commencement speech. The Kansas City Chiefs kicker has sparked...</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 20:29:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Your Portfolio Should Include Scarce Assets</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/10/why-your-portfolio-should-include-scarce-assets/</link><description>Portfolios that include both productive and scarce assets can deliver similar performance to the S&amp;P 500 with less risk than those that hold only productive assets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:34:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Some NYU students being disciplined for protests must reflect on a ‘Simpsons’ episode: ‘What, if anything, could Lisa have done or thought about to make better decisions?’</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/18/nyu-students-israel-gaza-hamas-protests-discipline-the-simpsons-lisa-simpson/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1074338030-e1716072038771.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>One workbook has a section based on an episode of “The Simpsons” in which Lisa uncharacteristically cheats on a test and is wracked by guilt.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 23:54:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Punchy Prints</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/punchy-prints/</link><description>Outfit Details: Pucci Top &amp; Pants, Chanel Bag (similar, less expensive here), Dior Sandals (similar, less expensive here), Louis Abel Earrings (less expensive here) Punchy prints are a favorite of mine… The post Punchy Prints appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 05:00:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What's going on here?</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/ae931z5</link><description>Tags: relationship , dafuq , omg 3596 points, 298 comments.</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 05:40:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Borussia Dortmund Aims for  a Modern Classic With 2024-25 Home Kits – Plus 3 Other European Kit Launches</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/17/borussia-dortmund-aims-for-a-modern-classic-with-2024-25-home-kits-plus-3-other-european-kit-launches/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>ACF Fiorentina leans hard into signature purple color; Bologna FC calls new home kits 'an act of love'; Athletic Bilbao goes with the flow with new away kit</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 15:54:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>VCs and the military are fueling self-driving startups that don’t need roads</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/18/vcs-and-the-military-are-fueling-self-driving-startups-that-dont-need-roads/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>A new crop of early-stage startups — along with some recent VC investments — illustrates a niche emerging in the autonomous vehicle technology sector. Unlike the companies bringing robotaxis to city streets, these startups are taking their tech off-road. Two recent entrants — Seattle-based Overland AI and New Brunswick-based Potential — are poised to get […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Marshall Project Wins the Dart Award for “The Mercy Workers”</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/06/the-marshall-project-wins-the-dart-award-for-the-mercy-workers</link><description>Our feature on mitigation specialists who help save people from the death penalty was recognized for making “significant contributions to public understanding of trauma-related issues.”</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Easy Grilled Bourbon Chicken</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/grilled-bourbon-chicken/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>One bite of this grilled bourbon chicken and your tastebuds will be dancing with delight! It’s marinated in a flavorful…</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Britney Spears Rants About Mexico Trip, Claims Injured Foot Healed</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/18/britney-spears-instagram-rant-mexico-trip-injure-foot-heal/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Britney Spears says she's healing all on her own after a trip to Mexico -- which she says included cursing out strangers -- but visuals of her battered foot seem to tell a drastically different story. Late Friday, the pop star posted a disturbing…</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 00:44:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Behind the Spike in Colorectal Cancer Among Young Americans</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/colorectal-cancer/news/20240515/behind-the-spike-in-colorectal-cancer-cases?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Colorectal cancer cases increased a whopping 333% among 15- to 19-year-olds and 185% among 20- to 24-year-olds from 1999 to 2020.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:59:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Corn Plant – Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/corn-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Corn plants ( Dracaena fragrans ) are popular low-maintenance houseplants you’ve probably seen at the nursery, home improvement store, or doctor’s office. I even had one in my college dorm room! You can recognize them by their spear-shaped leaves and woody, cane-line trunks that can grow up to 6 feet tall indoors. But did you know there are several varieties of corn plants? We didn’t! Heck, we didn’t even realize some of our smaller houseplants were in the same corn plant family! Currently, we own two smaller varieties of corn plants, pictured above. The one on the left is a Dracaena Limelight ( Dracaena fragrans ‘Limelight’ ) and the taller plant is a Draecanea Dorado ( Dracaena fragrans ‘Dorado’ ). We actually have several limelights around because we love their vibrant color on shelves, tabletops, and windowsills. Corn Plant Quick Facts Latin name : Dracaena fragrans Common names : Corn plant, cornstalk plant, false palms Light : Bright, indirect light but can tolerate lower-light conditions Watering : Keep soil moist, but not soggy. Continue reading Corn Plant – Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 17:37:33 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>