<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 06:52:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NFL Second, Third Helmet Concept Series – AFC West</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/18/nfl-second-third-helmet-concept-series-afc-west/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Our newest concept series that creates second and/or third helmet designs for every NFL team continues with the AFC West.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 17:07:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cocaine Stashes Wash Up on FL Shores After Hurricane Debby</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/18/cocaine-washes-up-miami-hurricane-debby/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Now THIS is a storm surge -- more than 100 pounds of coke washed up along Florida's shores in the wake of Hurricane Debby. While Debby did not make a direct hit on the Sunshine State, she did stir several narcotics stashes that ended up on or near…</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 06:52:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>First Look at the 2025 MLB Spring Training Logos</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/17/first-look-at-the-2025-mlb-spring-training-logos/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Is it that time of the year already? This week, Major League Baseball released its new official logos for its 2025 Spring Training schedule. This year’s logos for the annual six-week slate of exhibition games include an all-new primary mark, a slightly modified alternate design, and designs for both the</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 16:08:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kanye West and Bianca Censori Roll Up to Trump Rally in Beverly Hills</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/18/kanye-west-bianca-censori-trump-rally-beverly-hills/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Kanye West is still riding for Donald Trump, but now he's doing it in a Cybertruck with new wife Bianca Censori ... and their surprise appearance at a Trump rally quickly got outta hand. Ye and Bianca rolled up Saturday in Bev Hills, where…</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 06:52:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2024-25 European Football Kit Preview: Serie A</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/17/2024-25-european-football-kit-preview-serie-a/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>123rd season of top-flight soccer in Italy kicks off on Saturday, August 17, with defending champs Inter Milan taking on Genoa CFC</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rihanna Takes Shots with Friends at Beach Bar in Barbados</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/18/rihanna-shots-barbados-beach-bar/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Rihanna's getting rowdy down in the Caribbean ... downing shots with some friends at a beach bar in Barbados -- and, lifting a glass to her one-year-old son. The singer-songwriter hit Thunder Bay Beach Bar on the small island country ... pulling up…</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 06:52:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CFL Running Back Becomes First Pro Football Player to Wear Guardian Cap in Regular Season Game</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/16/cfl-running-back-becomes-first-pro-football-player-to-wear-guardian-cap-in-regular-season-game/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Saskatchewan Roughriders running back Thomas Bertrand-Hudon wears concussion prevention cover in game against Montreal Alouettes on Friday, August 16</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 03:05:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Robert De Niro Celebrates 81st Birthday with Daring Yacht Plunge</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/18/robert-de-niro-birthday-yacht-jump/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Robert De Niro's still looking like a raging bull as he celebrates another birthday ... taking a wild leap off a yacht while partying with his family! His daughter Drena De Niro was recording when her pop took the dive for his 81st birthday, and…</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 06:52:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Phoenix Suns, Washington Wizards’ 2024-25 City Edition Shorts Leak On Social Media</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/16/phoenix-suns-washington-wizards-2024-25-city-edition-shorts-leak-on-social-media/basketball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Continuing today’s theme, the Phoenix Suns and Washington Wizards’ new City Edition shorts were leaked on social media on Friday morning.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 18:43:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dakota Johnson Flaunts Engagement Ring After False Report of Chris Martin Split</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/18/dakota-johnson-engagement-ring-chris-martin/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Dakota Johnson's giving rumors she's single the finger ... her ring finger, which she's waving for all to see that she's still wearing her engagement ring from Chris Martin. DJ was out in Malibu with pals Jeremy Allen White and Blake Lee, and when…</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 06:52:56 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>