<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 06:37:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Spies in Historical Fiction from 1860 to 1975</title><link>https://bookriot.com/historical-spy-novels/</link><description>Grab your spyglasses and your trick pens!</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Porsche 911 Carrera T Road Test: What's 911 minus 718?</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/04/22/porsche-911-carrera-t-road-test/</link><description>Filed under:
					    Porsche,Coupe,Luxury,Performance,Road Tests
Continue reading Porsche 911 Carrera T Road Test: What's 911 minus 718?
Porsche 911 Carrera T Road Test: What's 911 minus 718? originally appeared on Autoblog on Mon, 22 Apr 2024 06:00:00 EDT.  Please see our terms for use of feeds.
Permalink | 
						Email this | 
					    Comments</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Emirates CEO issues apology after Dubai flood chaos; says airline has 30,000 suitcases to return</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/04/22/emirates-airline-ceo-issues-apology-after-dubai-flood-chaos.html</link><description>"We know our response has been far from perfect. We acknowledge and understand the frustration of our customers," Emirates Airline CEO Tim Clark wrote.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 11:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 552</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-552/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-552</link><description>When you are searching for a job, you will inevitably run into unexpected scenarios. You will have questions, experience self-doubt and even feel discouraged. You’ll also experience great wins, meet wonderful people and discover new things about yourself. That’s the roller-coaster of job search. Consider Summary Sunday your resource for getting questions answered and showing […]
The post Summary Sunday: Issue 552 appeared first on Career Sherpa.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 11:37:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Creamy Lemon Parmesan Chicken</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/creamy-lemon-parmesan-chicken/</link><description>Creamy Lemon Parmesan Chicken is an incredible restaurant-quality meal you can make in under 30 minutes. Tender, juicy chicken is…</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 13:00:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Golden Pothos – Plant Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/golden-pothos-plant-care-guide/</link><description>Pothos are easily our #1 favorite houseplant and the golden pothos is by far the most popular variety. They’re loved by beginners and plant experts alike because they’re affordable, attractive, and easy to care for. They’re quick-growing plants with beautiful trailing vines that add loads of life and color to any space. We have pothos in nearly EVERY room of our house!
There are over a dozen kinds of pothos (Epipremnum aureum), most of which share similar characteristics and care instructions as the golden pothos. You can read more about other varieties we love, like the marble queen pothos and neon pothos.
Golden Pothos Quick Facts
Here’s what you need to know about your golden pothos at a glance:

Latin name: Epipremnum aureum
Common names: Golden pothos, devil’s ivy, devil’s vine, hunter’s rove
Mistaken for: Neon pothos, marble queen pothos
Light: Prefers medium, indirect light but is low-light tolerant
Watering: Every 7-10 days during its growing season, or if the soil is dry &amp; leaves are drooping
Soil: Standard potting mix as long as it drains well
Ideal Humidity: Average household humidity, ideally 50-70%
Ideal Temperature: 65-85 degrees
Cold Hardiness: USDA Zones 10-12

What Is A Golden Pothos?
Continue reading Golden Pothos – Plant Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Strapless For Spring</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/04/strapless-for-spring/</link><description>Outfit Details: The Wolf Gang Dress, Dior Sandals, Prada Sunglasses, Gucci Bag (similar here and here) Strapless tops and dresses for spring are the season’s…
The post Strapless For Spring appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 05:00:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>8 Grim and Gruesome Medical Horror Books</title><link>https://bookriot.com/medical-horror-books/</link><description>Experiments going badly, parasitic creatures, piles of dead bodies... what's not to love?</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2024 Aston Martin DBX707 gets light updates, becomes only DBX</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/04/21/2024-aston-martin-dbx707-update-refresh-interior/</link><description>Filed under:
					    Aston Martin,Crossover,SUV,Luxury,Performance
Continue reading 2024 Aston Martin DBX707 gets light updates, becomes only DBX
2024 Aston Martin DBX707 gets light updates, becomes only DBX originally appeared on Autoblog on Sun, 21 Apr 2024 19:01:00 EDT.  Please see our terms for use of feeds.
Permalink | 
						Email this | 
					    Comments</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 00:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pro-China party reportedly wins big in the Maldives, likely accelerating its shift away from India</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/04/22/maldives-elections-pro-china-party-wins-landslide-victory.html</link><description>The outcome is widely expected to accelerate the Indian Ocean archipelago's shift toward China and away from its traditional ally of India.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 11:14:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you</link><description>While a little competition in the workplace might help bring out the best in everyone involved, an atmosphere rooted in envy, fear, or jealousy can do the exact opposite. This post will help you recognize signs that your coworker is threatened by you, and help you navigate the situation. 1. They Don’t Want You Involved […]
The post 10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You appeared first on Career Sherpa.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:07:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Swiss Meringue Buttercream</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/swiss-meringue-buttercream/</link><description>The most delicious Swiss Meringue Buttercream is easy to make with just 5 simple ingredients! It whips up deliciously light…</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Neon Pothos – Plant Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/neon-pothos-plant-care-guide/</link><description>Our top recommendation for an easy, starter houseplant? Pothos, pothos, pothos! They’re low-stress, high-impact, and fast-growing vines that are great for both beginners and experts. The golden pothos may be the most common variety but don’t overlook its more vibrant cousin: the neon pothos. We’ve got several neon pothos in our home, and they’re beautiful and so easy! So here’s all you need to know before you get your own.
There are over a dozen varieties of pothos, most of which share similar care instructions to the neon pothos. You can read more about other pothos we love, like the golden pothos and marble queen pothos.
Neon Pothos Quick Facts
Here’s what you need to know about your neon pothos at a glance:

Latin name: Epipremnum aureum ‘Neon’ 
Common names: Neon pothos, neon devil’s ivy
Mistaken for: Golden pothos
Light: Prefers bright, indirect light but is low-light tolerant
Watering: Every 7-10 days during its growing season, or if the soil is dry &amp; leaves are drooping
Soil: Standard potting mix as long as it drains well
Ideal Humidity: Average household humidity, ideally 50-70%
Ideal Temperature: 65-85 degrees
Cold Hardiness: USDA Zones 10-12

What Is A Neon Pothos?
Continue reading Neon Pothos – Plant Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 19:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Art Of Date Night Dressing</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/04/j-mclaughlin/</link><description>Outfit Details: J.McLaughlin Top, Pants &amp; Bag Thank you to J.McLaughlin for sponsoring this post. Spring is the perfect season…
The post The Art Of Date Night Dressing appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:00:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Riot’s Deals of the Day for April 21, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/book-riots-deals-of-the-day-for-april-21-2024/</link><description>Earth's last storyteller, four generations of magical Black women, a story steeped in Cherokee myth and history, and more of today's best book deals.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MotoGP races to capture a new U.S. audience the way F1 did</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/04/21/motogp-races-to-capture-a-new-u-s-audience-the-way-f1-did/</link><description>Filed under:
					    Motorsports,Motorcycle,Racing Vehicles
Continue reading MotoGP races to capture a new U.S. audience the way F1 did
MotoGP races to capture a new U.S. audience the way F1 did originally appeared on Autoblog on Sun, 21 Apr 2024 13:00:00 EDT.  Please see our terms for use of feeds.
Permalink | 
						Email this | 
					    Comments</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Here's why FEMA has spent about $4 billion to help destroy flood-prone homes</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/04/22/why-fema-has-spent-4-billion-to-help-destroy-flood-prone-homes.html</link><description>Floodplain buyouts allow homeowners to move out of harm's way and help the community create open space that can collect flood waters to protect other homes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 11:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 551</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-551/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-551</link><description>Job search requires writing and marketing skills. It also requires strong verbal communication. If these skills are not part of your normal work function, you’ll want some help. That’s what this week’s Summary Sunday is all about. There’s no doubt that LinkedIn is one of THE most powerful tools in your career toolbox. It contains […]
The post Summary Sunday: Issue 551 appeared first on Career Sherpa.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 11:37:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Meal Plan #1</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/weekly-menu-plan-1/</link><description>It’s week one of meal planning! Here you will find a free weekly menu plan with a printable shopping list.…</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Marble Queen Pothos – Plant Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/marble-queen-pothos-plant-care-guide/</link><description>Even though the marble queen isn’t the most popular pothos variety, it’s one of our personal favorites! Like all pothos plants, they’re a perfect starter houseplant because they’re resilient, low-maintenance, and fast-growing. Plus, we think it has some of prettiest leaves of all.
There are over a dozen kinds of pothos, most of which share similar characteristics and care instructions as the marble queen. You can read more about other pothos we love, like the golden pothos and neon pothos.
Marble Queen Quick Facts
Here’s what you need to know about your marble queen pothos at a glance:

Latin name: Epipremnum aureum ‘Marble Queen’ 
Common names: Marble queen pothos, marble pothos, pothos marble
Mistaken for: Golden pothos, snow queen pothos
Light: Prefers medium, indirect light but is low-light tolerant
Watering: Every 7-10 days during its growing season, or if the soil is dry &amp; leaves are drooping
Soil: Standard potting mix as long as it drains well
Ideal Humidity: Average household humidity, ideally 50-70%
Ideal Temperature: 60-85 degrees
Cold Hardiness: USDA Zones 10-12

What Is A Marble Queen Pothos?
Continue reading Marble Queen Pothos – Plant Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 18:39:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Warmer Days Of Spring</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/04/warmer-days-of-spring/</link><description>Outfit Details: Erdem Dress Thank you to Nordstrom for sponsoring this post. My wardrobe is fully embracing the warmth of…
The post Warmer Days Of Spring appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 05:00:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Riot’s YA Book Deals for April 20, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/book-riots-ya-book-deals-for-april-20-2024/</link><description>This weekend, snag excellent YA reads across a variety of genres in this megalist of deals under $5.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Junkyard Gem: 2006 Mitsubishi Raider DuroCross 4WD</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/04/21/junkyard-gem-2006-mitsubishi-raider-durocross-4wd/</link><description>Filed under:
					    Mitsubishi,Automotive History,Truck
Continue reading Junkyard Gem: 2006 Mitsubishi Raider DuroCross 4WD
Junkyard Gem: 2006 Mitsubishi Raider DuroCross 4WD originally appeared on Autoblog on Sun, 21 Apr 2024 12:00:00 EDT.  Please see our terms for use of feeds.
Permalink | 
						Email this | 
					    Comments</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ukraine is given a reprieve by the U.S., but faces race against the clock over weapons supplies</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/04/22/ukraine-given-reprieve-with-us-aid-package-after-months-of-delays.html</link><description>Time is of the essence for Ukraine, which has been pleading for more air defense systems, artillery and ammunition to turn the tide in the war.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>15 Ways to Own Digital Terrain</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/15-ways-to-own-digital-terrain/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=15-ways-to-own-digital-terrain</link><description>It is now no longer optional…you must have an online presence! Your career stability and your job search demand it. Here are some tips to help you begin claiming digital terrain and brand it with your unique messaging!   Why Should You Own Digital Terrain? You need to stake a claim by owning turf on the […]
The post 15 Ways to Own Digital Terrain appeared first on Career Sherpa.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 15:56:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lemon Crinkle Cookies</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/lemon-crinkle-cookies/</link><description>Lemon crinkle cookies are thick, soft pillows of lemon deliciousness! They have a refreshing flavor with an irresistible chewy texture.…</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Snake Plant – Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/snake-plant-care-guide/</link><description>If you’re someone who thinks you can’t keep a plant alive – this plant will prove you wrong! In fact, you’ve probably seen one at a doctor’s office, home improvement store, or hotel lobby because they’re so low maintenance. Thanks to being so easy to care for and widely liked, they’re a great option for anyone who wants a low-effort plant. So today we’ll share why serial plant-killers and seasoned plant lovers all love this spear-shaped beauty.
There are dozens of varieties of snake plants, but today we’ll mainly be talking about the most popular variety: Dracaena trifasciata ‘Laurentii.’ The Laurentii refers to the specific variant of this species seen in these photos. They’re identifiable by their stiff, sword-like leaves with bright yellow edges.
Snake Plant: Quick Facts
Here’s what you need to know about your snake plant at a glance:

Latin name: Dracaena Trifasciata (formerly Sansevieria Trifasciata)
Common names: Snake Plant, Mother-in-Law’s Tongue, Devil’s Tongue, Saint George’s Sword, Vipers Bowstring Hemp, Spear Plant
Native to: West Africa 
Light: Prefers medium, indirect light
Watering: About every 2 weeks or whenever the soil is dry
Soil: Well-drained soil such as a cactus, palm, or succulent mix
Ideal Humidity: Average household humidity
Ideal Temperature: 70-90 degrees
Cold Hardiness: USDA Zones 9-11

Benefits Of A Snake Plant
Beyond being attractive and low maintenance, snake plants are also popular houseplants for their health benefits.
Continue reading Snake Plant – Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 00:41:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spring Sets</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/04/spring-sets/</link><description>Outfit Details: Alexis Top &amp; Skirt (dress version here), Chanel Bag, Dior Sandals, Stella Kids Dress on C &amp; M I have always loved wearing matching sets, appreciating…
The post Spring Sets appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 05:00:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Riot’s Deals of the Day for April 20, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/book-riots-deals-of-the-day-for-april-20-2024/</link><description>A love letter to vintage horror, the trial of Lizzie Borden, a Viking enthusiast's quest to become legendary, and more of today's best book deals.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Close to the ground and pretty to behold, lowriders get museum honors</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/04/21/close-to-the-ground-and-pretty-to-behold-lowriders-get-museum-honors/</link><description>Filed under:
					    Design/Style,Chevrolet,Automotive History
Continue reading Close to the ground and pretty to behold, lowriders get museum honors
Close to the ground and pretty to behold, lowriders get museum honors originally appeared on Autoblog on Sun, 21 Apr 2024 11:00:00 EDT.  Please see our terms for use of feeds.
Permalink | 
						Email this | 
					    Comments</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Monday's analyst calls: Amazon a top pick into earnings, Apple price target cut</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/04/22/analyst-calls-all-the-market-moving-wall-street-chatter-from-monday.html</link><description>Monday's calls included a price target cut for one of the biggest tech companies and Goldman Sachs getting bullish on an e-commerce giant ahead of earnings.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 10:46:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 550</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-550/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-550</link><description>Job search strategies change based on the economy, the level and type of work you are looking for, and your personal situation. In other words, there’s no absolute right way for everyone. However, there are best practices you should know about. In this week’s Summary Sunday, you’ll learn about: I carefully curate these articles and […]
The post Summary Sunday: Issue 550 appeared first on Career Sherpa.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 10:44:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Grinder Sliders</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/grinder-sliders/</link><description>The classic grinder sandwich made into sliders to share! You’ve got Hawaiian rolls topped with layers of pepperoni, salami, turkey,…</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Weekend In Palm Springs With Kids</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/palm-springs-with-kids/</link><description>Palm Springs, California may not scream “kid-friendly destination” but we recently had THE BEST vacation there with our family (our kids are 9 and 13). So here’s a quick rundown of our favorite must-see attractions in Palm Springs as well as info about where we stayed, what we ate, and what we’re excited to check out next time. Because we definitely will be back!
Did I mention we also brought our nine-pound chihuahua with us? So most of our suggestions are dog-friendly too!
Why Vacation With Kids In Palm Springs?
We chose Palm Springs for a lot of reasons. First, our East Coast-born kids had never been to California! Of course, there are lots of options for California vacations. But we wanted to avoid the hustle of a bigger city like Los Angeles or San Francisco, and we liked the idea of introducing them to the unfamiliar desert geography.
Continue reading A Weekend In Palm Springs With Kids at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 18:51:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Swimsuit Season</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/04/swimsuit-season/</link><description>Outfit Details: Missoni Swimsuit (similar here, two piece here), Prada Sunglasses, Marysia Top and Bottoms on C &amp; M As…
The post Swimsuit Season appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 05:00:31 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>