<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 07:11:10 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>BiggerNews: 2024’s Cheaper, Better, Cash-Flowing “Sleeper” Investment</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-1014</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Are new construction homes a good investment right now? Well, that depends. If you want a lower price for a property in a better condition, with a lower mortgage rate […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 10:00:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Google faces provisional antitrust charges in UK for ‘self-preferencing’ its ad exchange</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/06/google-faces-provisional-antitrust-charges-in-uk-for-self-preferencing-its-ad-exchange/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>More antitrust woes for Google. The U.K’.s competition watchdog said on Friday that it suspects the company of adtech antitrust abuses. The tech giant will now have a chance to respond to the provisional findings before the regulator reaches a final decision. Confirmed violations of U.K. competition law can lead to corrective orders and fines […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 11:41:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Serious Case of Prison Visit Blues</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/09/06/tariq-maqbool-prison-visit-pandemic-covid-19</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Tariq MaQbool reflects on disruptive COVID-era visitation restrictions that remain in effect at New Jersey State Prison.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rookie Reply: Buying Your First Rental &amp; the BEST Properties for Appreciation</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-454</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>You’re trying to buy your first rental property, but you keep losing out to buyers making cash offers and waiving inspections. Are you doing something wrong? In this episode, we’ll […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 10:00:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Karo is a to-do app that lets you assign tasks to your friends and family</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/06/karo-is-a-to-do-app-that-lets-you-assign-tasks-to-your-friends-and-family/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>You can build a reminder and task management system for yourself, and use a service that works for your team. But it might not be easy to get your family members or friends to use the same task management app. iOS app Karo (which means “do it” in Hindi) aims to solve the problem even […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 11:19:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Efforts to Cut Long Prison Sentences Have Stalled</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/31/wisconsin-california-sentence-prison</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Crime victim advocates and conservative groups are resisting moves to revisit “truth-in-sentencing” laws.</description><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Happens if High Expenses Extinguish Your FIRE?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-561</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>You did it; you achieved FIRE! After over a decade of hard work, you’ve reached financial independence and can retire early. You’re making more money than you spend from passive […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 07:01:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elon Musk’s X could still face sanctions for training Grok on Europeans’ data</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/06/elon-musks-x-could-still-face-sanctions-for-training-grok-on-europeans-data/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Earlier this week, the EU’s lead privacy regulator ended its court proceeding related to how X processed user data to train its Grok AI chatbot, but the saga isn’t over yet for the Elon Musk-owned social media platform formerly known as Twitter. The Irish Data Protection Commission (DPC) has confirmed to TechCrunch that it’s received […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 10:33:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How a Massachusetts Cop Allegedly Groomed, Controlled and Killed Sandra Birchmore</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/30/police-explorer-sexual-abuse-massachusetts-birchmore</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Matthew Farwell met her in a police Explorer program. Prosecutors say he abused her for years before she became pregnant and he killed her.</description><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Your Ultimate Guide to Preparing for BPCON</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/ultimate-bpcon-guide</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Everything you need to make the most out of your trip to BPCON!</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 14:43:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Telegram quietly enables users to report private chats to moderators after founder’s arrest</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/05/telegram-quietly-enables-users-to-report-private-chats-to-moderators-after-founders-arrest/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Telegram has quietly updated its policy to allow users to report private chats to its moderators following the arrest of founder Pavel Durov in France last month over “crimes committed by third parties” on the platform. The messaging app, which serves nearly 1 billion monthly active users, has long maintained a reputation for minimal supervision […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 03:32:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>5 Things to Know About How Survivors Get Incarcerated for Their Abusers’ Crimes</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/28/accomplice-liability-laws-what-to-know</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Little-known laws allow people to be punished for crimes they didn’t directly commit. Survivors of domestic violence are especially vulnerable.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Job Numbers Turn Out to Be Overinflated, Will the Fed Make a Hard Pivot?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-249</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>One startup is aiming to end traditional real estate commissions for good. Jobs numbers get their most significant downgrade in over a decade, forcing the Fed to rethink its rate-cutting […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 10:00:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘Stop harassing Starlink,’ SpaceX president tells Brazilian judge</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/05/stop-harassing-starlink-spacex-president-tells-brazilian-judge/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>SpaceX President Gwynne Shotwell made a public plea to one of Brazil’s top judicial figures on Thursday, asking him to “please stop harassing Starlink” amid the ongoing battle in the country against Elon Musk’s social media business X. Musk has been engaged in a months-long dispute with the Brazilian courts, which have been waging a […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 23:55:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How a Drop in Border Crossings May Change the Presidential Campaign</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/24/kamala-harris-dnc-border-donald-trump</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>The Democratic National Convention sought to address one of the party’s biggest weaknesses with voters.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>