<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 22:36:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Your Favorite Queer Books of May</title><link>https://bookriot.com/your-favorite-queer-books-of-may/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/pole-position.png</image_url><description>Because you need a "Read Queer All Year" raccoon tee shirt.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Junkyard Gem: 1999 Pontiac Firebird Coupe</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/06/01/junkyard-gem-1999-pontiac-firebird/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/23105427/99-1999-Pontiac-Firebird-in-Colorado-junkyard-photo-by-Murilee-Martin.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Pontiac , Automotive History , Coupe , Classics Continue reading Junkyard Gem: 1999 Pontiac Firebird Coupe Junkyard Gem: 1999 Pontiac Firebird Coupe originally appeared on Autoblog on Sat, 1 Jun 2024 13:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>D.C. ethics board recommends Rudy Giuliani be disbarred</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/06/01/dc-ethics-board-recommends-rudy-giuliani-be-disbarred.html</link><description>The recommendation comes after Giuliani represented Donald Trump in a Pennsylvania court case that sought to overturn the state’s 2020 election results.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 21:26:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sharing Fun Facts About Yourself: 22 Examples &amp; Ideas</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/fun-facts-about-me/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fun-facts-about-me</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Asking to share some fun facts about yourself is a common icebreaker that’s used during job interviews. But the quality of your answer still matters. This guide will help you come up with some ideas for crafting a response that starts the interview on a good note. Table of contents Ideas for Sharing Fun Facts […] The post Sharing Fun Facts About Yourself: 22 Examples &amp; Ideas appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 15:26:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Children’s digital media exposure as a backdrop for multilingual learning</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/childrens-digital-media-exposure-as-a-backdrop-for-multilingual-learning/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=childrens-digital-media-exposure-as-a-backdrop-for-multilingual-learning</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Multilingual children use digital media regularly, in all their home languages. Digital media use may affect multilingual children’s early language learning by reducing opportunities for back-and-forth conversations with adults. This finding is similar to results of studies of digital media and language learning for children learning only one language. When using […] The post Children’s digital media exposure as a backdrop for multilingual learning appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 20:27:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Buffalo Chicken Enchiladas</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/buffalo-chicken-enchiladas/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>A new enchilada is in town! Get ready for the bold flavors in these buffalo chicken enchiladas! Chicken enchiladas loaded…</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Best Air Purifying Plants</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/best-air-purifying-plants/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>We love any excuse to buy more plants, and you may have heard they can improve your home’s indoor air quality. But before you blow your paycheck in the name of a healthier home, let’s dive deeper into plants’ air purifying powers. We’ll share which plants we recommend and what benefits you can actually expect from them. We’ve heard for years about how plants act as natural air filters for your home. So let’s dive a little deeper, shall we? 7 Air Purifying Plants If you just came here for a list, our favorite air purifying houseplants are bulleted below. The best part is these are all beautiful, low-maintenance plants. Many also appear on our best low-light indoor plants list too! Dracaena (including Corn Plant ) Snake Plant Aglaonema English Ivy Pothos Bamboo Palm Spider Plant There are certainly more that could be included here, but we narrowed it to the ones that are most often cited by experts AND the plants that we think look best too. Continue reading Best Air Purifying Plants at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 14:15:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Beach Day Basics</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/beach-day-basics/</link><description>Outfit Details: Show Me Your Mumu Coverup, LSpace Bikini, Janessa Leone Hat, Miu Miu Sandals, Illesteva Sunglasses, Hanna Andersson Set on C &amp; M, Amazon… The post Beach Day Basics appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 05:00:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Most Popular Stories of the Week</title><link>https://bookriot.com/best-of-book-riot-june-1-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/spelling-bee-trophy-winner-featured.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>Roll into your weekend with a look at Book Riot’s most popular stories. 🚀 Take a blast to the past ...</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2025 Cadillac XT4 drops base trim, adds standard equipment</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/06/01/2025-cadillac-xt4-drops-base-trim-adds-standard-equipment/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/29161944/2024_cadillac_xt41.png</image_url><description>Filed under: Cadillac , Car Buying , Crossover , SUV , Luxury Continue reading 2025 Cadillac XT4 drops base trim, adds standard equipment 2025 Cadillac XT4 drops base trim, adds standard equipment originally appeared on Autoblog on Sat, 1 Jun 2024 12:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Retired U.S. Navy admiral charged in bribery scheme with tech CEOs for $500,000 salary</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/06/01/retired-us-navy-admiral-charged-in-bribery-scheme-with-tech-ceos.html</link><description>Robert Burke started working as a senior partner at Next Jump with a starting annual salary of $500,000 and 100,000 stock options in 2022, the DOJ said.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 18:58:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 553</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-553/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-553</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Tools and technology change rapidly. Yet as wonderful as technology can be, it doesn’t replace the need for human connection through interactions. Keep this in mind as you are searching for a new job. It’s your human connections that often open doors! In this week’s collection of news and tips for job seekers, you’ll find: […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 553 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 12:19:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>La exposición de los niños a los medios digitales como contexto para el aprendizaje multilingüe</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/la-exposicion-de-los-ninos-a-los-medios-digitales-como-contexto-para-el-aprendizaje-multilingue/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=la-exposicion-de-los-ninos-a-los-medios-digitales-como-contexto-para-el-aprendizaje-multilingue</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Puntos clave para los cuidadores Los niños multilingües usan frecuentemente los medios digitales y los usan en los distintos idiomas que se hablan en su hogar. El uso de los medios digitales (por ej., la televisión, el computador o los “smartphones”) puede afectar negativamente el desarrollo del lenguaje en los niños que son multilingües porque […] The post La exposición de los niños a los medios digitales como contexto para el aprendizaje multilingüe appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 20:26:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Roasted Lemon Parmesan Garlic Asparagus</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/roasted-lemon-parmesan-garlic-asparagus/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>You’ll love the combination of flavors in this roasted lemon parmesan garlic asparagus! It’s a quick and easy side dish…</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Weekend In New Orleans With Kids</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/new-orleans-with-kids/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Since our travel guides to Charleston with kids and Palm Springs with kids have elicited requests for more travel ideas with kids, we’re back with an overdue recap of our 3-night trip to New Orleans. We’d never been to The Big Easy before and were impressed by how family-friendly the city is. It’s not all booze, beads, and Bourbon Street! So here’s a look at where we stayed, what we did, and what we’re excited to do next time we go back – because we will definitely go back! The four of us (well, five if you count our chihuahua!) went to NOLA for 3 nights in November of 2022. At the time, our kids were 8 and 12 years old. So unfortunately we can’t vouch for our suggestions being a good fit for toddlers or younger children. Although I’m sure ours would’ve loved the Louisiana Children’s Museum and Storyland playground back in the day! Continue reading A Weekend In New Orleans With Kids at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 17:17:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summer Stones</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/summer-stones/</link><description>Outfit Details: Parterre Top, Horror Vacui Skirt, JB x JB Necklace &amp; Jenna Blake Necklace, Chanel Bag, Irene Neuwirth Earrings (similar, less expensive here), Chanel Heels Infusing vibrant jewelry… The post Summer Stones appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 05:00:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Week in Review: June 1, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/today-in-books-june-1-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/person-holding-newspaper.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>Catch up on Book Riot's news coverage, including a look at the latest bestsellers, chilling editorial cartoons about book banning, and more.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kia's Australian division wants a body-on-frame SUV to take on the Land Cruiser</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/06/01/kia-australian-division-wants-a-body-on-frame-suv-to-take-on-the-land-cruiser/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/04/23085749/666339.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Kia , SUV , Off-Road Vehicles Continue reading Kia's Australian division wants a body-on-frame SUV to take on the Land Cruiser Kia's Australian division wants a body-on-frame SUV to take on the Land Cruiser originally appeared on Autoblog on Sat, 1 Jun 2024 10:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Boeing, NASA cancel Starliner launch attempt scheduled Sunday after failed Saturday take-off</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/06/01/boeings-starliner-first-launch-with-nasa-astronauts.html</link><description>Boeing aimed to launch its first Starliner flight with astronauts on board on Saturday but called it off minutes before take-off.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 16:29:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 552</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-552/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-552</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>When you are searching for a job, you will inevitably run into unexpected scenarios. You will have questions, experience self-doubt and even feel discouraged. You’ll also experience great wins, meet wonderful people and discover new things about yourself. That’s the roller-coaster of job search. Consider Summary Sunday your resource for getting questions answered and showing […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 552 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 11:37:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Becoming Confident in Parenting Abilities</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/confidence-in-parenting/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=confidence-in-parenting</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Parental self-efficacy (i.e., a parent’s confidence in their own ability to care for their infant and respond to the infant’s needs) is the first step to a good parent-child relationship. Research has explored the development of maternal self-efficacy beginning during pregnancy and continuing after childbirth. Mothers who have previous childbirth and […] The post Becoming Confident in Parenting Abilities appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 10:06:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Meal Plan #6</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/weekly-menu-plan-6/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Get ready for some seriously tasty meals with Weekly Meal Plan #6! I’ve got chicken, shrimp, and fresh salads on…</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>9 Easy Low-Light Indoor Plants</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/easy-low-light-indoor-plants/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>I used to think every houseplant needed a sunny corner or bright windowsill to thrive. But it turns out many of our favorite go-to houseplants do just fine in shady corners and low-light locations. So before you write off your house as too dark to sustain plant life, check out this list of the best indoor plants for low light. You might be surprised at how many good options there are! Our upstairs family room is the brightest room we’ve ever owned thanks to big unobstructed windows on all 4 sides. But most of our indoor plants live downstairs, where we get far less natural light. Luckily, that hasn’t stopped us from growing our collection of happy healthy houseplants. 9 Houseplants That Don’t Need A Lot Of Light Here are our favorite low-light indoor plants. We list a lot more info on them below, but here’s a quick list to bring on your next trip to the plant store: Snake Plant ZZ Plant Pothos Heartleaf Philodendron English Ivy Aglaonema Cast Iron Plant Monstera Parlor Palm Perhaps our favorite part of this list is that these aren’t ugly “consolation plants” that people begrudgingly buy for dark homes. Continue reading 9 Easy Low-Light Indoor Plants at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 14:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sea Star</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/sea-star/</link><description>Outfit Details: Sir Top, Zimmermann Skirt (love this similar dress too), Zara Necklace (similar here), Ciao Lucia Bag, Stella Kids Dress on M Living by the coast, we feel fortunate… The post Sea Star appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 21:15:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Riot’s YA Book Deals of the Day for June 1, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/book-riots-ya-book-deals-of-the-day-for-june-1-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/ya-deals-060124.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>Kick off your June reading with these fantastic YA book deals!</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 14:36:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amazon Prime Day 2024: Early deals to shop now, and what to expect</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/article/amazon-prime-day-2024-early-deals-and-what-to-expect/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/29125548/Amazon-Prime-Day-Featured.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Commerce Continue reading Amazon Prime Day 2024: Early deals to shop now, and what to expect Amazon Prime Day 2024: Early deals to shop now, and what to expect originally appeared on Autoblog on Sat, 1 Jun 2024 08:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The SEC ruling on Ethereum ETFs could mark a historic shift in crypto investing</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/06/01/major-cryptocurrency-shift-due-to-sec-ethereum-etf-ruling-vaneck-ceo.html</link><description>The VanEck CEO digs into the preliminary approval of his firm's Ethereum ETF and what the decision means for crypto investors.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>While a little competition in the workplace might help bring out the best in everyone involved, an atmosphere rooted in envy, fear, or jealousy can do the exact opposite. This post will help you recognize signs that your coworker is threatened by you, and help you navigate the situation. 1. They Don’t Want You Involved […] The post 10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:07:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A case for public preschool: New study reveals preschool benefits to be longer-lasting and substantial</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/benefits-of-public-preschool/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=benefits-of-public-preschool</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Preschool lays a foundation for elementary school students to succeed. In the United States, as children approach kindergarten entry, it is increasingly common for 4-year-olds to be in non-parental group care and education, often in a center- or school-based setting where they can learn alongside peers. For children from low-income communities, […] The post A case for public preschool: New study reveals preschool benefits to be longer-lasting and substantial appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 08:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Twinkie Cake</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/twinkie-cake/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>This Twinkie cake is a fun dessert that brings the classic snack cake to life. With its fluffy vanilla sponge…</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/how-to-remove-wallpaper/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Wallpaper has made a big comeback as a trendy home design choice. But despite its resurgence, there are still plenty of us dealing with dingy, dated, or downright ugly old wallpaper we don’t want. In our old home, we had to remove wallpaper in so many rooms: the kitchen, the dining room, the foyer, and two different bathrooms! As we traveled from room to room removing wallpaper, we tested 4 different methods, and today we’ll share what we learned. Removing wallpaper doesn’t require special tools or lots of money. It’s a totally doable project for any homeowner. However, it can be a tedious process that can take elbow grease and patience, depending on the size of your room and the stubbornness of your wallpaper. But having removed several rooms worth of decades-old wallpaper, we can confidently say it’s worth the effort! You can also check out more before and afters of our once-wallpapered rooms. Continue reading How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:21:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>La Vie En Rose</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/la-vie-en-rose/</link><description>Outfit Details: Erdem Dress, JB x Jennifer Behr Necklace (worn as bracelet) &amp; Earrings, Larroude Sandals, Sea NY Dress on C… The post La Vie En Rose appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 05:00:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Riot’s Deals of the Day for June 1, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/book-riots-deals-of-the-day-for-june-1-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/deals-060124.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>Resurrected mammoths, forbidden love, a sizzling workplace rom-com, and more of today's best book deals.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tesla recalling 125,000 cars over seatbelt warning failure</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/06/01/tesla-recalling-125000-cars-over-seatbelt-warning-failure/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/31145428/Updated-Tesla-Model-S3.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Recalls , Tesla Continue reading Tesla recalling 125,000 cars over seatbelt warning failure Tesla recalling 125,000 cars over seatbelt warning failure originally appeared on Autoblog on Sat, 1 Jun 2024 07:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Honolulu is the western metro area where 1-bedroom rent has gone up the most in a year</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/06/01/5-metro-areas-in-the-west-where-1-bedroom-rent-has-increased-the-most.html</link><description>CNBC Make It analyzed rent estimate data from Apartment List for April 2023 to April 2024, filtering metro areas by those with at least 500,000 residents.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 551</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-551/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-551</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Job search requires writing and marketing skills. It also requires strong verbal communication. If these skills are not part of your normal work function, you’ll want some help. That’s what this week’s Summary Sunday is all about. There’s no doubt that LinkedIn is one of THE most powerful tools in your career toolbox. It contains […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 551 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 11:37:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fathers’ views on family and work after COVID-19 lockdowns</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/fathers-views-on-family-and-work-after-covid-19-lockdowns/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fathers-views-on-family-and-work-after-covid-19-lockdowns</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Fathers often want to be present for their children and contribute to household tasks, but they can lack opportunities and confidence; they may see themselves as “helpers” instead of parents. Australian fathers in our small study reported that they spent more time with their children during the COVID-19 lockdowns, and they […] The post Fathers’ views on family and work after COVID-19 lockdowns appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ham and Cheese Croissant Casserole</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/ham-and-cheese-croissant-casserole/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>This Ham and Cheese Croissant Casserole is filled with comforting flavors of croissants, eggs, ham and plenty of melty cheese.…</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aglaonema Plant – Complete Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/aglaonema-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Aglaonema, also called the Chinese Evergreen Plant, is an easy-care houseplant that lives happily in many lighting conditions – even a dark corner of our daughter’s room. There are dozens of different Aglaonema varieties, most with large tropical foliage and colors ranging from silvery-green, red, and even vibrant pink. They’re also tough to kill, so they’re a great option for forgetful plant owners or anyone looking for an easy win in the plant department. These truly have been very low maintenance for us. We purchased our two Aglaonemas (pronounced ag-lee-oh-neem-ah ) to put atop our daughter’s closet. It’s sometimes hard to distinguish different varieties, but we believe that’s an Aglaonema Silver (right) and either a Candy Cane or Princess Silver Queen (left). Aglaonema Quick Facts Here’s what you need to know about your Aglaonema at a glance: Latin name : Aglaonema is the genus under which there are 21 recognized species . Continue reading Aglaonema Plant – Complete Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:47:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Print Mixing For Summer</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/print-mixing-for-summer/</link><description>Outfit Details: Bode Top, Zimmermann Skirt (longer version here &amp; dress version here), Prada Sandals, Chanel Bag (similar here), Marisa Klass Necklace I’ve always embraced the art of… The post Print Mixing For Summer appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 18:30:52 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>