<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 17:28:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Burnley FC Leave Umbro, Sign Kit Deal With Castore</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/08/burnley-fc-leave-umbro-sign-kit-deal-with-castore/soccer/</link><description>Burnley currently in Premier League relegation zone; if they stay up, they'll be one of two clubs in England's top flight outfitted by Castore</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 17:46:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Vanderpump Rules' Cast Turns on Ariana Madix During Heated Finale</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/08/vanderpump-rules-finale-costars-turn-ariana-madix-film-apology-tom-sandoval/</link><description>Ariana Madix is on the outs with her "Vanderpump Rules" castmates, and it's all thanks to her cheating ex-bf Tom Sandoval ... or, at least, her continued reaction to his cheating. The season 11 finale for 'VPR' aired Tuesday and it took a shocking…</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 17:28:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Report: Brazil Could Ditch Nike as Kit Supplier After Receiving Massive Offer</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/07/report-brazil-could-ditch-nike-as-kit-supplier-after-receiving-massive-offer/soccer/</link><description>Brazilian news outlet reports CBF has received an offer worth more than five times what Nike currently pays them from either Adidas or Puma</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:29:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bette Midler Regrets Not Suing Lindsay Lohan Over Her Failed Sitcom</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/08/bette-midler-regrets-not-suing-lindsay-lohan-failed-sitcom/</link><description>Bette Midler is still upset with Lindsay Lohan for bailing on their 2000s sitcom "Bette" ... and apparently feels like she should've taken her to court for jumping ship. Bette opened up about the failed endeavor on David Duchovny's podcast "Fail…</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 17:28:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>USL’s Orange County Try to Capture Magic with New Cup Kit</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/06/usls-orange-county-sc-try-to-capture-some-magic-with-new-cup-kit/soccer/</link><description>Kit is inspired by designs worn in 1910s, when U.S. Open Cup started, and will be worn when OCSC takes on Loudoun United in Round of 32 on Tuesday, May 7</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 03:31:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Antonio Brown Backs Off Caitlin Clark, Attempts To Squash Beef W/ Heartfelt Message</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/08/antonio-brown-backs-off-caitlin-clark-attempts-to-squash-beef-w-heartfelt-message/</link><description>Antonio Brown is attempting to bury the hatchet with Caitlin Clark ... sending a heartfelt message to the WNBA star with the clear intent of moving on from their beef. If you missed it, the former Tampa Bay Buccaneers wideout kicked off a feud with…</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 17:28:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Panama Football Unveils New National Team Crest</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/06/panamanian-football-federation-unveils-new-national-team-crest/soccer/</link><description>Crest depicts a harpy eagle — the national bird of Panama — with each feather representing one of the country's 10 provinces</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Michael Douglas Says Sex Scene Intimacy Coordinators Bad for Hollywood</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/08/michael-douglas-sex-scene-intimacy-coordinators-bad-hollywood/</link><description>Michael Douglas doesn't get the need for intimacy coordinators ... calling the new production protocol unnecessary for sex scenes, which he used to handle by himself just fine. The actor made his stance clear in an interview with Radio Times, as…</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 17:28:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Snoop Dogg’s Gin &amp; Juice Brand Becomes Presenting Sponsor of Arizona Bowl</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/06/snoop-doggs-gin-juice-brand-becomes-presenting-sponsor-of-arizona-bowl/college/</link><description>The Arizona Bowl announced a multi-year partnership with 17-time Grammy Award winning artist Snoop Dogg that makes his alcohol brand, Gin &amp; Juice by Dre and Snoop, the game’s presenting sponsor.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 21:55:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Travis Kelce Has Never Met Jana Kramer, Doesn't Know Who She Is</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/08/travis-kelce-never-met-jana-kramer-always-drunk-podcast-slam/</link><description>Jana Kramer said Travis Kelce is "always drunk" and a bad influence on Taylor Swift -- but she might as well be J Lo to Mariah Carey for him ... 'cause he doesn't even know her. Sources connected to Travis tell TMZ ... he's taken aback by her…</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 17:28:18 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>