<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 15:28:10 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Seeing Greene: Insurance and Taxes Killed My Cash Flow, Should I Sell?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-965</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Want a quicker way to buy rental properties? One that takes less cash, less time, and is beginner-friendly? Then you’re in the right place! In this Seeing Greene, we’re talking […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 07:02:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TikTok acknowledges exploit targeting high-profile accounts</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/04/tiktok-acknowledges-exploit-targeting-high-profile-accounts/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The malicious attack appears to have involved malware transmitted through TikTok's DMs. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 19:33:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Jury of Trump’s Peers Weighs In</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/04/trump-verdict-felony-prisoners-perspectives</link><description>We asked 12 people with criminal convictions what they think of the verdict in Trump’s hush money trial.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 18:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Federal Experts Talk Bird Flu ‘What Ifs’ in WebMD Live Event</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/cold-and-flu/news/20240516/federal-experts-talk-bird-flu-what-ifs?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>WebMD brought together experts from four federal agencies to talk prevention, monitoring, and what the “what ifs” of bird flu might look like.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:50:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coast FI at 24 and a $99K Net Worth Thanks to a Few Years of Pure Hustle</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-534</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Could Coast FI be your BEST path to financial independence? Maybe you don’t want to retire early—not yet, at least. Hustle for a few years, invest your money, and watch […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 07:01:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI apocalypse? ChatGPT, Claude and Perplexity all went down at the same time</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/04/ai-apocalypse-chatgpt-claude-and-perplexity-are-all-down-at-the-same-time/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>It's unusual for three major AI providers to all be down at the same time, which could signal a broader infrastructure issues or internet-scale problem. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 18:38:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In St. Louis, a Racial Disparity in Whose Killings Get Solved</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/04/st-louis-police-unsolved-murders-race</link><description>In the past decade, police solved fewer than half of the homicide cases with Black victims and two-thirds of the cases with White ones.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What’s Next in Health Care for Older Adults: Questions and Answers With John Whyte, MD</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/blog-aging-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>As WebMD’s chief medical officer, John Whyte, MD, is in a unique position to see both the current state of medical care for America’s older adults and the way things are trending for the future. We asked him to share his insight on a few topics, along with a bit of advice.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:29:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Malta is a Hot, Stunning Island Market in Europe—Here’s How to Invest There</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/investing-in-malta-real-estate</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>While golden visas are sunsetting or significantly changing around Europe, there are still a few opportunities for Americans to buy international real estate, to live in or rent out, at […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 19:27:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A look at LoanSnap’s troubles and which neobanks are having a moment</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/04/a-look-at-loansnaps-troubles-and-which-neobanks-are-having-a-moment/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Welcome to TechCrunch Fintech! This week, we’re looking at LoanSnap’s woes, Nubank’s and Monzo’s positive milestones, a plethora of fintech fundraises and more! To get a roundup of TechCrunch’s biggest and most important fintech stories delivered to your inbox every Tuesday at 7:00 a.m. PT, subscribe here. The big story AI mortgage startup LoanSnap is […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 18:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How We Reported on Homicide Investigations in St. Louis</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/03/st-louis-police-unsolved-murders-methods</link><description>Getting and interpreting homicide clearance data involved litigation, complex analysis and patience.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Get the Care You Need in a COVID-19 World</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/covid-senior-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>What to expect at the doctor’s office, hospitals, and long-term care facilities, the future of telemedicine, and how to get the best care during COVID-19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 19:50:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Preferred Equity is an Alternative Asset Class You Can Buy in Real Estate Right Now—These Are the Four Types</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/four-types-of-preferred-equity-and-how-to-evaluate-each</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>“You’re investing in preferred equity? No thanks—I don’t invest in rescue capital!” I’ve heard this comment from prospective investors in different forms more than a few times in the past […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 19:16:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Databricks acquires Tabular to build a common data lakehouse standard</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/04/databricks-acquires-tabular-to-build-a-common-data-lakehouse-standard/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Databricks, the analytics and AI giant, has acquired data management company Tabular for an undisclosed sum. (CNBC reports that Databricks payed over $1 billion.) According to Tabular co-founder Ryan Blue, he and Tabular’s other two co-founders, Daniel Weeks and Jason Reid, will be joining Databricks in some capacity. There, they’ll work to unify Tabular’s and […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 18:04:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why 1,000 Homicides in St. Louis Remain Unsolved</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/03/st-louis-police-unsolved-murders</link><description>In one of America’s deadliest cities, police have struggled to solve killings due to staffing shortages, shoddy detective work and lack of community trust.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Personal Shopper: A Savvy Black Entrepreneur Guides You to Eczema-Friendly Clothes, Creams, Cosmetics, and More</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/savvy-black-entrepreneur-guides-eczema-friendly-clothes-creams-cosmetics?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>A savvy black entrepreneur guides you on an eczema-friendly shopping spree.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:54:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Much Should a State’s Landlord-Tenant Laws Affect Your Real Estate Investing Strategy?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/how-changing-landlord-tenant-laws-could-impact-your-real-estate-strategy</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>If you are a new investor with limited capital, having the misfortune of renting to a bad tenant in a tenant-friendly state can cripple you financially and put you off […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 18:47:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ChatGPT: Everything you need to know about the AI-powered chatbot</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/04/chatgpt-everything-to-know-about-the-ai-chatbot/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>ChatGPT, OpenAI’s text-generating AI chatbot, has taken the world by storm. What started as a tool to hyper-charge productivity through writing essays and code with short text prompts has evolved into a behemoth used by more than 92% of Fortune 500 companies for more wide-ranging needs. And that growth has propelled OpenAI itself into becoming […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Abortion’s Legal Landscape Post-Roe is Causing Fear and Confusion</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/01/abortion-supreme-court-roe-dobbs</link><description>We spoke with seven reproductive rights organizations — here’s what we found.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Behind the Spike in Colorectal Cancer Among Young Americans</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/colorectal-cancer/news/20240515/behind-the-spike-in-colorectal-cancer-cases?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Colorectal cancer cases increased a whopping 333% among 15- to 19-year-olds and 185% among 20- to 24-year-olds from 1999 to 2020.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:59:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>