<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 14:04:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Making $5K/Month Cash Flow from ONE Property (and Dodging a $100K Mistake)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-480</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Real estate investing could help you achieve your financial goals, whether it’s to make enough cash flow to replace your W2 income or build wealth for an early retirement. Like […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 10:00:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Trump’s win might mean for Elon Musk</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/11/06/what-trumps-win-might-mean-for-elon-musk/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Elon Musk — the billionaire CEO of Tesla, SpaceX, and xAI, and the owner of The Boring Company, Neuralink, and X — took a sharp swing to the right this election to support President-elect Donald Trump, using his vast wealth, influence, and megaphone on X to influence the outcome of the election. Musk’s support came […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 18:51:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump’s Immigration Lies Paid Off at the Polls</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/11/06/election-result-trump-harris-immigration-crime</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Thousands of Trump’s public statements indicate his re-election will bring a return to hardline immigration policies.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 10:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Can You Still Find On-Market, Cash Flowing Rentals in 2024? (We Found Some)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-1040</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Can you invest in real estate with just $75,000? And not only invest but can you find cash-flowing rentals in solid markets with long-term profit potential without spending six figures? […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 10:00:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Week in AI: It’s shockingly easy to make a Kamala Harris deepfake</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/11/06/this-week-in-ai-its-shockingly-easy-to-make-a-kamala-harris-deepfake/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Hiya, folks, welcome to TechCrunch’s regular AI newsletter. If you want this in your inbox every Wednesday, sign up here. It was shockingly easy to create a convincing Kamala Harris audio deepfake on Election Day. It cost me $5 and took less than two minutes, illustrating how cheap, ubiquitous generative AI has opened the floodgates to […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 18:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Election Day 2024: Where Criminal Justice Is On the Ballot</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/11/02/election-florida-ballot-california-criminal-justice</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>From reproductive rights to border enforcement and marijuana legalization, voters across the nation will weigh in on criminal justice issues.</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best (and Worst) States in the US to Retire in 2024 (FIRE Faster?)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-578</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Should you move to reach FIRE? And if so, where to? In this episode, we’re pulling back the curtain and revealing the best places to retire in the US in […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 10:00:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pinstripe wants to redefine the way online sellers sell secondhand clothing</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/11/06/pinstripe-wants-to-redefine-the-way-online-sellers-sell-secondhand-clothing/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Pinstripe aims to reimagine the secondhand market by offering sellers the opportunity to have both a digital storefront and a physical retail presence. Launched in June, the platform offers an alternative approach compared with other marketplaces like Archive, Depop, Facebook Marketplace, and Poshmark. With Pinstripe, sellers take their clothes to local consignment stores, vintage shops, […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 17:58:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Life Inside, Remixed: An Incarcerated Artist Learns to Paint Through the Chaos of Prison</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/11/01/animation-life-inside-prison-artist-mentorship</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Rafael Rodriguez’s artistic mentor and cellmate, Memo, taught him how to pour his anger and pain into oil painting.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 11:00:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>13 Votes on Housing Proposals to Watch On Election Day</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/votes-on-housing-to-watch-this-election</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>California isn’t the only state that will decide on important housing issues at the ballot box on Nov. 5, but it is one of the most prominent. Thirteen state and […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 21:02:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Trump’s victory could mean for AI regulation</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/11/06/what-trumps-victory-could-mean-for-ai-regulation/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>A grueling election cycle has come to a close. Donald Trump will be the 47th president of the U.S., and, with Republicans in control of the Senate — and possibly the House — his allies are poised to bring sea change to the highest levels of government. The effects will be acutely felt in the […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 17:39:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Families Seek Answers, Solace as St. Louis Police Struggle to Solve Killings</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/10/31/st-louis-police-families-unsolved-murders</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>We investigate the impact of the St. Louis police’s failure to solve murders, and rapper G. Dep talks about healing after turning himself in.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 16:00:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Basics to Renting Out One of Your Rooms</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/the-basics-to-renting-out-one-of-your-rooms</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>If you are lucky enough to have a spare room in your house that is not filled with random junk, congratulations—you may be sitting on some extra cash. The threat […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 20:41:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI coding assistants can help startups develop products, seed VCs believe</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/11/06/ai-coding-assistants-can-help-startups-develop-products-seed-vcs-believe/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>By now, there’s hardly a coder in the world who isn’t using an AI copilot in some way. But using GitHub Copilot or Cursor.AI to ask technical questions and get debugging help could be just the beginning. AI coding may one day involve agents that can write the programs themselves based on a natural language […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Some States Are Turning Miscarriages and Stillbirths Into Criminal Cases Against Women</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/10/31/stillbirth-oklahoma-arkansas-women-investigated</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>How a person handles a pregnancy loss — and where it occurs — can be the difference between a private medical issue and facing criminal charges.</description><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>