<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Aggregated RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/aggregated_feed.xml</link><description>This is an aggregated feed of multiple RSS sources.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 18:31:12 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Seeing Greene: Paying Off Rentals, Estimating Crime, &amp; Replacing Your Salary</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-937</link><description>Should I pay off my rental property or reinvest? How do I replace my six-figure salary with cash flow from real estate investing? And what’s the best way to analyze […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 07:02:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The BEST Side Hustles You Can Start in 2024 (Outside of Real Estate!)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-520</link><description>The best side hustles can put some extra cash in your pocket, help you leave your W2 job, or even launch you toward FIRE. If you’re looking to make money […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 07:01:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Beyond the Mailbox: Innovative Direct Mail Strategies That Win in Today’s Market</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/direct-mail-strategies-for-real-estate-investors</link><description>This article is presented by DealMachine. Read our editorial guidelines for more information. Breaking news: Direct mail is still a key factor in real estate marketing, and it has the potential to be […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 20:24:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Rational Investor’s Case Against Bitcoin</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/why-you-should-reject-bitcoin</link><description>I don’t invest in Bitcoin because I am betting on the continuation of Western civilization, not its collapse or decline. If I did believe my government would collapse, I’d invest […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 20:05:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The BiggerPockets Flip/Off: My Weekly Progress Diary</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/flip-off-diary</link><description>Follow along as I share my progress in my house flipping battle with Henry Washington!</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 19:44:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Home Prices in Pittsburgh Are Up 22%, Making It The Fastest Gainer in the U.S.—Here’s Why Prices There are Exploding</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/why-pittsburgh-home-prices-are-rising-rapidly</link><description>Pittsburgh has the hottest housing market in the country. Who knew? According to Redfin, Pittsburgh housing prices were up a mighty 22% from February 2023 to February 2024, making it the city with […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 19:06:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>4 Ways to Start Investing in Real Estate with NO or LOW Money</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-936</link><description>Want to know how to invest in real estate with NO money down? Or, maybe you’ve got a bit of cash in the bank and think now is the time […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 07:02:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>$120K/Year from ONE “Sensory” Rental Property with a “Secret” Amenity</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-393</link><description>If you want your rental property to succeed, you’ve got to give people a reason to keep coming back. That’s exactly what today’s guest is doing—creating a one-of-one experience that […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 07:02:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Policies Take Aim At Boosting Affordable Housing, Investors Could Benefit w/Dennis Shea</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-208</link><description>America is in an affordable housing crisis. With home prices rising dramatically over the past four years and rents following right along, tens of millions of Americans are spending a […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 07:02:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BiggerPockets Investigates: Did Western Wealth Capital Cost Investors Thousands of Dollars?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/did-western-wealth-capital-cost-investors-thousands-of-dollars</link><description>How did this syndicator, with all of its promise and potential, fall from grace after several investors claimed they were burned? BiggerPockets set out to find out what went wrong, how it went wrong, and what it means to other investors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 21:01:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Moving Overseas Made Me a Better Real Estate Investor</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/how-living-overseas-made-me-a-better-investor</link><description>Whenever I hop on a conference call, someone asks, “Where are you located?” And then their eyes widen when I respond, “Lima, Peru.”  But back when I invested in rental […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 17:17:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>These 10 Markets Are Great Places to Find Fixer-Upper Properties—Here’s What You Need to Know</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/great-fixer-upper-markets-for-investors-in-2024</link><description>With home prices and interest rates still at record highs and inventory squeezed, homebuyers and real estate investors may be better off purchasing a fixer-upper in some cities.  At least that’s […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 17:10:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BiggerNews: Investing with High Rates, Stubborn Inflation, &amp; Low Supply</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-935</link><description>Mortgage rates are high, supply is low, and inflation just won’t go away. These market conditions make investing in real estate harder than ever…or so most investors think. The truth? […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 07:02:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rookie Reply: Should I Move (and Quit My Job!) to Invest in Real Estate?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-392</link><description>Can’t afford to buy a rental property due to your area’s high cost of living? At what point should you quit your W2 job and move elsewhere to realize your […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 07:02:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HSA vs. FSA and When to Drain Your Emergency Fund to Pay Off Deb</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-519</link><description>Want to know how to avoid capital gains on your next home sale? If you tune in, you may dodge a quarter-of-a-million-dollar bullet (or more!). What about investing in one […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 07:01:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Pay Less Taxes by Buying Real Estate (1 Write-Off You’re Overlooking)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-934</link><description>With so many real estate tax write-offs, it’s no wonder that CPA Brandon Hall says rental real estate is one of the most tax-advantaged assets on the planet. But, even […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 07:02:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Happens If Interest Rates Stay High?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-207</link><description>Mortgage rates were supposed to be going down by now, but what happened? Even in late 2023, many housing market experts predicted that we’d be seeing high to mid six […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 07:02:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>6 Ways You Can Slash $19,000 in Expenses Without Sacrificing Your Happiness</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/ways-to-cut-expenses-without-sacrificing-happiness</link><description>In a recent episode of the BiggerPockets Real Estate Podcast, I had the privilege of chatting with Mindy Jensen about my journey to financial independence. One burning question arose: How […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 21:45:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Newly-Built Condos in Cities Make Perfect Rentals—Here’s Why</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/newly-built-condos-make-great-rental-properties-in-cities</link><description>When discussing rental properties, it’s common for people to refer to multifamily residences. How many times have you heard someone say something like, “I have 20 units under management,” most of which […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 21:27:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I’m Bullish on Preferred Equity Right Now—Here’s Why</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/why-im-bullish-on-preferred-equity-right-now</link><description>If you’ve been reading our stuff for the past year or so, you know we’re bullish on preferred equity. And we believe there is a short window of opportunity to achieve […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 18:57:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Investing in Senior Housing Can Be Extremely Profitable—But You Need To Know What You’re Doing</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/senior-housing-is-a-great-investment-for-real-estate-investors</link><description>Growing old is a fact of life—even for Keith Richards—and while it’s doubtful you’ll see world-famous rock stars or aging screen stars in a residential assisted living (RAL) facility, for […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 18:43:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Designing for Dollars: 7 Design Tips That Could Double Your Airbnb Revenue</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-933</link><description>If you follow these Airbnb design tips, you could double your nightly rates almost instantly. Don’t believe us? Erica Dike, a short-term rental design expert, has done it before and […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 07:02:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Low-Cost Way to “Invest” in Real Estate in 2024 (Without Buying Rentals)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-391</link><description>A thriving real estate business without rental properties?! It might sound like an easy way to “invest,” but make no mistake—you’re going to need to sharpen your management, interior design, […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 07:02:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seeing Greene: When NOT to Build an ADU and How to Invest $300K</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-932</link><description>How does a HELOC work? Can you use one to start investing in real estate when you’re low on cash? And, if you do decide to go the rental property […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 07:02:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shrinkflation: How to Outsmart The Grocery Stores’ Rising Prices</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-518</link><description>Whether you know it or not, “shrinkflation” is costing you. You’re paying more for less, as manufacturers boast record profits. Your paycheck is getting eaten away faster and faster every […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 07:01:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Growing Home Insurance Costs Will Destroy Your Cash Flow—Here’s What You Can Do About It</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/growing-home-insurance-costs-will-hurt-cash-flow</link><description>Real estate investors are usually most concerned about rental income and property taxes. They seldom discuss home insurance. Many assume that home insurance is a standard fixed price in most […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 20:42:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is Now a Better Time to Invest in Real Estate Debt or Equity?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/should-you-invest-in-real-estate-debt-or-equity-right-now</link><description>Many investors assume that ownership is inherently safer than debt. I currently own equity in thousands of units and have invested six figures in real estate debts. I can tell […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 20:34:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Could Rehab Loans Replace Hard Money Loans for Investors?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/will-construction-loans-replace-hard-money-loans-for-investors</link><description>As most house flippers or BRRRR landlords will tell you, paying for hard money—with high interest rates and points tacked on top—can take huge chunks of profit out of a project. For landlords, extra expenses […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 17:23:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Build a Real Estate Portfolio from Scratch in 2024</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-931</link><description>If you have just $10,000, you can start investing in real estate THIS YEAR, even with ZERO experience. How are you going to do it? In this episode, we’re breaking […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 07:02:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Hidden Risks of “Subject To” Real Estate w/Eddie Speed</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-206</link><description>For the past few years, “subject to” real estate has been all the rage. Everyone is talking about how they scored a great real estate deal by taking over a […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 07:02:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Making Over $10K/Month Thanks to “Conscious” Multifamily Investing</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-390</link><description>With the right rental properties, you could not only bring in thousands of dollars in cash flow each month but also build long-term wealth. Just ask today’s guest! Despite her […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 07:02:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Home Insurance Premiums Are Set to Hit a Record This Year—When Will Prices Fall?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/insurance-premiums-to-reach-record-highs-in-2024</link><description>Insurance premiums are skyrocketing across the U.S., with no end in sight to annual increases that may just make you rethink investing in real estate in several parts of the country.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 21:55:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Student Housing Is Very Profitable—And There’s a Dire Shortage</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/student-housing-is-one-of-the-most-profitable-property-types-and-theres-a-shortage</link><description>Depending on the college, students nationwide looking to live at school have recently found themselves staying in luxury hotels, trailers, on friends’ couches, or Zooming in to class from their […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 21:42:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Surge Pricing: How You Can Reap the Benefits of High Short-Term Rental Demand</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/short-term-rental-demand-surge-pricing</link><description>During much of the year, this short-term, two-bedroom rental in Indio, California, a lovely, quiet, desert town about 35 minutes past Palm Springs, hovers around $172 a night. That is, until mid-April […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 21:30:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rookie Reply: How to Find a Property Manager &amp; Set up Rentals Out of State</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-389</link><description>Property management is a key component of real estate investing that can make or break your cash flow. Of course, every rookie investor could benefit from having a great property […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 07:02:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Agents React to NAR Lawsuit Commission Change</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-930</link><description>The NAR lawsuit changed the real estate industry overnight. Just like that, buyer’s agents were no longer getting their standard three percent commission, and many investors began imagining what buying […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 07:02:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Everything You Need to Know Before You Buy a Business</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-517</link><description>Buying a business? Maybe you’ve thought about it before. You could own a laundromat, self-storage facility, plumbing business, or landscaping service. It doesn’t sound glamorous, but these types of businesses […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 07:01:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spring Cleaning: Why We’re Selling Off Parts of Our Rental Portfolios</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-929</link><description>Why are David and Rob selling off parts of their rental portfolios? It’s a new season, and you know what that means—spring cleaning! And if you’ve got underperforming properties, a […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 07:02:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Squatters’ Rights, Rent Caps, and Blackstone Gets Ready to Buy</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-205</link><description>Squatters’ rights are quickly being stripped away as more states move to end this widespread illegal occupation of private property. Blackstone predicts real estate prices to “bottom” as they gear […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 07:02:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Luxury Brands Are Buying Up Properties—Will High-End Landlords Fade Away?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/luxury-brands-are-buying-properties-instead-of-renting</link><description>Why rent when you can buy? Luxury brands like Louis Vuitton and Prada have made moves to buy up huge commercial properties to convert them into flagship storefronts, with many deals totaling $200 million-plus.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 17:50:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>You Can Buy a Property for $1 in Baltimore—Here’s How</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/baltimore-sells-abandoned-homes-for-one-dollar</link><description>Abandoned homes have become a problem in some of America's largest cities. Baltimore has come up with an interesting solution by selling off these properties for $1. What's the catch?</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 17:45:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Foreclosures Are Rising Quickly, and CRE Delinquencies Are Exploding—What’s Going On?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/foreclosures-rising-and-commercial-delinquencies-increasing-q1-2024</link><description>Some states are seeing their highest REO increases since the 2008 recession. South Carolina saw a 51% increase, while cities like New York saw their totals increase in the commercial space. What does this mean for the housing market?</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 17:35:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>124 Units in 4 Years by Only Investing in Small Towns and Tiny Markets</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-928</link><description>In just four years, Dylan Osmon went from having no job, barely any money, and no real estate investing experience to owning over one hundred rental units. How’d he do […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 07:02:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Save Your Cash Flow When Dealing with a “Problem” Property</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-388</link><description>How many things can possibly go wrong with ONE rental property? Well, you’re about to find out! Today’s guest had to flex her problem-solving skills on multiple occasions to get […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 07:02:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seeing Greene: Refi vs. “Recast,” Tax-Free Equity, &amp; When to Cut Your Losses</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-927</link><description>When is it NOT worth taking a capital gains tax exemption? Wouldn’t it ALWAYS be a good time to pay Uncle Sam less? Not exactly…and today, we’re going to get […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 07:02:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jaspreet Singh: Getting Rich Slowly and Why Some People STAY Broke</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-516</link><description>Want to know how to get rich but fear it could be too late? Perhaps you’ve got responsibilities, bills to pay, and a family to feed. How can you possibly […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 07:01:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Location Is the Most Important Investment Decision You Will Make</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/why-location-is-important</link><description>Location determines all the long-term characteristics of your rental income. So to achieve and maintain financial independence, the most important decision you will make is to choose a city where all the following requirements are met:</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 20:56:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>These Markets Might Be the Best for Single-Family Rental Returns This Year</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/top-single-family-rental-markets-in-2024-according-to-attom-data</link><description>According to ATTOM Data’s latest Q1 2024 Single-Family Rental Market report, average gross rental yields on three-bedroom single-family homes are projected to rise by 7.55% this year. As ever, though, the […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 20:55:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Recession Predictions: Why They’re Often Wrong, and Why the Narrative Continues to Switch</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/recession-predictions-why-they-are-often-wrong</link><description>Why do recession predictions always make it into the mainstream? And why are they always changing, and often wrong?</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 20:43:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I’m a Real Estate Agent—This Is How I Feel About the NAR Settlement and the Changes to Come</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/im-a-real-estate-agent-this-is-how-i-feel-about-the-nar-case</link><description>After multiple lawsuits, the National Association of Realtors (NAR) has agreed to a settlement with home sellers amounting to a payment of $418 million and a few monumental rule changes […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 20:16:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Agents React to NAR Lawsuit Commission Change</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-204</link><description>The NAR lawsuit changed the real estate industry overnight. Just like that, buyer’s agents were no longer getting their standard three percent commission, and many investors began imagining what buying […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 07:02:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Step-by-Step Guide to Flipping Houses and High-ROI Home Renovations</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-387</link><description>Want to begin flipping houses in 2024? With this popular investing strategy, you could build a lucrative and flexible real estate business. All any rookie needs to get started is […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 07:02:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>6 Tips to Grow Your Real Estate Portfolio While Working 9-5</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-926</link><description>You want to grow your real estate side hustle, but your W2 is taking up too much of your time. How do you invest in real estate when you’re stuck […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 07:02:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Market Madness: 10 College Housing Markets That Buy-and-Hold Investors Should Consider</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/best-college-housing-markets-for-growth</link><description>These college markets might not have skyrocketing price or rent growth, but they certainly have long-term strength. From Tuscaloosa to Austin, long-term investors should look into these 10 housing markets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 17:00:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scammers Are Using AI Deepfakes to Steal Millions of Dollars, Including Real Estate—Here’s How You Can Protect Yourself From Fraud</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/ai-deepfakes-are-being-used-to-scam-investors-out-of-millions</link><description>Earlier this year, a group of scammers in Hong Kong used deepfake technology to steal more than $25 million from a company by impersonating its CFO. Real estate titles are already subject to fraud, and with AI tech, it could get even worse. Here's how to protect yourself.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 16:50:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Industrial Real Estate Investing: A Guide for Modern Investors</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/industrial-real-estate-investing</link><description>Real estate investments are available in many shapes and sizes, including industrial real estate investing. This is not the most common form of real estate investing, but it has a lot of potential when done right, and can be a great opportunity to diversify your investments.</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 13:59:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rookie Reply: Will It Cash Flow? Analyzing BRRRRs, Hotels, &amp; Commercial Deals</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-386</link><description>To land a great investment property, a true diamond in the rough, you’re going to need to master the art of analyzing deals. Whether you plan to use the BRRRR […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 07:02:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BiggerNews: Housing Inventory Up 24%, Are We Returning to “Normal”?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-925</link><description>Housing inventory has shot up over twenty percent year-over-year. So, are our low inventory struggles finally behind us? During the low interest rate days, housing inventory couldn’t keep up with […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 07:02:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How I Paid Off $150K in Debt and the 5 Factors That Boost Your Credit Score</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-515</link><description>Want to know how to get out of debt for good? It’s not as easy as it sounds! The more you chip away at that number, the harder it becomes […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 07:01:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Best Real Estate Investing Conferences in 2024 (Chronological Order)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-investing-conferences</link><description>If you’re looking to elevate your real estate investing knowledge, expand your contact list, and gain powerful insight into 2024 real estate trends, then you need to be at the places that can make it happen.</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 18:31:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Compass Settles for $57.5 Million, Inventory Jumps, Fed Talks Rate Cuts</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-203</link><description>Compass is the latest brokerage to settle after the recent NAR lawsuit made sweeping changes to agent commission payments. With NAR, Keller Williams, Compass, and more associations and brokerages paying […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 07:02:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Raising Private Money 101: Beginner Steps to Raise Your First $1,000,000</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-924</link><description>Want to explode your real estate portfolio? Then you MUST know about raising private money. When done correctly, private money (also called private capital) can help you and your investors […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 07:02:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Utilizing the 5 M’s for Multifamily Success in 2024 and Beyond</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/the-five-ms-for-multifamily-success</link><description>This article is presented by DeRosa Group. Read our editorial guidelines for more information. Real estate investing, particularly in the multifamily sector, is both a rewarding and complex venture. 2024 brings with […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 00:52:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Market Madness: 10 College Markets That Are Great for Cash Flow</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/best-college-housing-markets-for-cash-flow</link><description>With the college sports season’s thrilling climax, this is also an exciting time for real estate investors who own rentals in college towns that are being given a high profile. […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 22:11:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Landlord Rights Are Being Stripped Away—Why the Latest Examples of Squatting Should Concern You</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/landlord-rights-are-being-stripped-away-and-given-to-squatters</link><description>The media tends to side with tenants and take a negative view of landlords overall. One notable exception was an episode of HBO’s Silicon Valley, where the hapless Jared has tried […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:59:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Strategic Accounting for House Flipping Success</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/accounting-for-flipping-houses</link><description>There’s a lot that goes into house flipping. You need to choose the right market, negotiate a competitive price, work with the best contractors, and get an agent to help you sell for a profit. On top of that, a defined accounting strategy for house flipping is critical to your long-term success. Here’s how to create one.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 20:55:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Write Off Your BPCON Travel as a Business Expense</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/write-off-bpcon-travel-as-a-business-expense</link><description>For business travel to be tax-deductible, you need to leave your tax home. This is where you ordinarily conduct business, and you typically have to travel far enough to warrant an overnight stay (100 miles is a good rule to follow).</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 18:36:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Taxes &amp; Buying a Home—Here’s What You Should Know</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/new-home-buying-tax-deductions-and-implications</link><description>Many people understandably wonder what costs and expenses could be tax-deductible and what additional taxes they may need to pay as part of the homebuying and ownership process. Here, we’ll go over everything you need to know about taxes and home purchases, including what you’ll pay, potential deductions you may benefit from, and more.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 18:06:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Save Your Rental Property When “Good” Tenants Turn BAD</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-385</link><description>Could your rental property be occupied by bad tenants masquerading as good residents? After an incident that led to thousands in property damage, a complex insurance claim, and an eviction, […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 07:02:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From No Savings to Building 60 Houses in 5 Years!</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-923</link><description>Feeling scared to do your first or next real estate deal? Even if everything goes wrong, you may still be in a better position than Ayesha and Kevan Shelton were […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 07:02:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Strategically Reduce Your W-2 Taxes with Real Estate</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/reduce-w2-taxes-with-real-estate</link><description>There are several ways that you may be able to reduce your W-2 taxes with a real estate investment. The type and whether you have an equity or debt investment determines the strategies you will qualify for.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 01:35:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>5 Crucial Investment Criteria for Out-of-State Turnkey Investors</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/investment-criteria-for-out-of-state-turnkey-investors</link><description>Sloppy renovations and corner-cutting maintenance efforts aren’t good enough. As you navigate the world of single-family investing, focus on these five essential elements of due diligence.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 18:16:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seeing Greene: Signs It’s Time to STOP Investing in Real Estate</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-922</link><description>When is enough enough? When is it time to STOP investing in real estate? When you have a hundred units or a thousand? When can you step back and let […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 07:02:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to “Travel Hack” Like a Pro and Get FREE Flights, Hotel Stays, and More!</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-514</link><description>Want to know how to travel for FREE in 2024 and 2025? We’re about to introduce you to the magical world of travel hacking. Never heard of it before? You’re […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 07:01:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Property Taxes: Complete FAQ</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/property-tax-faq</link><description>It’s common to have questions about your property taxes, but one is more important than all the others combined: Why did my property taxes increase. There’s no individual answer to this question, as it can depend on a variety of factors. Here are 19 frequently asked questions (FAQs) to help you understand property taxes as a whole, and with that, determine why your taxes have increased.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 04:27:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Owner Financing: Complete FAQ</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/owner-financing-faq</link><description>Owner financing offers buyers and sellers more opportunities with real estate transactions. Before entering this type of transaction, it’s important to know what owner financing is, how it works, who benefits, and who pays property taxes on owner financing.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 00:19:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What I Learned From My First Investment Property—and How I Changed My Strategy</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/what-i-learned-from-my-first-investment-property</link><description>My first investment property was a C/D-class multifamily in Houston. I selected it primarily based on perceived cash flow. According to my calculations, the return on investment (ROI) was between 12% and 14%. And with a multifamily, even if one unit is vacant, I still have cash coming in. How could I lose?</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 22:50:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Vacant Offices the Next Big Opportunity for Residential Investors?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/vacant-offices-could-be-residential-investors-next-big-opportunity</link><description>Are empty city office buildings going the same way as zombie shopping malls, or can they be revitalized to become residential apartments and condos?  That question has many developers, city […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 19:27:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is a 1031 Exchange Really Worth It? After Three Months of Work, We’re Questioning It</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/1031-investor-journal-three</link><description>Is a 1031 exchange really worth it? That’s the question we asked ourselves as we ran property after property this month.  If you’re new here, we are selling our spacious Brooklyn […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 19:10:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>No, Wall Street Is Not Buying Up Main Street—Here’s Why It’s All a Myth</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wall-street-is-not-buying-up-main-street</link><description>Wall Street buyers only make up a tiny percentage of the market, yet there's an entire campaign to place the blame on them.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 18:50:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Get More Airbnb Bookings This Spring and Summer Break</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-921</link><description>Wondering how to get more bookings on Airbnb as spring break and summer vacation inch closer? With some expert tips, you’ll be able to bring in more revenue and higher […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 07:02:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Market Madness: 8 Housing Markets We’d Place Big Bets on in 2024</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-202</link><description>It’s March Madness season, so we thought we’d create a bracket of our own, pitting some of the best real estate markets against each other to see which one will […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 07:02:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The “Luxury” Rental Property That Brings in $150K/Year of Pure Profit</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-384</link><description>Making six figures from one rental property is every investor’s dream, but to achieve this, you need to choose the right investing market, buy the right property, and create luxurious […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 07:02:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Buying in a Historic District Can Be a Gold Mine—But Here’s Why You Should Be Careful</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/buying-a-home-in-a-historic-district-can-be-a-goldmine</link><description>A recent CNBC survey based on cost per square foot revealed that the United States’ most expensive real estate market is San Francisco’s South of Market, which contains historic Victorian buildings surrounded […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 22:27:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What the NAR Settlement Means for Real Estate Investors, According to Sources in the Industry</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/what-the-nar-settlement-means-for-real-estate-investors</link><description>The National Association of Realtors (NAR) agreed to a settlement last week that will eliminate its rules on sales commissions. The deal, if approved by the federal court, is likely to shake […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 22:16:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How a Squatter in Oregon “Stole” a Property, and the Rising Tide of Disputes Ending Badly for Landlords</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/how-a-squatter-in-oregon-was-paid-to-leave-home-he-was-not-renting</link><description>“I always thought stealing was wrong,” real estate investor and developer George McCleary remarks at the end of a viral video posted on social media last month, “But turns out, if you steal a […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 21:59:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Breaking: NAR Settles for $418M, Buying and Selling Homes Could Change Forever w/The New York Times’ Debra Kamin</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-201</link><description>A bombshell NAR settlement could bring wide-sweeping changes to the housing market. After a snowball of NAR lawsuits, the realtor association agreed to settle for a whopping $418 million and […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 07:02:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rookie Reply: “Managing” Your Property Manager &amp; How to Invest While in Debt</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-383</link><description>A property manager can alleviate the burden of screening tenants, collecting rents, and maintaining your property. But if you’re not careful, exorbitant fees and unexpected charges can quickly eat away […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 07:02:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Breaking: NAR Settles for $418M, Buying and Selling Homes Could Change Forever</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-920</link><description>A bombshell NAR settlement could bring wide-sweeping changes to the housing market. After a snowball of NAR lawsuits, the realtor association agreed to settle for a whopping $418 million and […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 07:02:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The “Red Flags” of Investment Fraud from a Former $3.8M Ponzi Scheme Manager</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-513</link><description>Please be advised: this podcast episode contains discussions about sensitive topics, including suicide, which may be distressing for some listeners. If you are experiencing thoughts of suicide or emotional distress, […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 07:01:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Federal Reserve Leaves Rates Untouched as Pressure Mounts on Inflation</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/the-federal-reserve-leaves-rates-untouched-as-pressure-mounts-on-inflation</link><description>With inflation hovering slightly north of 3%, the Federal Reserve’s meeting this week and its decision to leave interest rates where they are were seen by many as inevitable. Inflation has […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 18:08:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Use Real Estate to Quit the 9-5 Grind</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-919</link><description>Ready to escape the rat race and leave your nine-to-five behind? You’re tired of the early mornings, late nights, alarm clocks, and commuting. You want to go out on your […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 07:02:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Flip/Off: Whose House Flip Can Pull In the Biggest Return? (Dainard vs. Washington)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-200</link><description>James Dainard, a house flipper in Seattle, Washington, has been on a flipping spree for the past two decades. He’s flipped more homes than you can count, made tens of […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 07:02:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Rise of “15-Minute Cities,” and if Investors Should Cash In</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/what-are-15-minute-cities-and-should-you-buy-in</link><description>Paris officially implemented the "15-minute city" as an urban planning concept, and now city planners across the world are debating the merits of switching to this model. What is a 15-minute city, and is it something you should invest in?</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 21:14:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Comedian Richard Lewis Ensured His Home Was Protected After His Death—Here’s How You Can Do the Same</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/how-richard-lewis-protected-his-estate-with-an-assignment-of-rents-trust-deed</link><description>Curb Your Enthusiasm comedian and veteran stand-up act Richard Lewis, who recently passed away, didn’t just have a sharp wit; he had some sharp financial moves regarding real estate, too. According […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 21:00:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Home Prices Are Falling in These 10 Markets—Are They Ripe for Investing?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/housing-markets-with-declining-prices-march-2024</link><description>Falling prices haven't been common in today's market. With higher mortgage rates and low inventory, many investors have waited on the sidelines. Is now the time to plunge back in?</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 20:46:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The REAL Cost of Bad Tenants and “Cheap” Contractors (Mistakes to Avoid!)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-382</link><description>Want a successful, cash-flowing rental property? Make sure you don’t overlook the tenant screening process or hire the “cheap” contractor. Otherwise, you could be dealing with floods, evictions, project delays, […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 07:02:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Creating Their Own Demand By Ditching the “Cookie-Cutter Flips”</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-918</link><description>Fix and flips have looked a lot alike for the past few years. You see the same countertops, wall colors, appliances, and flooring in almost every new flip. While it […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 07:02:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seeing Greene: Can I Escape the Rat Race with Just $70K?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-917</link><description>Want to escape the rat race? To do so, you’ll need some serious investments. And if you want bigger and better cash flow or appreciation, commercial real estate is the […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 07:02:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Unemployment Inches Up, Inflation Returns, &amp; Serious News for Student Loans</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-512</link><description>Has the job market finally flipped? Throughout most of the pandemic, it seemed that any and every worker was a hot commodity. Job-hopping was the new norm as businesses outbid […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 07:01:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Do You Know Your FIRE Number? Here’s What That Means</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/discover-you-fire-number</link><description>Determining your FIRE number is the gateway to retiring early and living life on your terms. It's not necessarily easy to achieve your income goals, but it becomes possible once you set your sights on it.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 21:24:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Your Business Partners Determine Your Outcome—Here’s How to Find and Keep the Good Ones</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/how-to-find-and-keep-the-right-real-estate-partners</link><description>For many investors, partnering is the best or worst part of their real estate experience. Too many things can go wrong, so here's what you need to know about finding and keeping the right partners.</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 21:18:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Silent War on Landlords That No One Is Talking About</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/the-silent-war-on-tenant-screening</link><description>It’s no secret that legislation regarding tenant screening is becoming more and more restrictive. As of this writing, 20 states and 106 localities have passed bans on discriminating against source of […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 21:10:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Home Sales Are Up: Is the Real Estate Market Thawing Out?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/new-home-sales-rise-as-winter-market-ends-q1-2024</link><description>Existing home sales have been steadily declining, reaching the lowest levels in 30 years in 2023, according to the National Association of Realtors (NAR). Existing home sales rebounded slightly month over month in January […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 20:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Crucial Contractor Tips to Avoid Renovation Disaster</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-916</link><description>A bad contractor could not only ruin your home renovation but cost you tens if not hundreds of thousands of dollars. Don’t believe us? Just ask Rico to the Rescue’s […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 07:02:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Listings “Normalize,” Inflation Ticks Up, and Airbnb Bans Indoor Cameras</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-199</link><description>The Fed isn’t happy, but what’s new? After inflation numbers were released last week, showing higher-than-expected consumer price growth, our rate cut dreams could be slowly dwindling. Are we still […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 07:02:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Making $7K/Month in PURE Cash Flow with Only 3 Rental Properties</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-381</link><description>Many people buy rental properties for the cash flow, but today’s guest took it to another level—dropping out of college to go all-in on real estate investing. Find out how […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 07:02:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The NAR Will Eliminate 6% Commission Standards and Pay $418 Million in Damages After Settling Lawsuit</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/national-association-of-realtors-to-pay-418-million-and-remove-commission-standards-as-part-of-settlement</link><description>The NAR will pay $418 million in damages and remove its 6% commission standard, which is major news for investors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 21:12:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Housing Shortage Will Only Get Worse—Here’s What Investors Need to Know</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/the-housing-shortage-will-get-worse-in-2024</link><description>The U.S. is short several million housing units, and the situation is only getting worse. Supply gaps continue to widen on a national and regional level, and 73 out of the largest 100 markets are experiencing shortages. What should investors expect going forward?</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:33:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>It’s Time to Stop Relying on the Fed—You Should Do This Instead</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/stop-relying-on-the-fed-and-adapt-your-strategy-for-risk</link><description>In late 2022 and early 2023, private equity real estate investors sharply pulled back on funding. They caught on—in some cases, too late—that rising interest rates were going to annihilate […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 18:34:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rookie Reply: How to Start Investing, Walking Away from Deals, &amp; Co-hosting</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-380</link><description>You want to start real estate investing, but where should you start? Should you buy a course, join a mastermind, or do your own research? There’s no one-size-fits-all approach to […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 07:02:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BiggerNews: Why Mortgage Rates AREN’T Falling</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-915</link><description>The Fed has signaled something significant for mortgage rates. With inflation still rearing its head and the job market hot as ever, the Fed already has enough evidence to hold […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 07:02:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pay Your Rent and Level Up Your Home with THIS Creative Side Hustle</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-511</link><description>Could one side hustle help you pay rent, save money to invest in real estate, or reach financial independence? Today’s guest picked up the perfect hobby that combines his background […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 07:01:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From Big Data to Big Deals: Leveraging Data Analytics in Real Estate Investing</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/from-big-data-to-big-deals-leveraging-data-analytics-in-real-estate-investing</link><description>There’s no denying that big data and data analytics tools are transforming the real estate landscape. But just how is this happening? What is behind the power of analytics in […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 21:48:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deals We’re Doing: Rob’s Pink Pickle and How David Made $500K on ONE House</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-914</link><description>You hear us talk a lot about buying real estate, but what real estate deals are WE doing in 2024? Today, we’re pulling back the curtain on our portfolios, walking […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 07:02:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Real Deals We’re Doing RIGHT NOW (Flips, Developments, and Duplexes)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-198</link><description>Welcome to the “redemption year” for real estate investing. We talk a lot on this show about the real estate deals being done all across the country. From interviewing flippers […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 07:02:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>U.S. News Listed Its 20 Hottest Real Estate Markets—Should You Invest in Any of Them?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/us-news-hottest-market-list-ranks-denver-as-top-market-in-2024</link><description>U.S. News released its annual list of the hottest real estate markets for the year. Here's a look at what's included and our take on the rankings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 21:32:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Living Overseas Can Help You Earn More Money in Real Estate Over the Long Run—Here’s How</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-investors-living-overseas-can-scale-faster-in-the-us</link><description>The cost of living has been rising steadily over the last several decades, especially with inflationary pressures over the past couple of years. At this rate, is it easier to invest in U.S. real estate from overseas? The answer might surprise you.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 21:15:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway Records Rising Profits From Insurance Businesses—But Utilities Profits Are Down</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/berkshire-hathaway-earnings-paint-a-picture-of-the-real-estate-market</link><description>Warren Buffett's annual letter to investors has painted an interesting picture of the housing market: Utilities are down, but insurance is up. What does that mean for the market at large?</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 20:56:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Emergency Fund: How Much Do You Really Need in 2024?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/how-much-do-you-need-to-save-in-an-emergency-fund</link><description>As inflation continues to eat away at buying power, have the standards for optimal savings changed? And how much do you need to save for emergencies?</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 20:44:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>150+ Deals in 3 Years and Why You DON’T Want to Be a Landlord</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-913</link><description>Most real estate investors do a few deals a year if they’re lucky. But today’s guest was doing twenty to thirty real estate deals a MONTH. That’s right—not per YEAR, […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 07:02:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Buy Your First or Next Rental Property in 90 Days (or Less!)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-379</link><description>Want to know how to buy your first rental property? You’ve come to the right place! It’s no secret that investing in real estate is one of the best ways […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 07:02:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seeing Greene: Paying Off Rentals, Partnerships Splits, &amp; Using Home Equity</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-912</link><description>Want to double your real estate portfolio and bring in much more cash flow? What about using some of your untapped home equity to invest? Today, we’re showing you how […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 07:02:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Morgan Housel: Financial Lessons From History Anyone Can Use to Get Rich</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-510</link><description>Morgan Housel’s ground-breaking book, The Psychology of Money, changed how many Americans thought about saving, spending, and investing. Through a collection of financial lessons, Morgan opened up new thought patterns […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 07:01:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The “Value-Add” Playbook: How to Boost Equity and Bring in MORE Cash Flow</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-911</link><description>Want to turn your rental property into a cash-flowing machine? What about boosting your property’s equity by tens or hundreds of thousands? The “value-add” strategy can do all this and […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 07:02:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paying Off $100K in Debt with 3 Rentals Thanks to THIS Low-Money Strategy</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-378</link><description>Could rental properties help you switch careers, replace your W2 income, or get out of debt? According to today’s guest, yes! Once Dave learned of the flexibility that real estate […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 07:02:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NAR Finally Faces Competition: Is the Agent “Monopoly” Over? w/Jason Haber and Mauricio Umansky</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-197</link><description>Disclaimer: Opinions expressed in this episode and written below are solely opinions of the hosts, guests, and writers and do not reflect the views of BiggerPockets. The recent NAR lawsuits […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 07:02:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Air Quality Should Be a Factor In Your Next Investment Decision—You Might Be Surprised Why</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/air-quality-should-be-a-factor-into-your-investment-decisions</link><description>Poor air quality has been in the headlines about U.S. climate change, especially on the West Coast and in Southern states. Increasingly devastating wildfires are becoming a sad fact of life in […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 02:53:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The “Dirty Little Secret” of the FIRE Movement—and Why It’s Good News</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/the-dirty-little-secret-of-the-fire-movement-and-why-its-good-news</link><description>Love it or hate it, the financial independence, retire early (FIRE) movement has changed the conversation around financial planning. And any change that provokes new discussion and a fresh perspective […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 02:39:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>More Homes Are for Sale but the Market Remains at a Standstill—When Will Demand Come Back?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/more-homes-are-for-sale-but-the-market-remains-at-a-standstill</link><description>After a winter slump, the real estate market is starting to look a little brighter in time for spring. More homes are entering the market, and buyers are starting to […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 02:19:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From $0 to $40 Million: How a 10-Year Old Orphan Became a Successful Investor</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/john-mansor-real-estate-story</link><description>John Mansor was left a ward of the state at 10 years old. For 15 years, he climbed the ladder to success, all through real estate. Here's his inspiring story, which is proof that it doesn't matter where you come from—as long as you have the mindset to do what needs to be done.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 18:08:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is Puerto Rico America’s Best Investing Destination? Here’s What You Need to Know</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/investing-in-puerto-rico-real-estate</link><description>With markets across the country cash flow-strapped and unaffordable, where do you turn? We've mentioned Europe, but there's a closer destination that's worth a look too.</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 17:19:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rookie Reply: Cash Flow vs. Appreciation, Using HELOCs, and Trashed Rentals</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-377</link><description>Should you invest for cash flow or appreciation? Whether you need another income stream today or have one eye set on retirement, you have your own reason for investing in […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 07:02:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zillow’s “Trends Expert” on How to Sell Your Home Faster (and For More!)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-910</link><description>Did you know that a certain shade of paint can help you sell your home for more? Or that one type of countertop could cause buyers to get into a […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 07:02:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Build, Grow, Scale, and SELL Your Online Business</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-509</link><description>If you want to make money online in 2024, good news: it’s easier than ever! Just ask today’s guest, who had to bootstrap his online business before you could launch […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 07:01:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>China Falters, Israel’s Oil Danger, and Russia’s Assets Used Against Them w/Joe Brusuelas</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-196</link><description>China’s economy is on its last legs. Thanks to massive overspending and high unemployment, the Chinese economy is beginning to break down, with real estate prices crashing at a scale […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 07:02:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>6 Expert Tips for Out-of-State Real Estate Investing</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-909</link><description>Can’t invest in your own backyard? Out-of-state investing is the way to go! With it, you can invest nationwide, finding more cash flow or appreciation potential than you would in […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 07:02:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>America’s Suburbs: The Controversies, Conspiracies, and Greed That Built Them</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/americas-suburbs-the-controversies-conspiracies-and-greed-that-built-them</link><description>Are the suburbs an auto manufacturer-led Ponzi scheme designed to create a soulless maze of homes and streets to keep America car-dependent? Or a government ploy for control?</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 23:06:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Renters Are Still Moving—These Markets Are Where You Should Be Investing</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/migration-report-q1-2024</link><description>Migration has been one of the prevailing trends since the beginning of the COVID-19 pandemic, but it's slowing down, with several key stats showing less move intent and actual moves than the year prior. Here's where movers went last year and how investors can capitalize.</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 21:21:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The $150K “Stolen” Rental Property and How to Avoid a Real Estate Scam</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-376</link><description>Having your rental property stolen?! How is that possible? This would be a worst-case scenario for any investor, and it was nearly reality for today’s guest. Buckle up as we […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 07:02:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>$400,000/Year Cash Flow From One Unique Rental Property</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-908</link><description>Want BIG cash flow numbers? How about $400K/year cash flow? Would that be enough to set you financially free? For Amanda and David Fornelli, this is reality, and it’s all […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 07:02:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Today’s Impacts on Property Insurance Costs—And What Investors Can Do About It</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/todays-impacts-on-property-insurance-costs-and-what-investors-can-do-about-it</link><description>As insurance premiums climb, property owners need to grasp how economic conditions and natural disasters affect the insurance market. These insights provide practical guidance for real estate investors navigating a dynamic, unpredictable market.</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 20:46:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seeing Greene: $100K In Equity But NO Cash Flow, Should I Sell?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-907</link><description>Where’d all the cash flow go? More than ever, rental property owners are waking up to find less and less mailbox money coming in every month. This is doubly true […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 07:02:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Budgeting Tips for Families Living on ONE Income</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-508</link><description>Can you really be a one-income family in 2024? Not if you don’t know how to budget! To achieve her money goals while living on a single middle-class income, Emy […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 07:01:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quick Strategies: Earn More Money By Renting Your Property by the Room</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/renting-by-the-room</link><description>Renting by the room is still a sound strategy for those looking to invest in 2024, especially prospective house hackers looking to get into real estate investing. Here's how you can do it today.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 21:16:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Redfin Report Shows Investors “Piling In” to Low-Cost Properties—Here’s Why It’s Likely to Stay That Way</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/investors-piling-in-on-low-cost-properties-in-q4</link><description>Investors must switch up strategies now that easy money policies are a thing of the past. Low-cost properties have become a bigger slice of the pie, and it's likely to stay that way, even when mortgage rates inevitably fall.</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 21:04:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Here’s the Blueprint to Financial Freedom Today—Even When Mortgage Rates Are High</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/the-blueprint-to-financial-freedom-with-high-mortgage-rates</link><description>Most investment strategies touted by gurus involve first buying a course to learn their strategy to get rich in real estate. While subject-to deals, wholesaling, syndicating, BRRRRing, Airbnb arbitrage, and […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 20:53:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Bill in Congress Targets Real Estate Investors—Here’s Why This Could Be a Big Problem</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/how-the-affordable-housing-and-homeownership-protection-act-will-impact-investors</link><description>Another bill is targeting real estate investors—this time, with a goal to “help Main Street compete with Wall Street.” What's in the bill? And what are the consequences for investors if passed?</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 20:33:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Making $160K/Year From ONE “Rare” Property Thanks to Seller Financing</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-375</link><description>Every investor wants a rental property that brings in six figures, but not every investor is willing to scour old listings, bring in a partner, or exhaust all of their […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 07:02:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Become a Millionaire Through Real Estate Investing (Beginners!)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-906</link><description>Learn how to become a millionaire with real estate EVEN in 2024. You’re trying to make big wealth-building moves this year, but how do you reach seven figures without any […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 07:02:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Happens to Rent Prices When 1,000,000 New Units Come Online in 2024? w/Chris Salviati</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-195</link><description>Rent prices peaked in 2022 after a double-digit percentage run-up. Due to more household formation, disposable income, and remote work availability, Americans were doing whatever they could to upgrade their […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 07:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>There Is an Interest Rate That Will Unfreeze the Market—But Will We Ever Get There?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/what-interest-rate-will-unfreeze-housing</link><description>The beginning of 2024 has been a buzzkill for what many believed would be the beginning of federal interest rate cuts. Are we still on track for a summer cut, though?</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 22:34:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is There New Risk of a Crash This Year? Here’s What Pundits Are Warning About</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/will-there-be-a-recession-in-2024</link><description>Some pundits fear that a recession is likely to come due to factors that might not be as apparent as others. Here's what they're saying.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 22:19:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I Grew up Going To Real Estate Auctions With My Dad—These Are the Lessons I Learned</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/my-dad-took-me-to-my-first-auction-heres-what-i-learned-about-investing</link><description>I moved around a lot when I was younger. And I’m not talking from state to state or city to city—I moved a few doors down from wherever I was […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 19:53:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blowing the Lid Off Your Financial Ceiling Means Creating a Floor to Allow Risk</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/creating-a-floor-for-risk-in-investing</link><description>Without risk, there's no path to an extraordinary life. Here's what you should do instead.</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 19:17:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fannie Mae: Multifamily Is STILL Undersupplied, Rent Growth Likely w/Kim Betancourt</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-905</link><description>On a national level, Fannie Mae is predicting the multifamily market to remain subdued in 2024. Ever since interest rates began to rise, multifamily transactions have slowed considerably. Higher rates made profits […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 07:02:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rookie Reply: Screening Tenants, Using Hard Money, and Raising Rents</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-374</link><description>Every landlord wants the best possible tenants in their rental property, but of course, this doesn’t happen by chance. Today, we’re delivering several tips to help you improve the screening […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 07:02:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Path to Early FI, Transferring 401(k) Funds, &amp; Wiping Out Bad Car Debt</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-507</link><description>Everyone wants to reach financial independence as soon as possible. But if you really want to get on the path to early FI, you’ve got to start making savvy money […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 07:01:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Short vs. Long-Term Real Estate Investing</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/short-vs-long-term-real-estate-investing</link><description>There is no right or wrong way to invest in real estate. All that matters is that you’re comfortable with your strategy and positioned to generate a positive return on investment (ROI). However, it never hurts to compare all your options—and that means taking a closer look at short-term vs. long-term real estate investing.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 22:29:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>5 Grants for Real Estate Investing in 2024</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/grants-for-real-estate-investing</link><description>There are grants for real estate investors available. These grants are typically designed for specific purposes, but let’s discuss some of the most popular real estate investment grants available in 2024.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 22:11:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Mobile Homes a Good Investment for Rental Property?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/mobile-homes-for-rental-property</link><description>While there’s no defined strategy for success, key considerations include understanding the unique market demand for mobile homes, analyzing location benefits, assessing the condition and age of the mobile home, and understanding the legal and zoning regulations that apply.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 21:58:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Legal Considerations of House Hacking</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/is-house-hacking-legal</link><description>If you're looking to break into real estate investing but need to figure out what it takes, consider house hacking. You might wonder, though: Is house hacking legal?</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 21:49:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>5 Hedge Funds Investing in Real Estate in 2024</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/hedge-funds-investing-in-real-estate</link><description>There are plenty of hedge funds investing in real estate in 2024. As an investor, you can learn a lot about the real estate market—including where to invest—by closely following these hedge funds and their performance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 21:35:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Does the BRRRR Method Still Work in 2024?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-904</link><description>For years, the BRRRR method (buy, rehab, rent, refinance, repeat) was every real estate investor’s favorite strategy. And it’s easy to see why. Using this simple formula, you can buy […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 07:02:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>4 Hot Housing Markets with Huge Home Price Appreciation (50% Jumps!)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-194</link><description>Most real estate markets in America saw huge home price growth over the past five years. Ever since the pandemic, equity and appreciation have been slingshotted to new heights, with […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 07:02:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Can You Flip Houses While on Disability?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/flipping-houses-while-on-disability</link><description>Disability benefits provide important lifelines to those who are unable to work due to various medical conditions. Although your ability to work while on disability will be limited, you may still be able to earn income from certain passive investments. Whether flipping houses while on disability will affect your benefits depends on your degree of involvement in your properties.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 22:04:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Invest in Real Estate or Start a Franchise: Which Investment Opportunity Suits You?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/invest-in-real-estate-or-start-a-franchise</link><description>Real estate and franchising are two popular investment options offering significant financial returns. Both allow you to earn passive income, enjoy tax benefits, and benefit from regular cash flow. However, a real estate franchise and real estate investing each have pros and cons to consider.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 21:42:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Investing in Forest Land: Is It a Good Opportunity?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/investing-in-forest-land</link><description>Investing in forest land can be a great way to diversify your portfolio. Because tree growth doesn’t rely on economic factors, consistent biological growth can create more stable returns than other financial investments.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 21:16:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>15 Reasons Why Real Estate is the Best Investment</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/15-reasons-why-real-estate-is-the-best-investment</link><description>These 15 reasons real estate is the best investment are reason enough to diversify your capital and invest in real estate. Whether you're looking at your first real estate investment or you want to expand your portfolio, there are numerous benefits for doing so, giving you access to equity, cash flow, and a tangible asset that gives you control.</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 20:59:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Is the ‘’Cardboard-Box Indicator’’—Should Investors Pay Attention to It?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/what-the-cardboard-box-indicator-means-for-the-economy</link><description>According to Charles Schwab's Jeffrey Kleintop, cardboard boxes are a measure of demand and can be used to track the economy. Is he right?</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 20:15:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Investors Are Buying a Record Share of Low-Priced Homes—What Does It Mean for the Market?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/highest-share-of-investors-on-record-are-buying-low-value-homes</link><description>In Q1 2023, investors bought 49% fewer homes than the year prior. Now, we're seeing a rise in investor activity again, with certain property classes more popular than others. What are investors doing, and what should you be buying?</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 19:48:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>120 Rentals in 3 Years by Buying Multifamily During a BAD Market</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-903</link><description>Would you buy multifamily real estate now? Asset prices are falling, mortgage rates are still high, banks aren’t taking on new loans, and every real estate “expert” thinks that the […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 07:02:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wiping Out $130K of Debt in ONE Year With THIS “Steady” Real Estate Business</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-373</link><description>Building a real estate business is one of the best ways to unlock financial freedom, but that’s not to say that every strategy is the right fit for you. Today’s […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 07:02:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Three Principles That Will Turn You Into An Effective Property Manager</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/three-principles-for-effective-property-management</link><description>The top grievances of tenants are poor communication, unfair rent increases, and a lack of transparency. Don't neglect property management, as it will cost you more in the long run. These three principles will help you maximize its impact.</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 23:14:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seeing Greene: Investing WITHOUT Burning Out and What We’d Do With $1M</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-902</link><description>Want to build a real estate business? When done right, a real estate business could make you hundreds of thousands, if not millions, of dollars a year, even with a […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 07:02:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Use Your Money “Archetype” to Address Your Biggest Financial Burdens</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-506</link><description>After tremendous research, the “MoneyType” quiz was finally released. All you need to do is answer some basic questions, and in a matter of minutes, you’ll know your biggest financial […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 07:01:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Has the Housing Market Not Crashed in Over 15 Years?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/why-has-the-housing-market-not-crashed-in-15-years</link><description>Before I begin, I am not an economist. I don’t study the jobs report, watch the Dow, or follow economic TikTok accounts. I’m just a guy who loves real estate […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 21:30:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dave Ramsey Is Wrong—Doing This Won’t Make You Wealthy, But There Is Another Way</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/dave-ramsey-is-wrong-cutting-expenses-wont-make-you-rich</link><description>Dave Ramsey is famous for his personal finance tips, most of which revolve around cutting expenses and adopting more frugal habits. That's great and sound advice, but it won't make you "rich." This is what you should do instead.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 21:20:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What I Learned From National Retailers to Decide What and Where to Invest—And How You Can Do It Too</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/what-national-retail-chains-taught-me-about-investing</link><description>In 2005, I decided to start an investor services business. I reviewed all the popular investing literature. What I found were self-professed experts offering opinions and no processes. As an […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 21:01:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>4 Real Estate Investing Trends That Could Take Over in 2024, 2025, and Beyond</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-193</link><description>Which investing trends could make you wealthy in 2024? First, we had long-term rentals, then the BRRRR strategy, short-term rentals, medium-term rentals, syndications…the list goes on and on. And while […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 07:02:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>$4K/Month and Financial Stability From Rentals After Losing His “Safe” Job</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-372</link><description>For some people, real estate investing is “too risky.” But what if a small, cash-flowing portfolio could provide financial stability when you lose your job? If you asked today’s guests, […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 07:02:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 6 Beginner Steps to Take Before Investing in Real Estate</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-901</link><description>If you want to start investing in real estate and buy your first rental property, there are six beginner steps you’ll need to take. Following these steps to a tee […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 07:00:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Who Cares About the Number of Doors You Have—Cash Flow Is What Actually Matters</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/count-cash-flow-over-doors</link><description>Investors get hung up on their total number of doors, but does that really matter? Here's why investors need to track stats beyond doors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 20:57:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI Tools Can Save You 10 Hours Per Week If You Use Them Right—Here’s How</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/ai-tools-can-save-you-10-hours-in-real-estate</link><description>Between ChatGPT, Gemini, and other new AI tools, there are now a gazillion ways to outsource and delegate monotonous duties in your business.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 20:43:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Now Is a Great Time to Go Hunting for Passive Multifamily Deals—Regardless of the Headlines</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/2024-is-a-great-time-to-buy-passive-multifamily-real-estate</link><description>Sentiment has been sour on many things in real estate lately, but every market has deals to be made. The same is true for multifamily.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 20:31:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Truth About Real Estate Investing in 2024 (What Investors NEED to Know)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-900</link><description>The old ways of financial freedom are gone. Before, buying a rental or two and repeating the process for a few years was all you had to do to find […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 07:02:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rookie Reply: Estimating Rehab Costs, Finding “Hard Money,” &amp; Tax Planning</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-371</link><description>Need to estimate rehab costs or calculate ARV (after-repair value) on a property? For new investors, these tricky tasks can often make or break a deal. But, as always, our […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 07:02:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Need a Financial Advisor? Start Here!</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-505</link><description>Most financial advisors aren’t what they seem. They paint themselves as stewards of your financial security, carefully analyzing every investment they put your money into. But that’s far from the […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 07:01:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Quick Guide to Virtual House Flipping</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/virtual-house-flipping</link><description>Virtual house flipping can be an exciting, lucrative way to get involved in real estate investing. But as with as any type of investment, it’s important to understand the finer details to determine where you fit in.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 20:41:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cash Flow Isn’t Dead: 4 Markets With The Highest Rent-to-Price Around</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-192</link><description>Cash flow real estate is hard to find. In almost any big city, making financial freedom-producing cash flow is becoming a pipe dream. But that doesn’t mean there still aren’t […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 07:02:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Renovations That’ll Instantly Increase Your Home Value (Part 2)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-899</link><description>With some often overlooked home renovations, you could boost your property’s value by tens, if not hundreds, of thousands of dollars. But which home renovations have the best bang for […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 07:02:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>More Units Doesn’t Mean More Money—Why a Single-Family Home Can Beat a Fourplex</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/why-multifamily-properties-are-not-always-better-than-single-family</link><description>Conventional wisdom suggests more units would equal more money, but the numbers don't always check out. Here's what the calculations look like.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 22:22:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>We’re Selling Our Rental for $1 Million—This Is How We’ll Use the Money to Make More</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/1031-investor-journal-two</link><description>Liz Zack and her husband began their 1031 exchange journey on their Brooklyn rental. After assembling the team and doing market research, they've narrowed their options down to five markets. What comes next?</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 22:16:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Making $140K/Year &amp; Retiring His Wife in 18 Months with “Rental Arbitrage”</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-370</link><description>Airbnb arbitrage is a real estate investing strategy that provides a low-cost, low-risk entry point for new investors. While you don’t get the appreciation or tax benefits of property ownership, […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 07:02:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Making $175K in Instant Equity on Her First Real Estate Deal</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-898</link><description>What if you could make six figures on your first real estate deal? “Yeah, right! Where am I going to find a property like that?” you say. What if we […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 07:02:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Investors: Stop Worrying About Interest Rates—Here’s Why Right Now Is the Time to Buy</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/investors-stop-worrying-about-rates-in-2024</link><description>Now that the new year buzz has settled and the reality of persistently high mortgage rates has set in, how should investors react?</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 23:23:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seeing Greene: Generational Wealth 101 and Getting Started in a Tough Market</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-897</link><description>Want to know how to set your kids up for LIFE? The answer is pretty simple: rental properties. Whether you plan on keeping them or giving them to your children […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 07:02:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Early Retirement at 36 by Doing What EVERY Entrepreneur Should</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-504</link><description>If you want to reach early retirement, especially in your thirties, you’ll need to take some big risks. Today’s guest turned down what would have been a dream salary to […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 07:01:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Here’s How To Earn Modern and Traditional Passive Income in 2024</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/how-to-earn-passive-income-in-2024</link><description>From stocks to real estate to crypto to advertising on your car, passive income is the core goal of any investor. So how can you make the most of your opportunities in 2024?</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 17:09:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>11 Tips To Generate Cash Flow When Interest Rates Are High</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/ways-to-generate-cash-flow-with-high-interest-rates</link><description>Rental properties have been one of the largest real estate industry sectors to be hit by the increase in interest rates. Investor purchases of single-family homes tumbled 29% in 2023, […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 16:27:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Multifamily Is Likely To Start Recovering in 2024—Here’s Why</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/multifamily-is-likely-to-recover-in-2024</link><description>In his recent article, BiggerPockets CEO Scott Trench did a great job enumerating all the reasons why multifamily is in the difficult position it’s in. If he had written these same […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 16:13:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Financial Freedom in 10 Years and $200K Cash Flow with a Small Portfolio</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-369</link><description>Reaching financial freedom in ten years or less with a small real estate portfolio!? While it might seem like a lofty goal, it’s very doable when you maximize your cash […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 07:02:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Renovations That’ll Instantly Increase Your Home Value (Part 1)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-896</link><description>Which home renovations will boost your property’s value and put you in a better position to sell? Or, if you’re not selling, how do you rake in even more equity […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 07:02:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Million-Dollar Question: Is College Still Worth It in 2024?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-191</link><description>Is college worth it? Many Americans are beginning to boldly state, “Nope!” But does the growing anti-higher education sentiment point to facts or fiction around the cost of college? We […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 07:02:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>9 House-Flipping Tips for the Risk-Averse From Two Experienced Flippers</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/house-flipping-tips-for-the-risk-averse</link><description>Pittsburgh-based investor and house flipper John Walker of Turnkey Investment Properties and his business partner, Jim Auten, usually have around 10 flips on the go at any time. When rates were low, […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 20:16:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Warren Buffett Is Investing in New Construction—Here’s Why You Might Want to as Well</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/warren-buffett-is-buying-construction-stocks-should-you</link><description>This article is presented by Park Street Homes. Read our editorial guidelines for more information. If you’ve been paying attention to news in the real estate sector, you will know that new […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 19:57:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>#Airbnbust One Year Later: Did the Short-Term Rental Industry Ever Collapse?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/airbnbust-one-year-later</link><description>At the beginning of 2023, we reported on the advent of #Airbnbust, a term coined by Amy Nixon and amplified by vacation property operators on social media to describe falling revenues […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 19:24:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BiggerNews: How Climate is Exploding Insurance, Building, and Investing Costs</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-895</link><description>The climate crisis is already here, and the cost of real estate is being directly affected. Insurance premiums are skyrocketing, costs to build are rising, and your reserves need to […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 07:02:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pay Less Tax to the IRS This Year With THESE Real Estate Tax Strategies</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-368</link><description>Want to pay less money to the IRS in 2024? We’ve got the real estate tax strategies to help you do just that. And get this—you don’t need a large […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 07:02:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Keep MORE of Your Inheritance From the IRS (Avoid These Tax Mistakes!)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-503</link><description>With solid tax planning, receiving an inheritance could provide an enormous boost on your journey to financial freedom. One misstep, on the other hand, and you could be lining Uncle […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 07:01:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Keller Williams Settles for $70M in NAR Lawsuit, Banks “Rocked” by RE Losses</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-190</link><description>Just when you thought the NAR lawsuit coverage was over, Keller Williams agrees to settle for $70M, bringing a big blow to real estate agent commissions. How will this impact […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 07:02:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Buy a Rental Property in 90 Days (or Less!)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-894</link><description>Here’s exactly how to buy your first rental property in ninety days or less. And guess what? You don’t need ANY real estate investing experience to do it. After watching […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 07:02:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>After Several Years of Investing, These Are My Fundamentals for Generating Passive Income</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/after-years-of-investing-these-are-my-fundamentals-for-passive-income</link><description>A good investment strategy starts with clarifying your goals. For most investors, that means financial freedom, but a big part of getting there comes from passive income. These are the fundamentals for earning it.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 18:32:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is the Bilt Rewards Mastercard the Next Big Thing for Investors?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/is-the-bilt-rewards-mastercard-a-big-deal-for-investors</link><description>This credit card already rewards renters for paying rent, but there's also a down payment and mortgage program on the way, leading investors to think that this could become a huge deal for their businesses.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 18:04:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Buy a Hotel: Breaking Down Tony’s FIRST Commercial Real Estate Deal</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-367</link><description>Commercial real estate investing might seem intimidating, but in many cases, this kind of rental property is even easier to buy than a single-family home. After two failed attempts, our […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 07:02:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2024’s New BRRR Strategy: BUILD, Rent, Refinance, Repeat</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-893</link><description>Though only in her thirties, Natalie Cloutier has built a nine-million dollar real estate portfolio with just eight properties. Her secret to success? The “build-to-rent” strategy that so many real […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 07:02:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why More Investors Are Turning to Mid-Term Rentals: It’s Just Math</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/investors-are-abandoning-short-term-rentals-and-converting-them-into-mid-term-rentals</link><description>Now that hundreds of cities and towns across the country are moving to ban or limit short-term rentals, investors who used to make bank off these properties have to readjust their strategies to stay in the game. Here's one way that they're doing it—and it's proving to be just as lucrative.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 22:04:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seeing Greene: How to Retire with Real Estate and Negotiate Your Loans</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-892</link><description>It’s not too late to retire with real estate, EVEN if you’re just getting started in your late fifties or have NO experience investing. On this Seeing Greene, David gives […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 07:02:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Money Apps, Habits, and Productivity Hacks That Helped Us Find FI</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-502</link><description>These personal finance apps, tools, products, and habits helped us reach financial independence, and they can do the same for you. If you’re on the road to FIRE or have […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 07:01:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>We Bought 5 Properties and 20-Plus Units by Copying Other People’s Strategies—Here’s What We Did</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/how-we-bought-five-properties-copying-other-investors</link><description>I love telling people that I have been a Brandon Turner copycat when it comes to my real estate investing career. While our backgrounds in finding real estate are a bit different, […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 21:27:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Multifamily Is at High Risk of Continuing Its Historic Crash in 2024—Here’s Why</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/multifamily-crash-to-continue-through-2024</link><description>The multifamily and commercial real estate crash is in full swing. As much as $2.7 trillion in wealth has been wiped out with a historic surge in cap rates and […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 20:56:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The EASIEST Way to Get into Real Estate Investing With NO Money</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-366</link><description>Choosing to wholesale real estate might be the EASIEST way to kick-start your real estate investing journey. You don’t need a ton of money and you don’t need to take […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 07:02:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Negotiate a Deal When It’s Under Contract</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-891</link><description>We’re about to share the secrets NO seller wants you to know about. These secrets could save you tens of thousands of dollars on your next home purchase, and most […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 07:02:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Fed’s Plan “Backfired,” Now They’re Scrambling</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-189</link><description>The Fed is putting us all in danger. With high rates, low inflation, a strong job market, and millions of Americans wishing they could buy a home (but can’t), we’re […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 07:02:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Ryan Haywood Used Investing and Deal Generation As a Way to Build Communities and Wealth</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/how-ryan-haywood-used-investing-and-deal-generation-as-a-way-to-build-communities-and-wealth</link><description>“You’re making too much money.” That’s what echoed in Missouri native Ryan Haywood’s ears after his boss decided to slash his commissions—a “sales haircut,” as it’s bitterly known in the […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 22:10:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Much Money Is Enough to Make You Happy? Most Americans Say $284,000, Others Say $1.2 Million</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-happiness-and-the-real-cost-of-joy</link><description>In a recent survey, 67% of respondents said that their happiness hinged on their ability to pay bills on time. Another 45% said homeownership made them happy. Others said they needed $1 million in the bank to be secure. So what is the true cost of happiness, and how much does it take to really sit back and relax?</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 21:50:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Working at Walmart Could Help Make You a Millionaire in Just a Few Years—Here’s How</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/working-at-walmart-can-help-you-earn-400-thousand-per-year</link><description>If you dream of becoming a real estate investor but work at Walmart, you could well be on your way to realizing your dream much sooner than you think. This […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 21:44:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>We Ranked Every NFL Team’s Real Estate Market and Found the Best Cash Flow Opportunities</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/ranking-every-nfl-real-estate-market</link><description>While we didn't get the matchup America wanted (Lions vs. Ravens), we do get to watch a 2020 rematch between the 49ers and the Chiefs. To prep for the game, we crunched the data on every team's real estate market and found which ones had the best potential for investors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 21:00:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>100% Bonus Depreciation Coming Back? (Do NOT File…Yet)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-890</link><description>The biggest real estate tax deduction is coming back. That’s right—100% bonus depreciation is almost cleared for a triumphant return as the House pushed a new tax bill to the […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 07:02:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Super Bowl Show: Which Host City Has the BEST Housing Market?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-188</link><description>It’s February, and you know what that means…Groundhog Day! Just kidding, it’s almost Super Bowl Sunday, so we’re tackling some of the top Super Bowl housing markets to see which […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 07:02:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Finance Friday: When to STOP Investing and Start Saving Cash Instead</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-501</link><description>Do you have a cash flow problem? You’re not alone! Dan invests in real estate, has a great W2 job, and maxes out his investment accounts. He wants to hit […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 07:01:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Build Generational Wealth Without Losing it Along the Way</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-889</link><description>Want to learn how to create generational wealth? You know, the type of wealth that your children’s children’s children’s children can rely on. The type of wealth that allows your […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 07:02:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>100% Bonus Depreciation Coming Back? (Do NOT File…Yet)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-187</link><description>The biggest real estate tax deduction is coming back. That’s right—100% bonus depreciation is almost cleared for a triumphant return as the House pushed a new tax bill to the […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 07:02:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rookie Reply: How to Analyze Deals Like a PRO (Use THESE Numbers &amp; Tools)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-365</link><description>You could spend HOURS breaking down deals for cash flow, cash-on-cash return, return on investment, price-to-rent ratio, and countless other metrics. What do these terms mean, and which one is […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 07:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Don’t Skimp: Using a Free Lease Template Will Cost You More in the Long Run</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/dont-use-free-lease-templates</link><description>A free lease template on a subreddit somewhere sounds like an appealing, low-cost option. But going the cheap route on your lease documents might actually cost you more than getting it right from the start. Here's how to do that.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 20:44:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Underinvestment in Real Estate Might Be the Next Big Hurdle for Investors, According to a New Report</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/millenials-set-to-inherit-trillions-of-dollars-worth-of-underinvested-homes</link><description>Baby boomers hold the vast majority of wealth in the U.S.—many estimates suggest over $17 trillion. Much of that wealth has come from their homes, many of which have been underinvested in over the last few decades. This means the next generation could be facing an avalanche of renovation costs.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 20:13:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The House Voted Passed a Bill That Could Bring Back 100% Bonus Depreciation—Here’s What Investors Need to Know</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/tax-relief-for-american-families-and-workers-act-could-bring-bonus-depcreciation-back</link><description>As of the end of 2022, 100% bonus depreciation was set to be phased out by the end of the decade. Now, with the Tax Relief for American Families and Workers Act of 2024, it looks like we could see bonus depreciation and other benefits stick around. Here's what you need to know about the bill.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 19:52:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>25 Properties at 27 Years Old by Building His Own Rentals</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-888</link><description>Do NOT buy rental properties. There’s a MUCH better way to build wealth. And we mean that literally, “building” wealth is the best path. At just twenty-seven years old, today’s […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 07:02:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Making $115K From a Nightmare First Deal (Cops, Evictions, and Break-Ins!)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-364</link><description>Is the fear of “what if?” stopping you from investing in real estate? You could learn a thing or two from today’s guest. Despite a “nightmare” first deal involving every […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 07:02:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seeing Greene: Your Last Chance Before the House-Buying “Tsunami” Hits?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-887</link><description>Got just enough savings to buy a rental property? Before you pull the trigger, you’ll want to hear today’s episode because you could be making a big mistake. Speaking of […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 07:02:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Start an Airbnb Business in a Brand New Market</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-363</link><description>Want to know how to start an Airbnb business? If you find the right deal and build an all-star team, you could squeeze a TON of cash flow from just […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 07:02:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FIRE Advice from Codie Sanchez, Ramit Sethi, Money with Katie, and More!</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-500</link><description>After 500 BiggerPockets Money episodes, we’ve learned a thing or two about financial independence. But, for this special episode, we wanted to find some of the best advice we’ve ever […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 07:01:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Where Home Prices Grew the Most (and the Least) in 2023</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/where-home-prices-grew-the-most-in-2023</link><description>The U.S. as a whole only grew by about 1% last year, but other markets saw huge gains and massive losses. From New York City to Jackson, Mississippi, we analyzed the 100 largest metros in the nation and measured their home price growth from 2022 to 2023.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:23:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Should You Buy Now or Wait? Here’s How to Mathematically Calculate Your Options</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/calculate-if-you-should-buy-real-estate-now-or-wait</link><description>With high home prices and higher interest rates, investors have been wondering if now is the right time to buy. While it depends on the market and, even more so, the deal itself, with a long-term mindset, you can make it work by "marrying the property and dating the rate." Here's how to calculate if now is the right time to buy a property.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 21:03:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Warren Buffett Is Wrong: Diversification Isn’t Just for Ignorant Investors</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/warren-buffett-is-wrong-diversification-is-not-just-for-ignorant-investors</link><description>The so-called Oracle of Omaha said that diversification is protection against ignorance, but isn't this strategy a necessary part of intelligent investing? Here's why diversification, especially in real estate, is so essential.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 20:47:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Choose a Real Estate Investing Market (Step-by-Step)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-886</link><description>Before you buy your first rental property, you’ll need to choose a real estate market. If you’re like many Americans, your own backyard may not offer what you want out […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 07:02:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>4 Hot Housing Markets We’d Have a “Quick Flip” or “Long-Term Rental” With</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-186</link><description>These hot housing markets could make any investor start to sweat. You’ve been longing for some cash flow connection, but your prayers have gone unanswered. You don’t know what you’re […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 07:02:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>$2 Trillion in Commercial Debt is Coming Due—What Does That Mean for the Industry?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/2-trillion-in-commercial-debt-is-set-to-come-due</link><description>Over the next four years, commercial debt bills will total a whopping $2.8 trillion---many of which are balloon payments. It's led to the steepest drop in commercial asset valuations in recent history and created tremendous anxiety amongst investors. Where does the market go from here?</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 22:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Budgeting Is Dead—Do This Instead and Watch Your Wealth Grow</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/budgeting-is-dead</link><description>A recent poll showed 60% of Americans are scared of the word "budget," so they wind up doing nothing at all. You don't have to budget, but you do have to track. Here's how.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 21:42:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BiggerNews: America’s Path to “Renter Nation” as Prices Rise, Rates Stay Put</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-885</link><description>The US economy has survived the past few years surprisingly well. But there’s one huge threat on the horizon no one is watching. With layoffs and bankruptcies already starting to […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 07:02:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Former top SpaceX exec Tom Ochinero sets up new VC firm, filings reveal</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/16/former-top-spacex-exec-tom-ochinero-sets-up-new-vc-firm-filings-reveal/</link><description>Former senior SpaceX executive Tom Ochinero is teaming up with SpaceX alum-turned-VC, Achal Upadhyaya, and one of Sequoia’s top finance leaders, Spencer Hemphill, on a new venture called Interlagos Capital, TechCrunch has learned. There is little public information available about Interlagos, and the trio did not respond to TechCrunch’s request for comment. The company was […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 23:01:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FLO is improving EV charging infrastructure</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/16/flo-is-improving-ev-charging-infrastructure/</link><description>Founded by Louis Tremblay, FLO is looking to build robust EV charging infrastructure that will create a reliable web for drivers to get to where they need to go.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 23:00:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Waymo begins robotaxi testing in Atlanta</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/16/waymo-begins-robotaxi-testing-in-atlanta/</link><description>Waymo, the self-driving company under Alphabet, began testing its robotaxis in Atlanta on Tuesday, adding another city to its ever-expanding testing and deployment domain. Over the next few months, Waymo will deploy a handful of cars driven manually by humans to gather mapping data and get familiar with Atlanta’s environment, Sandy Karp, a Waymo spokesperson, […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 22:55:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tesla ditches EV inventory price discounts as Elon Musk moves to ‘streamline’ sales and delivery</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/16/tesla-ditches-ev-inventory-discounts-to-streamline-sales-and-delivery/</link><description>Tesla has ended discounts on inventory across its electric vehicle lineup — even as sales for EVs have flagged — as part of a larger and vague plan by CEO Elon Musk to “streamline the whole Tesla sales and delivery system.” “It has become complex and inefficient,” Musk wrote in a post on X, the […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:59:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HR startup Rippling is in discussions to raise at a $13.4B valuation, up from $11.25B</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/16/hr-startup-rippling-is-in-discussions-to-raise-at-a-13-4b-valuation-up-from-11-25b/</link><description>Late-stage HR tech startup Rippling is raising new capital. The company’s new round, which has not yet closed, would inject $200 million into Rippling with another $670 million worth of shares being sold by existing stockholders, according to two people familiar with the deal.  This will be Rippling’s Series F and could raise its valuation […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:39:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Space startups are licking their lips after NASA converts $11B Mars mission into a free-for-all</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/16/space-startups-licking-their-lips-after-nasa-converts-11b-mars-mission-into-a-free-for-all/</link><description>Considering how heavily both primes and space startups have been investing in interplanetary capability, this announcement arguably amounts to a historic windfall.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:27:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kickstarter launches pre-orders for completed campaigns</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/16/kickstarter-late-pledges/</link><description>Once a Kickstarter campaign is complete, you need to turn to a creator’s own page to pre-order the products — that is, until now. Today, Kickstarter announces that it is (finally!) including pre-order functionality once the campaign is over as part of its core platform. It calls the feature “Late pledges,” and the platform says […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 21:00:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Intel and others commit to building open generative AI tools for the enterprise</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/16/intel-and-others-commit-to-building-open-generative-ai-tools-for-the-enterprise/</link><description>Intel and other tech heavyweights say they'll work together to build open generative AI tools for businesses, as part of a new Linux Foundation organization.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 20:20:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A crypto wallet maker’s warning about an iMessage bug sounds like a false alarm</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/16/a-crypto-wallet-makers-warning-about-an-imessage-bug-sounds-like-a-false-alarm/</link><description>A crypto wallet maker claimed this week that hackers may be targeting people with an iMessage “zero-day” exploit — but all signs point to an exaggerated threat, if not a downright scam. Trust Wallet’s official X (previously Twitter) account wrote that “we have credible intel regarding a high-risk zero-day exploit targeting iMessage on the Dark […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 19:51:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump’s Truth Social plans to launch a live TV streaming platform</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/16/trumps-truth-social-plans-to-launch-a-live-tv-streaming-platform/</link><description>The streaming service will launch in three phases and will focus on "news networks" and "religious channels," as well as "family-friendly" offerings.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 18:47:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Betaworks bets on AI agents in latest ‘Camp’ cohort</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/16/betaworks-bets-on-ai-agents-in-latest-camp-cohort/</link><description>Betaworks is embracing the AI trend not with yet another LLM, but instead a clutch of agent-type models automating everyday tasks that nevertheless aren’t so simple to define. The investor’s latest “Camp” incubator trained up and funded nine AI agent startups they hope will take on today’s more tedious tasks. The use cases for many […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 18:02:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple will now let users in the EU download apps through web sites, not just the App Store</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/16/apple-web-distribution-ios/</link><description>Apple is opening up web distribution for iOS apps targeting users in the European Union starting Tuesday. Developers who opt in — and who meet Apple’s criteria, including app notarization requirements — will be able to offer iPhone apps for direct download to EU users from their own websites. It’s a massive change for a […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 18:00:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bay Bridge Ventures is raising $200M for a new climate fund, filings show</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/16/bay-bridge-ventures-climate-fund/</link><description>Bay Bridge Ventures' fundraising efforts come at a time when venture investors appear to be increasingly bullish on climate tech. 
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 17:56:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Evolution Equity Partners raises $1.1B for new cybersecurity and AI fund</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/16/evolution-equity-partners-raises-1-1b-for-new-cybersecurity-and-ai-fund/</link><description>Evolution Equity Partners, a growth capital firm based in NYC, has raised $1.1 billion for a new cyber- and AI-focused fund.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 17:32:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Investors and founders can meet their match with Cherub, the ‘Raya of angel investing’</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/16/cherub-the-raya-of-angel-investing-is-reinventing-angel-rounds-with-a-950-subscription/</link><description>Jaclyn Johnson and Angeline Vuong were on a hike deliberating how hard it can be for people to get started in angel investing when they realized they had stumbled upon a startup idea.  Today they are the co-founders of Cherub, a marketplace that pairs angel investors with entrepreneurs. Vuong spent nearly five years working in […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 17:07:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Consumer tech investing is still hot for Maven Ventures, securing $60M for Fund IV</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/16/consumer-tech-investing-maven-ventures-60m-fund-iv/</link><description>Overall, 16% of Maven’s portfolio companies have reached a minimum $500 million exit or valuation, which is 10x industry average, the firm said.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 17:00:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TechCrunch Minute: Why Tesla’s big layoffs happened, and what comes next</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/16/techcrunch-minute-why-teslas-big-layoffs-happened-and-what-comes-next/</link><description>Tesla’s layoffs and executive departures took a bite out of its share price this week. The well-known electric vehicle company shed around 10% of its staff, impacting an estimated 14,000 people or more. Two well-known executives also decided it was time to move on. In response to the news, shares of Tesla lost ground. The […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 17:00:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Silicon Valley artist Danielle Baskin launches Moonlight, an online tarot platform</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/16/silicon-valley-prankster-danielle-baskin-launches-moonlight-an-online-tarot-platform/</link><description>You might know Bay Area artist Danielle Baskin for her viral, immersive art installations and jokes. Her newest project, Moonlight, is certainly not a joke, but she still finds her characteristic whimsy when describing her new venture: “It’s SaaS for witches.” She’s not kidding. Moonlight is a free online tarot platform, where you can draw […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 16:34:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Substack’s Notes feature is getting more Twitter-like capabilities</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/16/substacks-notes-feature-is-getting-more-twitter-like-capabilities/</link><description>Substack is adding new capabilities to its Twitter-like Notes feature that bring it more in-line with the social network now known as X. The company announced on Tuesday that users can now post videos directly to Notes in the Substack app and on the web. Users can now also embed Notes on external webpages. The […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 16:00:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WhatsApp is adding filters to easily find messages</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/16/whatsapp-is-adding-filters-to-easily-find-messages/</link><description>For those who use WhatsApp more like an inbox, the app will now become more useful. WhatsApp on Tuesday announced a handful of new chat filters for the app to access certain types of messages easily: All, Unread and Groups. The “All” filter is selected by default and shows you an unfiltered version of your […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 16:00:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Parents Paying for Their Children’s Crimes</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/13/michigan-school-shooting-parents</link><description>Experts warn about a wave of legal consequences for parents like the Crumbleys, while some states consider prosecutions for kids as young as 10.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I Had a Tough Job at My Brooklyn Jail: Keeping Men From Taking Their Own Lives</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/12/brooklyn-jail-suicide-prevention-aide</link><description>As a suicide prevention aide, I had to make sure my fellow detainees didn’t harm themselves. It was surprisingly easy to get such a complex job.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Supreme Court Case on Homelessness May Limit Prisoner Rights and Expand Executions</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/10/supreme-court-homeless-grants-pass-originalism</link><description>In Grants Pass v. Johnson, a town in Oregon asks the court to reconsider what constitutes “cruel and unusual punishments”.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What an Eclipse Lockdown Reveals about Dignity in Prisons and Jails</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/06/eclipse-new-york-prison-discrimination</link><description>Recent lawsuits regarding the rights of incarcerated people and guards include gender, religious discrimination, and the right to watch the eclipse</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I Made 13 Cents an Hour as a Prison Janitor. Here’s Why I Donated My Wages to Gaza Relief</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/05/prison-janitor-donates-gaza-relief-islam</link><description>It’s a common misconception that once someone enters jail or prison, they lose their interest in the outside world.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Mississippi’s Jim Crow Laws Still Haunt Black Voters Today</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/04/mississippi-voting-rights-history-disenfranchisement</link><description>After the U.S. Civil War, white supremacists used felony disenfranchisement to suppress the Black vote. Even now, restoring rights has hit a roadblock.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Terror, Murder and Jim Crow Laws: Inside Mississippi’s Racial Voter Intimidation History</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/04/mississippi-voting-rights-history-discrimination</link><description>Black Mississippians’ right to vote has constantly been under threat. A recent bill that would have restored voting rights to thousands died in committee.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Marshall Project Wins Prestigious National Magazine Award for General Excellence</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/03/the-marshall-project-wins-prestigious-national-magazine-award-for-general-excellence</link><description>This is the third time the news site has won for the breadth and ambition of its coverage.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>He Faces Execution. His Lawyers May Have Earned Less Than $4 per Hour.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/03/execution-missouri-brian-dorsey-fees</link><description>Some death penalty lawyers get paid the same no matter how long they work on a case. Critics say it’s a perverse incentive when a life is at stake.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Ain’t Just Texas: More States Want Power to Wage ‘War’ on Migrants</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/03/30/texas-georgia-tennessee-immigration</link><description>Several states are sending troops to the Southern border, even as the legal battle over immigration enforcement rages on.</description><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Even Where Abortion Is Legal, People in Jail Face Huge Barriers</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/03/26/jail-abortion-policy-study-illinois-oregon</link><description>New reviews of jail policies in 13 states found vague, confusing or nonexistent guidelines and major hurdles to obtaining an abortion.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 18:04:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Who Can and Can’t Vote in Mississippi: A Guide to the State’s Lifetime Voting Ban</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/03/25/mississippi-voting-rights-ban-felony-conviction</link><description>This guide offers details about the state’s disenfranchisement laws and how you may still be able to vote from jail, even with a conviction.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>They’re Not Cops. They Don’t Have Guns. But They’re Responding to More 911 Calls.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/03/23/police-emergency-mental-health-911</link><description>A new generation of first responders is handling mental health calls and other emergencies in cities across the U.S.</description><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>For a Handful of Lawyers in Cuyahoga County, Juvenile Cases Are Big Business</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/03/22/kids-lawyer-cuyahoga-county-fees</link><description>Judges steered two-thirds of cases involving kids accused of crimes to just 10 lawyers in one year, according to a Marshall Project - Cleveland analysis.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Her Story</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/03/22/news-inside-issue-16</link><description>Issue 16 highlights women’s experiences in the U.S. criminal justice system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cleveland Promised Oversight of Police Surveillance. The Work Hasn’t Been Done.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/03/21/cleveland-police-surveillance-cameras-oversight</link><description>In 2022, Mayor Bibb pledged to form a panel to address concerns over cameras and high-tech tools. It’s finally set to happen.</description><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When Police Encounters With Autistic People Turn Fatal</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/03/16/california-police-autism-disability</link><description>The death of a 15-year-old is once again raising questions about training on neurodivergent and mental health diagnoses among law enforcement agencies.</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Boxer Shorts Blues: My Path to Gender-Affirming Underwear in Prison</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/03/15/nonbinary-prison-uniform-boxer-shorts</link><description>Nonbinary writer K.C. Johnson soon learned that behind bars, even their underwear was subject to deliberations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ohio Is Among 34 States That Criminalize People Living With HIV. Who Gets Prosecuted?</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/03/13/ohio-hiv-prosecutions-assault-discrimination</link><description>Cuyahoga County prosecutes the most people under laws with heightened penalties.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>He’s in an Ohio Prison for Exposing Someone to HIV - Even Though He Couldn’t Transmit the Virus</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/03/13/hiv-laws-ohio-prison</link><description>Ohio has six laws that criminalize living with HIV, leading to at least 200 prosecutions in recent years.</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Truth About Whole-Body Scans</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/a-to-z-guides/features/truth-about-whole-body-scans?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>What to know about whole-body CT scans and DEXA scans for body composition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 23:15:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When to Call a Pediatrician</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/parenting/baby/features/when-call-pediatrician?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Your child is sick. Do you know if you should call the pediatrician, or wait? Use this guide to know when to make the call.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 22:44:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Your Baby’s Reflux: What to Do</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/parenting/baby/features/soothing-baby-reflux?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>When is spitting up normal, and when is it a problem? Learn signs to watch out for, as a pediatrician and parent who’s been there share their wisdom.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 22:41:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How New Ideas Are Changing Advanced Breast Cancer Research</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/breast-cancer/features/breast-cancer-new-research?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>There are many reasons for women who have advanced breast cancer to be hopeful. For starters, the way we treat and study advanced, or metastatic, breast cancer is improving.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 18:01:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Heart Attack Hits Young Women, But Doctors Often Unaware</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/heart-disease/news/20240416/scad-heart-attacks-a-ticking-time-bomb-for-young-women?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>SCAD accounts for 1 in 3 acute heart events in younger women. Many doctors are not aware it exists.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 17:52:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Afford Biologics for RA</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/features/biologics-ra-pay?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Strategies for reducing the out-of-pocket cost for RA biologics, getting financial help, and researching viable drug options.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 17:44:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When and How to Stop Biologics for RA</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/features/misinformation-stopping-ra-biologic-therapy?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>What happens when you stop taking a biologic for RA? Learn more about when and how to go off a biologic drug.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 17:43:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Should You Try Another Biologic for RA?</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/features/first-biologic-ra-not-working?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Should you try another biologic for RA if the first one isn't working? Find out when it might be time to switch drugs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 17:42:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biologics for RA: Connecting With Others</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/features/ra-reach-out-biologic-users?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Rheumatoid arthritis support groups are great for tips and comfort, but not medical advice. Learn how to get support when you take a biologic for RA.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 17:40:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RA and Biologics: Why Time Matters</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/rheumatoid-arthritis/features/ra-biologics-drug-time?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Biologics for rheumatoid arthritis can take a few months to work their best. Find out when you can expect a biologic drug for RA to start working.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 17:38:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Crohn’s Disease Changed My Routines</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/ibd-crohns-disease/crohns-disease/features/crohns-routines?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Living with Crohn's disease means you need to be flexible in your daily routines. Learn one woman's tricks for living with Crohn's disease.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 23:52:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Stop Nighttime Coughing</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/cold-and-flu/features/nighttime-relief?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Nighttime coughs may affect your sleep quality. Learn tips for relief so you can get the rest you need for healing.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 15:57:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Even Women Doctors Find Their Symptoms Aren’t Taken Seriously</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/women/features/women-doctors-symptoms-dismissed?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Female doctors-turned-patients share their insights about why women’s symptoms are so often dismissed – and how to fix it.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 11:26:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Could U.S. Measles Cases Break a Record This Year? What to Know</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/children/news/20240412/us-measles-cases-record-what-to-know?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Within the first 3 months of 2024, the U.S. surpassed the total number of measles cases recorded in all of 2023. Could the nation break a record this year? Here's what to know.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 18:55:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Emulsifiers Make Food Appetizing yet Bring Health Dangers</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/diet/news/20240412/emulsifiers-in-food-may-bring-health-dangers?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Emulsifiers don’t necessarily equal junk food. Such substances can be found in many foods that are often considered healthy, such as some low-fat Greek yogurts, trail mix bars, or oat milk.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 18:44:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tylenol During Pregnancy Not Linked to Higher Risk of ADHD, Autism</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/baby/news/20240412/tylenol-during-pregnancy-wont-increase-risk-of-adhd-autism?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>New findings should bring comfort to pregnant people who need pain relief, given that full-dose aspirin and nonsteroidal anti-inflammatory drugs have been shown to pose serious risks to pregnant patients.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 16:08:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tips and Strategies for Managing Life With Children With ADHD</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/add-adhd/childhood-adhd/features/medication-strategies-adhd?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Parents and caregivers of children with ADHD share their advice on how to help manage symptoms, teach coping skills, and improve daily life.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 16:58:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Retool Your Parenting Skills When Raising a Child With ADHD</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/add-adhd/childhood-adhd/features/retool-parenting-skills-adhd?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>A new diagnosis calls for an adjustment to your discipline strategy. Here’s what may work best for your child.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 16:58:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Helping Your Child Come to Terms With Their ADHD</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/add-adhd/childhood-adhd/features/help-child-adhd?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>A new diagnosis can bring relief -- but also new worries. Here’s how to navigate them with your child.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 16:58:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Have Health Questions? Ask S.A.R.A.H., an AI Health Assistant</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/a-to-z-guides/news/20240410/who-launches-new-interactive-health-ai-named-sarah?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>S.A.R.A.H., which stands for Smart AI Resource Assistant for Health, uses Open AI’s GPT (generative pretrained transformer) large language model to answer a wide range of health questions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:44:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Deal With Side Effects of Multiple Myeloma Treatment</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/cancer/multiple-myeloma/features/multiple-myeloma-treatment-side-effects?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Diagnosed with multiple myeloma? WebMD shows how you can conquer treatment-related side effects.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 21:44:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Find an OB/GYN Supportive of Transgender Pregnancies</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/baby/features/ob-gyn-doctors-for-transgender-pregnancies?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Many transgender men and nonbinary people can carry a pregnancy. Here are tips to find an OB/GYN who will offer supportive transgender pregnancy care.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 20:57:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What’s Next in Health Care for Older Adults: Questions and Answers With John Whyte, MD</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/blog-aging-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>As WebMD’s chief medical officer, John Whyte, MD, is in a unique position to see both the current state of medical care for America’s older adults and the way things are trending for the future. We asked him to share his insight on a few topics, along with a bit of advice.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 19:25:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lessons In Cleaning House</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/parenting/features/cleaning-house?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Quick tips that encourage your child to help with cleaning the house</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 19:25:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Your ‘Sleep Style’ Can Determine Your Long-Term Health</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/sleep-disorders/news/20240409/how-your-sleep-style-can-determine-long-term-health?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>The way you sleep – or don’t -- can be surprisingly impactful. The type of sleeper you are may profoundly influence the roadmap your health takes for a decade or longer. Here's what to know.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 19:18:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When Autism Is Diagnosed in Adults</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/brain/autism/features/autism-adult-diagnosis?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Can you get diagnosed with autism spectrum disorder as an adult? Find out what that is like.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 21:25:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Saying ‘Hello, Stranger’ Could Be Key to Better Health</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/mental-health/news/20240408/saying-hello-stranger-could-be-key-to-better-health?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>We tend to keep to ourselves in public – but experts say chatting with acquaintances and bystanders could be good for our mood and physical health.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 18:25:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Collagen Supplements for Skin, Hair, and Nails: What to Know</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/vitamins-and-supplements/news/20240408/collagen-supplements-for-skin-hair-nails-what-to-know?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Data on collagen supplements is more plentiful than in the past, though still murky. Collagen supplements appear to be safe to take and somewhat effective, depending on what problem you’re trying to solve, what type of supplement you take, and which ingredients are included. Here's what to know.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 18:05:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IgA Nephropathy and Social Support</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/a-to-z-guides/features/iga-nephropathy-stay-social?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>IgA nephropathy can be challenging, but a support system makes it easier to manage. Learn how to take steps to stay connected to your community when dealing with this disease.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 14:36:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Your Mental and Kidney Health</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/a-to-z-guides/features/iga-nephropathy-mental-kidney-health?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>IgA nephropathy can raise your chances of depression, anxiety, and stress. Here are some steps you can take to manage your mental and kidney health.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 14:35:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Influencer: How Finding Her Voice Inspired a Community of Self-Healers</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/ibd-crohns-disease/crohns-disease/features/influencer-finding-voice-inspiring-community-self-healers?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>An Instagram influencer helps other people with Crohn’s and IBD heal themselves</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 07:49:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Need for Better Minority Enrollment in Multiple Myeloma Clinical Trials</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/cancer/multiple-myeloma/features/multiple-myeloma-minority-clinical-trials?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>African Americans are more likely to develop multiple myeloma but are underrepresented in clinical trials. Here’s why and what can be done about it.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 15:43:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How My New Golf Hobby Made Me Healthier in Unexpected Ways</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/fitness-exercise/news/20240405/spillover-effect-helps-make-hobbies-even-healthier?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>The “spillover effect” teaches us that doing one healthy thing can lead to a whole lot more – if you can stick with it and move past the bad shots.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 18:05:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Yoga Fitness</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/pain-management/features/yoga-fitness?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>There are many traditional fitness modalities from Asia that aim to cultivate the body and spirit together. Let's look at yoga.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 16:03:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tips to Feel Better All Day</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/pain-management/features/more-energy?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>What are the most important steps to follow if you want to feel good from morning to night?</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 16:03:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Yoga for Stress Management</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/pain-management/features/yoga-for-stress-management?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>The benefits of yoga include decreased stress and tension, increased strength and balance, increased flexibility, and lowered blood pressure -- so isn't it time you started?</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 16:03:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pick the Right Supplements and Vitamins</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/pain-management/features/what-vitamin-should-i-take?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Should you take supplements? Can they do you more harm than good? Learn if you need them and how to pick the right ones for you.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 16:03:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Herbs, Vitamins, and Supplements Used to Enhance Mood</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/pain-management/features/herbs-vitamins-and-supplements-used-to-enhance-mood?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Some supplements reportedly boost mood -- but what does the evidence show for mood enhancers?</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 16:03:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Managing Sore Muscles and Aches and Pains</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/pain-management/features/art-sore-muscles-joint-pain?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>It's normal to have sore muscles after you work out, play sports, or even do housework. Here are tips to help ease sore muscles at home.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 16:02:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Easing Stress, Easing Arthritis Symptoms</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/pain-management/features/reduce-stress-ease-pain?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Learn how to reduce stress and manage arthritis symptoms with these simple tips from WebMD.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 16:02:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Chef: How the Kitchen Can Heal and Help You Love Food Again</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/ibd-crohns-disease/crohns-disease/features/chef-kitchen-healed-helped-loved-food-again?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>A chef with Crohn’s disease found the kitchen was the best place to heal and to rediscover his love of food.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 13:02:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How the Body Reacts to Grief, and What It Can Mean</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/mental-health/news/20240404/how-the-body-reacts-to-grief-and-what-it-can-mean?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Fatigue, headaches, stomach pain, and a higher risk of heart disease: Although these things may not make you think of grief at first, many people who have a significant loss get these and other physical symptoms.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 17:47:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>6 Reasons to Drink Water</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/diet/features/6-reasons-to-drink-water?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>While we may not need eight glasses a day, there are plenty of reasons to drink water.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 16:02:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Seeker: How Searching for ‘Weird’ Holistic Remedies Make You Stronger</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/ibd-crohns-disease/crohns-disease/features/seeker-searching-weird-holistic-remedies-stronger?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Seeking out alternative remedies such as acupuncture, Chinese herbs, prenatal yoga, and baby food helped manage my Crohn’s.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 13:01:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Medications for Nasal Polyps</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/allergies/features/nasal-polyps-meds?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Learn about the many medications available to treat nasal polyps.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 22:41:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Therapeutic Ways to Alter Negative Thoughts</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/depression/features/therapy-change-negative-thoughts?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>We all have negative thoughts. We all think in ways that aren't healthy. Learning to recognize that, and to find different, more helpful ways to think, is critical to our well-being,</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 22:40:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Staying With Your Depression Treatment Plan</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/depression/features/stick-with-depression-treatment-plan?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>People go off their antidepressants for many reasons, but quitting too early could cause your symptoms to come back.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 22:39:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Truth About Belly Fat</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/diet/features/the-truth-about-belly-fat?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Do you have too much belly fat? Reducing visceral fat may be as simple as diet, exercise, sleep, and stress management. WebMD shares what works.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 21:13:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Therapy Can Help During Life-Changing Events Like COVID</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/anxiety-panic/news/20240403/how-therapy-can-help-life-changing-events?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Research shows that forms of talk therapy like cognitive-behavioral therapy or dialectical behavioral therapy helped people better cope with anxiety during COVID. Here's what to know and how it can help you today.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 18:52:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cancer Caregiving From Long Distance</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/cancer/features/cancer-caregiving-long-distance?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Cancer caregiving is never easy, and when you’re doing it long distance, there are extra challenges.  Here’s what you can do to provide support.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 17:59:56 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>