<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 13:33:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Behavior of Crowds not Wisdom of Crowds</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/06/21/behavior-of-crowds-not-wisdom-of-crowds/</link><description>When behavioral crowds are roiling the markets, as they are now, best idea active equity has an excellent chance of outperforming.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 17:54:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Olive Garden owner’s CEO says fast food is so expensive you might as well have a sit-down meal</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/06/21/olive-garden-ceo-rick-cardenas-darden-fast-food-restaurant-expensive-inflation/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/GettyImages-1573754918-e1718990067111.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>McDonald’s and Wendy’s have vexed budget-conscious consumers, and chains like Chili’s and Olive Garden are ready to take advantage.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 18:28:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is the Outright Ban on a US Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC) a Mistake?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/06/20/is-the-outright-ban-on-a-us-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc-a-mistake/</link><description>Instead of outright banning a US CBDC, wouldn’t it be preferrable to establish clear and enforceable legislative guardrails?</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 17:00:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Say goodbye to the 20% down payment. Zillow says you’ll need to put down roughly 35%, or almost $128,000, to afford a typical home</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/06/21/zillow-buyers-need-35-down-payment-instead-of-20-typical-home-2024/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/GettyImages-1300340919-1-e1718989191620.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>In Los Angeles, a median-income household would need to put roughly 80% down to afford a typical home and its monthly payments in the city, according to Zillow.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 18:11:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Concerned About Market Concentration and Lofty Valuations? Consider Small Caps</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/06/19/concerned-about-market-concentration-and-lofty-valuations-consider-small-caps/</link><description>Investors are showing increased concern about large-cap stocks due to high market concentration and lofty stock valuations. Other factors combine to make a compelling case for small caps.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 17:16:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Supreme Court upholds ‘common sense’ law banning domestic abusers from gun possession in 8-1 decision</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/06/21/supreme-court-guns-domestic-violence-rahimi/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/GettyImages-1232481853-e1718987032236.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>A week after overturning a ban on bump stocks, the court allowed a law than bans guns for people under restraining orders.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 17:24:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Is Systems Thinking? A Primer with Applications for Sustainable Investing</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/06/18/what-is-systems-thinking-a-primer-with-applications-for-sustainable-investing/</link><description>Systems thinking is gaining in popularity in many fields including economics, finance, and investment management. Learn what it means and how it's being applied to sustainable investing.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 16:33:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Incoming Washington Post editor won’t take the job after newsroom revolt: ‘The body is rejecting the transfusion’</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/06/21/washington-post-editor-robert-winnett-revolt/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/GettyImages-2155587478-e1718985998119.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Post staff had revolted at the leadership change. “The body is rejecting the transfusion,” one said.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 17:12:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: My Value Creation Journey</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/06/14/book-review-my-value-creation-journey/</link><description>Bartley J. Madden has produced a book that challenges business leaders and investment professionals to think outside the box systematically to solve difficult problems.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 18:04:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>90% of C-suite executives believe their company promotes worker well-being. Why do only 60% of workers agree?</title><link>https://fortune.com/well/2024/06/21/worker-wellbeing-executive-knowledge-gap/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/GettyImages-100377996-e1718895624114.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The third annual Workplace Well-being report from Deloitte indicates a major gulf in understanding between executives and employees.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>