<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 07:54:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Report: Brazil Could Ditch Nike as Kit Supplier After Receiving Massive Offer</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/07/report-brazil-could-ditch-nike-as-kit-supplier-after-receiving-massive-offer/soccer/</link><description>Brazilian news outlet reports CBF has received an offer worth more than five times what Nike currently pays them from either Adidas or Puma</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:29:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'DWTS' Cheryl Burke Plans 40th Birthday By Herself, Friends Don't Care</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/07/dwts-cheryl-burke-plans-40th-birthday-by-herself-friends-dont-care/</link><description>Cheryl Burke is turning 40, but is planning a party by herself and for herself -- the reason being, according to her, is that her good pals don't give a rip ... and she's salty about it. The "Dancing With the Stars" alum threw up a TikTok this week…</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 07:54:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>USL’s Orange County Try to Capture Magic with New Cup Kit</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/06/usls-orange-county-sc-try-to-capture-some-magic-with-new-cup-kit/soccer/</link><description>Kit is inspired by designs worn in 1910s, when U.S. Open Cup started, and will be worn when OCSC takes on Loudoun United in Round of 32 on Tuesday, May 7</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 03:31:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kendall Jenner Reunites with Bad Bunny at Met Gala, Same Hotel</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/07/kendall-jenner-bad-bunny-reunite-met-gala-looking-cozy-party-hotel-overnight/</link><description>Kendall Jenner seems to be back with Bad Bunny -- at least that's what it looked like at the Met Gala ... where they were seen getting cozy, and possibly even staying at the same hotel. The model and pop star were photographed hanging out at an…</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 07:54:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Panama Football Unveils New National Team Crest</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/06/panamanian-football-federation-unveils-new-national-team-crest/soccer/</link><description>Crest depicts a harpy eagle — the national bird of Panama — with each feather representing one of the country's 10 provinces</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ric Flair Heated Altercation W/ Bar Employee Caught On Video, Fight Nearly Ensues</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/07/ric-flair-piesanos-restaurant-verbal-altercation-argument-fight-video-wwe/</link><description>Ric Flair nearly handed out figure four leg locks outside a pizza joint in Florida after a heated argument at the bar ended with a challenge to fight in the parking lot ... and the entire ordeal was captured on video! The 3-minute long video shows…</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 07:54:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Snoop Dogg’s Gin &amp; Juice Brand Becomes Presenting Sponsor of Arizona Bowl</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/06/snoop-doggs-gin-juice-brand-becomes-presenting-sponsor-of-arizona-bowl/college/</link><description>The Arizona Bowl announced a multi-year partnership with 17-time Grammy Award winning artist Snoop Dogg that makes his alcohol brand, Gin &amp; Juice by Dre and Snoop, the game’s presenting sponsor.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 21:55:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Johnny Depp's French Movie Was Not 'Pulled' from Theaters, Had Limited Run</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/07/johnny-depp-french-movie-jeanne-du-barry-not-pulled-limited-run-theaters/</link><description>Johnny Depp's new movie has been accused of being a stinker in terms of getting asses in seats -- and some have even claimed it's getting yanked because of that ... but it's BS. Here's the deal ... there are social media posts floating around that…</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 07:54:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bayern Munich Goes All In On Red With 2024-25 Home Kits</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/06/bayern-munich-goes-all-in-on-red-with-2024-25-home-kits/soccer/</link><description>Sponsor logo on left sleeve contains QR code that fans can scan to participate in exclusive promotions throughout the 2024-25 season</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:48:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rick Ross Miami Mansion Undergoing $20 Mil Renovation Amid Drake Beef</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/07/rick-ross-mansion-drake-20-million-renovations-star-island/</link><description>Rick Ross' estate caught a few strays in his short-lived rap battle with Drake but the Bawse is currently making $20 million tweaks to his property as we speak! Last weekend, construction spearheaded by celebrity homebuilder Manny Angelo Varas,…</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 07:54:25 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>