<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 06:48:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Brooklyn Nets Subtly Update Logos, Introduce New Secondary Mark For 2024-25 Season</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/07/brooklyn-nets-subtly-update-logos-introduce-new-secondary-mark-for-2024-25-season/basketball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Brooklyn Nets have made several changes to their logo set for the 2024-25 season, including introducing a new secondary logo that depicts a stylized net.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 19:12:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Bob's Burgers' Star Jay Johnston Pleads Guilty in Jan. 6 Capitol Riot</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/08/bobs-burgers-jay-johnston-pleads-guilty-capitol-riot/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Jay Johnston -- best known for the animated sitcom "Bob's Burgers" -- is pleading guilty to his involvement in the Jan. 6 U.S. Capitol attack. The comedian entered his plea Monday to a single count of obstructing officers during a civil disorder.…</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 06:48:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PSG Pay Homage to Eiffel Tower With New Away Kit – Plus More European Kit Launches</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/05/psg-pay-homage-to-eiffel-tower-with-new-away-kit-plus-more-european-kit-launches/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Other clubs unveiling 2024-25 kits include Napoli, Wolves, West Ham, Stade de Reims, Mallorca, Real Betis, Villarreal, Bochum, Stuttgart, Mainz 05 and Union Berlin</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 20:20:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Hawk Tuah' Girl Haliey Welch Gets Emotional at First Paid Appearance</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/08/hawk-tuah-haliey-welch-celebration-paid-appearance-emotional/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>"Hawk Tuah" is enriching Haliey Welch's life -- literally and figuratively -- and she's getting a lil' emotional about the whole thing as she cashes in on her instant celebrity. In the video, obtained by TMZ, you can see Haliey getting an…</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 06:48:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Look at the New NHL Practice Jersey Design</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/04/a-look-at-the-new-nhl-practice-jersey-design/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Thanks to the Utah Hockey Club, we got ourselves a look at the new NHL practice jersey design. With the switch from Adidas to Fanatics for 2024-25, we knew there’d be some changes to the on-ice NHL uniform. We’ve already seen that each team’s jersey will now include the Fanatics</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 22:20:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alec Baldwin Wins Huge Victory Day Before 'Rust' Manslaughter Trial Begins</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/08/alec-baldwin-rust-shooting-producer-manslaughter-trial/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Alec Baldwin just got a huge part of the prosecution's case thrown out ... a day before his manslaughter trial kicks off. The judge ruled prosecutors cannot introduce evidence of Baldwin's role as a producer in the film ... something that was a…</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 06:48:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MLB Teams Wearing USA-Themed Caps Today for Fourth of July</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/04/mlb-teams-wearing-usa-themed-caps-today-for-fourth-of-july/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>All 30 Major League Baseball teams will wear stars-and-stripes-themed caps on-field during today’s games in honour of Independence Day in the United States. This year, all 30 clubs will wear a cream-coloured crown, with teams again having the option of a red or navy blue visor and button. One more</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 16:34:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kyle Richards Defends Pal Kesha From Body-Shamers, 'Focus on Yourself'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/08/kyle-richards-defends-kesha-from-body-shamers/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Kyle Richards can't wrap her head around people needing to comment on women's bodies in this day and age -- this in response to body-shamers attacking her pal Kesha. We caught up with the "RHOBH" star at LAX Monday following her Aspen trip with the…</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 06:48:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2024 MLB All-Star Game Uniforms Revealed</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/03/2024-mlb-all-star-game-uniforms-revealed/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Major League Baseball has officially unveiled the uniforms their best players will wear when they take the field at Globe Life Field in Arlington later this month. The uniforms, as you’d expect, incorporate some of that Texas style, with an Old West style typeface across the chest and again in</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 02:02:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kevin Bacon Posts Thirst Trap to Celebrate 66th Birthday</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/08/kevin-bacon-thirst-trap-shirtless-celebrate-66-birthday/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Kevin Bacon is still feeling sexy well into his 60s ... because he's fishing for likes with a bare-chested photo. The actor is celebrating his 66th birthday today and he's marking the occasion with a topless thirst trap ... showing off his abs,…</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 06:48:46 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>