<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:28:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Bullish Breadth (Act Fast)</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/bullish-breadth-act-fast/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, it's Ross Givens here with the Chart of the Day. The percentage of stocks trading above their 50-day moving average, a key metric for medium-term momentum, has surged, signaling a potential continuation of the bull market. Nearly double the levels seen during the April pullback, it mirrors the market's upward trajectory observed from February to mid-March. This resurgence indicates an opportunity for swift action. Learn more about the implications in my detailed analysis below. The post Bullish Breadth (Act Fast) appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden plans to target tariffs on Chinese tech, including EVs</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/10/biden-plans-to-target-tariffs-on-chinese-tech-including-evs/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/10111652/2024-05-10T010515Z_1_LYNXMPEK4900P_RTROPTP_4_US-CLIMATE-CHINA.jpg.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Government/Legal , Green , Electric Continue reading Biden plans to target tariffs on Chinese tech, including EVs Biden plans to target tariffs on Chinese tech, including EVs originally appeared on Autoblog on Fri, 10 May 2024 11:18:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 16:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Florida Is the Perfect Rent-to-Own Market—Should You Take Advantage?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/why-florida-is-the-perfect-rent-to-own-market</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>The Sunshine State offers the exact combination of factors that make this investment option attractive.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 14:08:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Most Read Books on Goodreads This Week</title><link>https://bookriot.com/most-read-books-on-goodreads-this-week-may-10-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/image-of-a-Black-person-reading.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>What book are you reading this week?</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 553</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-553/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-553</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Tools and technology change rapidly. Yet as wonderful as technology can be, it doesn’t replace the need for human connection through interactions. Keep this in mind as you are searching for a new job. It’s your human connections that often open doors! In this week’s collection of news and tips for job seekers, you’ll find: […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 553 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 12:19:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>There's a new big bull on Wall Street, and he sees the S&amp;P 500 rising above 5,400 by year-end</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/10/theres-a-new-big-bull-on-wall-street-and-he-sees-the-sp-500-rising-above-5400-by-year-end.html</link><description>The CFRA chief investment strategist hiked his year-end target for the equity benchmark to 5,415 from 4,940.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 15:32:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2023 NBA turnovers per game leaders</title><link>https://deadspin.com/2023-nba-turnovers-per-game-leaders-1851036203</link><description>This article is based on data from Sportradar. Read more...</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:10:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meghan Markle Details Sweet Moment With Her &amp; Prince Harry’s Daughter</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1401339/meghan-markle-details-moving-moment-she-had-with-her-and-prince-harrys-daughter-lilibet?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>Meghan Markle is seeing another side of motherhood. While spending time with students at the Lightway Academy during her and Prince Harry's three-day tour in Nigeria May 10, the Duchess of Sussex...</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 16:15:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Your Portfolio Should Include Scarce Assets</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/10/why-your-portfolio-should-include-scarce-assets/</link><description>Portfolios that include both productive and scarce assets can deliver similar performance to the S&amp;P 500 with less risk than those that hold only productive assets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:34:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Target's Pride Month presence will be subdued in 2024 after last year's protests</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/10/target-pride-month-merchandise-2024/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1496446925-e1715350325650.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Company says it will carry merchandise only in “select stores”.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 15:40:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shell Season</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/shell-season/</link><description>Spring welcomes the captivating allure of shell season. As nature awakens and warmth spreads, ocean treasures inspire wardrobe choices. This… The post Shell Season appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:58:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Germany natives in shock what they see in Frankfurt, Germany</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/agm03ew</link><description>Tags: frankurt , germany 2714 points, 837 comments.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 16:26:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New USL Super League Team Dallas Trinity FC Unveils Name, Logo</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/10/new-usl-super-league-team-dallas-trinity-fc-unveils-name-logo/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>New professional women's soccer team in North Texas will begin inaugural season in August and play out of historic Cotton Bowl stadium</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 16:10:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Microsoft is launching its mobile game store in July</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/10/microsoft-is-launching-its-mobile-game-store-in-july/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Microsoft will launch its own mobile game store in July, the company announced at the Bloomberg Technology Summit on Thursday. Xbox president Sarah Bond shared that the company plans to bring its first-party portfolio, which includes titles like Candy Crush and Minecraft, to the mobile store at launch. Microsoft then plans to open up the […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 15:11:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Rare Bright Spot for a Canine Lover Doing Time: Raising Puppies to Become Service Dogs</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/10/service-dogs-training-prison-essay</link><description>Adam Roberts reflects on the highs and occasional lows of training Labrador retrievers for the Puppies Behind Bars program.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Meal Plan #4</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/weekly-menu-plan-4/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Take advantage of this weekly meal plan that has all the favorite recipes that families love! It is so easy…</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Andy Cohen Cleared in Bravo Misconduct Investigation, 'WWHL' Renewed</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/09/andy-cohen-cleared-bravo-misconduct-investigation-wwhl-renewed/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Andy Cohen's position at Bravo has been secured for the foreseeable future ... not long after being cleared in a misconduct investigation, TMZ has learned. The network confirmed Thursday that Andy and "Watch What Happens Live" will continue on…</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:28:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Healthy Lifestyle Can Add Years to Life, Despite 'Bad' Genes</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/balance/news/20240509/defeat-bad-genes-with-healthy-lifestyle?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Turn around those bad family genes with four lifestyle changes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 19:47:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/how-to-remove-wallpaper/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Wallpaper has made a big comeback as a trendy home design choice. But despite its resurgence, there are still plenty of us dealing with dingy, dated, or downright ugly old wallpaper we don’t want. In our old home, we had to remove wallpaper in so many rooms: the kitchen, the dining room, the foyer, and two different bathrooms! As we traveled from room to room removing wallpaper, we tested 4 different methods, and today we’ll share what we learned. Removing wallpaper doesn’t require special tools or lots of money. It’s a totally doable project for any homeowner. However, it can be a tedious process that can take elbow grease and patience, depending on the size of your room and the stubbornness of your wallpaper. But having removed several rooms worth of decades-old wallpaper, we can confidently say it’s worth the effort! You can also check out more before and afters of our once-wallpapered rooms. Continue reading How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:21:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Bull Market is Still Young</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/this-bull-market-is-still-young/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, it's Ross Givens here with the Chart of the Day. In analyzing historical data, it's evident that bull markets typically extend for years from the bear market bottom to the peak. Surprisingly, our current market cycle has seen a peak just 19 months post the last bear market bottom, contrasting with the typical 61-month duration. This insight suggests that the current bull market is still in its infancy, promising ample opportunities ahead. Stay tuned as I delve into the implications of this data in today's analysis. The post This Bull Market is Still Young appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The now-confirmed smaller Lucid SUV will be called 'Earth,' trademark suggests</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/10/the-now-confirmed-smaller-lucid-suv-will-be-called-earth-trademark-suggests/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/04/24121044/PXL_20240411_172454946.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Green , Crossover , SUV , Electric , Luxury , Lucid Continue reading The now-confirmed smaller Lucid SUV will be called 'Earth,' trademark suggests The now-confirmed smaller Lucid SUV will be called 'Earth,' trademark suggests originally appeared on Autoblog on Fri, 10 May 2024 11:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What If We Replaced Income Taxes with Property and Sales Taxes? Would Real Estate Investing Even Work?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/should-the-us-eliminate-income-taxes-and-replace-it-with-sales-and-property-tax</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>A few reasons for—and against—this proposed shift in U.S. tax laws.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:15:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Prepare for Pride Month in Libraries 2024: Book Censorship News, May 10, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/pride-month-in-libraries-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/site-book-censorship-image.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>How to prepare for Pride month in the library, both as library workers and library lovers. That, plus this week's book censorship news roundup.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 552</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-552/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-552</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>When you are searching for a job, you will inevitably run into unexpected scenarios. You will have questions, experience self-doubt and even feel discouraged. You’ll also experience great wins, meet wonderful people and discover new things about yourself. That’s the roller-coaster of job search. Consider Summary Sunday your resource for getting questions answered and showing […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 552 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 11:37:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Consumer sentiment tumbles as inflation fears surge, closely watched survey shows</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/10/consumer-sentiment-tumbles-as-inflation-fears-surge-closely-watched-survey-shows.html</link><description>The University of Michigan Survey of Consumers posted a reading of 67.4 for May, down from 77.2 in April.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 15:13:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2023 NHL goals against average leaders</title><link>https://deadspin.com/2023-nhl-goals-against-average-leaders-1851061822</link><description>This article is based on data from Sportradar. Read more...</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:10:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>You Can Now Shop Bella Hadid's Fragrance Line, 'Ôrəbella, At Ulta</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1401327/embrace-your-unique-aura-with-bella-hadids-fragrance-line-orbella-now-available-at-ulta?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>We independently selected these deals and products because we love them, and we think you might like them at these prices. E! has affiliate relationships, so we may get a commission if you...</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 16:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coiled Tight: Smaller Companies Are Primed for Outperformance</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/08/coiled-tight-smaller-companies-are-primed-for-outperformance/</link><description>Small-cap companies are poised for a rebound. The sector is best approached through an active investment strategy where expertise and a deep understanding of the individual businesses and their risk-and-reward characteristics are necessary for success.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:40:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bumble founder says your dating 'AI concierge' will soon date hundreds of other people's 'concierges' for you</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/10/bumbles-whitney-wolfe-herd-dating-concierge-artificial-intelligence/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1637465569-e1715350282772.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Bumble is now navigating itself in a world of AI—which means rethinking how humans will interact with each other in an increasing age of chatbots.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 15:34:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Discovering My Avaline Favorites</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/discovering-my-avaline-favorites/</link><description>Thank you to Avaline for sponsoring this post. Spring symbolizes fresh starts and cleaner living. In my quest to align… The post Discovering My Avaline Favorites appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:50:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This video feels very uncomfortable.</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/aE0wLmM</link><description>Tags: stinging nettle , pain , health , nature 8370 points, 897 comments.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 16:25:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paris Saint-Germain Draws From Urban Art Scene for 2024-25 Home Kit</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/10/paris-saint-germain-draws-from-urban-art-scene-for-2024-25-home-kit/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Traditional red-and-white Hechter stripe returns to center of jersey, but is "reinterpreted with a fluid and dynamic brushstroke style"</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 15:29:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oura launches two new heart health features</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/10/oura-new-heart-health-features/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Smart ring maker Oura is launching two new features focused on heart health, the company announced on Friday. The first claims to help users get an idea of their cardiovascular age, while the second feature aims to estimate their cardio capacity. Depending on a person’s results, Oura will offer strategies on how to sleep, move, […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Marshall Project Wins the Dart Award for “The Mercy Workers”</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/06/the-marshall-project-wins-the-dart-award-for-the-mercy-workers</link><description>Our feature on mitigation specialists who help save people from the death penalty was recognized for making “significant contributions to public understanding of trauma-related issues.”</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Garlic Balsamic Mushrooms</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/garlic-balsamic-mushrooms/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>The depth of flavors in these garlic balsamic mushrooms is next level! Sauteed mushrooms are coated in a sweet balsamic…</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zayn Malik Says He Doesn't Think He's Been In Love, Shading Gigi Hadid?</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/09/zayn-malik-doesnt-think-ever-been-in-love-shading-gigi-hadid/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Zayn Malik might've just thrown an unintentional dig at Gigi Hadid ... saying he's not sure he's ever fallen in love with someone -- which seems to apply to the mother of his child. The One Direction star lifted the lid on his past relationships on…</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:28:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Taking Racism out of the Kidney Disease Equation</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/a-to-z-guides/features/end-of-racist-kidney-math?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Kidney care in the U.S. is at a watershed moment of moving past a deeply entrenched, institutionally racist equation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 04:17:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aglaonema Plant – Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/aglaonema-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Aglaonema, also called the Chinese Evergreen Plant, is an easy-care houseplant that lives happily in many lighting conditions – even a dark corner of our daughter’s room. There are dozens of different Aglaonema varieties, most with large tropical foliage and colors ranging from silvery-green, red, and even vibrant pink. They’re also tough to kill, so they’re a great option for forgetful plant owners or anyone looking for an easy win in the plant department. These truly have been very low maintenance for us. We purchased our two Aglaonemas (pronounced ag-lee-oh-neem-ah ) to put atop our daughter’s closet. It’s sometimes hard to distinguish different varieties, but we believe that’s an Aglaonema Silver (right) and either a Candy Cane or Princess Silver Queen (left). Aglaonema Quick Facts Here’s what you need to know about your Aglaonema at a glance: Latin name : Aglaonema is the genus under which there are 21 recognized species . Continue reading Aglaonema Plant – Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:47:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Earnings Divergence Opportunity</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/the-earnings-divergence-opportunity/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, it's Ross Givens here with the Chart of the Day. Amidst economic concerns, analysts have defied expectations by boosting their earnings estimates for S&amp;P 500 companies. This unexpected trend challenges prevailing pessimism about the market's trajectory. In today's analysis, I delve into what this shift means and why it's crucial not to let pessimism hinder your pursuit of current market opportunities. The post The Earnings Divergence Opportunity appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Yay, our long-term 2024 Mazda CX-90 doesn't use piano black plastic</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/10/long-term-2024-mazda-cx-90-phev-no-piano-black-plastic/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/09163401/IMG_104921.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Green , Mazda , Long-Term Garage , Crossover , SUV , Hybrid Continue reading Yay, our long-term 2024 Mazda CX-90 doesn't use piano black plastic Yay, our long-term 2024 Mazda CX-90 doesn't use piano black plastic originally appeared on Autoblog on Fri, 10 May 2024 10:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Couple Goals: Navigating Real Estate Investment Decisions With Your Significant Other</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-investing-with-your-significant-other</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>7 steps to earn your significant other's support in real estate investing.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:52:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Celebrating Life Through Delicious Food</title><link>https://bookriot.com/read-this-book-may-10-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/bite-by-bite.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>The perfect new read for food lovers everywhere.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>While a little competition in the workplace might help bring out the best in everyone involved, an atmosphere rooted in envy, fear, or jealousy can do the exact opposite. This post will help you recognize signs that your coworker is threatened by you, and help you navigate the situation. 1. They Don’t Want You Involved […] The post 10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:07:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rivian, Lucid and other EV startups scramble to shore up cash and reassure Wall Street</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/10/rivian-lucid-nikola-shore-up-cash.html</link><description>Rivian, Lucid and Nikola this week each detailed plans to reduce costs while attempting to grow operations and make their first profits.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 14:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2023 NBA steals per game leaders</title><link>https://deadspin.com/2023-nba-steals-per-game-leaders-1851036198</link><description>This article is based on data from Sportradar. Read more...</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:10:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Heather Rae El Moussa Details How Son Tristan Has Changed Her</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1401338/heather-rae-el-moussa-details-how-son-tristan-has-changed-her?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>Heather Rae El Moussa didn't have to be sold on motherhood. After all, the Selling Sunset alum recently shared how much fuller her life feels as mom to her and husband Tarek El Moussa's...</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 16:02:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Investment Returns Are NOT Random</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/07/investment-returns-are-not-random/</link><description>Are investment returns random across time as Burton Malkiel suggests in his book, A Random Walk Down Wall Street? There is notable disagreement on this topic. This research finds that practitioners may need to rethink their portfolio optimization routines.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:22:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BYD plots to overtake Tesla in Europe by 2030</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/10/byd-tesla-european-ev-market-chinese-carmaker-elon-musk-2030/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1644925828-e1715347149347.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>BYD's Europe managing director plans to get around looming tariffs by building the ultra-cheap EVs on the continent.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 14:38:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spring Slumber</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/spring-slumber/</link><description>In the gentle embrace of mid-spring, there’s a delightful charm in refreshing my sleepwear collection. I tend to gravitate towards… The post Spring Slumber appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 20:00:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>100%</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/adBNZ6N</link><description>Tags: funny 6889 points, 344 comments.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 16:25:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Report: WNBA Expanding to Toronto for 2026</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/10/report-wnba-expanding-to-toronto-for-2026/basketball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The WNBA is crossing the border! According to a CBC report, Toronto will be getting a Women’s National Basketball Association expansion franchise for the 2026 WNBA season. Kilmer Sports Inc., led by Toronto billionaire Larry Tanenbaum, will own the franchise. The report says the league’s official announcement is expected to</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 14:25:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Week in AI: OpenAI considers allowing AI porn</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/10/this-week-in-ai-openai-considers-allowing-ai-porn/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Keeping up with an industry as fast-moving as AI is a tall order. So until an AI can do it for you, here’s a handy roundup of recent stories in the world of machine learning, along with notable research and experiments we didn’t cover on their own. By the way, TechCrunch plans to launch an AI newsletter […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weinstein Ruling Poses Quandary: Can #MeToo Coexist With Protections for Defendants?</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/04/sex-crimes-weinstein-me-too</link><description>Proving sex crimes often requires evidence that is generally excluded to protect the rights of the accused.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Creamy Cucumber Salad</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/creamy-cucumber-salad/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Creamy Cucumber Salad is a delicious and refreshing side dish. All it takes is a handful of fresh simple ingredients…</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Joe Biden Flubs Aces Championship Speech, Calls Candace Parker Greatest 'Coach'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/09/president-joe-biden-candace-parker-aces-white-house-visit-wnba/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>President Joe Biden has suffered yet another gaffe at a podium ... this time, he incorrectly ID'ed WNBA superstar Candace Parker as a "coach." The flub happened as Biden was hosting Parker's Las Vegas Aces at the White House to celebrate their 2023…</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:28:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Plant-Powered Sleep: Vegan, Vegetarian Diets Unlock Extra ZZZs</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/sleep-disorders/news/20240508/plant-powered-sleep-vegan-vegetarian-diet-unlocks-extra-zzzs?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Vegans and vegetarians sleep around 30 more minutes per night than average and up to 90% of them report good or excellent sleep quality, according to a new survey published by the Sleep Foundation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 19:12:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Corn Plant – Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/corn-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Corn plants ( Dracaena fragrans ) are popular low-maintenance houseplants you’ve probably seen at the nursery, home improvement store, or doctor’s office. I even had one in my college dorm room! You can recognize them by their spear-shaped leaves and woody, cane-line trunks that can grow up to 6 feet tall indoors. But did you know there are several varieties of corn plants? We didn’t! Heck, we didn’t even realize some of our smaller houseplants were in the same corn plant family! Currently, we own two smaller varieties of corn plants, pictured above. The one on the left is a Dracaena Limelight ( Dracaena fragrans ‘Limelight’ ) and the taller plant is a Draecanea Dorado ( Dracaena fragrans ‘Dorado’ ). We actually have several limelights around because we love their vibrant color on shelves, tabletops, and windowsills. Corn Plant Quick Facts Latin name : Dracaena fragrans Common names : Corn plant, cornstalk plant, false palms Light : Bright, indirect light but can tolerate lower-light conditions Watering : Keep soil moist, but not soggy. Continue reading Corn Plant – Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 17:37:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Opportunity Window is Closing</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/the-opportunity-window-is-closing/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, it's Ross Givens here with the Chart of the Day. In market dynamics, volatility often mirrors market trends – as volatility rises, markets tend to dip, and as it falls, markets typically climb. Looking at historical data, this relationship holds true across various market conditions. Currently, with volatility showing signs of calming down, it suggests that the market might be on its way out of the recent pullback. Discover more insights on this intriguing correlation in today's analysis below. The post The Opportunity Window is Closing appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The best truck bed liners of 2024</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/article/best-truck-bed-liners/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2023/07/07140418/Rust-Oleum-342668-Automotive-Truck-Bed-Lead-Image.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Commerce , Parts and Accessories Continue reading The best truck bed liners of 2024 The best truck bed liners of 2024 originally appeared on Autoblog on Fri, 10 May 2024 09:45:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 14:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BiggerNews: Why Low Mortgage Rates Can’t Solve Our Affordability Crisis</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-951</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Housing prices won’t budge, but there could be some relief on the horizon for homebuyers. As America’s affordability crisis continues to strain consumers, one of the most considerable costs, housing, […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 07:02:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New YA Books By Asian American and Pacific Islander Authors</title><link>https://bookriot.com/2024-ya-books-by-asian-american-and-pacific-islander-authors/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/AAPI-YA-2024.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>Whatever genre is your favorite, you'll find some excellent new YA books by Asian American and Pacific Islander authors right here.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 551</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-551/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-551</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Job search requires writing and marketing skills. It also requires strong verbal communication. If these skills are not part of your normal work function, you’ll want some help. That’s what this week’s Summary Sunday is all about. There’s no doubt that LinkedIn is one of THE most powerful tools in your career toolbox. It contains […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 551 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 11:37:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sam Altman takes nuclear energy startup Oklo public to help power his AI ambitions</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/10/sam-altman-takes-nuclear-startup-oklo-public-to-power-ai-ambitions.html</link><description>Sam Altman, best known as the CEO of OpenAI, is also chairman of a nuclear power company called Oklo, which has just gone public through a SPAC.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 14:34:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2023 NBA free throws per game leaders</title><link>https://deadspin.com/2023-nba-free-throws-per-game-leaders-1851036206</link><description>This article is based on data from Sportradar. Read more...</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:09:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Best Hair Products for Thin Hair and Fine Hair</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1396472/best-hair-products-for-thin-hair-and-fine-hair-that-really-pump-up-the-volume?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>The products featured in this article are from brands that are available in the NBCUniversal Checkout Marketplace. If you purchase something through our links, we get a commission. If you have...</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Generational Wealth: Does the Apple Fall Far From the Tree?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/06/generational-wealth-does-the-apple-fall-far-from-the-tree/</link><description>There is strong evidence that most “rich families” will be poorer after several generations. Some of the reasons for this are systemic like taxes. But most factors that diminish a family’s wealth over generations are the choices that heirs make.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 12:37:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why a $3 billion software firm is betting on a flexible-work future—'the focus for us is carrot, not stick'</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/10/sarah-franklin-lattice-flexible-work-marc-benioff-remote-return-to-office/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-925709916-e1715282212105.jpeg?w=2048</image_url><description>Sarah Franklin, a 15-year Salesforce alum, helms Lattice with the best of her former boss’ flexibility practices close at hand.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 14:35:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coral Crush</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/coral-crush/</link><description>Outfit Details: Sir Top &amp; Skirt (also love the dress version), Loro Piana Hat, Prada Sunglasses Spring welcomes the delightful hue of coral, a color that perfectly… The post Coral Crush appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 05:00:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>If you know, you know</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/a34YV97</link><description>Tags: tag 1 3304 points, 247 comments.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 16:25:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Report: Fanatics NHL Jerseys to Debut in June</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/10/report-fanatics-nhl-jerseys-to-debut-in-june/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The NHL’s shift to Fanatics on-ice jerseys could be revealed as soon as next month, according to former NFL quarterback Boomer Esiason. While on his morning Boomer and Gio radio program, Esiason revealed that the new Fanatics NHL jerseys for all 32 teams (Utah too?) would be revealed sometime in</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:55:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Garena is quietly making India-themed games even as Free Fire’s relaunch remains doubtful</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/10/garena-india-themed-games-free-fire-launch/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Garena is quietly developing new India-themed games even though Free Fire, its biggest title, has still not made a comeback to the country. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 14:17:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mississippi Lawmakers Considered Modest Public Defense Reforms. They Rejected All of Them.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/02/mississippi-public-defense-legislative-reforms</link><description>With its refusal to impose oversight or consistent standards in local defense, Mississippi risks falling further behind rest of the U.S., critics say.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Beginner’s Guide to Baking Bread</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/beginners-guide-to-baking-bread/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>You want to make bread, but where do you start? My beginner’s guide to baking bread is here to save…</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bear Attack Caught on Video, Rushes Car and Smashes Windshield</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/09/bear-attackr-car-smashes-windshield-new-video-shows-caught-japan/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>A couple foragers ended up in a hairy situation out in Japan -- speeding down the road in a forest when a bear attacked their car, cracking their window ... and it's all on camera. Check out this wild footage out out of Hokkaido last week ... the…</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:28:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anorexia: The Body Neglected</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/mental-health/eating-disorders/anorexia-nervosa/features/anorexia-body-neglected?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>What, exactly, does anorexia nervosa do inside the human body? The heart and bones suffer the most.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Using Solid Stain In Our Outdoor Shower</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/solid-deck-stain-outdoor-shower/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>In all of our years of DIYing, I don’t think we’ve ever used a solid stain before. But we recently had a project that was *perfectly* suited for it and, well, solid stain quickly won us over. It was recommended by a professional house painter to us, specifically because he thought it would be great for our outdoor shower. And we found it easy to apply, it gave us great coverage, and we got an even-better-than-we-expected result (which is always the best kind!). So here’s a post that covers all the pros &amp; cons and hows &amp; whys of solid stain. As you can see, the “canvas” for this staining project was our outdoor shower. We gave it a mini-makeover right after moving in, but we knew it may need more attention and care down the line. Honestly, we dreaded the task of stripping and restaining it – so many nooks &amp; crannies! Continue reading Using Solid Stain In Our Outdoor Shower at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 17:46:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Keep Buying the Dips</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/how-to-keep-buying-the-dips/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, it's Ross Givens here with the Chart of the Day. In recent weeks, market movements have shifted to a more favorable pattern, oscillating within a consolidation range after a turbulent start to April. Now, signs suggest a potential breakout from this range, signaling a crucial turning point for traders. Learn how to navigate this evolving market landscape in today's Insight of the Day. The post How to Keep Buying the Dips appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NHTSA opens probe into over 200,000 Ford vehicles on fuel leak risks</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/10/nhtsa-opens-probe-into-over-200000-ford-vehicles-on-fuel-leak-risks/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/10092534/2020-ford-f-superduty-actfront-31.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Government/Legal , Ford , Safety , Truck , Diesel Vehicles Continue reading NHTSA opens probe into over 200,000 Ford vehicles on fuel leak risks NHTSA opens probe into over 200,000 Ford vehicles on fuel leak risks originally appeared on Autoblog on Fri, 10 May 2024 09:32:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 14:32:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rookie Reply: The Rental Property Expenses You CAN’T Afford to Miss</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-404</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>How do you know if a rental property will make enough cash flow before you buy? Budgeting is KEY. When breaking down a deal, it’s critical that you account for […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 07:02:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What are You Reading This Week — May 9, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/read-harder-updates-may-9-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/book-in-grass.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>What's the last book you finished reading, and what did you think of it?</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>15 Ways to Own Digital Terrain</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/15-ways-to-own-digital-terrain/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=15-ways-to-own-digital-terrain</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>It is now no longer optional…you must have an online presence! Your career stability and your job search demand it. Here are some tips to help you begin claiming digital terrain and brand it with your unique messaging! Why Should You Own Digital Terrain? You need to stake a claim by owning turf on the […] The post 15 Ways to Own Digital Terrain appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 15:56:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump was 'very upset' when Stormy Daniels story came out, top White House aide testifies</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/10/trump-trial-hush-money-testimony-white-house-aide.html</link><description>The Donald Trump hush money trial resumed after porn star Stormy Daniels finished testimony and Judge Juan Merchan denied mistrial and gag order bids.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 14:13:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2023 NBA field goals per game leaders</title><link>https://deadspin.com/2023-nba-field-goals-per-game-leaders-1851036211</link><description>This article is based on data from Sportradar. Read more...</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:09:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Angel Reese Reacts to Criticism For Attending Met Before WNBA Game</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1401329/wnba-star-angel-reese-claps-back-at-criticism-for-attending-met-gala-ahead-of-game?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>Angel Reese isn't going to let this criticism travel. After fans faulted the Chicago Sky player for attending the May 6 Met Gala the day before her preseason game against the New York Liberty, the...</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 15:14:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>State Capitalism in Private Markets: Mission Creep</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/03/state-capitalism-in-private-markets-mission-creep/</link><description>Governments relish mingling in markets. Yet, if past policies are any guide, taxpayers are being shortchanged.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 12:30:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Upgrade OneCard: An All-Hassle Rewards Card</title><link>https://fortune.com/recommends/credit-cards/upgrade-onecard-review/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/Recommends_Upgrade-One-Card.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The Upgrade OneCard offers great rewards, but you have to jump through a lot of hoops to get them.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Favorite Buys Under $200</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/favorite-buys-under-200-2/</link><description>Outfit Details: Zara Top, Marysia Shorts, Prada Sunglasses, Valentino Hat, Marni Bag As I continue to add to my wardrobe, phasing out older… The post Favorite Buys Under $200 appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 05:00:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>As long as it works..</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/aD20E6K</link><description>Tags: karaoke , singing 7065 points, 135 comments.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 16:25:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New England Patriots Subtly Reveal New Secondary Logo</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/09/new-england-patriots-subtly-reveal-new-secondary-logo/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Following a recent visit to Gillette Stadium, former New England Patriots linebacker Brandon Spikes posted a photo of what appears to be the franchise’s new secondary logo prominently displayed inside the facility.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 20:58:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fisker Ocean faces fourth federal safety probe</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/10/fisker-ocean-nhtsa-investigation-automatic-emergency-braking/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The U.S.' NHTSA has opened a fourth investigation into the Fisker Ocean SUV, spurred by multiple claims of "inadvertent Automatic Emergency Braking." © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 14:05:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In This Police Youth Program, a Trail of Sexual Abuse Across the U.S.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/01/police-explorer-sexual-abuse-boy-scouts</link><description>Explorer posts, overseen by the Boy Scouts, are supposed to foster an interest in policing. They have faced nearly 200 allegations of misconduct.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 18:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mushroom Swiss Burger</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/mushroom-swiss-burger/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Create the most flavorful, juicy Mushroom Swiss Burger! Perfectly seasoned ground beef is topped with sautéed buttery mushrooms and melty…</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Real-Life 'Baby Reindeer' Martha Says She Sent Gadd Less Than 10 Emails</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/09/real-life-baby-reindeer-martha-fiona-harvey-sent-gadd-10-emails/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>The real-life woman behind the villain in "Baby Reindeer" -- who's portrayed as a stalker -- just went on TV to deny how she was depicted ... insisting she only sent a few emails. Fiona Harvey appeared as a guest on Piers Morgan's show Thursday --…</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:28:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Postpartum PTSD: Right Diagnosis Can Help Mothers and Babies</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/mental-health/news/20240506/postpartum-ptsd-right-diagnosis-can-help-mothers-and-babies?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Many new mothers aren’t aware that postpartum PTSD even exists, but it’s far from rare. Here's what to know.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:19:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ZZ Plant – Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/zz-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>The ZZ plant is another one of our favorite low-maintenance houseplants. They’re easy to care for, hard to kill, and always look full &amp; leafy. They’ve even earned the nickname “Eternity Plant” because they’re practically indestructible! That’s why they’re a top choice for commercial spaces, doctor’s offices, and busy homes like ours. Don’t you love a house plant you can forget about? ZZ plants are sold in a variety of sizes, meaning they’re great for shelves, tabletops, and small surfaces as well as larger statements on the floor. We have some that are over 3 feet tall with their pots! ZZ Plant Quick Facts Here’s what you need to know about your ZZ plant at a glance: Latin name : Zamioculcas zamiifolia Plant family : Araceae or Arums, which includes Philodendron , Alocasia, Aglaonema, Monstera , and Peace Lily Common name s: ZZ plant, Zanzibar Gem, Zuzu plant, Emerald Palm, Eternity plant Native to : East Africa Light : Medium indirect light, but is also low-light tolerant Watering : Every 2-3 weeks during its growing season Soil : Standard potting mix as long as it drains well Ideal Humidity : Average household humidity, ideally 40-50% Ideal Temperature : 65°F to 75°F Cold Hardiness : USDA Zones 9b-11 What Is A ZZ Plant? Continue reading ZZ Plant – Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 19:36:48 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>