<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from multiple RSS sources, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 06:57:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Boost Your Cash Flow in 2024 with These “Self-Management” Tips</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-401</link><description>Want more cash flow with less stress while running your rental property portfolio? Then you need self-management! Amelia McGee and Grace Gudenkauf, seasoned investors and the minds behind BiggerPockets’ newest […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 07:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Google dubs Epic’s demands from its antitrust win ‘unnecessary’ and ‘far beyond the scope’ of the verdict</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/03/google-dubs-epics-demands-from-its-antitrust-win-unnecessary-and-far-beyond-the-scope-of-verdict/</link><description>The new filing, along with Epic's proposal, will help to inform Judge James Donato in a hearing scheduled on May 23 about what actions to take next to put Google’s power in check.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 09:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mississippi Lawmakers Considered Modest Public Defense Reforms. They Rejected All of Them.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/02/mississippi-public-defense-legislative-reforms</link><description>With its refusal to impose oversight or consistent standards in local defense, Mississippi risks falling further behind rest of the U.S., critics say.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When Does Old Age Start? It Depends on Who You Ask</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/news/20240502/when-does-old-age-start-many-disagree?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>The goalpost for old age has been moving. Until now.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 18:45:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Rational Investor’s Case Against Bitcoin</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-525</link><description>Cryptocurrency enthusiasts can’t fathom why Bitcoin will fail. If you tell them that you’re not investing in Bitcoin or other cryptos, they look at you like an uneducated investor, a […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 07:01:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple: pay attention to emerging markets, not falling China sales</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/02/apple-cfo-tells-investors-to-pay-attention-to-emerging-markets-not-falling-china-sales/</link><description>Apple’s chief financial officer Luca Maestri challenged investor worries over an 8% drop in China revenue, by noting that sales in other emerging markets are growing. “When we start looking at places like India, like Saudi, like Mexico, Turkey, Brazil…and Indonesia, the numbers are getting large, and we’re very happy because these are markets where […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 23:59:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In This Police Youth Program, a Trail of Sexual Abuse Across the U.S.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/01/police-explorer-sexual-abuse-boy-scouts</link><description>Explorer posts, overseen by the Boy Scouts, are supposed to foster an interest in policing. They have faced nearly 200 allegations of misconduct.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 18:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prospects for Crohn's Relief Brighten With New Advancements</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/ibd-crohns-disease/crohns-disease/news/20240502/prospects-crohns-relief-brighten-with-new-advancements?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>More than 1 million Americans live with Crohn’s, a chronic and sometimes crippling bowel disease that affects the intestines and leads to digestive issues. But in 2024, breakthroughs could bring relief in different ways. Here's what to know.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 17:59:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2024 Deals We’re Doing with High Cash Flow and Rock-Bottom Rates (4.75%!)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-947</link><description>Want a low mortgage rate? We mean a really low rate—like 4.75% in 2024 low. What about half a million in profit on a sneaky development deal? Or, maybe you’d […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 07:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple iPad event: What to expect</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/02/apple-ipad-event-what-to-expect/</link><description>So far, the biggest surprise about May 7’s “Let Loose” event is that it’s happening at all. We’re just over a month out from Apple’s annual Worldwide Developer Conference, and yet the company determined there was enough news to warrant a stand-alone event. iPads (including the iPad Pro and iPad Air) will be the focus, […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 23:12:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Campus Protests Could Shape the 2024 Elections — And Not Just the Presidency</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/30/campus-protests-gaza-arrests-prosecutors-elections</link><description>With hundreds of arrests and more campus standoffs looming, local law enforcement officials could face consequences at the ballot box.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 21:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Truth or TV: Is Grey's Anatomy's Parkinson's 'Cure' Real?</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/parkinsons-disease/features/is-greys-anatomys-parkinsons-cure-real?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>How realistic is the Grey’s Anatomy episode that shows a Parkinson’s disease cure? A neurosurgery professor weighs in.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 08:17:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Home Prices Stagnate in The South and America’s New #1 Housing Market</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-213</link><description>Texas and Florida are seeing stagnating home prices as housing inventory booms while demand slips away. Housing is still expensive, but with more inventory, why is it staying that way? […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 07:02:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Microsoft bans US police departments from using enterprise AI tool for facial recognition</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/02/microsoft-bans-u-s-police-departments-azure-openai-facial-recognition/</link><description>Microsoft has reaffirmed its ban on U.S. police departments from using generative AI for facial recognition through Azure OpenAI Service, the company’s fully managed, enterprise-focused wrapper around OpenAI tech. Language added Wednesday to the terms of service for Azure OpenAI Service more obviously prohibits integrations with Azure OpenAI Service from being used “by or for” […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 21:57:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>They Killed Their Abusive Partners. Now Their Sentences Could Be Reconsidered.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/27/oklahoma-oregon-minnesota-domestic-violence</link><description>Oklahoma could re-examine how it punishes people whose crimes came after years of domestic abuse. Other states may follow.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Easing Marijuana Laws Doesn’t Mean the Drug Is Safer</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/mental-health/addiction/news/20240501/reclassification-of-marijuana-doesnt-mean-its-safer?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>You shouldn’t draw major conclusions about the safety of marijuana amid the recent announcement that federal regulators may reclassify the drug, experts are cautioning.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 23:29:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Contractor Nightmares: 5 Red Flags to Watch For and How to Escape a Bad Hire</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/red-flags-to-avoid-with-contractors-and-how-to-escape-a-bad-hire</link><description>What’s easier to find, a unicorn or a rock star contractor? If you asked most value-add real estate investors, the answer would be obvious: “Unicorns, of course.” We all know the inherent […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 17:18:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple earnings see 10% iPhone sales drop, massive buyback fuels stock jump</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/02/apple-earnings-see-10-iphones-sales-drop/</link><description>Apple on Thursday reported a 10% drop in iPhone sales for the second fiscal quarter, dropping from $51.33 billion to $45.96 billion, year-over-year. The slowdown was fueled, in part, by an 8% drop in China. Apple’s slow adoption of AI versus competitors like Google and Microsoft likely played a role in consumers’ decision to hold […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 21:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Being Trans in Prison Is Really Like</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/26/trans-prison-voices-gender-essay</link><description>Amid a wave of anti-trans legislation, and the violence that often follows, four people share their experiences in the criminal justice system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 11:00:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Female Doctors Better? Here's What to Know</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/women/news/20240501/are-female-doctors-better-heres-what-to-know?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>A new study suggests female doctors may provide patients better care, especially when those patients are women. Here's what to know.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 18:11:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>