<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 06:50:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>San Fransico Giants Add #24 Memorial Patch for Willie Mays</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/20/san-fransico-giants-add-24-memorial-patch-for-willie-mays/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The San Francisco Giants have added a memorial patch to the front of their uniform’s jersey in honour of the great Willie Mays. The patch shows Mays’ legendary number 24 in orange on a black circle, his name “MAYS” arched above in orange. There’s an additional orange outline around the</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 22:25:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lakers Hire JJ Redick As Next Head Coach</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/20/los-angeles-lakers-hire-jj-redick-next-head-coach/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>JJ Redick is the guy for the Los Angeles Lakers -- the ex-NBA player was reportedly just hired as the organization's next head coach. ESPN's Adrian Wojnarowski dropped the news on Thursday ... saying after a thorough interview process, Redick was…</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 06:50:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Los Angeles Kings Unveil New Logos, Modernized Take on ’90s Classic</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/20/los-angeles-kings-unveil-new-logos-modernized-take-on-90s-classic/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Los Angeles Kings are goin’ back to the ’90s, kids! This morning, the Kings unveiled their new, old logo via their social media channels, one day after posting a teaser graphic simply showing the outline of the logo. It’s a throwback, mostly, to what the club wore from 1988</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 17:13:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Nuttin But Azz' Basketball Tournament Canceled After Raunchy Theme Sparks Outrage</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/20/nuttin-but-azz-basketball-tournament-canceled-after-outrage-over-raunchy-theme/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>A celebrity basketball tournament slated to go down at a high school in New Jersey next month has been axed ... after the event's raunchy theme sparked outrage in the community. The "Nuttin But Azz" Celebrity Baddies Basketball contest was all set…</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 06:50:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Here’s A Visual Guide to the Colors on the Euro 2024 Logo</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/20/heres-a-visual-guide-to-the-colors-on-the-euro-2024-logo/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>If you've been watching Euro 2024 this summer, you may have noticed the dizzying number of colors in the tournament logo and television graphics. But those colors are there and arranged the way there for a good reason.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 16:50:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Justin Timberlake DWI Arrest Body Cam Video Won't Be Released Anytime Soon</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/20/justin-timberlake-dwi-arrest-body-cam-video-wont-be-released-during-investigation/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Justin Timberlake's DWI arrest was caught on body cam video -- but cops aren't planning to release it to the public anytime soon ... at least not until their investigation is wrapped. TMZ officially submitted a request for a copy of the video --…</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 06:50:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Los Angeles Kings Tease New Logo, Returning to an Old Favourite, for 2024-25</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/20/los-angeles-kings-tease-new-logo-returning-to-an-old-favourite-for-2024-25/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>There’s room for teasin’ from two Southern California teams in the NHL this week. Just two days after the Anaheim Ducks did so, the Los Angeles Kings have decided to join in. Last night, the Kings—wildly rumoured to be getting a new logo—changed their profile photo to show just the</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 15:43:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Khloé Kardashian to Launch Podcast Collab on Elon Musk's X</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/20/khloe-kardashian-launch-video-podcast-x-elon-musk/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>The Kardashian empire is expanding ... with Khloe Kardashian prepping her very own podcast, powered by Elon Musk's X. The reality star revealed she's signed a deal with the social media platform to host the original video podcast starting this…</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 06:50:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NFL Second, Third Helmet Concept Series – AFC East</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/19/nfl-second-third-helmet-concept-series-afc-east/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Our newest concept series creates second and/or third helmet designs for every NFL team, starting with the AFC East.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 14:24:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Travis Kelce Attends Cannes Lions Festival With Brother Jason Kelce</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/20/travis-kelce-brother-jason-cannes-lions-festival/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Travis Kelce joined his brother Jason Kelce for a trip across the pond to France -- this right after lighting it up in Nashville ... just proving that the dude's real busy in the off-season. Despite their whirlwind schedule, the Kelce brothers…</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 06:50:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>