<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 06:56:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Book Review: Trailblazers, Heroes, and Crooks</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/26/book-review-trailblazers-heroes-and-crooks/</link><description>Stephen Foerster, CFA, extracts lessons from exceptional episodes in financial history that ordinary investors and seasoned professionals alike can put to profitable use. The bonus is that you'll be entertained from start to finish.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Goldman Sachs has warned its staff about sneaking off to Paris during the Olympics—and leaving the bank to pick up the tab</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/29/goldman-sachs-paris-olympics-staff-warning/</link><description>“In line with previous Olympic games, we have asked our people to effectively manage their spend and ensure coordination."</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 11:54:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Price Risk? Unpacking the Equity Risk Premium</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/24/what-price-risk-unpacking-the-equity-risk-premium/</link><description>Stocks are a good wager over the long term, on favorable odds. But stocks remain a bet, and investors must grasp how much returns can vary over long time horizons.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ryanair's Michael O'Leary, who is up for a $108 million bonus, doesn’t see high CEO pay as a problem: 'Footballers are getting half a million a week'</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/04/29/ryanair-michael-oleary-100-million-euros-bonus-ceo-pay-footballers-millions-a-week/</link><description>Michael O'Leary says that if football players and their managers can get paid in the multi-millions, why not him?</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 11:54:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Equity Income Investing Redux</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/22/equity-income-investing-redux/</link><description>No doubt the past year has been difficult for equity income investors. But history, inherent biases, mean reversion, and the current market backdrop point to a comeback.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 17:19:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>EU's unwinnable EV price war: BYD cars 11 times more profitable in Europe than in China</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/04/29/eu-unwinnable-price-war-chinese-evs-byd-cars-11-times-more-profitable-in-europe-than-in-china/</link><description>Only a highly unlikely 50% import tariff would be enough to deter Chinese automakers from Europe, new research finds.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 11:48:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: Enrich Your Future</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/18/book-review-enrich-your-future/</link><description>This engaging book is simultaneously memorable and humorous. The numerous sports analogies will have you smiling as you absorb Larry Swedroe's unforgettable investment precepts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 18:07:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>McKinsey boss tries to boost staff morale amid layoffs by blasting Eminem, Bob Marley and Chumbawamba</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/29/mckinsey-boss-boost-staff-morale-layoffs-political-backlash-eminem-bob-marley-chumbawamba/</link><description>Global Managing Partner Bob Sternfels told his fellow partners at the mid-April event that McKinsey is expecting a good 2024 after its challenges of the past 18 months.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 11:34:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CAPE Is High: Should You Care?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/17/cape-is-high-should-you-care/</link><description>A simple analysis shows that Robert Shiller's cyclically adjusted price-to-earnings ratio changed in the 1990s and that mean-reversion concerns may be misplaced. If CAPE changed three decades ago, however, there is nothing preventing it from doing so again.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 15:18:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Sam Bankman-Fried is turning against A-list FTX boosters—and what could happen to them</title><link>https://fortune.com/crypto/2024/04/29/sam-bankman-fried-ftx-endorsements-lawsuit-tom-brady-gisele-shaq-larry-david/</link><description>Some of the celebs who took money to tout SBF’s exchange may be in hotter water than others.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>