<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from multiple RSS sources, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 07:25:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Rookie Investor? Never Make This $40,000 Mistake</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-400</link><description>This episode could make you $40,000. Seriously, one property management mistake cost our own expert investor, Dave Meyer, anywhere from $30,000 to $40,000, BUT it’s easier to avoid than you […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 07:02:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chicago-based Hyde Park Venture Partners closes $98M Fund IV with two investments made so far</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/01/hyde-park-venture-partners-98m/</link><description>Hyde Park Venture Partners is known for having visibility into more than 90% of mid-continent startups and being early backers of companies like ShipBob, FourKites, G2, LogicGate and Dentologie.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 12:00:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Campus Protests Could Shape the 2024 Elections — And Not Just the Presidency</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/30/campus-protests-gaza-arrests-prosecutors-elections</link><description>With hundreds of arrests and more campus standoffs looming, local law enforcement officials could face consequences at the ballot box.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 21:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NIH’s Eliseo Pérez-Stable, MD, Talks Health Disparities, Biology, Behavior, and Culture</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/a-to-z-guides/features/nimhd-perez-stable-health-disparities?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Eliseo Pérez-Stable, MD, director of the National Institute on Minority Health and Health Disparities, talks about health disparities and how his studies aim to improve interventions in clinical settings and across communities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 22:06:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Supplement Your Income with Real Estate (So You Can Do What You Love)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-946</link><description>Why are rock stars turning to real estate side hustles to pay their bills? During the lockdowns, many musicians, gig workers, and creatives saw their income streams dwindle. There were no […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 07:02:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Midi is building a digital platform for an oft-overlooked area of women’s health</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/30/midi-is-building-a-digital-platform-for-an-oft-overlooked-area-of-womens-health/</link><description>When Joanna Strober was around 47, she stopped sleeping. While losing sleep is a common symptom of perimenopause, she first had to go to multiple providers, including driving 45 minutes out of San Francisco to pay $750 out of pocket, to get that diagnosis and proper treatment. “That feeling of wow, I’ve really been suffering […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 21:54:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>They Killed Their Abusive Partners. Now Their Sentences Could Be Reconsidered.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/27/oklahoma-oregon-minnesota-domestic-violence</link><description>Oklahoma could re-examine how it punishes people whose crimes came after years of domestic abuse. Other states may follow.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New ‘FLiRT’ Variants Spark Summer COVID Surge Warning</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/covid/news/20240430/new-variant-sparks-summer-covid-surge-warning?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>A data scientist who has accurately predicted COVID waves since the beginning of the pandemic warns that a surge is on the horizon.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 18:16:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seeing Greene: Stolen Properties and Why Your Rate Doesn’t (Really) Matter</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-945</link><description>There’s a silent threat out there that most real estate investors have no idea about. It’s a threat that could take away all your cash flow, ruin your real estate […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 07:02:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Razer hit with $1.1M FTC fine over glowing ‘N95’ mask COVID claims</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/30/razer-hit-with-1-1m-ftc-fine-over-glowing-n95-mask-covid-claims/</link><description>The Federal Trade Commission hit Razer with a $1.1 million fine Tuesday. The order claims that the gaming accessory maker misled consumers by claiming that its flashy Zephyr mask was certified as N95-grade. “These businesses falsely claimed, in the midst of a global pandemic, that their face mask was the equivalent of an N95 certified […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 21:53:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Being Trans in Prison Is Really Like</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/26/trans-prison-voices-gender-essay</link><description>Amid a wave of anti-trans legislation, and the violence that often follows, four people share their experiences in the criminal justice system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 11:00:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>You Give Me (Spring) Fever</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/women/features/you-give-me-spring-fever?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>New Season Brings Boost of Energy, but Also Unplanned Pregnancies</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 16:57:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lessons From the Rich That Took Me from $0 to a $1,000,000+ Business</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-524</link><description>Want to be a millionaire or build a business that brings in seven figures? Want generational wealth and to be debt-free? Want to know that you have enough money to […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 07:01:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>With $175M in new funding, Island is putting the browser at the center of enterprise security</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/30/island-secure-enterprise-browser-lands-175m-3b-valuation/</link><description>When a company raises $175M at a $3B valuation, it gets your attention. When that startup is a browser company, all the more.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 20:52:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Enduring Use of Solitary, and New Proposed Limits That Will Likely Fail (Again)</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/20/solitary-confinement-reform-oklahoma-washington-florida</link><description>Isolation’s damaging effects are widely known. But many facilities confine people — even youth — virtually all day, sometimes in shower stalls.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Older Adults: 9 Nutrients You May Be Missing</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/missing-nutrients?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>With age, your body doesn’t absorb nutrients well, so every calorie you consume must be packed with nutrition. Here are 9 nutrients older adults often need more of.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 16:57:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tenant Not Paying Rent? Here’s What to Do</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/tenant-not-paying-rent</link><description>A tenant not paying rent can turn your profit upside down. Should you find yourself in this situation, there are several key steps you must take.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 04:43:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Screenshots suggest TikTok is circumventing Apple App Store commissions</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/30/screenshots-suggest-tiktok-is-circumventing-apple-app-store-commissions/</link><description>The feature may be hidden from most users, either by design or because it's only shown to users in a specific group, like testers or high spenders.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 20:46:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Officials Failed to Act When COVID Hit Prisons. A New Study Shows the Deadly Cost.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/18/covid-prison-deaths-data</link><description>People in prison died at 3.4 times the rate of the free population, with the oldest hit hardest. New data holds lessons for preventing future deaths.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Immunity Challenge: How aging affects your immune system</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/seniors-boost-immunity?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>How does getting older affect your immune system? How can you keep those effects to a minimum? Your answers are here.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 16:57:15 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>