<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 08:43:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>New Women’s 3-on-3 Basketball League Unveils  Logo</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/10/new-womens-3-on-3-basketball-league-unveils-logo/basketball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Unrivaled league will feature six teams of five players each playing compressed full-court 3-on-3 games in Miami starting in January 2025</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:10:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>D.L. Hughley Rips George Clooney &amp; Others as Cowards for Turning on Biden</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/10/dl-hughley-rips-george-clooney-president-biden-drop-out-coward/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>D.L. Hughley is going scorched earth on George Clooney for calling on President Biden to drop out of the presidential race ... and he says Democrats are missing the big picture. The comedian joined us on "TMZ Live" Wednesday and ripped into George…</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 08:43:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Boston Celtics Partner With Amica For New Jersey Patch</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/10/boston-celtics-partner-with-amica-for-new-jersey-patch/basketball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The reigning NBA champion Boston Celtics have announced a multi-year jersey patch partnership with Amica, a Rhode Island-based auto, home and life insurance company. “The Boston Celtics jersey is not only recognized all across New England, it’s recognized all across the world,” team president Rich Gotham said during a press</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 17:05:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Megan Thee Stallion Fans Rage Against 'Family Feud' For 'Feet' Question</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/10/megan-thee-stallion-fans-family-feud-steve-harvey-feet-question-tory-lanez-shooting/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Megan Thee Stallion was such a good sport participating on "Celebrity Family Feud," and even made it to the bonus round, but some of her fans think one of Steve Harvey's questions crossed a line! Steve tossed up the question to Megan and Ne-Yo,…</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 08:43:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Winston-Salem Dash pay tribute to Windy City with Italian Beef alternate</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/10/winston-salem-dash-pay-tribute-to-windy-city-with-italian-beef-alternate/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Winston-Salem, North Carolina, is not exactly known for its Italian beef, but the High-A Winston-Salem Dash will wear jerseys featuring the sandwiches later this season. Italian beef sandwiches—made of slow roasted beef and giardiniera, an Italian relish of pickled vegetables—are a signature food item in Chicago, where the Dash’s parent</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 15:18:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>George Clooney Forced Biden to Change Fundraiser Date, Says Campaign Source</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/10/george-clooney-force-joe-biden-change-fundraiser-date-campaign-source/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>The gloves are off between George Clooney and President Biden -- folks involved with the campaign are firing back at Clooney over the Hollywood fundraiser the actor co-hosted ... saying he was anything but accommodating to POTUS. As you know,…</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 08:43:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lehigh Valley IronPigs City Connect series to highlight Bethlehem, PA</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/10/lehigh-valley-ironpigs-city-connect-series-to-highlight-bethlehem-pa/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Triple-A Lehigh Valley IronPigs’ “City Connect” series pays tribute to three Pennsylvania towns, Allentown, Bethlehem, and Easton, over the course of three seasons. Last year the first installment highlighted the famous strawberry pie at the Allentown department store Hess. This year the team will honor the “Christmas City” of</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 14:55:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Philly Man Accused of Ejaculating on Woman's Leg in Shocking Video</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/10/man-ejaculates-woman-leg-runs-away-shocking-video-philadelphia-dollar-tree/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Philadelphia cops, and Meek Mill, are searching for a man who allegedly masturbated on a woman's leg in a Dollar Tree store, and new footage captures the shocking aftermath. The video posted on X was apparently recorded by the alleged victim ...…</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 08:43:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Portland Sea Dogs to play as Maine Lobster Bakes</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/10/portland-sea-dogs-to-play-as-maine-lobster-bakes/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Double-A Portland Sea Dogs will pay tribute to one of their home state’s oldest and largest industries when they play as the Maine Lobster Bakes later this season. Per the team, the state of Maine harvests more than 100 million pounds of lobster every year—roughly 90 percent of the</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 14:14:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Simpsons' Writer Stunned Cypress Hill Prediction Coming True</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/10/simpsons-writer-stunned-cypress-hill-prediction-coming-true/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>A fan-favorite 'Simpsons' gag from nearly 30 years ago is about to become a real life event -- courtesy of Cypress Hill -- and the writer who came up with the joke tells TMZ, he's freaking out ... in a good way. The west coast rap legends --…</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 08:43:06 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>