<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 07:25:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Trans Historical Fiction Books</title><link>https://bookriot.com/trans-historical-fiction/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/trans-historical-fiction-books.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>Because trans people have always existed, and always will.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2024 Nissan Frontier Review: The driver's choice in an array of configurations</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/06/13/2024-nissan-frontier-review/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/06/11162431/BB1A8987-1-copy.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Nissan , Truck Continue reading 2024 Nissan Frontier Review: The driver's choice in an array of configurations 2024 Nissan Frontier Review: The driver's choice in an array of configurations originally appeared on Autoblog on Thu, 13 Jun 2024 06:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>5 things to know before the stock market opens Thursday</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/06/13/5-things-to-know-before-the-stock-market-opens-thursday-june-13.html</link><description>Here are five key things investors need to know to start the trading day.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 12:22:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 555</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-555/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-555</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Staying up-to-date with today’s job search can feel overwhelming. That’s why I publish this summary, to help share trends and issues impacting job seekers. In this week’s summary, you’ll learn about: If you enjoyed any of these resources, be sure and follow them or subscribe to their newsletters. To subscribe to Summary Sunday, here’s the […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 555 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 11:47:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Children’s digital media exposure as a backdrop for multilingual learning</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/childrens-digital-media-exposure-as-a-backdrop-for-multilingual-learning/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=childrens-digital-media-exposure-as-a-backdrop-for-multilingual-learning</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Multilingual children use digital media regularly, in all their home languages. Digital media use may affect multilingual children’s early language learning by reducing opportunities for back-and-forth conversations with adults. This finding is similar to results of studies of digital media and language learning for children learning only one language. When using […] The post Children’s digital media exposure as a backdrop for multilingual learning appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 20:27:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Breakfast Egg Rolls</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/breakfast-egg-rolls/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Breakfast Egg Rolls are a fun and delicious way to change up breakfast! The inside is filled with savory sausage,…</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Best Air Purifying Plants</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/best-air-purifying-plants/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>We love any excuse to buy more plants, and you may have heard they can improve your home’s indoor air quality. But before you blow your paycheck in the name of a healthier home, let’s dive deeper into plants’ air purifying powers. We’ll share which plants we recommend and what benefits you can actually expect from them. We’ve heard for years about how plants act as natural air filters for your home. So let’s dive a little deeper, shall we? 7 Air Purifying Plants If you just came here for a list, our favorite air purifying houseplants are bulleted below. The best part is these are all beautiful, low-maintenance plants. Many also appear on our best low-light indoor plants list too! Dracaena (including Corn Plant ) Snake Plant Aglaonema English Ivy Pothos Bamboo Palm Spider Plant There are certainly more that could be included here, but we narrowed it to the ones that are most often cited by experts AND the plants that we think look best too. Continue reading Best Air Purifying Plants at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 14:15:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What I’m Packing For My Girls</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/06/what-im-packing-for-my-girls/</link><description>Traveling to Italy in the summer with our girls means thoughtful planning to ensure their comfort and fun throughout the… The post What I’m Packing For My Girls appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 21:00:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>11 Compelling Nonfiction Audiobooks for Children</title><link>https://bookriot.com/compelling-nonfiction-audiobooks-for-children/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/kid-wearing-headphones.png</image_url><description>What's your favorite kids' audiobook?</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2025 BMW M2 gets more powerful — and lots more colorful</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/06/12/2025-bmw-m2-refresh-more-power/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/06/12151231/P90553488_highRes1.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: BMW , Coupe , Luxury , Performance Continue reading 2025 BMW M2 gets more powerful — and lots more colorful 2025 BMW M2 gets more powerful — and lots more colorful originally appeared on Autoblog on Wed, 12 Jun 2024 18:30:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 23:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tesla shareholder vote on Musk's historic pay package won't resolve 'legal disputes'</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/06/13/tesla-shareholder-vote-on-musk-pay-plan-wont-clear-legal-disputes.html</link><description>While Tesla shareholders will vote on whether they think Elon Musk should get his mammoth pay package, the courts will have the final say.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 554</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-554/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-554</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>We all need trusted sources for job search. Searching the internet and watching Tiktok videos isn’t always the best solution. There is and always has been conflicting advice and opinions when it comes to job search and especially resumes. (If you’ve ever asked 10 people for feedback on your resume then you know what I […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 554 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 11:13:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>La exposición de los niños a los medios digitales como contexto para el aprendizaje multilingüe</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/la-exposicion-de-los-ninos-a-los-medios-digitales-como-contexto-para-el-aprendizaje-multilingue/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=la-exposicion-de-los-ninos-a-los-medios-digitales-como-contexto-para-el-aprendizaje-multilingue</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Puntos clave para los cuidadores Los niños multilingües usan frecuentemente los medios digitales y los usan en los distintos idiomas que se hablan en su hogar. El uso de los medios digitales (por ej., la televisión, el computador o los “smartphones”) puede afectar negativamente el desarrollo del lenguaje en los niños que son multilingües porque […] The post La exposición de los niños a los medios digitales como contexto para el aprendizaje multilingüe appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 20:26:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Italian Pasta Salad</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/italian-pasta-salad/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Indulge in the flavors of Italy with this irresistible Italian pasta salad. Each bite is bursting with flavor from cherry…</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Weekend In New Orleans With Kids</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/new-orleans-with-kids/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Since our travel guides to Charleston with kids and Palm Springs with kids have elicited requests for more travel ideas with kids, we’re back with an overdue recap of our 3-night trip to New Orleans. We’d never been to The Big Easy before and were impressed by how family-friendly the city is. It’s not all booze, beads, and Bourbon Street! So here’s a look at where we stayed, what we did, and what we’re excited to do next time we go back – because we will definitely go back! The four of us (well, five if you count our chihuahua!) went to NOLA for 3 nights in November of 2022. At the time, our kids were 8 and 12 years old. So unfortunately we can’t vouch for our suggestions being a good fit for toddlers or younger children. Although I’m sure ours would’ve loved the Louisiana Children’s Museum and Storyland playground back in the day! Continue reading A Weekend In New Orleans With Kids at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 17:17:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mermaid Moments</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/06/mermaid-moments/</link><description>Outfit Details: Wardrobe NYC Top, Parterre Skirt, Loro Piana Hat, Prada Sunglasses, JB x Jennifer Behr Turquoise Necklace, Heritage NYC &amp; Sherman Fields Necklaces This… The post Mermaid Moments appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 05:00:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best Book Club Books to Read for Pride</title><link>https://bookriot.com/the-best-book-club-books-to-read-for-pride/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/two-fair-skinned-Asian-women-rading-next-to-each-other.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>Which book is your book club reading to celebrate Pride?</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 21:33:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2025 BMW 2 Series gets a fresh interior look and improved tech</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/06/12/2025-bmw-2-series-refresh-revealed/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/06/12130520/P90554918.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: BMW , Coupe , Luxury , Performance Continue reading 2025 BMW 2 Series gets a fresh interior look and improved tech 2025 BMW 2 Series gets a fresh interior look and improved tech originally appeared on Autoblog on Wed, 12 Jun 2024 18:01:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 23:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Britain's Labour Party pledges 'wealth creation' as it targets landslide election victory</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/06/13/uk-general-election-2024-labour-publishes-manifesto-.html</link><description>Britain's Labour Party, considered the frontrunner in the upcoming national election, on Thursday said it would be "pro-business" and prioritize "wealth creation" as it released its manifesto.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 11:58:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sharing Fun Facts About Yourself: 22 Examples &amp; Ideas</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/fun-facts-about-me/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fun-facts-about-me</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Asking to share some fun facts about yourself is a common icebreaker that’s used during job interviews. But the quality of your answer still matters. This guide will help you come up with some ideas for crafting a response that starts the interview on a good note. Table of contents Ideas for Sharing Fun Facts […] The post Sharing Fun Facts About Yourself: 22 Examples &amp; Ideas appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 15:26:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Becoming Confident in Parenting Abilities</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/confidence-in-parenting/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=confidence-in-parenting</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Parental self-efficacy (i.e., a parent’s confidence in their own ability to care for their infant and respond to the infant’s needs) is the first step to a good parent-child relationship. Research has explored the development of maternal self-efficacy beginning during pregnancy and continuing after childbirth. Mothers who have previous childbirth and […] The post Becoming Confident in Parenting Abilities appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 10:06:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Guide to Different Cuts of Meat</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/different-cuts-of-meat/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Learn the basics of using meat in the kitchen! I walk you through the different cuts of meat and help…</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>9 Easy Low-Light Indoor Plants</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/easy-low-light-indoor-plants/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>I used to think every houseplant needed a sunny corner or bright windowsill to thrive. But it turns out many of our favorite go-to houseplants do just fine in shady corners and low-light locations. So before you write off your house as too dark to sustain plant life, check out this list of the best indoor plants for low light. You might be surprised at how many good options there are! Our upstairs family room is the brightest room we’ve ever owned thanks to big unobstructed windows on all 4 sides. But most of our indoor plants live downstairs, where we get far less natural light. Luckily, that hasn’t stopped us from growing our collection of happy healthy houseplants. 9 Houseplants That Don’t Need A Lot Of Light Here are our favorite low-light indoor plants. We list a lot more info on them below, but here’s a quick list to bring on your next trip to the plant store: Snake Plant ZZ Plant Pothos Heartleaf Philodendron English Ivy Aglaonema Cast Iron Plant Monstera Parlor Palm Perhaps our favorite part of this list is that these aren’t ugly “consolation plants” that people begrudgingly buy for dark homes. Continue reading 9 Easy Low-Light Indoor Plants at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 14:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JB x Jennifer Behr Drop Two</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/06/jb-x-jennifer-behr-drop-two/</link><description>Outfit Details: Pucci Swimsuit, Prada Sunglasses I am thrilled to share my second collection with Jennifer Behr, which was inspired by… The post JB x Jennifer Behr Drop Two appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 05:00:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>First Looks of the New Lord of the Rings: The War of the Rohirrim Anime</title><link>https://bookriot.com/lord-of-the-rings-the-war-of-the-rohirrim-anime/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/Lord-of-the-Rings-The-War-of-the-Rohirrim-Anime-title-image.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>Will you be watching this in theaters?</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 20:32:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Inside Henrik Fisker's second failed automotive startup</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/06/12/inside-henrik-fisker-second-failed-automotive-startup/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/crop/1778x1000+0+76/resize/800x450!/format/jpg/quality/85/https://media.zenfs.com/en/business_insider_articles_888/3f51ee97f4581fb90da34ebf37117469</image_url><description>Filed under: BMW , Coupe , Luxury , Performance Continue reading Inside Henrik Fisker's second failed automotive startup Inside Henrik Fisker's second failed automotive startup originally appeared on Autoblog on Wed, 12 Jun 2024 15:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tesla expects to raise Model 3 prices in Europe after higher EU tariffs on China EVs</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/06/13/tesla-to-likely-raise-model-3-prices-in-europe-after-eu-tariffs-on-china-evs.html</link><description>Tesla said it may have to increase the price of the Model 3 sold in the EU after the bloc said it could impose higher tariffs on electric cars imported from China.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 11:06:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 553</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-553/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-553</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Tools and technology change rapidly. Yet as wonderful as technology can be, it doesn’t replace the need for human connection through interactions. Keep this in mind as you are searching for a new job. It’s your human connections that often open doors! In this week’s collection of news and tips for job seekers, you’ll find: […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 553 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 12:19:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A case for public preschool: New study reveals preschool benefits to be longer-lasting and substantial</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/benefits-of-public-preschool/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=benefits-of-public-preschool</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Preschool lays a foundation for elementary school students to succeed. In the United States, as children approach kindergarten entry, it is increasingly common for 4-year-olds to be in non-parental group care and education, often in a center- or school-based setting where they can learn alongside peers. For children from low-income communities, […] The post A case for public preschool: New study reveals preschool benefits to be longer-lasting and substantial appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 08:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Swedish Cream with Berries</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/swedish-cream/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Treat yourself to this luxurious and refreshing Swedish Cream, a classic dessert that’s easy to make. With a few simple…</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/how-to-remove-wallpaper/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Wallpaper has made a big comeback as a trendy home design choice. But despite its resurgence, there are still plenty of us dealing with dingy, dated, or downright ugly old wallpaper we don’t want. In our old home, we had to remove wallpaper in so many rooms: the kitchen, the dining room, the foyer, and two different bathrooms! As we traveled from room to room removing wallpaper, we tested 4 different methods, and today we’ll share what we learned. Removing wallpaper doesn’t require special tools or lots of money. It’s a totally doable project for any homeowner. However, it can be a tedious process that can take elbow grease and patience, depending on the size of your room and the stubbornness of your wallpaper. But having removed several rooms worth of decades-old wallpaper, we can confidently say it’s worth the effort! You can also check out more before and afters of our once-wallpapered rooms. Continue reading How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:21:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What I’m Packing For Italy</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/06/what-im-packing-for-italy/</link><description>Outfit Details: Jil Sander Shirt, Joseph Pants, Alaia Flats (sold out, similar here), Delvaux Bag, Saint Laurent Sunglasses, NST Studio… The post What I’m Packing For Italy appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 05:00:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 2024 Lambda Literary Award Winners</title><link>https://bookriot.com/the-2024-lambda-literary-award-winners/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/The-Lambda-Literary-Awards.png</image_url><description>The 36th annual Lambda Literary Awards in 26 different categories of LGBTQ+ books were announced. Here are the winners.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 17:52:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>F1 Canadian Grand Prix: 7 things I learned attending the race in 2024</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/06/12/f1-canadian-grand-prix-7-things-i-learned-attending-the-race-in-2024/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/06/12135637/f1_grand_prix_of_canada.jpeg</image_url><description>Filed under: Motorsports Continue reading F1 Canadian Grand Prix: 7 things I learned attending the race in 2024 F1 Canadian Grand Prix: 7 things I learned attending the race in 2024 originally appeared on Autoblog on Wed, 12 Jun 2024 14:45:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 19:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Solugen locks in $214 million Energy Department loan to build a 'bioforge' for sustainable chemicals production</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/06/13/solugen-locks-in-214-million-energy-department-loan-to-build-a-bioforge-for-sustainable-chemicals-production.html</link><description>A Houston-based startup called Solugen has locked in a $214 million loan commitment from the Department of Energy to build a sustainable chemicals plant in Marshall, Minnesota.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 552</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-552/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-552</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>When you are searching for a job, you will inevitably run into unexpected scenarios. You will have questions, experience self-doubt and even feel discouraged. You’ll also experience great wins, meet wonderful people and discover new things about yourself. That’s the roller-coaster of job search. Consider Summary Sunday your resource for getting questions answered and showing […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 552 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 11:37:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fathers’ views on family and work after COVID-19 lockdowns</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/fathers-views-on-family-and-work-after-covid-19-lockdowns/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fathers-views-on-family-and-work-after-covid-19-lockdowns</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Fathers often want to be present for their children and contribute to household tasks, but they can lack opportunities and confidence; they may see themselves as “helpers” instead of parents. Australian fathers in our small study reported that they spent more time with their children during the COVID-19 lockdowns, and they […] The post Fathers’ views on family and work after COVID-19 lockdowns appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blue Cheese Burger</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/blue-cheese-burger/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Get ready to be blown away by this Blue Cheese Burger! It’s thick, juicy, and filled with flavor. If you…</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aglaonema Plant – Complete Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/aglaonema-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Aglaonema, also called the Chinese Evergreen Plant, is an easy-care houseplant that lives happily in many lighting conditions – even a dark corner of our daughter’s room. There are dozens of different Aglaonema varieties, most with large tropical foliage and colors ranging from silvery-green, red, and even vibrant pink. They’re also tough to kill, so they’re a great option for forgetful plant owners or anyone looking for an easy win in the plant department. These truly have been very low maintenance for us. We purchased our two Aglaonemas (pronounced ag-lee-oh-neem-ah ) to put atop our daughter’s closet. It’s sometimes hard to distinguish different varieties, but we believe that’s an Aglaonema Silver (right) and either a Candy Cane or Princess Silver Queen (left). Aglaonema Quick Facts Here’s what you need to know about your Aglaonema at a glance: Latin name : Aglaonema is the genus under which there are 21 recognized species . Continue reading Aglaonema Plant – Complete Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:47:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vintage Vault</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/06/vintage-vault/</link><description>Outfit Details: Vintage Fendi Jacket (similar here), Dior Jeans, Jemma Wynne Necklace, Retrouvai Emerald Over the years, I’ve been drawn to both Etsy and,… The post Vintage Vault appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 05:00:20 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>