<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 07:11:22 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Utah NHL Team Releases 20 Possible Names, Fan Vote Begins</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/08/utah-nhl-team-releases-20-possible-names-fan-vote-begins/hockey-2/</link><description>Utah’s new NHL franchise has released its list of twenty team names it is considering for its inaugural 2024-25 season. Fans can vote for up to four of the twenty finalists on their ballot but can only cast one ballot. Voting starts tonight and will conclude after two weeks on</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 02:38:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Patrick Beverley Under Police Investigation For Ball-Throwing Incident</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/08/patrick-beverley-under-police-investigation-for-ball-throwing-incident/</link><description>Cops are now looking into the Patrick Beverley ball-throwing incident ... confirming to TMZ Sports on Wednesday the NBA player is currently under police investigation. A spokesperson for the Indianapolis Metropolitan Police Department tells us ...…</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 07:11:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Burnley FC Leave Umbro, Sign Kit Deal With Castore</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/08/burnley-fc-leave-umbro-sign-kit-deal-with-castore/soccer/</link><description>Burnley currently in Premier League relegation zone; if they stay up, they'll be one of two clubs in England's top flight outfitted by Castore</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 17:46:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Andy Cohen Denies Rumors He and John Mayer Are Hooking Up</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/08/andy-cohen-confirm-no-banging-john-mayer-sex-straight-rock-star-platonic-friends/</link><description>Andy Cohen swears he doesn't know if John Mayer's body's a wonderland ... as he tries to put rumors to rest he and the Grammy winner are getting it on. The King of Bravo sat down and addressed it head-on when he was asked about longstanding…</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 07:11:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Report: Brazil Could Ditch Nike as Kit Supplier After Receiving Massive Offer</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/07/report-brazil-could-ditch-nike-as-kit-supplier-after-receiving-massive-offer/soccer/</link><description>Brazilian news outlet reports CBF has received an offer worth more than five times what Nike currently pays them from either Adidas or Puma</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:29:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Farrah Abraham Seems to Shade Jenelle Evans 'Teen Mom' Return</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/08/farrah-abraham-shade-jenelle-evans-teen-mom-return/</link><description>Farrah Abraham never seems to miss an opportunity to roast her nemesis Jenelle Evans ... and she kinda did again for her going back to 'Teen Mom' ... albeit, very politely. The former reality star and content creator posted a video Wednesday that…</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 07:11:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>USL’s Orange County Try to Capture Magic with New Cup Kit</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/06/usls-orange-county-sc-try-to-capture-some-magic-with-new-cup-kit/soccer/</link><description>Kit is inspired by designs worn in 1910s, when U.S. Open Cup started, and will be worn when OCSC takes on Loudoun United in Round of 32 on Tuesday, May 7</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 03:31:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shohei Ohtani's Interpreter Pleading Guilty To Federal Charges, Facing Up To 33 Yrs</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/08/shohei-ohtani-interpreter-ippei-mizuhara-plead-guilty-gambling-debt-dodgers-mlb/</link><description>Shohei Ohtani's ex-translator and best friend, Ippei Mizuhara, will plead guilty to multiple federal charges -- after admitting to taking nearly $17 million from the Dodgers superstar -- and now faces up to 3+ decades in prison! On Wednesday, The…</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 07:11:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Panama Football Unveils New National Team Crest</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/06/panamanian-football-federation-unveils-new-national-team-crest/soccer/</link><description>Crest depicts a harpy eagle — the national bird of Panama — with each feather representing one of the country's 10 provinces</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paris Hilton &amp; Nicole Richie Reuniting for New Reality TV Show</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/08/paris-hilton-nicole-richie-reuniting-new-reality-tv-show/</link><description>Paris Hilton and Nicole Richie are getting ready to be reality TV stars all over again -- 'cause the 2000s darlings are teaming up anew to run it back ... but for a whole new project. Production sources tell TMZ ... Paris and Nicole are both on…</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 07:11:22 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>