<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 06:57:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>How Big of a Problem is Inflation Really?</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/how-big-of-a-problem-is-inflation-really/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, Ross here. As we navigate through the bull market, one looming question persists: How big of a problem is inflation really? Despite the alarm bells rung by bears and the media, our latest data shows a decrease in the number of S&amp;P 500 companies concerned about inflation during their earnings calls. This signals a potentially overstated issue, with corporate earnings—key market drivers—still on solid ground. If you're watching the market meander sideways and finding it "boring," you might be missing out. Sideways markets are ripe for strategic positioning, often preceding significant movements. Join me tomorrow at 10 a.m. Eastern for a masterclass where I'll delve into insider trading insights, showing you how to distinguish between high and low signal trades and uncover the top-performing insiders. Plus, I'll share an exclusive opportunity that's just come onto my radar. Don’t miss this chance to learn from the insiders—reserve your spot now! The post How Big of a Problem is Inflation Really? appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2025 Honda HR-V Review: Checks boxes, does not pull heartstrings</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/article/2025-honda-hr-v-review/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2022/06/17112552/2023-Honda-HR-V-EX-L-front-three-quarter-Mt-St-Helens.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Honda , Buying Guide , New Car Reviews , Crossover , SUV Continue reading 2025 Honda HR-V Review: Checks boxes, does not pull heartstrings 2025 Honda HR-V Review: Checks boxes, does not pull heartstrings originally appeared on Autoblog on Fri, 24 May 2024 06:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BiggerNews: 2024 Housing Market Update and Why Prices Are Still Rising</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-959</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>The 2024 housing market isn’t turning out how most of us thought. At the beginning of the year, real estate investors were hopeful that mortgage rates would fall, affordability would […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 07:02:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10 Exciting Books to Read this Summer</title><link>https://bookriot.com/books-to-read-this-summer-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/summer-2024-books-to-read.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>These 10 books will have you set up for an excellent summer of reading.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sharing Fun Facts About Yourself: 22 Examples &amp; Ideas</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/fun-facts-about-me/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fun-facts-about-me</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Asking to share some fun facts about yourself is a common icebreaker that’s used during job interviews. But the quality of your answer still matters. This guide will help you come up with some ideas for crafting a response that starts the interview on a good note. Table of contents Ideas for Sharing Fun Facts […] The post Sharing Fun Facts About Yourself: 22 Examples &amp; Ideas appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 15:26:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Becoming Confident in Parenting Abilities</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/confidence-in-parenting/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=confidence-in-parenting</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Parental self-efficacy (i.e., a parent’s confidence in their own ability to care for their infant and respond to the infant’s needs) is the first step to a good parent-child relationship. Research has explored the development of maternal self-efficacy beginning during pregnancy and continuing after childbirth. Mothers who have previous childbirth and […] The post Becoming Confident in Parenting Abilities appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 10:06:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Former TikTok CEO Kevin Mayer says AI hype is at an all-time fever pitch right now</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/24/former-tiktok-ceo-kevin-mayer-says-ai-hype-at-an-all-time-fever-pitch.html</link><description>Former TikTok CEO and Candle Media co-CEO Kevin Mayer believes that the hype around artificial intelligence has reached a crescendo.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 11:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kandi Burruss Shares a Hack for Lasting Makeup &amp; Wedding Must-Haves</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1402273/real-housewives-of-atlanta-kandi-burruss-shares-a-hack-for-lasting-makeup-wedding-must-haves?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>We included these products chosen by Kandi Burruss because we think you'll like her picks at these prices. Kandi is a paid spokesperson for the Amazon Influencer Program. E! has affiliate...</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Factor Strategies Belong in Your Completion Portfolio Toolkit</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/23/factor-strategies-belong-in-your-completion-portfolio-toolkit/</link><description>Why wouldn't you include factor strategies in your completion portfolio? A review of the two commonly used approaches for managing institutional assets highlights their symbiotic nature.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 19:09:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elon Musk predicts jobs will become ‘kinda like a hobby’</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/24/elon-musk-future-work-jobs-hobbies-artificial-intelligence/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2151277355_d43a40-e1716545591403.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>"In a benign scenario probably none of us will have a job."</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 11:38:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Colors Of The Sea</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/colors-of-the-sea/</link><description>Outfit Details: Show Me Your Mumu Coverup (also similar here), Good American Swimsuit, Miu Miu Sandals, Valentino Hat, Prada Sunglasses, Hanna Andersson Dress, Teva Sandals &amp; Stella Kids… The post Colors Of The Sea appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 05:00:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oops</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/agm0wPr</link><description>Tags: facepalm 2824 points, 247 comments.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 11:55:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Football in Their DNA: AC Milan Launches 2024-25 Home Kit</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/23/football-in-their-dna-ac-milan-launches-2024-25-home-kit/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Tonal segmented stripes inside red stripes are a visual representation of the human genome; patch on back collar celebrates club's 125th anniversary</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 16:11:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jio Financial unit to buy $4.32B of telecom gear from Reliance Retail</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/23/jio-financial-unit-to-buy-4-32b-of-telecom-gear-from-reliance-retail/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>A Jio Financial unit plans to purchase customer premises equipment and telecom gear worth $4.32 billion from Reliance Retail. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 06:43:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Out of the Blue: The Rise and Fall of a Black Cop</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/23/black-police-officers-cleveland-black-shield</link><description>After Cleveland officer Vincent Montague shot a Black man, he got promoted. Then he allied with Black Lives Matter, and his life went off the rails.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Grilled Tilapia</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/grilled-tilapia/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Fire up the grill! This grilled tilapia is deliciously seasoned and has the best flaky texture. Mix a few simple…</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sean Kingston's Florida Home Raided by Cops, Mom Arrested</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/23/sean-kingston-florida-home-raided-cops-mom-janice-arrested/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>12:12 PM PT -- Sean Kingston just addressed the raid on his IG Story writing, "People love negative energy! I am good and so is my mother!.. my lawyers are handling everything as we speak🙏🏽🙏🏽." Sean Kingston is in the crosshairs of a…</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 06:57:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Federal Experts Talk Bird Flu ‘What Ifs’ in WebMD Live Event</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/cold-and-flu/news/20240516/federal-experts-talk-bird-flu-what-ifs?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>WebMD brought together experts from four federal agencies to talk prevention, monitoring, and what the “what ifs” of bird flu might look like.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:50:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Weekend In New Orleans With Kids</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/new-orleans-with-kids/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Since our travel guides to Charleston with kids and Palm Springs with kids have elicited requests for more travel ideas with kids, we’re back with an overdue recap of our 3-night trip to New Orleans. We’d never been to The Big Easy before and were impressed by how family-friendly the city is. It’s not all booze, beads, and Bourbon Street! So here’s a look at where we stayed, what we did, and what we’re excited to do next time we go back – because we will definitely go back! The four of us (well, five if you count our chihuahua!) went to NOLA for 3 nights in November of 2022. At the time, our kids were 8 and 12 years old. So unfortunately we can’t vouch for our suggestions being a good fit for toddlers or younger children. Although I’m sure ours would’ve loved the Louisiana Children’s Museum and Storyland playground back in the day! Continue reading A Weekend In New Orleans With Kids at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 17:17:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Don’t Wait for This to Happen</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/dont-wait-for-this-to-happen/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Markets are soaring to new all-time highs, and the bears are out in full force. But don't be fooled—this bull market extends beyond the U.S. Today's chart highlights the All-Country World Index, showcasing the global market's performance. It’s at an all-time high too, proving the American bull market is not an outlier. Tune in at 3 p.m. Eastern for my live masterclass, where I'll show you how to position yourself for super performance by following corporate insiders. Don't miss this opportunity! The post Don’t Wait for This to Happen appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 15:55:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indy 500's intriguing Row 7 lineup: Andretti, Castroneves and Dixon</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/23/indy-500s-intriguing-row-7-lineup-andretti-castroneves-and-dixon/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/23174153/indycar_indy_500_auto_racing-3.jpeg</image_url><description>Filed under: Motorsports Continue reading Indy 500's intriguing Row 7 lineup: Andretti, Castroneves and Dixon Indy 500's intriguing Row 7 lineup: Andretti, Castroneves and Dixon originally appeared on Autoblog on Thu, 23 May 2024 18:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fundamentals of Funding: How to Finance Real Estate Without the Big Banks</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-410</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Private money is a “secret weapon” for real estate investing, allowing you to dodge the major banks and fund real estate deals on your terms. But just how easy is […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 07:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The State of Publishing, As Seen From the Inside: Notes from the 2024 Publishers Weekly U.S. Book Show</title><link>https://bookriot.com/publishers-weekly-us-book-show/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/us-book-show-700-x-375.png</image_url><description>Get insights on the state of publishing from agents, editors, and other industry professionals from the 2024 U.S. Book Show.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 19:14:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 553</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-553/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-553</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Tools and technology change rapidly. Yet as wonderful as technology can be, it doesn’t replace the need for human connection through interactions. Keep this in mind as you are searching for a new job. It’s your human connections that often open doors! In this week’s collection of news and tips for job seekers, you’ll find: […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 553 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 12:19:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A case for public preschool: New study reveals preschool benefits to be longer-lasting and substantial</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/benefits-of-public-preschool/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=benefits-of-public-preschool</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Preschool lays a foundation for elementary school students to succeed. In the United States, as children approach kindergarten entry, it is increasingly common for 4-year-olds to be in non-parental group care and education, often in a center- or school-based setting where they can learn alongside peers. For children from low-income communities, […] The post A case for public preschool: New study reveals preschool benefits to be longer-lasting and substantial appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 08:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nvidia's stock split makes it a Dow contender — but not a shoo-in</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/24/nvidias-stock-split-makes-it-a-dow-contender-but-not-a-shoo-in.html</link><description>An index committee looks for a stock with "an excellent reputation" and sustained growth that is "of interest to a large number of investors."</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 11:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Best Coffee &amp; Espresso Machines</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1401485/the-5-best-coffee-espresso-machines-to-make-cafe-worthy-drinks-at-home?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>The products featured in this article are from brands that are available in the NBCUniversal Checkout Marketplace. If you purchase something through our links, we get a commission. The only thing...</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>For the Analyst: Peer Benchmarking Methods to Improve Earnings Forecasts</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/21/for-the-analyst-peer-benchmarking-methods-to-improve-earnings-forecasts/</link><description>Peer benchmarking is a vexing task for financial analysts but one that is critical for forecasting earnings. This straightforward measure can help find peers for relative performance, compensation, and valuation benchmarking.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 12:47:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘A glaring blind spot’ in housing affordability: Mortgage underwriting and home appraisals should account for energy costs. Here’s why</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/24/glaring-blind-spot-housing-affordability-mortgage-underwriting-home-appraisals-energy-costs-enviornment-personal-finance/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1695945927-e1716545436797.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Ensuring home affordability is crucial to protecting the American Dream, but the monthly mortgage payment is just one part of the cost of owning a home.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 11:19:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Walmart Summer Fashion Under $50</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/walmart-summer-fashion-under-50/</link><description>Thank you to Walmart for sponsoring this post. I have a passion for finding beautiful fashion pieces for women and… The post Walmart Summer Fashion Under $50 appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 05:00:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Female gaming PC.</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/awybj18</link><description>Tags: tell me you are rich , without saying , you are rich 5818 points, 503 comments.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 11:55:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Could West Virginia Mountaineers Wear 1965 Throwback Uniforms In 2025?</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/22/could-west-virginia-mountaineers-wear-1965-throwback-uniforms-in-2025/college/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>A recent exchange on social media between West Virginia's athletic director, head coach and a fan indicates throwback uniforms might be in the works for next season.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 22:17:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Foursquare just laid off 105 employees</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/23/foursquare-just-laid-off-105-employees/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Foursquare, the location-focused outfit that in 2020 merged with Factual, another location-focused outfit, is joining the parade of companies to make cuts to one of its biggest cost centers – employees – in 2024. Per an email sent out to staffers Thursday afternoon by current CEO Gary Little and viewed by TechCrunch, 105 employees were […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 05:27:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Marshall Project Wins Prestigious Robert F. Kennedy Journalism Award for Criminal Justice</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/21/marshall-project-rfk-award</link><description>The award recognizes our 2023 investigation exposing lax prison discipline for abusive guards in New York state prisons.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best Burger and Secret Sauce</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/the-best-burger-and-secret-sauce-recipe/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Get ready for the ultimate burger experience topped with my irresistible Secret Sauce. The flavor packed into this burger is…</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jennifer Lopez, Netflix Banned Ben Affleck Questions Ahead of Premieres</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/23/jennifer-lopez-netflix-ban-ben-affleck-questions-movie-atlas-premiere/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>All Bennifer questions are off-limits, at least if you're media covering Jennifer Lopez for her new movie -- and reporters were warned about it before she arrived ... TMZ has learned. Sources with direct knowledge tell TMZ ... Netflix alerted all…</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 06:57:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What’s Next in Health Care for Older Adults: Questions and Answers With John Whyte, MD</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/blog-aging-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>As WebMD’s chief medical officer, John Whyte, MD, is in a unique position to see both the current state of medical care for America’s older adults and the way things are trending for the future. We asked him to share his insight on a few topics, along with a bit of advice.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:29:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Easy Low-Light Indoor Plants</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/easy-low-light-indoor-plants/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>I used to think every houseplant needed a sunny corner or bright windowsill to thrive. But it turns out many of our favorite go-to houseplants do just fine in shady corners and low-light locations. So before you write off your house as too dark to sustain plant life, check out this list of the best indoor plants for low light. You might be surprised at how many good options there are! Our upstairs family room is the brightest room we’ve ever owned thanks to big unobstructed windows on all 4 sides. But most of our indoor plants live downstairs, where we get far less natural light. Luckily, that hasn’t stopped us from growing our collection of happy healthy houseplants. 9 Houseplants That Don’t Need A Lot Of Light Here are our favorite low-light indoor plants. We list a lot more info on them below, but here’s a quick list to bring on your next trip to the plant store: Snake Plant ZZ Plant Pothos Heartleaf Philodendron English Ivy Aglaonema Cast Iron Plant Monstera Parlor Palm Perhaps our favorite part of this list is that these aren’t ugly “consolation plants” that people begrudgingly buy for dark homes. Continue reading Easy Low-Light Indoor Plants at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 14:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Data-Backed Glimpse of the Market’s Future</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/a-data-backed-glimpse-of-the-markets-future/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>The bears keep insisting this bull market can't last, but let's dive into the data. The S&amp;P 500 has surged about 48% since its October 2022 lows. Historically, the average gain two years in is 57%, suggesting even more upside by October 2024. Ignore the naysayers and focus on the facts. Join me at 11 a.m. ET for a live masterclass where I'll show you how to align with top corporate insiders. Learn their winning strategies and spot a hot insider opportunity. Don't miss out—secure your spot now! The post A Data-Backed Glimpse of the Market’s Future appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Civic goes hybrid, driving the Nissan Z Nismo and more | Autoblog Podcast #833</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/23/podcast-833-2025-honda-civic-maverick-delica-id7-delay-f1-cx-90-nissan-z-nismo/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/23164201/Podcast833Photo.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Government/Legal , Green , Motorsports , Podcasts , Ford , Honda , Mazda , Mercedes-Benz , Mitsubishi , Nissan , Toyota , Volkswagen , Truck , Crossover , Hatchback , SUV , Electric , Hybrid , Luxury , Off-Road Vehicles , Performance , Sedan Plus, is Ford developing a sportier Maverick? Continue reading The Civic goes hybrid, driving the Nissan Z Nismo and more | Autoblog Podcast #833 The Civic goes hybrid, driving the Nissan Z Nismo and more | Autoblog Podcast #833 originally appeared on Autoblog on Thu, 23 May 2024 17:20:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 22:20:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Financial Freedom in 9 Steps: The Money Guy’s Financial Order of Operations</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-531</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>If you follow these nine steps, you will reach financial independence. How do we know? Well, The Money Guy Show’s Brian Preston and Bo Hanson have tested it hundreds of […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 07:01:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What are You Reading This Week? — May 23, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/read-harder-updates-may-23-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/reading-and-water.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>What are you reading right now? Would you recommend it?</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 552</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-552/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-552</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>When you are searching for a job, you will inevitably run into unexpected scenarios. You will have questions, experience self-doubt and even feel discouraged. You’ll also experience great wins, meet wonderful people and discover new things about yourself. That’s the roller-coaster of job search. Consider Summary Sunday your resource for getting questions answered and showing […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 552 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 11:37:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fathers’ views on family and work after COVID-19 lockdowns</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/fathers-views-on-family-and-work-after-covid-19-lockdowns/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fathers-views-on-family-and-work-after-covid-19-lockdowns</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Fathers often want to be present for their children and contribute to household tasks, but they can lack opportunities and confidence; they may see themselves as “helpers” instead of parents. Australian fathers in our small study reported that they spent more time with their children during the COVID-19 lockdowns, and they […] The post Fathers’ views on family and work after COVID-19 lockdowns appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chinese EV makers continue aggressive push into Europe under growing threat of tariffs</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/24/chinese-ev-makers-continue-push-into-europe-amid-tariff-threat.html</link><description>Nio, Xpeng and BYD have continued their European expansion even as an ongoing EU probe into Chinese electric vehicle subsidies could result in tariffs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 10:19:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>See Remi Bader's Pics of Fitness Transformation After Quitting Ozempic</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1402328/tiktoker-remi-bader-reveals-before-and-after-of-fitness-transformation-after-quitting-ozempic?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>Remi Bader is sharing insight into her wellness journey. A year after revealing she quit using the drug Ozempic to lose weight, the TikTok star shared a before-and-after video documenting how her...</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 03:34:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Building LLMs in the Open-Source Community: A Call to Action for Investment Professionals</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/20/building-llms-in-the-open-source-community-a-call-to-action-for-investment-professionals/</link><description>Large language models like ChatGPT are changing the way we think about investing and reshaping roles in the investment profession.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 16:26:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fake AI-generated Biden robocalls orchestrator faces $6m fine and criminal charges</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/24/steve-kramer-biden-robocalls-new-hampshire-presidential-primary/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1252481749-e1716543841316.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The Federal Communications Commission said the fine it proposed for Steven Kramer is its first involving generative AI technology.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 10:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summer Ready With Saks Designer Sale</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/summer-ready-with-saks-designer-sale/</link><description>Thank you to Saks Fifth Avenue for sponsoring this post. Summer is just around the corner, making it the perfect… The post Summer Ready With Saks Designer Sale appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 05:00:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Female Brain works</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/aLnQOqP</link><description>Tags: funny , wtf , random , relationship , humor 8194 points, 713 comments.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 11:55:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OHL’s Guelph Storm File Trademarks for Three New Logos</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/22/ohls-guelph-storm-file-trademarks-for-three-new-logos/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>It's unclear if the Storm would keep their crimson, silver and black color scheme as trademark filing images are usually only available in grayscale</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 20:47:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Using memes, social media users have become red teams for half-baked AI features</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/23/using-memes-social-media-users-have-become-red-teams-for-half-baked-ai-features/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>“Running with scissors is a cardio exercise that can increase your heart rate and require concentration and focus,” says Google’s new AI search feature. “Some say it can also improve your pores and give you strength.” Google’s AI feature pulled this response from a website called Little Old Lady Comedy, which, as its name makes […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 01:21:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Police Tactics at Some Pro-Palestine Protests Ignore Past Lessons</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/18/police-israel-palestine-campus-protests</link><description>While some universities have sought peaceful approaches, others have used aggressive policing that bucks research from the protests following George Floyd’s murder.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Grilling Basics (Tips for Beginners)</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/how-to-grill/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Fire up your grill because these grilling basics will give you all the confidence you need! Discover how easy it…</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NBA Closes Investigation Into Josh Giddey</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/23/nba-closes-investigation-into-josh-giddey/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Josh Giddey is now in the clear ... months after police closed their investigation into allegations the Thunder star had an inappropriate relationship with an underage girl -- the NBA has followed suit. Sources told ESPN's Adrian Wojnarowski the…</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 06:57:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Get the Care You Need in a COVID-19 World</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/covid-senior-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>What to expect at the doctor’s office, hospitals, and long-term care facilities, the future of telemedicine, and how to get the best care during COVID-19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 19:50:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/how-to-remove-wallpaper/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Wallpaper has made a big comeback as a trendy home design choice. But despite its resurgence, there are still plenty of us dealing with dingy, dated, or downright ugly old wallpaper we don’t want. In our old home, we had to remove wallpaper in so many rooms: the kitchen, the dining room, the foyer, and two different bathrooms! As we traveled from room to room removing wallpaper, we tested 4 different methods, and today we’ll share what we learned. Removing wallpaper doesn’t require special tools or lots of money. It’s a totally doable project for any homeowner. However, it can be a tedious process that can take elbow grease and patience, depending on the size of your room and the stubbornness of your wallpaper. But having removed several rooms worth of decades-old wallpaper, we can confidently say it’s worth the effort! You can also check out more before and afters of our once-wallpapered rooms. Continue reading How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:21:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Profit from the Market’s Appetite</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/profit-from-the-markets-appetite/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, Ross here. Last week showed us that even after a brief slowdown, the markets are still on an upward trajectory—and it's clear from today's Bitcoin chart that we're just getting started. The bull flag pattern I highlighted is unfolding right before our eyes, with Bitcoin surging nearly 10% in just four days. This movement isn't just about Bitcoin; it reflects a broader market craving for risk, and today, I'll show you how to leverage this appetite to your advantage. Ready to join the insiders who are already capitalizing on this trend? Join me tomorrow at 11 a.m. Eastern for a can’t-miss masterclass. The post Profit from the Market’s Appetite appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 14:46:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What is a catalytic converter? And how can you protect yourself from theft?</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/article/what-is-a-catalytic-converter/</link><image_url>https://o.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/crop/1493x840+0+108/resize/800x450!/format/jpg/quality/85/https://s.yimg.com/os/creatr-uploaded-images/2023-09/a728f1d0-5186-11ee-abea-248734a09619</image_url><description>Filed under: Government/Legal , Green , Emissions , Auto Repair , Ownership , Parts and Accessories Continue reading What is a catalytic converter? And how can you protect yourself from theft? What is a catalytic converter? And how can you protect yourself from theft? originally appeared on Autoblog on Thu, 23 May 2024 16:37:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 21:37:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>12 Questions to Ask Tenant References</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/questions-to-ask-tenant-references</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>It’s not good enough to simply contact tenant references. You need to contact them and then ask all the right questions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 20:58:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best New Summer YA Books, According to Goodreads</title><link>https://bookriot.com/best-ya-books-coming-out-this-summer-according-to-goodreads/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/partial-cover-of-thirsty.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>Which of these YA books are you adding to your summer TBR?</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 17:58:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>While a little competition in the workplace might help bring out the best in everyone involved, an atmosphere rooted in envy, fear, or jealousy can do the exact opposite. This post will help you recognize signs that your coworker is threatened by you, and help you navigate the situation. 1. They Don’t Want You Involved […] The post 10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:07:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Strong Latine Identity Supports U.S. Latine Children’s Well-Being</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/a-strong-latine-identity-supports-u-s-latine-childrens-well-being/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=a-strong-latine-identity-supports-u-s-latine-childrens-well-being</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key Takeaways for caregivers Children tend to have better health and well-being when they have a strong ethnic identity (affinity and adoption of ethnicity-based self-concept). A traditional Latine cultural value (familismo) that emphasizes family bonds is also associated with better developmental outcomes. Caregivers can support the development of U.S. Latine children (and possibly other children […] The post A Strong Latine Identity Supports U.S. Latine Children’s Well-Being appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 03:03:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>British retail sales plunge 2.3% in April, missing estimates</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/24/british-retail-sales-plunge-2point3percent-in-april-missing-estimates.html</link><description>U.K. retail sales volumes dropped 2.3% in April as wet weather deterred shoppers, the Office for National Statistics said Friday.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 08:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wheel of Fortune Contestant's NSFW Answer Shocks Crowd</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1402329/wheel-of-fortune-contestants-nsfw-puzzle-answer-leaves-the-crowd-gasping?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>One contestant's Wheel of Fortune answer brought him anything but big money. On the May 23 episode of the iconic game show, a player named Tavaris Williams left the crowd and host Pat...</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 03:00:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sustainability Reporting: Navigating Assurance Practices</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/17/sustainability-reporting-navigating-assurance-practices/</link><description>Don't be lulled into a false sense of security by the word "assurance" when evaluating sustainability reports. Assurance practices vary, and investors would be wise to learn more about the different levels of coverage.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 17:57:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tiny Scottish island, with more sheep than people, becomes the U.K.'s first spaceport for vertical rockets</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/24/tiny-scottish-island-saxavord-first-uk-spaceport-vertical-rockets/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-169163247-e1716542367454.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Former military site, SaxaVord, is one of seven spaceports being built around the U.K. in the wake of new laws encouraging private investment in the space industry.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 10:33:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wedding Guest Edit</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/wedding-guest-edit/</link><description>Outfit Details: Siedres Dress, JB x Jennifer Behr Necklace, Sherman Fields Necklace, Prada Bag, Hermes Bangles (similar, less expensive here) Wedding season… The post Wedding Guest Edit appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 05:00:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why doesn't she just send an ambulance immediately?</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/avyZqrW</link><description>Tags: wtf 4424 points, 766 comments.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 11:55:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2024 MLB Father’s Day Caps Revealed</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/22/2024-mlb-fathers-day-caps-revealed/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Father’s Day is quickly approaching. In the world of Major League Baseball, this means we’ll see baby blue-themed baseball caps and ribbons on the uniforms of Major League Baseball players, coaches, managers, and umpires for all games played on Sunday, June 16th. SHOP: 2024 MLB Father’s Day team caps available</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 15:50:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ESA prepares for the post-ISS era, selects The Exploration Company, Thales Alenia to develop cargo spacecraft</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/23/esa-prepares-for-the-post-iss-era-selects-the-exploration-company-thales-alenia-to-develop-cargo-spacecraft/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The European Space Agency selected two companies on Wednesday to advance designs of a cargo spacecraft that could establish the continent’s first sovereign access to space. The two awardees, major aerospace prime Thales Alenia Space and French startup The Exploration Company, will receive €25 million ($27 million) each to advance concepts for vehicles that can […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 23:03:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Susan Chira to Step Down as The Marshall Project’s Editor-in-Chief in January</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/16/susan-chira-eic-step-down</link><description>Under her stewardship, the news nonprofit more than doubled in size, opened local newsrooms and won its second Pulitzer Prize.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Grilled Chicken Caesar Salad</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/grilled-chicken-caesar-salad/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Fresh and delicious Grilled Chicken Caesar Salad is a crowd-pleasing hearty salad with tender grilled chicken, crisp romaine lettuce, cherry tomatoes,…</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pete Buttigieg Defends Air Travel, Says FAA Holding Boeing to High Standard</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/23/pete-buttigieg-boeing-defend-air-travel-singapore-manufacturing-issues-dead/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Pete Buttigieg knows Americans have travel on the brain heading into the holiday weekend, and for those concerned about Boeing's issues, he says the government's holding the company to a very high standard. The Secretary of Transportation was on…</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 06:57:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Personal Shopper: A Savvy Black Entrepreneur Guides You to Eczema-Friendly Clothes, Creams, Cosmetics, and More</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/savvy-black-entrepreneur-guides-eczema-friendly-clothes-creams-cosmetics?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>A savvy black entrepreneur guides you on an eczema-friendly shopping spree.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:54:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aglaonema Plant – Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/aglaonema-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Aglaonema, also called the Chinese Evergreen Plant, is an easy-care houseplant that lives happily in many lighting conditions – even a dark corner of our daughter’s room. There are dozens of different Aglaonema varieties, most with large tropical foliage and colors ranging from silvery-green, red, and even vibrant pink. They’re also tough to kill, so they’re a great option for forgetful plant owners or anyone looking for an easy win in the plant department. These truly have been very low maintenance for us. We purchased our two Aglaonemas (pronounced ag-lee-oh-neem-ah ) to put atop our daughter’s closet. It’s sometimes hard to distinguish different varieties, but we believe that’s an Aglaonema Silver (right) and either a Candy Cane or Princess Silver Queen (left). Aglaonema Quick Facts Here’s what you need to know about your Aglaonema at a glance: Latin name : Aglaonema is the genus under which there are 21 recognized species . Continue reading Aglaonema Plant – Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:47:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Indicator Tells Me NOW is the Time to Strike</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/this-indicator-tells-me-now-is-the-time-to-strike/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Markets dipped slightly yesterday after a strong Wednesday, and I'm closely watching the 10-year U.S. Treasury yield. This yield typically moves opposite the stock market and has been falling steadily since May. Now, it's hit technical support, temporarily halting its decline. If it breaks this support, we could see a market surge. Until then, we have a narrow opportunity window. Tomorrow at 11 a.m. Eastern, I’m hosting a special masterclass to show you how to target stocks poised to surge. Don't miss out – secure your spot now and join me for this essential session! The post This Indicator Tells Me NOW is the Time to Strike appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 14:26:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2024 Shelby Super Snake starts at $160,000, offers four options</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/23/2024-shelby-super-snake-starts-at-160000-offers-four-options/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/23133152/2024_shelby_super_snake.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Ford , Car Buying , Convertible , Coupe , Special and Limited Editions , Performance Continue reading 2024 Shelby Super Snake starts at $160,000, offers four options 2024 Shelby Super Snake starts at $160,000, offers four options originally appeared on Autoblog on Thu, 23 May 2024 15:21:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 20:21:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Is Buying a Rental Property Different from Buying a Primary Residence?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/how-is-buying-a-rental-property-different-from-buying-a-primary-residence</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>If you’re new to real estate investment, we know you have plenty of questions. Buying your first property is a big deal, a huge step, and one of the best […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 18:47:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Which Is the Best Book Tracking App? A Comparison of 5 Book Trackers</title><link>https://bookriot.com/which-is-the-best-book-tracking-app-a-comparison-of-5-book-trackers/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/book-tracking-apps.png.webp</image_url><description>Today on Book Riot: a deep dive into the leading book trackers, star-crossed fantasy romances, Historical fantasy great for book clubs, and more.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 17:13:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 551</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-551/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-551</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Job search requires writing and marketing skills. It also requires strong verbal communication. If these skills are not part of your normal work function, you’ll want some help. That’s what this week’s Summary Sunday is all about. There’s no doubt that LinkedIn is one of THE most powerful tools in your career toolbox. It contains […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 551 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 11:37:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Children caught between highly conflicted divorced parents at greater risk of mental health problems</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/children-caught-between-conflicted-divorced-parents/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=children-caught-between-conflicted-divorced-parents</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Interparental conflict after divorce escalates the risk of mental health problems in children and adolescents. Elevated levels of conflict between parents can also induce fear and worry in children about their future and whether they will be adequately taken care of. In turn, a greater fear of abandonment puts children at […] The post Children caught between highly conflicted divorced parents at greater risk of mental health problems appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 08:59:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>F1 dispute with Andretti Global draws in U.S. lawmakers</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/24/f1-dispute-with-andretti-global-draws-in-us-lawmakers.html</link><description>A dispute over whether to accept American motorsports giant Andretti Global as Formula One's 11th team is reaching boiling point.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 08:16:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Original Lyrics to Katy Perry's "Teenage Dream" Will Blow Your Mind</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1402323/the-original-lyrics-to-katy-perrys-teenage-dream-will-blow-your-mind?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>Katy Perry's team was initially hot and cold about "Teenage Dream." Bonnie McKee, who co-wrote the 2010 hit with the singer, revealed that the track went through a few different...</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 02:17:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Power of Clicks, Likes, and Shares: Promote the Right Kind of Financial Content</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/16/the-power-of-clicks-likes-and-shares-promote-the-right-kind-of-financial-content/</link><description>Not all financial content creators on social media are created equal. A broad differentiation can be made between influencers, knowledge sharers, and aspiring thought leaders.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 14:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Louisiana legislature approves bill that would punish the possession of abortion pills without a prescription with hefty fines and jail time</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/24/louisiana-legislature-bill-possession-abortion-pills-prescription-fines-jail-time/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/AP24144612578102-e1716542205494.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Two abortion-inducing drugs could soon be reclassified as controlled and dangerous substances in Louisiana under a first-of-its-kind bill that received final legislative passage Thursday.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 10:25:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pastel Palette Picks</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/pastel-palette-picks/</link><description>Outfit Details: Pucci Swimsuit, Janessa Leone Hat, Prada Sunglasses One of the joys of embracing spring and early summer in Charleston is… The post Pastel Palette Picks appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 21:30:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gf marking her territory because presenter is hot</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/a87b9ZV</link><description>Tags: wtf , women , cringe 7423 points, 626 comments.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 11:55:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>They’ve Got the Power: Washington, D.C., USL Super League Club Unveils Name, Logo</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/21/theyve-got-the-power-washington-d-c-usl-super-league-club-unveils-name-logo/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Crest features black, red and white shield with eagle wing cutting through the middle; lightning bolts in negative represent three communities in D.C. metro area</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 21:15:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Expressable brings speech therapy into the home</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/23/expressable-brings-speech-therapy-into-the-home/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Expressable is a platform that offers one-on-one virtual sessions with speech language pathologists. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 22:49:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When Bad Cops Become Private Security Guards</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/11/police-private-guard-florida-chicago</link><description>There’s growing evidence that former officers with troubling histories of abuse can easily find second careers in private security.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Burger Seasoning</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/burger-seasoning/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>This flavorful Burger Seasoning will take your favorite burger recipe to a new level of delicious! It’s a simple, yet…</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kelly Rowland Hints Race Played a Factor in Cannes Security Fight</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/23/kelly-rowland-hints-race-factor-cannes-security-fight/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Kelly Rowland is speaking out about her heated exchange with a security guard at the Cannes Film Festival ... and strongly suggesting she was singled out because she's Black. The Destiny's Child singer addressed the drama Thursday for the first…</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 06:57:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Behind the Spike in Colorectal Cancer Among Young Americans</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/colorectal-cancer/news/20240515/behind-the-spike-in-colorectal-cancer-cases?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Colorectal cancer cases increased a whopping 333% among 15- to 19-year-olds and 185% among 20- to 24-year-olds from 1999 to 2020.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:59:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Corn Plant – Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/corn-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Corn plants ( Dracaena fragrans ) are popular low-maintenance houseplants you’ve probably seen at the nursery, home improvement store, or doctor’s office. I even had one in my college dorm room! You can recognize them by their spear-shaped leaves and woody, cane-line trunks that can grow up to 6 feet tall indoors. But did you know there are several varieties of corn plants? We didn’t! Heck, we didn’t even realize some of our smaller houseplants were in the same corn plant family! Currently, we own two smaller varieties of corn plants, pictured above. The one on the left is a Dracaena Limelight ( Dracaena fragrans ‘Limelight’ ) and the taller plant is a Draecanea Dorado ( Dracaena fragrans ‘Dorado’ ). We actually have several limelights around because we love their vibrant color on shelves, tabletops, and windowsills. Corn Plant Quick Facts Latin name : Dracaena fragrans Common names : Corn plant, cornstalk plant, false palms Light : Bright, indirect light but can tolerate lower-light conditions Watering : Keep soil moist, but not soggy. Continue reading Corn Plant – Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 17:37:33 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>