<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 08:54:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Texas Tech Red Raiders Unveil New Football Uniforms With Move To adidas</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/02/texas-tech-red-raiders-unveil-new-football-uniforms-with-move-to-adidas/college/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Texas Tech unveiled new uniforms on Monday, the first day of the Red Raiders' deal with adidas after being outfitted by Under Armour since 2006.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 19:54:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deshaun Watson Grabs Model GF Jilly Anais' Butt On Baecation In Spain</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/02/deshaun-watson-jilly-anais-baecation-grab-butt-spain-cleveland-browns-nfl/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Deshaun Watson is having some fun in the sun with his model girlfriend Jilly Anais at one of the most picturesque places in the world ... before the star quarterback heads to training camp later this month! The singer/model -- who's been with the…</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 08:54:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Manchester United Ready to Shine in New Home Kits – Plus More Unveilings From Europe’s Top Leagues</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/02/manchester-united-ready-to-shine-in-new-home-kits-plus-more-unveilings-from-europes-top-leagues/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Other clubs unveiling 2024-25 kits recently include Tottenham Hotspur, VfL Wolfsburg, Eintracht Frankfurt, Villarreal, Girona, CD Leganés, Lazio, Olympique de Marseille, Toulouse</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:54:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bronny James Says No. 9 Jersey Is Tribute To Juice WRLD</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/02/bronny-james-says-no-9-jersey-number-tribute-juice-wrld/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Bronny James is opening up on his decision to rock No. 9 in the NBA ... confirming he chose it to honor late musician Juice WRLD. LeBron's eldest son faced the media for the first time as a Los Angeles Laker on Tuesday ... and after fielding…</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 08:54:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MLS Throws It Back to the ’90s With New All-Star Kits</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/02/mls-throws-it-back-to-the-90s-with-new-all-star-kits/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Kit design "celebrates the best MLS has to offer and honors the iconic style and flash of ‘90s soccer on the 30th anniversary of the last time the United States hosted the World Cup"</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 15:51:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Hawk Tuah' Girl Hailey Welch's Management Team Revealed</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/02/hawk-tuah-girl-hailey-welch-management-team-revealed/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Hailey Welch, who is best known for being the viral "Hawk Tuah" girl, is ready to extend her 15 minutes of fame ... as she's officially landed representation. The management firm Penthouse has come forward as Hailey's new rep, confirming to TMZ…</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 08:54:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bismarck Larks honor ranchers with Heartland Holy Cow identity</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/02/bismarck-larks-honor-ranchers-with-heartland-holy-cow-identity/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The collegiate summer level Bismarck Larks will pay tribute to the ranching community of North Dakota (and roughly 19 surrounding US states) when they play a game as the Heartland Holy Cows this summer. The identity features a startled cow with a halo over its head, playing off both the</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 12:13:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Murray the Magician Resigns From Academy of Magical Arts, Exposed Tricks</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/02/murray-the-magician-resigning-from-academy-of-magical-arts/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Murray The Magician is pulling a disappearing act on the Academy of Magical Arts -- this after having his fill of what he deems as the org's inconsistent values. TMZ has obtained Murray's resignation letter -- and he makes it clear the recent…</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 08:54:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BYU Cougars Unveil 1996 Throwback Football Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/01/byu-cougars-unveil-1996-throwback-football-uniforms/college/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>As part of its 100th season celebration, BYU has unveiled 1996 throwback uniforms that will be worn in the Big XII opener against Kansas State on Sept. 21.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 20:03:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Florida Woman Met With Instant Karma After Swinging At YouTuber, On Camera</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/02/florida-woman-swings-youtuber-fight-parking-lot-knocked-down/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>A Florida woman got a taste of instant karma when she punched a YouTuber and ended up flat on the ground herself -- and the whole thing's on camera! As you see ... it kicks off when content creator Wtfbroward starts filming an unidentified woman…</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 08:54:51 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>