<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:33:12 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>From Making $40K/Year as a Teacher to Reaching FI in 4 Years by Doing THIS</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-552</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>You can take your time to reach financial independence, but why wait? With a combination of hard work, savvy investing, and additional income streams, today’s guest reached FI by the […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 07:01:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>X is getting closer to launching its payment service</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/06/x-twitter-payment-service-update/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>X (formerly Twitter) appears to be making progress on its upcoming payments system, bringing it closer to Elon Musk’s vision of turning X into an “everything app.” According to a recent finding by app researcher Nima Owji, the company is working on adding a “Payments” button to the navigation bar under the bookmarks tab. Owji, […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:00:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tim Walz on Criminal Justice: 5 Things to Know</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/06/tim-walz-kamala-harris-vp-criminal-justice</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>Where Minnesota Gov. Tim Walz, Vice President Kamala Harris’ running mate, stands on policing, guns, prison reform and other issues.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>San Francisco Leaders Approve Measure to Ban Price-Setting Software To Combat High Rent Prices</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/san-francisco-leaders-approve-measure-to-ban-price-fixing-software</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>The city may become the first in the country to ban tech tools allegedly associated with rent price fixing.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 21:29:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dawn Aerospace’s rocket-propelled aircraft takes flight</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/06/dawn-aerospace/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>Dawn Aerospace’s rocket-powered aircraft soared to new heights in its latest test campaign, as the company looks to build what could be the highest-performance aircraft to take off from a runway. The series of three flights, which were completed in late July, saw the Mk-II Aurora vehicle achieve a maximum speed of Mach 0.92 and […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>They Exposed Police Misconduct. Now They’re Paying a Steep Price.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/03/police-congress-corruption-whistleblower</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>Whistleblower laws have advanced in public and private sectors, but protections for police who report illegal or unethical behavior lag far behind.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Avoid Costly Repairs: Don’t Ignore the Red Flags in a Property Inspection</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/dont-ignore-the-red-flags-in-a-property-inspection</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>Avoid costly surprises when buying property by addressing red flags in inspection reports.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 19:53:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Made by Google 2024: Pixel 9, Gemini, a new foldable and other things to expect from the event</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/06/made-by-google-2024-pixel-9-gemini-a-new-foldable-and-other-things-to-expect-from-the-event/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>Google unveiled the Nest Learning Thermostat 4 and Google TV Streamer. It's expected to announce four Pixel devices, including the Pixel 9 and Pixel 9 Pro. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 18:58:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Drawing Attention</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/01/news-inside-issue-17</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>News Inside Issue 17 features the opinions of justice-affected people on Trump’s felonies, and a nonfiction comic about death penalty mitigation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>5 Key Steps For Running a Successful Rental Business</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/key-steps-for-running-a-successful-rental-business</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>If you're not following these five key steps, you're managing your rental business all wrong.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 19:27:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Waymo expands robotaxi coverage in Los Angeles and San Francisco</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/06/waymo-expands-robotaxi-coverage-in-los-angeles-and-san-francisco/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>Waymo, the Alphabet-owned self-driving car company, is adding another 10 square miles to its robotaxi service area to include cities surrounding San Francisco. The move, which adds Daly City, Broadmoor and Colma, pushes its total commercial service territory to about 55 square miles. Waymo said Tuesday it is also adding 16 square miles of new robotaxi […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 18:48:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>These Private Centers Lack Oversight. Cuyahoga County Judges Send Kids Anyway.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/01/juvenile-justice-detention-prison-youth-treatment-cuyahoga-county</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>Courts are increasingly sending children to private youth care centers, spending millions while detention center overcrowding persists.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Transforming Setbacks Into Success: 3 Personal Growth Lessons from My Real Estate Journey</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/transforming-setbacks-into-success</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageOne.png</image_url><description>Discover how setbacks in real estate can lead to success.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 16:33:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Europe’s most valuable fintech, and which startups became unicorns this year</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/06/europes-most-valuable-fintech-and-which-startups-became-unicorns-this-year/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageTwo.png</image_url><description>Welcome to TechCrunch Fintech! This week, we’re looking at Revolut’s reported valuation hike, fintech unicorns, the Disrupt Fintech Stage, and more. To get a roundup of TechCrunch’s biggest and most important fintech stories delivered to your inbox every Tuesday at 8 a.m. PT, subscribe here. The big story Revolut reportedly told staff last week of […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 18:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Facing Rollbacks, Criminal Justice Reformers Argue Policies Make People Safer</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/01/california-illinois-crime-public-safety-reform</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImages/imageThree.png</image_url><description>Advocates are refining their rebuttal to “tough on crime” messaging: Don’t focus on punishment, but on reforms that improve public safety.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>