<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 07:23:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Queer Gothic Horror, a Gay Fantasy Mystery, and More New LGBTQ Books</title><link>https://bookriot.com/new-lgbtq-books-august-20-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/rainbow-bookstore-1600-×-900-px.png</image_url><description>What's the next queer book on your TBR?</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dodge Hurricrate engines are finally here: Cat 3 has 550 hp and 531 lb-ft</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/08/19/dodge-hurricrate-engines-are-finally-here-cat-3-has-550-hp-and-531-lb-ft/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1200x675/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/08/10174827/hurricrate_engine.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Aftermarket , Dodge Continue reading Dodge Hurricrate engines are finally here: Cat 3 has 550 hp and 531 lb-ft Dodge Hurricrate engines are finally here: Cat 3 has 550 hp and 531 lb-ft originally appeared on Autoblog on Mon, 19 Aug 2024 16:44:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 21:44:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eli Lilly's weight loss drug slashes the risk of developing diabetes in long-term trial</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/20/eli-lilly-weight-loss-drug-cuts-risk-of-developing-diabetes-in-trial.html</link><description>The late-stage trial on tirzepatide also found that patients experienced sustained weight loss over the roughly three-year treatment period.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 11:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tracking Your Job Search Activities</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/tracking-your-job-search-activities/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=tracking-your-job-search-activities</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Ever feel like your job search is going nowhere fast? You’re not alone. I’ve talked to countless job seekers who are putting in tons of effort but can’t seem to make progress. The problem? They’re not tracking their activities. Without a system to monitor what you’re doing, it’s impossible to know what’s working and what’s […] The post Tracking Your Job Search Activities appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 11:20:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How parents can support math learning at home and through everyday activities</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/how-parents-can-support-math-learning-at-home/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=how-parents-can-support-math-learning-at-home</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Math skills at kindergarten entry predict children’s academic success in school. Young children usually enjoy learning math and can develop understanding about math in all the content areas they will encounter in school: number, patterns, shapes, spatial relations, and data. Parents can grow their young children’s math knowledge through playful activities […] The post How parents can support math learning at home and through everyday activities appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 23:18:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biscoff Cookies</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/biscoff-cookies/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Satisfy your sweet tooth with loaded Biscoff Cookies. They are soft and chewy and infused with the flavor of Biscoff…</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Get Rid Of Fruit Flies: 7 Tested Methods</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/how-to-get-rid-of-fruit-flies/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Got little bugs buzzing around your kitchen? Congratulations, you may have fruit flies! Don’t fret. These annoying pests are pretty common but luckily, it doesn’t take a lot of money, supplies, or effort to get rid of them. In fact, you can probably find everything you need in your cabinets! We recently had a fruit fly problem in our home (the first time in over four years here – we have no idea what brought them in). So I seized the opportunity to test 7 different methods of eliminating them. Yes, there were copious notes taken and even a spreadsheet. So today I’m sharing the best fruit fly traps and how to make them. Each homemade trap is easy to make and uses natural ingredients that we already had around the house. So let’s just call this extremely D.I.Y friendly and chemical free. You can also set the fruit flies free outside if you’d rather not let them perish. Continue reading How To Get Rid Of Fruit Flies: 7 Tested Methods at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 16:08:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>See Through</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/08/see-through/</link><description>Outfit Details: Sea Dress, Prada Bag, Loeffler Randall Sandals, Lili Claspe Necklace &amp; Earrings As summer gives way to the crisp beginnings of fall, our… The post See Through appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 05:00:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Hasn’t Amazon Released a Color Kindle Yet?</title><link>https://bookriot.com/why-hasnt-amazon-released-a-color-kindle/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/kindle.png</image_url><description>Would you buy a color Kindle?</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2025 Nissan Rogue Rock Creek starts at $36,810</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/08/19/2025-nissan-rogue-rock-creek-starts-at-36810/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1200x675/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/07/08092454/2025-Nissan-Rogue-Rock-Creek-edition-45-copy.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Nissan , Crossover , SUV , Off-Road Vehicles Continue reading 2025 Nissan Rogue Rock Creek starts at $36,810 2025 Nissan Rogue Rock Creek starts at $36,810 originally appeared on Autoblog on Mon, 19 Aug 2024 15:17:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 20:17:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How the Inflation Reduction Act sparked a manufacturing and clean energy boom in the U.S.</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/20/inflation-reduction-act-sparked-a-manufacturing-clean-energy-boom.html</link><description>The IRA has had a transformative impact on U.S. manufacturing, according to the Rhodium Group.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 11:36:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 560</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-560/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-560</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>There is a steep learning curve involved in job search. And many skills you need to succeed in a job search are not skills you would typically use in your job. The good news is there are resources and tools to help you! In this week’s Summary Sunday, you will find curated articles from respected […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 560 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 13:26:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Do infants feel excluded? Early signs and why it matters</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/do-infants-feel-excluded/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=do-infants-feel-excluded</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Social exclusion harms individuals of all ages, leading to feelings of loneliness, decreased self-esteem, and even changes in brain activity. Humans’ ability to recognize and react to social exclusion emerges early, suggesting the importance of considering and addressing ostracism even when caring for very young children. Babies are sensitive to social […] The post Do infants feel excluded? Early signs and why it matters appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 01:37:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cowboy Cornbread Casserole</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/cowboy-cornbread-casserole/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Cowboy Cornbread Casserole is a flavorful, comforting meal that’s so easy to make. Seasoned ground beef, corn, pinto beans, and…</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Summer Trip To South Dakota</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/south-dakota-family-vacation/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>I’ll be the first to admit that South Dakota wasn’t high on my vacation bucket list. But I ended up there this summer on a dad-and-daughter trip I took with some family members: and WOW, we loved it. It was a surprising and wonderful departure from our usual family trips, so I wanted to share some highlights in case anyone else is interested in breaking out of the more typical beach or theme park vacation routine. Growing up on the East Coast and now living in Florida, I haven’t spent much time in the upper Midwest. So these sights may be old hat for some of you. But just like our trip to the California desert earlier this year, this was a chance for us to soak up some new-to-us geography. Why We Vacationed In South Dakota South Dakota is home to lots of epic vistas, charming towns, and outdoor adventures. Continue reading A Summer Trip To South Dakota at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 18:09:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amazon Sundays</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/08/amazon-sundays-7-28-24/</link><description>Outfit Details: Amazon Top &amp; Skirt, Similar Necklace Welcome to Amazon Sundays, filled with the latest from Amazon that I’m… The post Amazon Sundays appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 05:00:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Most Anticipated Historical Fiction Books of Fall 2024, According to Goodreads</title><link>https://bookriot.com/most-anticipated-historical-fiction-books-of-fall-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/book-stack.png</image_url><description>Can anyone unseat Kristin Hannah as the bestselling historical fiction book of the moment?</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 11:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Get the best-selling car sun shade on Amazon for 17% off today</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/article/get-the-best-selling-car-sun-shade-on-amazon-for-17-off-today/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1200x675/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/08/19112520/EcoNour-Sun-Shades1.jpeg</image_url><description>Filed under: Commerce Continue reading Get the best-selling car sun shade on Amazon for 17% off today Get the best-selling car sun shade on Amazon for 17% off today originally appeared on Autoblog on Mon, 19 Aug 2024 15:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lowe's cuts full-year outlook as it expects home improvement sales to weaken</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/20/lowes-low-q2-2024-earnings.html</link><description>Lowe's said customers took on fewer discretionary home projects and unfavorable weather hurt sales of outdoor and seasonal items.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 11:27:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Checklist for a Job Search</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/check-list-for-a-job-search/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=check-list-for-a-job-search</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Having a checklist for job search makes sure you have the right equipment and tools to compete. Without having everything you need, you potentially waste a lot of time. While gathering this checklist of items in this order is not required, it is *highly* recommended you do them all. Job Search Checklist – Things You […] The post Checklist for a Job Search appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 09:26:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10 Actions Parents Can Take to Help their Children Be More Resilient in a World of Adversity</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/10-actions-to-help-children-be-more-resilient/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=10-actions-to-help-children-be-more-resilient</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Decades of research points to specific ways parents can build resilience that can help protect children from the challenges of adverse experiences and stress. Strategies include parent-focused tips such as practicing self care, reflecting on one’s own past experiences, and developing emotional control. Additional strategies focus on ways to navigate relationships […] The post 10 Actions Parents Can Take to Help their Children Be More Resilient in a World of Adversity appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 02:36:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spaghetti alla Nerano (Stanley Tucci Zucchini Pasta)</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/spaghetti-alla-nerano/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Spaghetti alla Nerano is an unforgettable pasta dish packed with flavor! It has a rich and creamy zucchini sauce infused…</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>100 Classic Boy Names</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/100-classic-boys-names/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>A friend of mine is pregnant and it’s reminding me how exciting it was to name our own kids. We love traditional names (aka: old-fashioned names, aka classic names) and both of our children are named after our grandparents – one on John’s side and one on my side. So I had fun putting together this list of my favorite 100 classic boy names. They feel established, like they stand the test of time, and can carry special meaning if they’re already names in your family. ALSO IS THERE ANYTHING CUTER THAN BABY SUSPENDERS?!? One interesting thing I found when I was writing this post was that many of the top ten most popular names for boys in 2024 are arguably pretty classic: #1: Liam #2: Noah #3: Oliver #4: James #5: Elijah #6: Mateo #7: Theodore #8: Henry #9: Lucas #10: William But beyond that short list of the most popular boy names this year, there are so many other classic boy names to choose from. Continue reading 100 Classic Boy Names at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 17:55:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Finds From Italy</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/08/finds-from-italy/</link><description>Outfit Details: Tulsi Coverup, Janessa Leone Hat, Matteau Bikini Top and Bikini Briefs During our summer travels through Italy, I found… The post Finds From Italy appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 05:00:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>8 Punk Manga That Feel Like a Rebellion in Ink</title><link>https://bookriot.com/punk-mangas/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/Akira-cropped-cover.png</image_url><description>What's your favorite punk subgenre to read?</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2025 Nissan Altima loses turbo engine, gains a few new options</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/08/19/2025-nissan-altima-loses-turbo-engine-gains-a-few-new-options/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1200x675/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/08/17211404/2025_nissan_altima_sv_special_edition_001.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Nissan , Car Buying , Sedan Continue reading 2025 Nissan Altima loses turbo engine, gains a few new options 2025 Nissan Altima loses turbo engine, gains a few new options originally appeared on Autoblog on Mon, 19 Aug 2024 14:01:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 19:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>European Union slashes planned tariffs on China-made Tesla EVs, other Chinese firms</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/20/european-union-slashes-planned-tariff-on-china-made-tesla-evs.html</link><description>The European Union on Tuesday said a planned tariff on Tesla vehicles being imported from China would be cut to 9% from 20.8%.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 11:19:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10 Questions To Ask Before Launching Your Job Search</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/questions-to-ask-before-launching-job-search/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=questions-to-ask-before-launching-job-search</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>So this is the year you are finally ready to change jobs. Congratulations! Before you dust off your resume, there are some questions you need to ask before launching your job search. Searching for a job while employed requires you do it under the radar so that your employer doesn’t find out. Some employers have […] The post 10 Questions To Ask Before Launching Your Job Search appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 14:55:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Let Children Choose: Autonomy-Supportive Care for Cognitive Growth</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/autonomy-supportive-care-for-cognitive-growth/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=autonomy-supportive-care-for-cognitive-growth</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Executive function (EF) skills: EF skills are brain-based processes that allow us to remember goals, resist impulses, and think flexibly. Early EF skills matter: Developing EF skills early in life is crucial for various outcomes like social competence, emotion regulation, academic achievement, and keeping out of legal trouble. Parental and caregiver […] The post Let Children Choose: Autonomy-Supportive Care for Cognitive Growth appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 14:29:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Meal Plan #15</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/weekly-meal-plan-15/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>This weekly meal plan has some classics with a twist that you are going to love! It gives you a…</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Best Air Purifying Plants</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/best-air-purifying-plants/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>We love any excuse to buy more plants, and you may have heard they can improve your home’s indoor air quality. But before you blow your paycheck in the name of a healthier home, let’s dive deeper into plants’ air purifying powers. We’ll share which plants we recommend and what benefits you can actually expect from them. We’ve heard for years about how plants act as natural air filters for your home. So let’s dive a little deeper, shall we? 7 Air Purifying Plants If you just came here for a list, our favorite air purifying houseplants are bulleted below. The best part is these are all beautiful, low-maintenance plants. Many also appear on our best low-light indoor plants list too! Dracaena (including Corn Plant ) Snake Plant Aglaonema English Ivy Pothos Bamboo Palm Spider Plant There are certainly more that could be included here, but we narrowed it to the ones that are most often cited by experts AND the plants that we think look best too. Continue reading Best Air Purifying Plants at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 14:15:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seasonal Shifts With Walmart</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/08/seasonal-shifts-with-walmart/</link><description>Thank you to Walmart for sponsoring this post. As summer fades into early fall, Walmart is your ally in navigating… The post Seasonal Shifts With Walmart appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Backpack Fantasy Recs for Heroes on the Go</title><link>https://bookriot.com/best-of-book-riot-august-19-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/backpack-hike-journey-adventure.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>Raise your hand if you just learned what backpack fantasy is, even though you've been reading it for years!</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 19:44:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GM lays off 1,000 salaried employees</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/08/19/gm-lays-off-1000-salaried-employees/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/crop/4492x2527+0+527/resize/1200x675/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/08/19131145/file_photo__logo_of_gm_atop_the_company_headquarters.jpeg</image_url><description>Filed under: Hirings/Firings/Layoffs , GM Continue reading GM lays off 1,000 salaried employees GM lays off 1,000 salaried employees originally appeared on Autoblog on Mon, 19 Aug 2024 13:12:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 18:12:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tuesday analyst calls: There's strong upside ahead for Eli Lilly, Vista Energy and AMD</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/20/tuesday-analyst-calls-theres-strong-upside-ahead-for-eli-lilly-and-amd.html</link><description>This is CNBC Pro's live coverage of Tuesday analyst calls and Wall Street chatter.</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 11:16:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 559</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-559/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-559</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Do you understand how recruiters work and how they think? Well, this should help! There’s no magic. Every recruiter has their own set of preferences for sourcing and vetting candidates. But many share tips and insights to give job seekers valuable information. In this week’s summary, you’ll find: Please follow and support the talented experts […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 559 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 12:33:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Children’s digital media exposure as a backdrop for multilingual learning</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/childrens-digital-media-exposure-as-a-backdrop-for-multilingual-learning/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=childrens-digital-media-exposure-as-a-backdrop-for-multilingual-learning</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Multilingual children use digital media regularly, in all their home languages. Digital media use may affect multilingual children’s early language learning by reducing opportunities for back-and-forth conversations with adults. This finding is similar to results of studies of digital media and language learning for children learning only one language. When using […] The post Children’s digital media exposure as a backdrop for multilingual learning appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 20:27:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chocolate Whipped Cream</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/chocolate-whipped-cream/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Fluffy Chocolate Whipped Cream is a wonderful combination of chocolate and fresh whipped cream. It’s the perfect topping for fruit,…</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Weekend In New Orleans With Kids</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/new-orleans-with-kids/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Since our travel guides to Charleston with kids and Palm Springs with kids have elicited requests for more travel ideas with kids, we’re back with an overdue recap of our 3-night trip to New Orleans. We’d never been to The Big Easy before and were impressed by how family-friendly the city is. It’s not all booze, beads, and Bourbon Street! So here’s a look at where we stayed, what we did, and what we’re excited to do next time we go back – because we will definitely go back! The four of us (well, five if you count our chihuahua!) went to NOLA for 3 nights in November of 2022. At the time, our kids were 8 and 12 years old. So unfortunately we can’t vouch for our suggestions being a good fit for toddlers or younger children. Although I’m sure ours would’ve loved the Louisiana Children’s Museum and Storyland playground back in the day! Continue reading A Weekend In New Orleans With Kids at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 17:17:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dresses To Buy Now</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/08/dresses-to-buy-now-2/</link><description>Outfit Details: Loro Piana Dress (skirt version here), Sherman Fields Necklace, Amanu Sandals As summer wanes, dresses in vibrant and muted hues, crafted from… The post Dresses To Buy Now appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 05:00:31 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>