<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 06:59:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Preserving the Dollar: The Role of CBDCs in Securing Economic Stability for Future Generations</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/16/preserving-the-dollar-the-role-of-cbdcs-in-securing-economic-stability-for-future-generations/</link><description>As financial systems evolve, preserving the US dollar's dominance will require skillful policy management and the integration of cutting-edge technologies.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:24:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Malaysian cyberbully who threatened a TikTok user who then committed suicide only had to pay a $21 fine as punishment</title><link>https://fortune.com/asia/2024/07/17/malaysian-cyberbully-threat-tiktok-user-committed-suicide-21-fine/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/GettyImages-1306560823-e1721213666112.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The death of a Malaysian TikTok user has prompted the government to look into criminalizing cyberbullying and increasing accountability among internet service providers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 11:57:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Can Equal Weight Solve Our Concentration Crisis? Not So Fast…</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/15/can-equal-weight-solve-our-concentration-crisis-not-so-fast/</link><description>Mega-cap concentration has exploded since 2015. The corollary to an increasingly top-heavy benchmark is that market diversification and breadth have never been more limited. A multifactor methodology can be a restorative balance to US equities when more traditional measures fall short.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 22:43:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>After water pistols in Barcelona and hunger strikes in Spain, cruise ships may avoid European hotspots where ‘passengers will not be well-treated’</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/07/17/europe-overtourism-water-pistols-barcelona-hunger-strikes-spain-cruise-ships-avoid-european-hotspots-passengers-not-well-treated/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/GettyImages-537657813-e1721211580813.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The world's biggest cruise trade body says it may move to protect passengers' safety amid a wave of overtourism protests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 11:40:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In Search of the Elusive Neutral Interest Rate</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/10/in-search-of-the-elusive-neutral-interest-rate/</link><description>With Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell's semiannual address to the Senate Banking Committee this week fresh in mind, it is an ideal time to consider the drivers of r*.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 12:17:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Mirage is disappearing from the Las Vegas strip—but new operators Hard Rock will reinvent it as a massive guitar-shaped hotel</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/07/17/the-mirage-closing-hard-rock-new-hotel/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/GettyImages-2147847031-e1721212662872.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>New operators Hard Rock International plan to add 600 rooms to an existing 3,044 in a bright new guitar-shaped hotel.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 11:39:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Commodities for the Long Run?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/08/commodities-for-the-long-run/</link><description>Asset classes such as commodities have historically had notable diversification benefits for longer-term investors who are concerned with inflation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 21:50:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ex-CIA analyst specializing in North Korea accused of working as South Korean agent in exchange for Bottega Veneta and Louis Vuitton handbags</title><link>https://fortune.com/asia/2024/07/17/ex-cia-analyst-accused-south-korea-agent-bottega-veneta-louis-vuitton-handbags/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/GettyImages-1655885124-e1721211277571.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Sue Mi Terry, now a senior fellow at the Council on Foreign Relations, was indicted on charges of operating as a foreign agent for more than a decade.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 11:16:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vanguard’s Former OCIO Clients Must Stand Their Ground</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/03/vanguards-former-ocio-clients-must-stand-their-ground/</link><description>Vanguard's OCIO clients should be wary of the higher-fee active funds and alternative investments that are now open to them.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 12:13:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dior and Armani face antitrust probe in Italy over alleged labor exploitation</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/07/17/dior-armani-face-antitrust-probe-in-italy-over-alleged-labor-exploitation/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/GettyImages-1954159138-e1721209209226.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The antitrust regulator said that the two brands may have used supplies from laboratories where workers had to work illegally long hours in inadequate health and safety conditions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 10:58:44 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>