<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 08:43:09 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>In Search of the Elusive Neutral Interest Rate</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/10/in-search-of-the-elusive-neutral-interest-rate/</link><description>With Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell's semiannual address to the Senate Banking Committee this week fresh in mind, it is an ideal time to consider the drivers of r*.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 12:17:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Copenhagen wants to do tourism differently by rewarding visitors with free coffee, food and museum passes if they cycle in the city and keep it clean</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/07/11/copenhagen-tourism-reward-visitors-free-coffee-food-museum-passes-copenpay/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/Frameandwork_bikes_-30-e1720695818665.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>“It is an experimental and a small step towards creating a new mindset amongst travelers,” said Mikkel Aarø-Hansen, CEO of Wonderful Copenhagen.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 12:33:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Commodities for the Long Run?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/08/commodities-for-the-long-run/</link><description>Asset classes such as commodities have historically had notable diversification benefits for longer-term investors who are concerned with inflation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 21:50:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gen Z want to live in expensive cities—instead of moving to the outskirts, their parents are paying their rent</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/07/11/gen-z-expensive-areas-parents-paying-rent-bank-of-america/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/GettyImages-1092407658-e1720692897291.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Young people have always wanted a bustling life and career in the city. The only problem? Gen Z can’t actually afford it.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 12:13:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vanguard’s Former OCIO Clients Must Stand Their Ground</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/03/vanguards-former-ocio-clients-must-stand-their-ground/</link><description>Vanguard's OCIO clients should be wary of the higher-fee active funds and alternative investments that are now open to them.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 12:13:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The U.K. has ‘far more millionaires than it deserves’ and will watch 500,000 flee to the likes of Italy and Spain by 2028, UBS says</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/07/11/uk-millionaires-deserves-flee-italy-spain-2028-ubs-wealth-report/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/GettyImages-1440344960-e1720694703280.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The U.K. will lose 17% of its millionaires in the coming years, but the country's government shouldn't worry.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 11:54:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Your Data Governance and Management Practices Keeping Pace with the AI Boom?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/02/are-your-data-governance-and-management-practices-keeping-pace-with-the-ai-boom/</link><description>No matter how sophisticated and expensive a firm's AI tools are, it should not forget that the principle “garbage in, garbage out” (GIGO) applies to the entire investment management process.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:21:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ask Andy: Can generative AI solve a startup’s problems?</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/07/11/ask-andy-startups-founder-culture-generative-ai-mental-health-self-care/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/DUNN-WEB.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Bonobos and Pie founder Andy Dunn answers questions about startup problems that technology can't solve, and about grappling with a bipolar disorder.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: Default</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/06/28/book-review-default/</link><description>Argentina’s debt restructuring tests the theoretical limits of chaos theory. Gregory Makoff's feat is to build his narrative as a thriller without losing the detailed facts valued by specialists.</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 12:33:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>U.K. faces highest level of financial distress in Europe with corporate deleveraging at its peak since 2008</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/07/11/u-k-faces-highest-level-of-financial-distress-in-europe-with-corporate-deleveraging-at-peak-since-2008/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/GettyImages-1244799735-e1720689114497.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>A slowdown in consumer spending impacted the retail fashion sector significantly with 21% of firms in the industry now in distress.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 11:07:51 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>