<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 06:55:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The Changing Nature of Cannabis Consumption: Investment Opportunities</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/08/13/the-changing-nature-of-cannabis-consumption/</link><description>For investors in the space, the changing cannabis consumption landscape opens challenges and opportunities in product creation, marketing, and targeting new consumer groups.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:46:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Italian winemakers are fighting to banish ‘prosecco’ from your wine collection</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/08/13/why-italian-winemakers-are-fighting-to-banish-prosecco-from-your-wine-collection-valdobbiadene/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/GettyImages-1446478741-e1723543999625.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Prosecco is one of the most consumed sparkling wines in the world, but some producers feel the name has become a hindrance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:22:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From Sandpiles to Angel Investments</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/08/12/from-sandpiles-to-angel-investments/</link><description>The presence of power law returns in angel investing, with the potential for significant contributions from a handful of investments, has implications for portfolio construction, investment strategies, and diversification.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 13:19:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Billionaire Sir Jim Ratcliffe says he doesn’t wear a watch in London anymore amid Rolex mugging surge</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/08/13/british-billionaire-sir-jim-ratcliffe-says-he-doesnt-wear-a-watch-in-london-anymore-amid-rolex-mugging-surge/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/MixCollage-13-Aug-2024-10-58-AM-8515.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The Manchester United minority owner has stopped flaunting his watches in London after 6,800 were stolen in the capital last year.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:04:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: Pause to Think</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/08/09/book-review-pause-to-think/</link><description>This book is direct, delightful, and articulate in suggesting that we take a slow rather than fast approach to getting things thoughtfully done. It touches the minds and hearts of investment professionals.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 12:59:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why The New York Times, Washington Post, and Politico won’t print leaked emails from the Trump camp</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/08/13/why-new-york-times-washington-post-politico-wont-print-leaked-trump-emails/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/GettyImages-2165917707-e1723542779715.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The emails from a person identified as “Robert” include a 271-page campaign document about JD Vance and a partial vetting report on Sen. Marco Rubio.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:55:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is Illiquidity a Blessing in Disguise for Some Investors?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/08/07/is-illiquidity-a-blessing-in-disguise-for-some-investors/</link><description>Rather than running away from illiquidity, investment professionals, investors, and regulators alike should recognize its potential benefits and consider a more balanced approach.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 17:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This sleepy town in the Czech Republic known for its sweet pies and wooden houses just got $2 billion to help Europe compete in the global chip war</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/08/13/town-czech-republic-2-billion-europe-compete-global-chip-war-onsemi-roznov-volkswagen/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/GettyImages-462915106-e1723541034764.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>U.S. chipmaker Onsemi picked Roznov for a new $2 billion manufacturing hub in June. A contract with Volkswagen is already lined up.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:42:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scenario Planning, Foresight, and the Power of Imagination: Navigating an Uncertain Future</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/08/05/scenario-planning-foresight-and-the-power-of-imagination-navigating-an-uncertain-future/</link><description>By fostering resilience through the consideration of various outcomes, investment practitioners can better anticipate and manage the complexities and disruptions that characterize today's dynamic environment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 17:28:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mercedes-Benz reveals EV battery maker names after South Korea car explosion prompted parking garage bans</title><link>https://fortune.com/asia/2024/08/13/mercedes-benz-reveals-ev-battery-maker-names-south-korea-car-explosion/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/GettyImages-2166023214-e1723541905879.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The August 1 fire damaged hundreds of vehicles and created a national panic, with car parks across South Korea imposing a wave of adhoc restrictions amid growing calls for transparency on battery supply chains.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:40:42 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>