<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 07:03:43 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>BiggerNews: 6 Rules for Real Estate Investing in 2024</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-963</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Real estate investing in 2024 isn’t as easy as a few years ago. When interest rates are low, housing inventory is high, the economy is booming, and everyone’s happy, real […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 07:02:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spain bans Meta from launching election features on Facebook, Instagram over privacy fears</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/31/spain-bans-meta-from-launching-election-features-on-facebook-instagram-over-privacy-fears/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Meta has been banned from launching features on Facebook and Instagram that would have collected data on voters in Spain using the social networks ahead of next month’s European Elections. The local data protection authority, the AEPD, has used emergency powers to protect local users’ privacy. Meta confirmed to TechCrunch it has complied with the […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 11:52:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I Recorded a Whole Hip-Hop Album on a Death Row Telephone</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/31/north-carolina-death-row-rapper-book-excerpt</link><description>In this new book excerpt, incarcerated rapper Alim “RRome Alone” Braxton describes his early attempts to record vocals over a phone in the dayroom.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Federal Experts Talk Bird Flu ‘What Ifs’ in WebMD Live Event</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/cold-and-flu/news/20240516/federal-experts-talk-bird-flu-what-ifs?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>WebMD brought together experts from four federal agencies to talk prevention, monitoring, and what the “what ifs” of bird flu might look like.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:50:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rookie Reply: How to Invest in Real Estate While Working 9-5</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-413</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>If real estate investing was easy, everyone would be doing it! The truth is that, despite the financial freedom and flexibility it offers, investing is hard work. And it’s even […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 07:02:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stripe curbs India ambitions over regulatory changes</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/31/stripe-curbs-india-ambitions-over-regulatory-changes/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Stripe, the global fintech giant, said on Friday that it will temporarily move to an invite-only model for new account sign-ups in India, “a tough decision” it’s making as it navigates the country’s evolving regulatory landscape. In a statement posted on its website, Stripe said that businesses in India will no longer be able to […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 11:45:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Legal Doctrine That Shields Police From Many Lawsuits May Be Losing Support</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/25/police-mississippi-courts-judges-qualified-immunity</link><description>A federal judge in Mississippi joined other courts in recently rejecting police arguments that qualified immunity protected their actions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What’s Next in Health Care for Older Adults: Questions and Answers With John Whyte, MD</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/blog-aging-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>As WebMD’s chief medical officer, John Whyte, MD, is in a unique position to see both the current state of medical care for America’s older adults and the way things are trending for the future. We asked him to share his insight on a few topics, along with a bit of advice.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:29:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Even We Didn’t Know About “Protecting” Our Wealth</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-533</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Are you working towards FIRE or building a financial legacy? Then DON’T skip this episode! What’s the point of creating generational wealth if it will be lost after you’re gone? […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 07:01:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Voice cloning of political figures is still easy as pie</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/31/voice-cloning-of-political-figures-is-still-easy-as-pie/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The 2024 election is likely to be the first in which faked audio and video of candidates is a serious factor. As campaigns warm up, voters should be aware: voice clones of major political figures, from the President on down, get very little pushback from AI companies, as a new study demonstrates. The Center for […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 09:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Out of the Blue: The Rise and Fall of a Black Cop</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/23/black-police-officers-cleveland-black-shield</link><description>After Cleveland officer Vincent Montague shot a Black man, he got promoted. Then he allied with Black Lives Matter, and his life went off the rails.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Get the Care You Need in a COVID-19 World</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/covid-senior-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>What to expect at the doctor’s office, hospitals, and long-term care facilities, the future of telemedicine, and how to get the best care during COVID-19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 19:50:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BiggerPockets Hosts Powerhouse Real Estate Investors Conference With BPCON2024</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/biggerpockets-hosts-powerhouse-real-estate-investors-conference-with-bpcon2024</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>BPCON2024 will be held from Oct. 6-8 in Cancun, Mexico.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 21:25:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OneScreen.ai brings startup ads to billboards and NYC’s subway</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/30/onescreen-ai-brings-startup-ads-to-billboards-and-nycs-subway/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>When Alex Ewing was a kid growing up in Purcell, Oklahoma, he knew how close he was to home based on which billboards he could see out the car window. Now, as the CEO of OneScreen.ai, he’s helping startups like fintech Ramp and technical recruiter Karat advertise on billboards and beyond. “I think billboards are […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 02:34:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Marshall Project Wins Prestigious Robert F. Kennedy Journalism Award for Criminal Justice</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/21/marshall-project-rfk-award</link><description>The award recognizes our 2023 investigation exposing lax prison discipline for abusive guards in New York state prisons.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Personal Shopper: A Savvy Black Entrepreneur Guides You to Eczema-Friendly Clothes, Creams, Cosmetics, and More</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/savvy-black-entrepreneur-guides-eczema-friendly-clothes-creams-cosmetics?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>A savvy black entrepreneur guides you on an eczema-friendly shopping spree.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:54:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Data-Backed Solutions: Addressing the Top Real Estate Challenges of 2024</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/data-backed-solutions-addressing-the-top-real-estate-challenges-of-2024</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>This article is presented by PropStream. Read our editorial guidelines for more information. The housing market is an increasingly challenging place for investors right now. The costs of investing in real estate […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 18:57:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SpaceX sent Starship to orbit — the next launch will try to bring it back</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/30/spacex-sent-starship-to-orbit-the-next-launch-will-try-to-bring-it-back/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>SpaceX’s massive Starship rocket could take to the skies for the fourth time on June 5, with the primary objective of evaluating the second stage’s reusable heat shield as the vehicle tries to safely reenter the atmosphere for the first time. CEO Elon Musk said on his social media platform X that “There are many […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 22:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Police Tactics at Some Pro-Palestine Protests Ignore Past Lessons</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/18/police-israel-palestine-campus-protests</link><description>While some universities have sought peaceful approaches, others have used aggressive policing that bucks research from the protests following George Floyd’s murder.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Behind the Spike in Colorectal Cancer Among Young Americans</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/colorectal-cancer/news/20240515/behind-the-spike-in-colorectal-cancer-cases?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Colorectal cancer cases increased a whopping 333% among 15- to 19-year-olds and 185% among 20- to 24-year-olds from 1999 to 2020.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:59:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>