<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:50:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>What Price Risk? Unpacking the Equity Risk Premium</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/24/what-price-risk-unpacking-the-equity-risk-premium/</link><description>Stocks are a good wager over the long term, on favorable odds. But stocks remain a bet, and investors must grasp how much returns can vary over long time horizons.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden administration’s ‘commonsense’ retirement rule could save workers $5 billion a year</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/24/biden-administrations-common-sense-retirement-rule-could-save-workers-5-billion-a-year/</link><description>“This rule ensures that advisors must put their clients’ interests front and center.”</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 20:14:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Equity Income Investing Redux</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/22/equity-income-investing-redux/</link><description>No doubt the past year has been difficult for equity income investors. But history, inherent biases, mean reversion, and the current market backdrop point to a comeback.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 17:19:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RE/MAX chairman shrugs off groundbreaking $418 million commissions settlement, saying realtors will adapt</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/24/re-max-chairman-founder-nar-commissions-settlement-realtors/</link><description>"If you look at the oil embargoes, you look at 17% interest rates, you look at the 2007 financial crisis, realtors learn to adapt, change their sales, and continue to succeed,” RE/MAX cofounder Dave Liniger said.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:56:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: Enrich Your Future</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/18/book-review-enrich-your-future/</link><description>This engaging book is simultaneously memorable and humorous. The numerous sports analogies will have you smiling as you absorb Larry Swedroe's unforgettable investment precepts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 18:07:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'We need to move fast'— Biden signs TikTok ban along with $95 billion war aid for Ukraine, Israel and Taiwan</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/24/biden-signs-bill-tiktok-israel-ukraine-taiwan-95-billion/</link><description>“History will remember this moment," the president said.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:52:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CAPE Is High: Should You Care?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/17/cape-is-high-should-you-care/</link><description>A simple analysis shows that Robert Shiller's cyclically adjusted price-to-earnings ratio changed in the 1990s and that mean-reversion concerns may be misplaced. If CAPE changed three decades ago, however, there is nothing preventing it from doing so again.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 15:18:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GM is on the rise—but for now, EVs are holding it back, not leading the charge</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/24/gm-earnings-beat-gas-ev-electric-trucks-profitable/</link><description>Strong quarterly earnings are countered by continued losses on EV production, but GM says its EVs will be profitable as soon as later this year.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:42:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI to the Rescue? Overhauling the US Power Grid on the Path to Net Zero</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/15/ai-to-the-rescue-overhauling-the-us-power-grid-on-the-path-to-net-zero/</link><description>Once known as secure and profitable investments, utilities are now viewed as enterprises fraught with financial risks. Investors should favor utilities that employ AI and other digital strategies to minimize damage from natural disasters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 21:24:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chase Sapphire Reserve review: A rockstar among premium travel cards</title><link>https://fortune.com/recommends/credit-cards/chase-sapphire-reserve-review/</link><description>Do the Sapphire Reserve's benefits and perks upstage the high annual fee?</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:35:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>