<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 13:56:39 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>St Louis Cardinals Unveil New “The Lou” City Connect Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/20/st-louis-cardinals-unveil-new-the-lou-city-connect-uniforms/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>They’re from “The Lou,” and they’re proud. This morning, the St. Louis Cardinals became the 26th team to unveil their new Nike MLB City Connect uniform, doing so with the help of Grammy Award-winning hip-hop artist Nelly, a St. Louis native. It’s the first time in franchise history that the</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 13:59:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Founding Staind Drummer Jon Wysocki Dead at 53</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/19/jon-wysocki-dead-53-drummer/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Jon Wysocki, best known as a founding member and drummer of Staind, has reportedly died. The news of his passing was shared on social media by Jon's bandmates -- from his other rock group Lydia's Castle -- who confirmed the drummer died Saturday…</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 13:56:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chicago Bears Add George S. Halas’ Initials To 1936 Throwback Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/18/chicago-bears-add-george-s-halas-initials-to-1936-throwback-uniforms/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Chicago Bears have subtly added the initials of late founder, owner and coach George S. Halas to the left sleeve of their 1936 throwback uniforms, matching their navy blue home, white road and orange alternate jerseys.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 22:34:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kylie Jenner &amp; Aire Enjoy Sweet Mommy-Son Date to Monster Truck Rally</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/19/kylie-jenner-son-aire-enjoy-date-monster-truck-rally/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Kylie Jenner is proving to be quite the boy mom ... hitting up an unexpected event with her son, Aire -- which looked really loud! The reality star swung by SoFi Stadium in Los Angeles this weekend, but not for a concert or an NFL game -- which is…</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 13:56:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fanatics and NFLPA Reveal 2024 NFL Rookie Jerseys</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/18/fanatics-and-nflpa-reveal-2024-nfl-rookie-jerseys/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Last night, Fanatics and the NFLPA held a special “Jersey Reveal” event in Los Angeles to unveil the official game jerseys for 39 NFL rookies during the NFLPA Rookie Premiere. Several high-profile 2024 NFL Draft picks and rookies attended the event, including Caleb Williams and Rome Odunze of the Chicago</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 17:58:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Internet Loses It Over Baby Knowing What the Four Seasons Is</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/19/four-seasons-orlando-baby-viral-tiktok/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>The Internet is envious of one very well-informed and sophisticated baby -- who may be more cultured than many of us ... 'cause a viral video suggests she's in the know on fancy living. Check it out ... in a now viral TikTok, a woman off camera…</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 13:56:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Carolina Disco Turkeys to play as Camel City Humps</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/18/carolina-disco-turkeys-to-play-as-camel-city-humps/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The town of Winston-Salem, North Carolina, is called “Camel City” because since 1875 it has been home to the R.J. Reynolds Tobacco Company, which produces Camel brand cigarettes. The town of Winston-Salem is also home to the collegiate summer level Carolina Disco Turkeys, who will put a new twist on</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 17:29:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>J Lo and Ben Affleck Do Sunday Funday Together Despite Living Apart</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/19/j-lo-ben-affleck-together-sunday-funday-kids-events-marriage-living-apart/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Jennifer Lopez and Ben Affleck seem to be saying they're all good, maritally speaking -- even though they're not living under the same roof, they spent much of Sunday together ... looking like a happy couple. The apparently estranged couple met up…</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 13:56:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>All MLB Teams are Wearing Black Camo Caps Today</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/17/all-mlb-teams-are-wearing-black-camo-caps-today/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Why are all the Major League Baseball teams wearing black and green camouflage hats today? Well, that’s because MLB and New Era are in the midst of their annual Armed Forces Day ballcap celebration; here in 2024, the caps will be worn across the league over the May 17-18-19 weekend.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 23:44:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Flight Attendant Steve In 'Bridesmaids' 'Memba Him?!</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/20/flight-attendant-steve-bridesmaids-memba-him/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>American actor Mitch Silpa was in his mid-40s when he played Steve the flight attendant -- who puts up with the rowdy bridesmaids en route to the Las Vegas bachelorette party -- in the 2011 romantic comedy film "Bridesmaids." The ensemble cast of…</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 13:56:39 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>