<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 06:35:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Athletics Announce Uniform Change for Sacramento Shift, Las Vegas Design Process Underway</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/11/athletics-announce-uniform-change-for-sacramento-shift-las-vegas-design-process-underway/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The President of the Oakland Athletics gave the world an update about the future of the team’s uniforms as the club prepares for a chaotic few seasons. Speaking with the Las Vegas Review-Journal, A’s president Dave Kaval said the club has already begun the process of developing the team’s uniforms</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 03:13:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Travis Kelce Dodges Taylor Swift Cooking Question, But Confirms She Makes Mean Pop-Tart</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/11/travis-kelce-reveals-taylor-swift-makes-great-pop-tart-and-cinnamon-roll/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Travis Kelce gave a little taste on Tuesday of what Taylor Swift's cooking is like ... confirming she does make some good desserts -- although, at first, he was reluctant to give any juicy details. The pop star's kitchen skills were brought up…</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 06:35:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bayer Leverkusen Home Kit Headlines Unveilings From Germany and Beyond</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/11/bayer-leverkusen-home-kit-headlines-kit-unveilings-from-germany-and-beyond/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Other unveilings include newly promoted Bundesliga teams FC St. Pauli and Holstein Kiel, along with French side RC Lens and Portugal's FC Porto</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kevin Spacey Tells Piers Morgan He's Lost His Home &amp; Owes Millions</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/11/kevin-spacey-piers-morgan-lost-home-millions-legal-debt-broke/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Kevin Spacey broke down into tears to reveal a hard truth: he's destitute -- so deep in the hole, in fact, that he's about to lose his home ... this on the heels of his #MeToo scandal. In his first major TV appearance in years, the embattled actor…</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 06:35:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Messi Tops List of Best-Selling MLS Jerseys Once Again</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/11/messi-tops-list-of-best-selling-mls-jerseys-once-again/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Rest of top five includes Messi's Inter Miami teammate Luis Suárez; reigning MVP Luciano Acosta of FC Cincinnati; Columbus Crew's Cucho Hernández and LA Galaxy's Riqui Puig</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 21:11:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Major League Eating Hoping To Resolve Joey Chestnut Issue Before July 4 Contest</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/11/major-league-eating-hoping-to-resolve-joey-chestnut-issue-before-july-4-contest/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Don't give up hope just yet, America -- there's still a chance Joey Chestnut could take the stage and devour dozens of hot dogs this Fourth of July ... with sources telling TMZ Sports event organizers are keeping the door open for the greatest…</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 06:35:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Will The Indiana Pacers Have New Uniforms Next Season?</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/11/will-the-indiana-pacers-have-new-uniforms-next-season/basketball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>If a retail listing in the official online team store is any indication, the Indiana Pacers may have new uniforms for the 2024-25 season.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 19:35:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jeremy Allen White, Travis Barker, Matty Healy Among NYT's Hot 'Rodent Men'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/11/hot-rodent-men-jeremy-allen-white-matty-healy-travis-barker-new-york-times/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>The new sex symbols of Hollywood have arrived -- and they're now being dubbed "rodent men," whose critter features ladies just can't resist ... so says The New York Times. The publication's Styles team just put together a comprehensive list of hot…</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 06:35:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Ripple Effect: Minnesota Twins Launch New City Connect Uniform</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/10/the-ripple-effect-minnesota-twins-launch-new-city-connect-uniform/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Minnesota Twins dropped their new 10,000 Lakes themed City Connect uniform. We spoke with the team and explored every aspect of the new uniform together.</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 14:34:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Compton Pool Party Ends in Fatal Shooting, New Video Shows People Running</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/11/compton-pool-party-ends-shooting-new-video-people-running/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>A pool party in Compton ended in bullets flying and people running for their lives -- and TMZ has new video showing the chaos on the ground ... which ended with at least one death. Check out this footage we obtained from a get-together on Friday in…</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 06:35:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>