<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 15:17:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>State Capitalism in Private Markets: Mission Creep</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/03/state-capitalism-in-private-markets-mission-creep/</link><description>Governments relish mingling in markets. Yet, if past policies are any guide, taxpayers are being shortchanged.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 12:30:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Most Americans believe it will take over two decades to pay off their student loans</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/03/student-loans-time-it-takes-to-pay-off-northwestern-mutual-survey/</link><description>What some call the best four years of your life might end up leaving a decades-long aftertaste.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 19:52:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Implementation Shortfalls Hamstring Factor Strategies</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/01/implementation-shortfalls-hamstring-factor-strategies/</link><description>Smart rebalancing rules help portfolio managers capture more of the return that is inherent in their factor strategies. Concentrating on “priority best” trading improves factor portfolio performance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 11:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I’m paid $14 an hour to rate AI-generated Google search results. Subcontractors like me do key work but don’t get fair wages or benefits</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/03/google-search-raters-wages-benefits-contractors-tech-ai-employment/</link><description>Quality raters are critical to ensuring that Google search results aren’t littered with fraudulent or dangerous results.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 18:20:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IFRS Accounting Standard Will Support Better Investment Decisions</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/30/ifrs-accounting-standard-will-support-better-investment-decisions/</link><description>IFRS 18 responds to investors' concerns about challenges in comparing companies' financial performance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 11:34:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>It’s ‘just what the Fed chair wanted’ as the economy adds fewer jobs and unemployment rises to 3.9%</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/03/jobs-report-april-just-what-fed-chair-wanted-jerome-powell-rate-hikes/</link><description>“For those grappling with renewed stagflation fears, this payrolls report supports what Powell said earlier this week about not seeing the ‘stag’ or the ‘-flation’ right now,” J.P. Morgan’s Elyse Ausenbaugh noted.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 18:05:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meir Statman: Your State of Mind Influences Your Investing Success</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/29/meir-statman-your-state-of-mind-influences-your-investing-success/</link><description>Meir Statman shares his insights on the broader aspects of financial well-being and its interconnection with life satisfaction.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 12:58:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump Media's accounting firm accused of massive fraud as a 'sham audit mill' that created false papers, did nonexistent work, and fabricated meetings</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/03/trump-media-and-technology-djt-stock-accounting-firm-borgers-massive-fraud-sec/</link><description>Trump Media “looks forward to working with new auditing partners in accordance with today’s SEC order,” a representative for the company said.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 17:11:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: Trailblazers, Heroes, and Crooks</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/26/book-review-trailblazers-heroes-and-crooks/</link><description>Stephen Foerster, CFA, extracts lessons from exceptional episodes in financial history that ordinary investors and seasoned professionals alike can put to profitable use. The bonus is that you'll be entertained from start to finish.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OpenAI’s Sam Altman doesn’t care how much AGI will cost: Even if he spends $50 billion a year, some breakthroughs for mankind are priceless</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/03/openai-sam-altman-microsoft-agi-artificial-general-intelligence-costs/</link><description>Altman is more worried about how quickly society can adapt to the technology: “One thing we’ve learned is that AI and surprise don’t go well together.”</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 17:11:26 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>