<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 06:52:30 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>PSG Pay Homage to Eiffel Tower With New Away Kit – Plus More European Kit Launches</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/05/psg-pay-homage-to-eiffel-tower-with-new-away-kit-plus-more-european-kit-launches/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Other clubs unveiling 2024-25 kits include Napoli, Wolves, West Ham, Stade de Reims, Mallorca, Real Betis, Villarreal, Bochum, Stuttgart, Mainz 05 and Union Berlin</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 20:20:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Travis Kelce Sweet Head Kiss For Taylor Swift After Amsterdam 'Eras' Tour Show</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/06/travis-kelce-sweet-kiss-taylor-swift-amsterdam-eras-tour/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Taylor Swift's clearly moved on to the sweetest man who ever lived ... because the head kiss Travis Kelce laid on her last night is sending fans straight to the dentist. Trav was in attendance once again for Taylor's latest "Eras" tour stop Friday,…</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 06:52:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Look at the New NHL Practice Jersey Design</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/04/a-look-at-the-new-nhl-practice-jersey-design/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Thanks to the Utah Hockey Club, we got ourselves a look at the new NHL practice jersey design. With the switch from Adidas to Fanatics for 2024-25, we knew there’d be some changes to the on-ice NHL uniform. We’ve already seen that each team’s jersey will now include the Fanatics</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 22:20:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Lioness' Actor Mike Heslin Dead At 30</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/06/lioness-actor-mike-heslin-dead-dies-30/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Actor Mike Heslin, who had a role in Taylor Sheridan's 2023 show "Special Ops: Lioness" has passed away at 30. Heslin's husband Scotty Dynamo released the sad news on his Instagram account Friday ... telling the public the budding actor had died on…</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 06:52:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MLB Teams Wearing USA-Themed Caps Today for Fourth of July</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/04/mlb-teams-wearing-usa-themed-caps-today-for-fourth-of-july/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>All 30 Major League Baseball teams will wear stars-and-stripes-themed caps on-field during today’s games in honour of Independence Day in the United States. This year, all 30 clubs will wear a cream-coloured crown, with teams again having the option of a red or navy blue visor and button. One more</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 16:34:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Diddy Boards Private Jet In First Post Since Scrubbing His Instagram</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/06/diddy-sean-combs-boards-private-jet-combs-air-first-instagram/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Sean Diddy Combs was back on the radar Friday night ... but this time he was seen boarding his jet to fly out of town as his federal sex trafficking case continues to loom over him. The rap mogul posted a new video on his Instagram Story -- showing…</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 06:52:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2024 MLB All-Star Game Uniforms Revealed</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/03/2024-mlb-all-star-game-uniforms-revealed/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Major League Baseball has officially unveiled the uniforms their best players will wear when they take the field at Globe Life Field in Arlington later this month. The uniforms, as you’d expect, incorporate some of that Texas style, with an Old West style typeface across the chest and again in</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 02:02:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kylie Kelce Wears T-Shirt with Image of Viral Fan Confrontation on Front</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/06/kylie-kelce-wear-t-shirt-viral-clash-fight-new-jersey-confrontation-fan/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Kylie Kelce's turning a viral moment into a new wardrobe choice ... 'cause she's rocking a new t-shirt with a pic of her famous confrontation with a fan on the front. The wife of Jason Kelce wore the top while at an event recently ... and, check…</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 06:52:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Leaked Photos Show 2024 MLB All-Star Jerseys</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/03/leaked-photos-show-2024-mlb-all-star-jerseys/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>With just under two weeks until this year’s Mid-Summer Classic, the jerseys for one of the two teams have leaked. Posted by SNY’s Twitter account dedicated to the New York Yankees, the photos show the front and back of a cream-coloured American League jersey bearing the name of Yankees outfielder</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 20:37:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Emma Roberts Says She's Never Gotten A Job Because of Nepotism</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/06/emma-roberts-claims-nepo-baby-status-lost-more-jobs-gained-eric-julia/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Emma Roberts is doubling down on how nepo baby status ain't all it's cracked up to be ... claiming once again it's lost her jobs -- but never helped her land one. The actress sat down for an interview with the magazine Flaunt that dropped earlier…</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 06:52:30 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>