<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 06:57:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Football in Their DNA: AC Milan Launches 2024-25 Home Kit</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/23/football-in-their-dna-ac-milan-launches-2024-25-home-kit/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Tonal segmented stripes inside red stripes are a visual representation of the human genome; patch on back collar celebrates club's 125th anniversary</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 16:11:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sean Kingston's Florida Home Raided by Cops, Mom Arrested</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/23/sean-kingston-florida-home-raided-cops-mom-janice-arrested/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>12:12 PM PT -- Sean Kingston just addressed the raid on his IG Story writing, "People love negative energy! I am good and so is my mother!.. my lawyers are handling everything as we speak🙏🏽🙏🏽." Sean Kingston is in the crosshairs of a…</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 06:57:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Could West Virginia Mountaineers Wear 1965 Throwback Uniforms In 2025?</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/22/could-west-virginia-mountaineers-wear-1965-throwback-uniforms-in-2025/college/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>A recent exchange on social media between West Virginia's athletic director, head coach and a fan indicates throwback uniforms might be in the works for next season.</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 22:17:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jennifer Lopez, Netflix Banned Ben Affleck Questions Ahead of Premieres</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/23/jennifer-lopez-netflix-ban-ben-affleck-questions-movie-atlas-premiere/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>All Bennifer questions are off-limits, at least if you're media covering Jennifer Lopez for her new movie -- and reporters were warned about it before she arrived ... TMZ has learned. Sources with direct knowledge tell TMZ ... Netflix alerted all…</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 06:57:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OHL’s Guelph Storm File Trademarks for Three New Logos</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/22/ohls-guelph-storm-file-trademarks-for-three-new-logos/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>It's unclear if the Storm would keep their crimson, silver and black color scheme as trademark filing images are usually only available in grayscale</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 20:47:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NBA Closes Investigation Into Josh Giddey</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/23/nba-closes-investigation-into-josh-giddey/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Josh Giddey is now in the clear ... months after police closed their investigation into allegations the Thunder star had an inappropriate relationship with an underage girl -- the NBA has followed suit. Sources told ESPN's Adrian Wojnarowski the…</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 06:57:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2024 MLB Father’s Day Caps Revealed</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/22/2024-mlb-fathers-day-caps-revealed/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Father’s Day is quickly approaching. In the world of Major League Baseball, this means we’ll see baby blue-themed baseball caps and ribbons on the uniforms of Major League Baseball players, coaches, managers, and umpires for all games played on Sunday, June 16th. SHOP: 2024 MLB Father’s Day team caps available</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 15:50:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pete Buttigieg Defends Air Travel, Says FAA Holding Boeing to High Standard</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/23/pete-buttigieg-boeing-defend-air-travel-singapore-manufacturing-issues-dead/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Pete Buttigieg knows Americans have travel on the brain heading into the holiday weekend, and for those concerned about Boeing's issues, he says the government's holding the company to a very high standard. The Secretary of Transportation was on…</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 06:57:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>They’ve Got the Power: Washington, D.C., USL Super League Club Unveils Name, Logo</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/21/theyve-got-the-power-washington-d-c-usl-super-league-club-unveils-name-logo/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Crest features black, red and white shield with eagle wing cutting through the middle; lightning bolts in negative represent three communities in D.C. metro area</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 21:15:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kelly Rowland Hints Race Played a Factor in Cannes Security Fight</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/23/kelly-rowland-hints-race-factor-cannes-security-fight/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Kelly Rowland is speaking out about her heated exchange with a security guard at the Cannes Film Festival ... and strongly suggesting she was singled out because she's Black. The Destiny's Child singer addressed the drama Thursday for the first…</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 06:57:05 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>