<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 07:10:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Utah NHL Team Logos, Colours, and Possible Uniforms for Year One</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/27/utah-nhl-team-logos-colours-and-possible-uniforms-for-year-one/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Utah’s new National Hockey League team, set to debut for the upcoming 2024-25 NHL season, will reportedly start without a permanent name or logo. However, a look at some of the early merchandise being prepared for the team has revealed what appears to be a temporary design featuring “UTAH” in</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 17:51:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kelly Rowland's Cannes Security Guard Also Had Run-In with South Korean Actress</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/27/cannes-film-festival-security-guard-third-incident-kelly-rowland-yoona-discrimination/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>11:58 AM PT -- Another Cannes' attendee has called out the same security guard ... Ukrainian model Sawa Pontyjska -- better known as Miss Europe 2023 -- shared a clip where she ended up in a bear hug by security. Unclear exactly what led up to the…</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 07:10:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blue Jays to Unveil City Connect Uniform Thursday, Wear it Thrice for “City Week”</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/27/blue-jays-to-unveil-city-connect-uniform-thursday-wear-it-thrice-for-city-week/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Today, the Toronto Blue Jays announced some details surrounding their upcoming Nike MLB City Connect uniform release and the accompanying “City Week” promotion, which will run during their next homestand from May 31 through June 6. Things get underway on Thursday night when the Blue Jays unveil the new look</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 14:54:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Diddy's Sean John Frames Pulled From America's Best Contacts and Eyeglasses</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/27/diddy-sean-john-pull-america-best-contacts-eyeglasses-frames/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Diddy's wallet's about to take a hit ... 'cause his famed Sean John frames are out at a huge eyewear retailer while his legal troubles mount. America's Best Contacts &amp; Eyeglasses has halted sales of Diddy's company's frames, TMZ has learned ...…</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 07:10:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Red Poppy Flower Patches on Baseball Jerseys Today for Memorial Day</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/27/red-poppy-flower-patches-on-baseball-jerseys-today-for-memorial-day/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Major League Baseball will once again honour those who lost their lives while serving in the United States Armed Forces with a special patch worn on player uniforms. For all MLB games played on Memorial Day, Monday, May 27, 2024, players will wear a red poppy flower patch on the</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 14:12:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sean Kingston's Mom Bails Out of Jail After Fraud, Theft Arrest</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/27/sean-kingston-mom-janice-turner-bond-bail-jail-release-theft-fraud-arrest-home-raid/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Sean Kingston's mother is breathing fresh Florida air again -- after spending 4 days behind bars, she's bailed out following her arrest in the raid at Sean's house. Janice Turner got busted a few hours before Sean during the Broward County…</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 07:10:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Our Chat with Cards’ President Bill DeWitt III About New City Connect Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/25/our-chat-with-cards-president-bill-dewitt-iii-about-new-city-connect-uniforms/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The St. Louis Cardinals brand new Nike MLB City Connect uniforms will be making their on-field début this afternoon. The red jerseys with “The Lou” scripted across the chest, inspired by the hit song from Nelly, were unveiled on Monday to an overall positive reaction from fans and media alike.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 17:17:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chris Brown's Daughter Royalty Celebrates 10th Birthday</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/27/chris-brown-daughter-rodeo-royalty-birthday-party-nia/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Chris Brown's little girl ain't so little anymore -- his daughter Royalty's celebrating her 10th birthday today, and it looks like she's a big Beyoncé fan! Chris and Royalty were super close and in the pics her mom, Nia Guzman, posted from the…</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 07:10:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ligue 1’s Lille OSC Put Unique Spin on Traditional Chevron for 2024-25 Home Kits</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/24/ligue-1s-lille-osc-put-unique-spin-on-traditional-chevron-for-2024-25-home-kits/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Club's traditional chevron, which they've used in some form since the 1940s, appears on new kits made up of several tonal mini-chevrons</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 22:01:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Britney Spears Claims Someone Stole All Her Jewelry</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/27/britney-spears-claim-jewelry-stolen-instagram-video-sherriff-police-report-theft/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Britney Spears says she's been the victim of theft ... telling her millions of Instagram followers someone stole all her jewelry -- but, she hasn't filed a police report yet. The singer-songwriter took to IG Sunday night and shared a video she took…</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 07:10:28 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>