<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:41:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Minor League Baseball teams, local indie bands team up on brands</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/14/minor-league-baseball-teams-local-indie-bands-team-up-on-brands/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Three affiliated Minor League Baseball teams will partner with local independent musicians to create the “Capsule Collection.” This collaboration is intended to do what minor league baseball branding specializes in: highlight connections between teams and their local community. In its just-announced initial stages, the Capsule Collection will combine design elements</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 18:30:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TMZ TV Hot Takes: Taylor Swift, Zendaya's Stylist, Tyson Fury's Dad</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/14/tmz-tv-hot-takes-taylor-swift-zendayas-stylist-tyson-fury-s-dad/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Another Monday has come and gone ... so be sure to end your day with some TMZ TV hot takes. First up, we have "TMZ Live," where Mike and Charles discuss the surprising events from Taylor Swift's updated Eras tour ... including a guest who probably…</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:41:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WNBA Expansion Team Golden State Valkyries Unveil Name, Logo</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/14/wnba-expansion-team-golden-state-valkyries-unveil-name-logo/basketball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Franchise name references warrior women from Norse mythology; logo depicts Bay Bridge between Oakland, where they'll train, and San Francisco, where they'll play home games</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 15:56:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Magic Johnson Not Interested In Return To Coaching, Hopes Lakers Get 'Good One'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/14/magic-johnson-not-interested-in-return-to-coaching-hopes-lakers-get-good-one/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Magic Johnson claims he has no idea who the Lakers' next head coach will be ... but he definitely knows who it WON'T be -- Magic Johnson -- 'cause the Hall of Famer tells TMZ Sports those days are long gone. The Purple and Gold are currently…</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:41:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New York Giants Unveil 100th Season Logo, Uniform Patch</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/13/new-york-giants-unveil-100th-season-logo-uniform-patch/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The New York Giants kicked off their 100th season celebration on Monday morning by unveiling a commemorative logo, which will be worn as a patch on their uniforms this fall.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 02:05:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Silence of the Lambs' Producer Slams Trump for Praising Hannibal Lecter</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/14/silence-of-the-lambs-producer-slams-trump-praise-hannibal-lecter/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Donald Trump's rant about the "wonderful" Hannibal Lecter isn't sitting well with one of the guys who helped make "The Silence of the Lambs," and he's taking a bite out of DT's rhetoric. Edward Saxon -- part of the Oscar-winning trio that produced…</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:41:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>La Liga’s Real Betis Focus on Water With Newest Edition of ‘Forever Green’ Kits</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/13/la-ligas-real-betis-focus-on-water-with-newest-edition-of-forever-green-kits/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Club aims to raise awareness about the responsible use of water and the impact climate change is having on fields in Spain and all over the world</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 15:54:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kelly Clarkson Admits to Using Weight Loss Drug After Physical Transformation</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/13/kelly-clarkson-admits-using-weight-loss-drug-medication-physical-transformation/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Kelly Clarkson is getting honest about her physical transformation ... admitting she used a weight loss drug to help shed pounds -- something she'd kinda tip-toed around until now. The singer got candid about her health journey during Monday's…</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:41:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Leak: Los Angeles Dodgers City Connect Jersey Spotted in Japan</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/13/leak-los-angeles-dodgers-city-connect-jersey-spotted-in-tokyo/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Los Angeles Dodgers’ new City Connect uniform was leaked this weekend. The jersey, spotted hanging up in a store in Japan, shows a vibrant pattern that departs from the traditional Dodgers’ style. The photo shows a white jersey speckled with tiny blue, red, and yellow dots, giving the feeling</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 15:25:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sylvester Stallone's 'Holy Grail' Watch Will Fetch Over $5 Mil, Expert Says</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/14/sylvester-stallone-grandmaster-chime-holy-grail-watch-nico-van-der-horst/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Sylvester Stallone is about to score a massive payday after putting his watch collection up for auction, because one of the timepieces could fetch a literal king's ransom. As you might have heard, the 'Rocky' star is selling 11 watches from his…</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:41:34 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>