<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 06:58:03 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>NLL’s Ottawa Black Bears Ready to Roar in Inaugural Season Jerseys</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/25/nlls-ottawa-black-bears-ready-to-roar-in-inaugural-season-jerseys/other/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Franchise announced relocation to Canadian capital from Long Island in February; striping around waist and sleeves features Indigenous pattern of peace and friendship</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 01:18:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Celine Dion's Return to Stage Is Encouraging, But Risky</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/25/celine-dion-performance-risk-dr-pavan-tankha/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Celine Dion is set to make her triumphant return to the stage for both the Olympics and a Las Vegas residency ... a decision TMZ is told is both a positive sign about her Stiff-Person Syndrome treatments ... and also risky. Here's the deal ... CD…</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 06:58:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jacksonville Jaguars Unveil New “Shell White” Alternate Helmets</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/25/jacksonville-jaguars-unveil-new-shell-white-alternate-helmets/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Confirming our report from April, the Jacksonville Jaguars unveiled their new "Shell White"alternate helmets early Thursday morning.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 12:21:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oprah Winfrey, Gayle King Say They'd Admit If They Were a Gay Couple</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/25/oprah-winfrey-gayle-king-say-would-admit-gay-couple-lesbian-rumors/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Oprah Winfrey and Gayle King say they're a couple of straight shooters who'd admit if they were a gay couple -- a rare denial of a longtime rumor that's swirled around them. The talk show hosts sat down for an interview with Melinda Gates on her…</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 06:58:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Notre Dame Unveils Shamrock Series Uniforms For Game Against Army At Yankee Stadium</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/24/notre-dame-unveils-shamrock-series-uniforms-for-game-against-army-at-yankee-stadium/college/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Notre Dame unveiled its latest Shamrock Series uniforms, which are inspired by the "Four Horsemen" and will be worn against Army at Yankee Stadium on Nov. 23.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 21:21:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ronda Rousey Announces She's Pregnant With Second Child</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/25/ronda-rousey-announces-pregnant-second-child/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Ronda Rousey is ready for round 2!!! The former UFC champion and WWE Superstar announced Thursday she's pregnant with her second child ... sharing the big news while speaking at a San Diego Comic-Con panel to promote her new graphic novel,…</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 06:58:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MLB All-Star Game Logos, Like Super Bowls, May Get a Templated Look Going Forward</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/23/mlb-all-star-game-logos-like-super-bowls-may-get-a-templated-look-going-forward/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Standardized sports logos are trending, from the Super Bowl to literally everything in the NBA. But what about Major League Baseball’s All-Star Game… Well, guess what? It looks like baseball’s annual Mid-Summer Classic is ready to join the club. “You might start to see some similarities in the format and</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 21:37:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kamala Harris' Stepdaughter Ella Emhoff Slams J.D. Vance's 'Cat Lady' Remark</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/25/kamala-harris-stepdaughter-ella-emhoff-rips-jd-vance-cat-lady-comment/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Vice President Kamala Harris' stepdaughter, Ella Emhoff, is firing back at J.D. Vance for his controversial “childless cat lady” remark aimed at women like her stepmom. Ella -- the daughter of Kamala's hubby Douglas Emhoff -- was trailed by her…</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 06:58:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stellar Real Madrid Away Kit Headlines Recent Launches from Spain, Rest of Europe</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/23/stellar-real-madrid-away-kit-headlines-recent-launches-from-spain-and-rest-of-europe/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Inter Milan adds gold flourishes to home kit to celebrate 20th Serie A title; other clubs unveiling 24-25 kits include Aston Villa, Real Valladolid, Girona, Osasuna, Borussia Dortmund, Stade Rennais, Toulouse</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 17:27:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Palm Beach Sheriff Candidates Go At It During Debate, 'F***ing A**hole'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/25/palm-beach-sheriff-debate-fiery-f-bomb-showdown-caught-zoom/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Now THIS is a debate -- the race for Sheriff in Florida's Palm Beach County has one candidate so fired up, he said what's really on his mind after getting roasted in a showdown with his rivals. The debate went down by Zoom earlier this week, and…</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 06:58:03 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>