<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 06:51:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Anaheim Ducks Drop a Mighty Good Teaser</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/17/anaheim-ducks-drop-a-mighty-good-teaser/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Anaheim Ducks today posted a teaser graphic that teases a potential new Mighty Ducks of Anaheim themed uniform. Posted to their various social media channels, the teaser shows a closeup of the eye of the mask from the club’s original Mighty Ducks logo but with some subtle modernizations. Unfortunately,</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 22:39:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sabrina Carpenter Addresses SKIMS Campaign Criticism From Swifties</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/17/sabrina-carpenter-addresses-skims-campaign-criticism-taylor-swift-fans/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Sabrina Carpenter is chalking up the backlash she faced for appearing in Kim Kardashian's SKIMS campaign as a bunch of nonsense ... 'cause she made sure to loop in the Queen. The singer addressed the hate she received from Taylor Swift's fans over…</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 06:51:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Uruguay Launches First Home and Away Kits Under New Nike Deal</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/17/uruguay-launches-first-home-and-away-kits-under-new-nike-deal/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Kits are not yet available for retail purchase; AUF warns that any shirts out there are fakes and they will take "necessary legal action" against counterfeiters</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 20:53:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gisele Bündchen, Joaquim Valente Spend Time With Tom Brady's Kids on Father's Day</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/17/gisele-bundchen-joaquim-valente-spend-time-tom-brady-kids-fathers-day-broadcast-tv-debut/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Gisele Bündchen and Joaquim Valente filled in for Tom Brady on Father's Day ... looking after her and TB12's kiddos as pops made his broadcast television debut. The supermodel and her jiu-jitsu trainer boyfriend had Benjamin and Vivian Brady in…</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 06:51:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TCU Horned Frogs Unveil New, Simplified Football Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/17/tcu-horned-frogs-unveil-new-simplified-football-uniforms/college/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>TCU unveiled new uniforms on Monday morning, simplifying the design the Horned Frogs have worn since 2019.</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 20:06:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Love Island' Star Jack Fowler Rips Airline Over Food Allergy Incident</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/17/love-island-jack-fowler-rips-emirates-airline-food-allergy-nut/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>"Love Island Games" champion Jack Fowler is ripping an airline over an allergic reaction he says he suffered on a flight ... accusing the company of not taking food allergies seriously. Jack just shared what he characterizes as a travel nightmare…</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 06:51:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Los Angeles Dodgers Reveal Their Second City Connect Uniform</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/17/los-angeles-dodgers-reveal-their-second-city-connect-uniform/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>This afternoon, the Los Angeles Dodgers became the ninth and final team to unveil their Nike MLB City Connect uniform for the 2024 season. No, this isn’t some “Mandela-effect” thing; the Dodgers had a City Connect uniform before, worn from 2021 to 2023. This is their second City Connect design,</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 17:47:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fat Joe Says Rihanna Attack Only Difference Between Chris Brown &amp; Michael Jackson</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/17/fat-joe-chris-brown-rihanna-michael-jackson/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Chris Brown and Michael Jackson are one and the same -- with the only difference being one of them beat the hell out of Rihanna ... so says Fat Joe. In his latest IG Live session, FJ came with a bit of a hot take -- namely, arguing the only thing…</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 06:51:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blue Caps, Ribbons in Baseball Today for Father’s Day</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/16/blue-caps-ribbons-in-baseball-today-for-fathers-day/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Why are all the baseball teams wearing blue logos on their caps and blue ribbons on their jerseys today? Because it’s Father’s Day, of course! In the world of Major League Baseball, this means we get baby blue-themed baseball caps and ribbons on the uniforms of Major League Baseball players,</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 13:27:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Diddy Showered With Father's Day Love From Kids, Have His Back Amid Woes</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/17/diddy-fathers-day-tribute-kids/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Diddy's family made sure to let him know he was loved and appreciated on Father's Day -- this after most of Hollywood turned their back on him amid his legal woes. His brood littered their IG account with throwback pics this weekend -- with his…</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 06:51:56 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>