<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 16:01:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Stellar Real Madrid Away Kit Headlines Recent Launches from Spain, Rest of Europe</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/23/stellar-real-madrid-away-kit-headlines-recent-launches-from-spain-and-rest-of-europe/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Inter Milan adds gold flourishes to home kit to celebrate 20th Serie A title; other clubs unveiling 24-25 kits include Aston Villa, Real Valladolid, Girona, Osasuna, Borussia Dortmund, Stade Rennais, Toulouse</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 17:27:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Keanu Reeves Says He Thinks About Death 'All the Time'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/23/keanu-reeves-thinks-about-death-all-the-time/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Keanu Reeves is sharing his candid thoughts on mortality, and the fact is ... "the end" is something that's top of mind for him right now. The actor joined author China Miéville on the BBC to promote their new novel, "The Book of Elsewhere," which…</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 16:01:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2025 MLB All-Star Game Logo Revealed; Hosted by Atlanta Braves</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/22/2025-mlb-all-star-game-logo-revealed-hosted-by-atlanta-braves/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Atlanta… You’re on the clock. Four years after they lost the game with just months to go, the Atlanta Braves are back and ready to host. Major League Baseball, along with the team, today unveiled the logo for the 2025 MLB All-Star Game, to be played at Truist Field on</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 00:18:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'All My Children's Esta TerBlanche's Death Scene Required Animal Rescue Response</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/23/all-my-children-esta-terblanche-death-scene-animal-rescue-response/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Esta TerBlanche left behind a bunch of animals -- including some very unique pets -- when she died last week, and they had to be collected by a third party ... TMZ has learned. Law enforcement sources tell us cops got called to the "All My…</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 16:01:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are The Kansas City Chiefs Considering Alternate Uniforms?</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/22/are-the-kansas-city-chiefs-considering-alternate-uniforms/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Don't expect the Kansas City Chiefs to get an alternate uniform anytime soon, though their owner appears to be warming up to the idea.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 22:23:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Thirteen Brazilian Sharks Test Positive for Cocaine, Researchers Say</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/23/sharks-test-positive-cocaine-brazilian-coast/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>More than a dozen sharks in Brazil have tested positive for cocaine -- elevating concerns that the open waters in the area are being contaminated with drugs and affecting wildlife. A handful of research groups recently published findings after…</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 16:01:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New York Jets Unveil “The Classic” Throwback Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/22/new-york-jets-unveil-the-classic-throwback-uniforms/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Although it’s only been five years since they moved away from the design, the New York Jets unveiled a familiar throwback uniform that will be worn against the Buffalo Bills on Monday Night Football on Oct. 14.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 20:04:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Secret Service Director Kimberly Cheatle Resigns After Trump Shooting</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/23/secret-service-director-kimberly-cheatle-resign-trump-shooting-attempted-assassination/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Secret Service Director Kimberly Cheatle is throwing in the towel on her job at the federal agency -- this after the bungled attempted assassination of Donald Trump ... and all the scrutiny that's followed, TMZ has confirmed. Cheatle tendered her…</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 16:01:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AFC Bournemouth Launch Michael B. Jordan-Designed Kits for Preseason U.S. Tour</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/21/afc-bournemouth-launch-michael-b-jordan-designed-kits-for-preseason-u-s-tour/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>English Premier League club AFC Bournemouth have enlisted some Hollywood help for the kits for their preseason tour of the United States.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 16:54:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tiger Woods Shows Off Gnarly Leg Scars Three Years After Car Crash</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/23/tiger-woods-shows-off-gnarly-leg-scar-two-years-after-car-crash/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Tiger Woods gave the public its first glimpse of his right leg since he mangled it in a 2021 car crash ... and check it out, the Big Cat's got some really big scars. Eldrick has usually rocked a leg sleeve when around cameras since requiring…</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 16:01:13 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>