<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 06:36:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Leveraging AI to Identify and Predict Financial Crises</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/13/leveraging-ai-to-identify-and-predict-financial-crises/</link><description>Despite some current limitations, AI stands to offer significant advantages versus traditional approaches to identifying and predicting financial crises.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 14:39:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Uber stokes monopoly fears with plan to pay almost $1bn for its only major food delivery competitor in Taiwan</title><link>https://fortune.com/asia/2024/05/14/uber-monopoly-fears-pay-1bn-delivery-hero-food-delivery-competitor-taiwan/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1754862834-e1715680578250.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Uber, whose meal delivery business outperformed globally during the most recent quarter, aims to complete the all-cash deal by the first half of 2025.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 11:08:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Your Portfolio Should Include Scarce Assets</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/10/why-your-portfolio-should-include-scarce-assets/</link><description>Portfolios that include both productive and scarce assets can deliver similar performance to the S&amp;P 500 with less risk than those that hold only productive assets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:34:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Switzerland shouldn't follow Europe's lead on tax, says Roche CEO</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/14/switzerland-tax-europe-lead-roche-ceo-thomas-schinecker-compete-dubai-china-india/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1968671907-e1715678773771.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Europe is falling behind China and the U.S. in competitiveness, according to Thomas Schinecker, Roche CEO.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 10:42:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coiled Tight: Smaller Companies Are Primed for Outperformance</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/08/coiled-tight-smaller-companies-are-primed-for-outperformance/</link><description>Small-cap companies are poised for a rebound. The sector is best approached through an active investment strategy where expertise and a deep understanding of the individual businesses and their risk-and-reward characteristics are necessary for success.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:40:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Emmanuel Macron woos Wall Street as he tries to position Paris as Europe’s top financial hub, calling Basel banking regulations 'a killer for risk taking'</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/14/paris-emmanuel-macron-wall-street-basel-regulations-europes-top-financial-hub/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2152250578-e1715677864499.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The push to lure more business to Paris has translated into more than 7,000 extra jobs in the financial sector between 2017 and 2022.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 10:37:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Investment Returns Are NOT Random</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/07/investment-returns-are-not-random/</link><description>Are investment returns random across time as Burton Malkiel suggests in his book, A Random Walk Down Wall Street? There is notable disagreement on this topic. This research finds that practitioners may need to rethink their portfolio optimization routines.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:22:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BYD has been frozen out of the U.S. market so it’s debuting its first hybrid pickup truck in Mexico</title><link>https://fortune.com/asia/2024/05/14/byd-us-market-debuting-first-hybrid-pickup-truck-shark-mexico/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2152729589-e1715677641149.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>While BYD has said previously the Shark will be distributed globally, the automaker doesn’t have any plans to sell in the U.S. at the moment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 10:16:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Generational Wealth: Does the Apple Fall Far From the Tree?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/06/generational-wealth-does-the-apple-fall-far-from-the-tree/</link><description>There is strong evidence that most “rich families” will be poorer after several generations. Some of the reasons for this are systemic like taxes. But most factors that diminish a family’s wealth over generations are the choices that heirs make.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 12:37:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vodafone turnaround: $11.9 billion earnings and a return to growth in Germany, but 'much more still needs to be done'</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/14/vodafone-turnaround-earnings-growth-germany/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2060423726-e1715675956407.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Vodafone is increasing its focus on the German market and exiting unprofitable ones, as part of CEO Della Valle’s turnaround strategy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 10:02:04 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>