<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 06:53:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>4 Tips for Managing Long-Distance Turnkey Rentals Without Cutting Corners</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/tips-for-managing-a-long-distance-turnkey-rental-property</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Taking the easy way out is generally bad practice. Manage your long-distance rentals this way instead.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 18:53:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Waymo robotaxi pulled over by Phoenix police after driving into the wrong lane</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/06/waymo-robotaxi-pulled-over-by-phoenix-police-after-driving-into-the-wrong-lane/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>A police officer pulled over a self-driving Waymo vehicle in Phoenix after it ran a red light and pulled into a lane of oncoming traffic, according to dispatch records. The incident took place on June 19, but local media including Arizona Republic released bodycam footage of the traffic stop this week, showing the vehicle weaving […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 22:10:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Love Beyond Bars: Miguel and Silvia</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/05/photo-essay-wrongful-conviction-love-story</link><description>While Miguel Solorio did 25 years for a crime he didn’t commit, his wife, Silvia, was right by his side. Here’s their California love story in pictures.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Federal Experts Talk Bird Flu ‘What Ifs’ in WebMD Live Event</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/cold-and-flu/news/20240516/federal-experts-talk-bird-flu-what-ifs?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>WebMD brought together experts from four federal agencies to talk prevention, monitoring, and what the “what ifs” of bird flu might look like.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:50:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>High-End Homes Hit Peak Prices as Luxury Investors Scramble for Better Deals</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/luxury-homes-reach-highest-prices-yet-as-investors-look-for-deals</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Luxury home prices have made these properties even more unaffordable, but we talked to investors who told us what to look for.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 18:23:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Figma pauses its new AI feature after Apple controversy</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/06/figma-pauses-its-new-ai-feature-after-apple-controversy/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Welcome back to TechCrunch’s Week in Review — TechCrunch’s newsletter recapping the week’s biggest news. Want it in your inbox every Saturday? Sign up here. This week, Figma CEO Dylan Field said the company will temporarily disable its “Make Design” AI feature after it was accused of “heavily” training the tool on existing apps. The […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 21:16:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Crime Rates and the 2024 Election: What You Need to Know</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/27/trump-and-biden-spar-over-crime-rates-ahead-of-their-debate-what-do-we-really-know</link><description>As crime data again becomes a flashpoint in the presidential campaign, experts push for better national statistics.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What’s Next in Health Care for Older Adults: Questions and Answers With John Whyte, MD</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/blog-aging-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>As WebMD’s chief medical officer, John Whyte, MD, is in a unique position to see both the current state of medical care for America’s older adults and the way things are trending for the future. We asked him to share his insight on a few topics, along with a bit of advice.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:29:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is Virtual Staging Better than Real Staging When It Comes to Selling a Flip?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/is-virtual-staging-the-best-thing-for-a-flip</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>With AI tools and Matterport, virtual staging could earn you more dollars on your flip than you might expect.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 18:02:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to set up parental controls on Facebook, Snapchat, TikTok and more popular sites</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/06/how-to-set-up-parental-controls-on-facebook-snapchat-tiktok-and-more-popular-sites/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>We’ve created this guide to help parents navigate the controls offered by popular social media companies. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 20:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Death Row Prisoner’s Parting Interview</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/24/texas-death-row-prisoner-final-interview</link><description>Days before his scheduled execution in Texas, Ramiro Gonzales speaks on faith, legacy — and apologizing to the family of his victim, Bridget Townsend.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Get the Care You Need in a COVID-19 World</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/covid-senior-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>What to expect at the doctor’s office, hospitals, and long-term care facilities, the future of telemedicine, and how to get the best care during COVID-19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 19:50:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BiggerNews: With Slow Spring Homebuying, Zillow Predicts Price Drops in 2025</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-983</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Zillow’s latest housing market forecast shows a decline in home prices over the next year after a very slow spring homebuying season. While spring is traditionally the hottest time of […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 07:02:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>You could learn a lot from a CIO with a $17B IT budget</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/06/you-could-learn-a-lot-from-a-cio-with-a-15b-it-budget/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Lori Beer's work is a case study for every CIO out there, most of whom will never come close to JP Morgan Chase’s scale, but who can still learn from how it goes about its business. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The New Battle Over an Old Institution: Forced Prison Labor</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/22/prison-slavery-forced-labor-lawsuits-bills</link><description>Inside the latest legal and legislative efforts to close state constitutional loopholes that allow slavery as punishment for a crime.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Personal Shopper: A Savvy Black Entrepreneur Guides You to Eczema-Friendly Clothes, Creams, Cosmetics, and More</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/savvy-black-entrepreneur-guides-eczema-friendly-clothes-creams-cosmetics?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>A savvy black entrepreneur guides you on an eczema-friendly shopping spree.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:54:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rookie Reply: How to Analyze Rentals for Cash Flow &amp; Manage a Rehab Project</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-428</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Most investors buy rental properties for cash flow, and the fear of losing money keeps many rookies on the sidelines. How can you be certain that you’re going to make […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 07:02:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tesla makes it onto Chinese government purchase list</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/06/tesla-makes-it-onto-chinese-government-purchase-list/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>For the first time, Chinese government workers will be able to purchase Tesla’s Model Y for official use. Specifically, officials in eastern China’s Jiangsu province included the Model Y in a government procurement list, which was also reported in the state-owned publication The Paper. As the only foreign-owned electric vehicle company on the list, Tesla’s […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 18:43:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mississippi Wants to Allow Some Votes From Jails and Prisons. Red Tape May Stop It.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/20/mississippi-voting-from-prison-and-jails</link><description>A new state law will allow more people in jails and prisons to cast absentee ballots, but many obstacles remain.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Behind the Spike in Colorectal Cancer Among Young Americans</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/colorectal-cancer/news/20240515/behind-the-spike-in-colorectal-cancer-cases?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Colorectal cancer cases increased a whopping 333% among 15- to 19-year-olds and 185% among 20- to 24-year-olds from 1999 to 2020.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:59:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>