<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 13:26:12 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The Books Readers Are Most Anticipating This Fall</title><link>https://bookriot.com/the-books-readers-are-most-anticipating-this-fall/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/books-in-a-library-feature.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>The fall books readers are most anticipating, THE SHAWSHANK REDEMPTION at 30, and more in today's book news.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 17:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GM's Mark Reuss talks Cadillac's EV game plan and the return of the Corvette ZR1</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/08/21/gms-mark-reuss-talks-cadillacs-ev-game-plan-and-the-return-of-the-corvette-zr1/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/crop/736x414+2+175/resize/1200x675/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/08/21131839/Reuss1.jpeg</image_url><description>Filed under: Green , Cadillac , GM , Electric , Luxury , Performance Continue reading GM's Mark Reuss talks Cadillac's EV game plan and the return of the Corvette ZR1 GM's Mark Reuss talks Cadillac's EV game plan and the return of the Corvette ZR1 originally appeared on Autoblog on Wed, 21 Aug 2024 13:20:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 18:20:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stocks making the biggest moves midday: Target, JD.com, Macy's and more</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/21/stocks-making-the-biggest-moves-midday-tgt-jd-m-and-more.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>These are the stocks posting the largest moves in midday trading.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 17:33:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tracking Your Job Search Activities</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/tracking-your-job-search-activities/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=tracking-your-job-search-activities</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Ever feel like your job search is going nowhere fast? You’re not alone. I’ve talked to countless job seekers who are putting in tons of effort but can’t seem to make progress. The problem? They’re not tracking their activities. Without a system to monitor what you’re doing, it’s impossible to know what’s working and what’s […] The post Tracking Your Job Search Activities appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 11:20:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How parents can support math learning at home and through everyday activities</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/how-parents-can-support-math-learning-at-home/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=how-parents-can-support-math-learning-at-home</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Math skills at kindergarten entry predict children’s academic success in school. Young children usually enjoy learning math and can develop understanding about math in all the content areas they will encounter in school: number, patterns, shapes, spatial relations, and data. Parents can grow their young children’s math knowledge through playful activities […] The post How parents can support math learning at home and through everyday activities appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 23:18:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Baked Turkey Meatballs</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/baked-turkey-meatballs/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Baked Turkey Meatballs are tender, juicy, and perfectly seasoned. They’re made with simple ingredients but big on flavor! These homemade…</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Get Rid Of Fruit Flies: 7 Tested Methods</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/how-to-get-rid-of-fruit-flies/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Got little bugs buzzing around your kitchen? Congratulations, you may have fruit flies! Don’t fret. These annoying pests are pretty common but luckily, it doesn’t take a lot of money, supplies, or effort to get rid of them. In fact, you can probably find everything you need in your cabinets! We recently had a fruit fly problem in our home (the first time in over four years here – we have no idea what brought them in). So I seized the opportunity to test 7 different methods of eliminating them. Yes, there were copious notes taken and even a spreadsheet. So today I’m sharing the best fruit fly traps and how to make them. Each homemade trap is easy to make and uses natural ingredients that we already had around the house. So let’s just call this extremely D.I.Y friendly and chemical free. You can also set the fruit flies free outside if you’d rather not let them perish. Continue reading How To Get Rid Of Fruit Flies: 7 Tested Methods at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 16:08:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fringe Finds</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/08/fringe-finds/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Outfit Details: Paco Rabanne Top, Dries Van Noten Skirt (old, similar here), Amanu Sandals, Ferragamo Bag, Sherman Fields Necklace Fringe is a delightful detail… The post Fringe Finds appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 05:00:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Biggest Book Club Books To Look For This Fall</title><link>https://bookriot.com/the-biggest-book-club-books-coming-out-this-fall-2/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/Untitled-1.png</image_url><description>Fall book club picks, historical fiction for kids, the most interesting questions in books, and more today on Book Riot</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 17:25:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ford cancels electric three-row SUV, pivots to hybrid</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/08/21/ford-cancels-electric-three-row-suv/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1200x675/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/08/21120107/IMG_941831.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Earnings/Financials , Green , Ford , Truck , Crossover , SUV , Commercial Vehicles , Electric , Hybrid Continue reading Ford cancels electric three-row SUV, pivots to hybrid Ford cancels electric three-row SUV, pivots to hybrid originally appeared on Autoblog on Wed, 21 Aug 2024 12:18:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 17:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Epic Systems is building more than 100 new AI features for doctors and patients. Here's what's coming</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/21/epic-systems-ugm-2024-ai-tools-in-mychart-cosmos-.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Health-care executives are visiting Epic's headquarters this week to learn about its new software products and updates.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 16:49:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 560</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-560/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-560</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>There is a steep learning curve involved in job search. And many skills you need to succeed in a job search are not skills you would typically use in your job. The good news is there are resources and tools to help you! In this week’s Summary Sunday, you will find curated articles from respected […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 560 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 13:26:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Do infants feel excluded? Early signs and why it matters</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/do-infants-feel-excluded/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=do-infants-feel-excluded</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Social exclusion harms individuals of all ages, leading to feelings of loneliness, decreased self-esteem, and even changes in brain activity. Humans’ ability to recognize and react to social exclusion emerges early, suggesting the importance of considering and addressing ostracism even when caring for very young children. Babies are sensitive to social […] The post Do infants feel excluded? Early signs and why it matters appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 01:37:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Smothered Chicken</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/smothered-chicken/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Smothered chicken is a flavorful comfort food full of rich, creamy gravy, tender chicken cutlets, and savory mushrooms. Perfect on…</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Summer Trip To South Dakota</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/south-dakota-family-vacation/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>I’ll be the first to admit that South Dakota wasn’t high on my vacation bucket list. But I ended up there this summer on a dad-and-daughter trip I took with some family members: and WOW, we loved it. It was a surprising and wonderful departure from our usual family trips, so I wanted to share some highlights in case anyone else is interested in breaking out of the more typical beach or theme park vacation routine. Growing up on the East Coast and now living in Florida, I haven’t spent much time in the upper Midwest. So these sights may be old hat for some of you. But just like our trip to the California desert earlier this year, this was a chance for us to soak up some new-to-us geography. Why We Vacationed In South Dakota South Dakota is home to lots of epic vistas, charming towns, and outdoor adventures. Continue reading A Summer Trip To South Dakota at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 18:09:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>All New With Nordstrom</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/08/all-new-with-nordstrom/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Outfit Details: Max Mara Top, Slvrlake Jeans, Celine Belt (sold out, similar here) Thank you to Nordstrom for sponsoring this post. As… The post All New With Nordstrom appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 05:00:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best Romance Deals of the Day for August 21, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/the-best-romance-deals-of-the-day-for-august-21-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/romance-deals-collage-for-82124.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>A Foodie Romance, Love in the Highlands, Rebecca Yarros, a Time-Travel Romance, and More in Today's Best Romance Deals</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 16:56:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Choosing the perfect cooler for your adventure: a guide to REI's best options</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/article/choosing-the-perfect-cooler-for-your-adventure-a-guide-to-reis-best-options/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1200x675/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/08/21120123/IMG_7915-Edit.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Commerce Continue reading Choosing the perfect cooler for your adventure: a guide to REI's best options Choosing the perfect cooler for your adventure: a guide to REI's best options originally appeared on Autoblog on Wed, 21 Aug 2024 12:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This payments stock has broken out of a 2-year sideways pattern. Using options to play it</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/21/this-payments-stock-has-broken-out-of-a-2-year-sideways-pattern-using-options-to-play-it.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>The stock finally broke out from its two-year consolidation and triggered a new bullish signal.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 15:38:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Checklist for a Job Search</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/check-list-for-a-job-search/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=check-list-for-a-job-search</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Having a checklist for job search makes sure you have the right equipment and tools to compete. Without having everything you need, you potentially waste a lot of time. While gathering this checklist of items in this order is not required, it is *highly* recommended you do them all. Job Search Checklist – Things You […] The post Checklist for a Job Search appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 09:26:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10 Actions Parents Can Take to Help their Children Be More Resilient in a World of Adversity</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/10-actions-to-help-children-be-more-resilient/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=10-actions-to-help-children-be-more-resilient</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Decades of research points to specific ways parents can build resilience that can help protect children from the challenges of adverse experiences and stress. Strategies include parent-focused tips such as practicing self care, reflecting on one’s own past experiences, and developing emotional control. Additional strategies focus on ways to navigate relationships […] The post 10 Actions Parents Can Take to Help their Children Be More Resilient in a World of Adversity appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 02:36:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biscoff Cookies</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/biscoff-cookies/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Satisfy your sweet tooth with loaded Biscoff Cookies. They are soft and chewy and infused with the flavor of Biscoff…</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>100 Classic Boy Names</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/100-classic-boys-names/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>A friend of mine is pregnant and it’s reminding me how exciting it was to name our own kids. We love traditional names (aka: old-fashioned names, aka classic names) and both of our children are named after our grandparents – one on John’s side and one on my side. So I had fun putting together this list of my favorite 100 classic boy names. They feel established, like they stand the test of time, and can carry special meaning if they’re already names in your family. ALSO IS THERE ANYTHING CUTER THAN BABY SUSPENDERS?!? One interesting thing I found when I was writing this post was that many of the top ten most popular names for boys in 2024 are arguably pretty classic: #1: Liam #2: Noah #3: Oliver #4: James #5: Elijah #6: Mateo #7: Theodore #8: Henry #9: Lucas #10: William But beyond that short list of the most popular boy names this year, there are so many other classic boy names to choose from. Continue reading 100 Classic Boy Names at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 17:55:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>See Through</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/08/see-through/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Outfit Details: Sea Dress, Prada Bag, Loeffler Randall Sandals, Lili Claspe Necklace &amp; Earrings As summer gives way to the crisp beginnings of fall, our… The post See Through appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 05:00:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quirky Family Mystery, Did They Or Didn’t They Mysteries, News + More Mystery &amp; Thrillers!</title><link>https://bookriot.com/quirky-family-mystery-did-they-or-didnt-they-mysteries-news-more-mystery-thrillers/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/a-lighter-skinned-woman-looking-in-a-rear-view-mirror-in-a-car.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>What's your favorite "did they or didn't they do it?" book?</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 16:50:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2025 Dodge Durango SRT Hellcat Silver Bullet continues the Last Call</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/08/21/2025-dodge-durango-srt-hellcat-silver-bullet-continues-the-last-call/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1200x675/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/08/20153141/2025_dodge_durango_rt_20th_anniversary_0061.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Dodge , SUV , Special and Limited Editions , Performance Continue reading 2025 Dodge Durango SRT Hellcat Silver Bullet continues the Last Call 2025 Dodge Durango SRT Hellcat Silver Bullet continues the Last Call originally appeared on Autoblog on Wed, 21 Aug 2024 10:32:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 15:32:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nonfarm payroll growth revised down by 818,000, Labor Department says</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/21/nonfarm-payroll-growth-revised-down-by-818000-labor-department-says.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>The U.S. economy created far fewer jobs than originally reported in the 12-month period through March 2024, the Labor Department reported.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 15:37:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10 Questions To Ask Before Launching Your Job Search</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/questions-to-ask-before-launching-job-search/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=questions-to-ask-before-launching-job-search</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>So this is the year you are finally ready to change jobs. Congratulations! Before you dust off your resume, there are some questions you need to ask before launching your job search. Searching for a job while employed requires you do it under the radar so that your employer doesn’t find out. Some employers have […] The post 10 Questions To Ask Before Launching Your Job Search appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 14:55:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Let Children Choose: Autonomy-Supportive Care for Cognitive Growth</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/autonomy-supportive-care-for-cognitive-growth/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=autonomy-supportive-care-for-cognitive-growth</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Executive function (EF) skills: EF skills are brain-based processes that allow us to remember goals, resist impulses, and think flexibly. Early EF skills matter: Developing EF skills early in life is crucial for various outcomes like social competence, emotion regulation, academic achievement, and keeping out of legal trouble. Parental and caregiver […] The post Let Children Choose: Autonomy-Supportive Care for Cognitive Growth appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 14:29:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cowboy Cornbread Casserole</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/cowboy-cornbread-casserole/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Cowboy Cornbread Casserole is a flavorful, comforting meal that’s so easy to make. Seasoned ground beef, corn, pinto beans, and…</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Best Air Purifying Plants</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/best-air-purifying-plants/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>We love any excuse to buy more plants, and you may have heard they can improve your home’s indoor air quality. But before you blow your paycheck in the name of a healthier home, let’s dive deeper into plants’ air purifying powers. We’ll share which plants we recommend and what benefits you can actually expect from them. We’ve heard for years about how plants act as natural air filters for your home. So let’s dive a little deeper, shall we? 7 Air Purifying Plants If you just came here for a list, our favorite air purifying houseplants are bulleted below. The best part is these are all beautiful, low-maintenance plants. Many also appear on our best low-light indoor plants list too! Dracaena (including Corn Plant ) Snake Plant Aglaonema English Ivy Pothos Bamboo Palm Spider Plant There are certainly more that could be included here, but we narrowed it to the ones that are most often cited by experts AND the plants that we think look best too. Continue reading Best Air Purifying Plants at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 14:15:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amazon Sundays</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/08/amazon-sundays-7-28-24/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Outfit Details: Amazon Top &amp; Skirt, Similar Necklace Welcome to Amazon Sundays, filled with the latest from Amazon that I’m… The post Amazon Sundays appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 05:00:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Historical Fiction Books for Kids</title><link>https://bookriot.com/historical-fiction-books-for-kids/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/partial-cover-of-The-Hundred-Choices-Department-Store-by-Ginger-Park.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>Gather up the kiddos and read about the Silk Road, 1940s Korea, and Hiroshima.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 16:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Armor All 1.5-gallon shop vac is available for its lowest price ever</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/article/this-armor-all-1-5-gallon-shop-vac-is-available-for-its-lowest-price-ever/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1200x675/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/08/21093810/Armor-All-Car.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Commerce Continue reading This Armor All 1.5-gallon shop vac is available for its lowest price ever This Armor All 1.5-gallon shop vac is available for its lowest price ever originally appeared on Autoblog on Wed, 21 Aug 2024 10:20:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 15:20:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>As strength training gets more popular, Peloton and Planet Fitness shift focus</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/08/21/strength-training-demand-fitness-industry-peloton-planet-fitness-ladder.html</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>With more women and young people opting for weights at the gym, both Peloton and Planet Fitness are expanding investments in strength over cardio.</description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 559</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-559/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-559</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Do you understand how recruiters work and how they think? Well, this should help! There’s no magic. Every recruiter has their own set of preferences for sourcing and vetting candidates. But many share tips and insights to give job seekers valuable information. In this week’s summary, you’ll find: Please follow and support the talented experts […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 559 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 12:33:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Children’s digital media exposure as a backdrop for multilingual learning</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/childrens-digital-media-exposure-as-a-backdrop-for-multilingual-learning/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=childrens-digital-media-exposure-as-a-backdrop-for-multilingual-learning</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Multilingual children use digital media regularly, in all their home languages. Digital media use may affect multilingual children’s early language learning by reducing opportunities for back-and-forth conversations with adults. This finding is similar to results of studies of digital media and language learning for children learning only one language. When using […] The post Children’s digital media exposure as a backdrop for multilingual learning appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 20:27:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spaghetti alla Nerano (Stanley Tucci Zucchini Pasta)</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/spaghetti-alla-nerano/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Spaghetti alla Nerano is an unforgettable pasta dish packed with flavor! It has a rich and creamy zucchini sauce infused…</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Weekend In New Orleans With Kids</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/new-orleans-with-kids/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Since our travel guides to Charleston with kids and Palm Springs with kids have elicited requests for more travel ideas with kids, we’re back with an overdue recap of our 3-night trip to New Orleans. We’d never been to The Big Easy before and were impressed by how family-friendly the city is. It’s not all booze, beads, and Bourbon Street! So here’s a look at where we stayed, what we did, and what we’re excited to do next time we go back – because we will definitely go back! The four of us (well, five if you count our chihuahua!) went to NOLA for 3 nights in November of 2022. At the time, our kids were 8 and 12 years old. So unfortunately we can’t vouch for our suggestions being a good fit for toddlers or younger children. Although I’m sure ours would’ve loved the Louisiana Children’s Museum and Storyland playground back in the day! Continue reading A Weekend In New Orleans With Kids at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 17:17:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Finds From Italy</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/08/finds-from-italy/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Outfit Details: Tulsi Coverup, Janessa Leone Hat, Matteau Bikini Top and Bikini Briefs During our summer travels through Italy, I found… The post Finds From Italy appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 05:00:08 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>