<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 08:44:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Housing Market “Stuck” Until 2026 as Insurance Prices Rise, Rents Slow</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-233</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>See Dave, Henry, James, and Kathy at BPCon2024 in Cancún, Mexico! Grab your ticket here! The housing market is “stuck” and may stay that way for the next two years. […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 07:02:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Medal raises $13M as it builds out a contextual AI assistant for desktop</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/11/medal-raises-13m-as-it-builds-out-a-new-ai-platform-for-desktop/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Medal, a startup that is better known for its video game clipping product, just announced that it has raised $13 million at a valuation of $333 million from several investors, including Horizons Ventures, OMERS Ventures, peak6 and Arcadia Investment Partners. The company also unveiled Highlight, a new cross-platform desktop app that acts as a contextual […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 13:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jackson, Mississippi, Wants Curfew Centers to Cut Crime. Here’s What Other Cities Learned.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/09/jackson-mississippi-youth-curfew-centers</link><description>After a teen’s murder, city officials hope a curfew and youth centers will get kids off the street. Young people are skeptical.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 11:00:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>These 11 Markets Used to Be America’s Hot Spots. Now They’ve Gone Cold.</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/11-formerly-hot-markets-that-are-not-so-hot-anymore</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>The pandemic-fueled explosion of growth has waned, and now these real estate hot spots have gotten icy.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 22:30:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alpine Space Ventures close first fund to grow the space economy on both sides of the pond</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/11/alpine-space-ventures-close-first-fund-to-grow-the-space-economy-on-both-sides-of-the-pond/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>When early SpaceX engineer Bulent Altan and long-time investor Joran Voelklein surveyed the European space sector at the end of the 2010s, they were surprised: it looked a whole lot like the beginnings of American NewSpace in the early 2000s, when SpaceX and other companies were just setting up shop. The pair decided to go […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Love Beyond Bars: Miguel and Silvia</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/05/photo-essay-wrongful-conviction-love-story</link><description>While Miguel Solorio did 25 years for a crime he didn’t commit, his wife, Silvia, was right by his side. Here’s their California love story in pictures.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Homebuying Reality Check: College Graduates Can Still Succeed</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/college-graduates-can-still-buy-real-estate-and-succeed</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>In an environment of high rates, high prices, and low wage growth, can new college graduates really succeed with real estate?</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 19:57:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Intel Capital backs AI construction startup that could boost Intel’s own manufacturing prospects</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/11/intel-capital-backs-ai-construction-startup-that-could-boost-intels-own-manufacturing-prospects/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Intel could be giving its burgeoning foundry ambitions a much-needed shot in the arm, as the chip giant’s venture capital arm today revealed that it’s making a “strategic” investment in an Israel- and U.K.-based AI construction startup. Intel Capital is leading a $15 million investment into Buildots, a company that uses AI and computer vision […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Crime Rates and the 2024 Election: What You Need to Know</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/27/trump-and-biden-spar-over-crime-rates-ahead-of-their-debate-what-do-we-really-know</link><description>As crime data again becomes a flashpoint in the presidential campaign, experts push for better national statistics.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>My Rental Burned Down! What I Wish I Knew Before It Happened</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-430</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>You get a call one day from the fire department, telling you, “You’ve had a house fire that’s destroyed your rental property.” What do you do first? Check on the […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 07:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI-powered Regard nabs $61M to find missed illness, boost hospital revenue</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/11/ai-powered-regard-nabs-61m-to-find-missed-illness-boost-hospital-revenue/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>People in tech often say that data is the new oil. That phrase, coined by British mathematician Clive Humby, of course implies that data is valuable. Data about a person’s health can also provide meaningful insights and improve outcomes, but only 3% of patient data is currently used by physicians, according to the World Economic […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Death Row Prisoner’s Parting Interview</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/24/texas-death-row-prisoner-final-interview</link><description>Days before his scheduled execution in Texas, Ramiro Gonzales speaks on faith, legacy — and apologizing to the family of his victim, Bridget Townsend.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Tiny Homes a Good Investment? How a $50,000 Home Pencils Out</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-986</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Are tiny homes a good investment? For just $50,000, you can get a brand new tiny home investment—not even fifteen percent of the average single-family home price in the United […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 07:02:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>EU ends Apple Pay antitrust probe with binding commitments to open up contactless payments</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/11/eu-ends-apple-pay-antitrust-probe-with-binding-commitments-to-open-up-contactless-payments/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The European Union has accepted commitments from Apple over how it operates Apple Pay to settle a long running competition investigation. Commission EVP Margrethe Vestager, who heads up the EU’s competition division, announced the development in a press conference Thursday. Apple has until July 25 to implement changes that will allow developers of rival mobile […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 11:04:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The New Battle Over an Old Institution: Forced Prison Labor</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/22/prison-slavery-forced-labor-lawsuits-bills</link><description>Inside the latest legal and legislative efforts to close state constitutional loopholes that allow slavery as punishment for a crime.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>