<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 12:44:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Implementation Shortfalls Hamstring Factor Strategies</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/01/implementation-shortfalls-hamstring-factor-strategies/</link><description>Smart rebalancing rules help portfolio managers capture more of the return that is inherent in their factor strategies. Concentrating on “priority best” trading improves factor portfolio performance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 11:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Donald Trump just added another $1.8 billion to his Truth Social fortune—on paper</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/01/truth-social-donald-trump-billion-stock/</link><description>He now controls another 36 million shares, almost 65% of the company.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 17:06:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IFRS Accounting Standard Will Support Better Investment Decisions</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/30/ifrs-accounting-standard-will-support-better-investment-decisions/</link><description>IFRS 18 responds to investors' concerns about challenges in comparing companies' financial performance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 11:34:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Japan has had so many bear attacks in the past year it’s turning to AI to act as a warning system</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/01/japan-bear-attacks-ai/</link><description>More than 200 people have been injured.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 16:21:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meir Statman: Your State of Mind Influences Your Investing Success</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/29/meir-statman-your-state-of-mind-influences-your-investing-success/</link><description>Meir Statman shares his insights on the broader aspects of financial well-being and its interconnection with life satisfaction.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 12:58:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chase IHG One Rewards Business Premier card ups its welcome bonus—Ends soon</title><link>https://fortune.com/recommends/credit-cards/chase-ihg-cards-up-their-welcome-bonuses-should-you-apply/</link><description>Chase announced new welcome bonuses for its IHG One Rewards consumer credit cards. New cardholders can earn up to 165,000 bonus points, depending on which card they choose.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 16:21:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: Trailblazers, Heroes, and Crooks</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/26/book-review-trailblazers-heroes-and-crooks/</link><description>Stephen Foerster, CFA, extracts lessons from exceptional episodes in financial history that ordinary investors and seasoned professionals alike can put to profitable use. The bonus is that you'll be entertained from start to finish.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Outdated laws prevent gig economy workers from getting benefits. This pilot program shows the path forward</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/01/gig-economy-worker-benefits-doordash-pennsylvania/</link><description>Benefits for app-based workers can be flexible, portable, and proportional to the hours they put in.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 15:57:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Price Risk? Unpacking the Equity Risk Premium</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/24/what-price-risk-unpacking-the-equity-risk-premium/</link><description>Stocks are a good wager over the long term, on favorable odds. But stocks remain a bet, and investors must grasp how much returns can vary over long time horizons.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bumble, the dating app where women make the first move, is rolling out a feature where men get an ‘opening move’</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/01/bumble-changes-dating-app-women-make-first-opening-move/</link><description>The “opening moves” feature will be an optional one.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 15:39:30 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>