<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 18:05:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Stocks for the Long Run? Setting the Record Straight</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/30/stocks-for-the-long-run-setting-the-record-straight/</link><description>Stocks are a good investment long-term, providing that you dial in your expectations. New historical findings provide a richer, more complete understanding of international returns.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 16:55:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How much you can make as an information security analyst in each state</title><link>https://fortune.com/education/articles/information-security-analyst-salary/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Recommends_information-security-analyst-salary-e1715867702906.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Washington, New York, and Iowa pay top dollar for information security analysts—up to $148,000 in annual salary.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 22:26:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rethinking Retirement Planning Amidst Aging Demographic Frontiers</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/28/rethinking-retirement-planning-amidst-aging-demographic-frontiers/</link><description>Forward-thinking approaches to policy and wealth management are needed to ensure a better financial future across generations and income brackets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 20:32:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New York jury finds Trump guilty on all 34 felony counts in hush-money trial</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/30/donald-trump-guilty-hush-money-stormy-daniels/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2154735028-e1717105217573.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>A New York jury found him guilty of falsifying business records in a scheme to illegally influence the 2016 election through hush money payments to porn actor Stormy Daniels.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 22:11:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: The New World Economy in 5 Trends</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/24/book-review-the-new-world-economy-in-5-trends/</link><description>A diligent economist and an eclectic bookworm serve up an analysis of megatrends that will have the greatest impact on economies and investments: innovation, productivity, climate, multiglobalization, debt, and aging.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 12:22:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Three Black men sue American Airlines, saying they were kicked off their flight after a random complaint about body odor</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/30/american-airlines-sued-black-passengers-body-odor/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2153943827-e1717102554125.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The lawsuit alleges that the men were ejected from the plane "without any valid reason, and solely based on their race."</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 21:58:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Factor Strategies Belong in Your Completion Portfolio Toolkit</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/23/factor-strategies-belong-in-your-completion-portfolio-toolkit/</link><description>Why wouldn't you include factor strategies in your completion portfolio? A review of the two commonly used approaches for managing institutional assets highlights their symbiotic nature.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 19:09:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hopes of a 10-year EV transition are ‘irrational’ pipe dreams because we don’t have enough battery materials—opening up a single copper mine takes 23 years</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/30/electric-vehicles-ev-transition-copper-mining-shortage-research-minerals-metals/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2147921949-e1717100040938.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>An expected copper shortage and mining industry dynamics are threatening to stop the EV transition in its tracks.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 21:36:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>For the Analyst: Peer Benchmarking Methods to Improve Earnings Forecasts</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/21/for-the-analyst-peer-benchmarking-methods-to-improve-earnings-forecasts/</link><description>Peer benchmarking is a vexing task for financial analysts but one that is critical for forecasting earnings. This straightforward measure can help find peers for relative performance, compensation, and valuation benchmarking.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 12:47:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alexander Wang dropped a wild ad featuring doppelgängers for Taylor Swift, Beyoncé, and Kylie Jenner—'this video is diabolical'</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/30/alexander-wang-taylor-swift-beyonce-kylie-jenner-ad-video/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1204546087-e1717100764970.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Among the TikTok stars featured are Paige Niemann, Taylor Madison, and Ashley Leechin, who resemble Ariana Grande, Kylie Jenner, and Taylor Swift.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 21:29:18 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>