<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:28:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Book Riot’s YA Book Deals of the Day for May 11, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/book-riots-ya-book-deals-of-the-day-for-may-11-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Untitled-design-51.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>A Korean folktale retelling, a dark academia mystery, the search for a teen's husband, and more of today's best YA book deals.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Junkyard Gem: 2005 Honda Accord, Hello Kitty Edition</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/11/junkyard-gem-2005-honda-accord-hello-kitty-edition/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/04/24102933/99-2005-Honda-Accord-Hello-Kitty-Edition-in-Colorado-junkyard-photo-by-Murilee-Martin.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Design/Style , Humor , Weird Car News , Honda , Automotive History , Sedan Continue reading Junkyard Gem: 2005 Honda Accord, Hello Kitty Edition Junkyard Gem: 2005 Honda Accord, Hello Kitty Edition originally appeared on Autoblog on Sat, 11 May 2024 12:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Musk's Starlink satellites disrupted by major solar storm</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/11/musks-starlink-satellites-disrupted-by-major-solar-storm.html</link><description>Starlink owns around 60% of the roughly 7,500 satellites orbiting Earth and is a dominant player in satellite internet.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 23:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 553</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-553/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-553</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Tools and technology change rapidly. Yet as wonderful as technology can be, it doesn’t replace the need for human connection through interactions. Keep this in mind as you are searching for a new job. It’s your human connections that often open doors! In this week’s collection of news and tips for job seekers, you’ll find: […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 553 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 12:19:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A case for public preschool: New study reveals preschool benefits to be longer-lasting and substantial</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/benefits-of-public-preschool/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=benefits-of-public-preschool</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Preschool lays a foundation for elementary school students to succeed. In the United States, as children approach kindergarten entry, it is increasingly common for 4-year-olds to be in non-parental group care and education, often in a center- or school-based setting where they can learn alongside peers. For children from low-income communities, […] The post A case for public preschool: New study reveals preschool benefits to be longer-lasting and substantial appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 08:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Thai Chicken Salad</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/thai-chicken-salad/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Crunchy and bright, this Thai Chicken Salad with creamy peanut dressing is bursting with flavor, texture and deliciousness! Prep it in…</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/how-to-remove-wallpaper/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Wallpaper has made a big comeback as a trendy home design choice. But despite its resurgence, there are still plenty of us dealing with dingy, dated, or downright ugly old wallpaper we don’t want. In our old home, we had to remove wallpaper in so many rooms: the kitchen, the dining room, the foyer, and two different bathrooms! As we traveled from room to room removing wallpaper, we tested 4 different methods, and today we’ll share what we learned. Removing wallpaper doesn’t require special tools or lots of money. It’s a totally doable project for any homeowner. However, it can be a tedious process that can take elbow grease and patience, depending on the size of your room and the stubbornness of your wallpaper. But having removed several rooms worth of decades-old wallpaper, we can confidently say it’s worth the effort! You can also check out more before and afters of our once-wallpapered rooms. Continue reading How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:21:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amazon Home Refresh Tips</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/amazon-home-refresh-tips/</link><description>Embrace the mid-spring refresh with Amazon and give your home a vibrant makeover for the season. Amazon makes it easy… The post Amazon Home Refresh Tips appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 05:00:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Riot’s Deals of the Day for May 11, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/book-riots-deals-of-the-day-for-may-11-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/deals-051124.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>A twisty and unexpected thriller, a long-forgotten queen, a post-apocalyptic journey of survival, and more of today's best book deals.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chinese car exports jump 38% in April</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/11/chinese-car-exports-jump-38-in-april/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/crop/5272x2966+0+178/resize/800x450!/format/jpg/quality/85/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/10124149/cars_parked_at_the_international_cargo_terminal.jpeg</image_url><description>Filed under: Green , Electric Continue reading Chinese car exports jump 38% in April Chinese car exports jump 38% in April originally appeared on Autoblog on Sat, 11 May 2024 11:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Donald Trump shuts down rumors about considering Nikki Haley for vice president</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/11/donald-trump-shuts-down-nikki-haley-vp-rumors.html</link><description>Donald Trump has several names on his VP shortlist already, including Sen. Tim Scott, Rep. Elise Stefanik and Gov. Doug Burgum.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 18:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 552</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-552/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-552</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>When you are searching for a job, you will inevitably run into unexpected scenarios. You will have questions, experience self-doubt and even feel discouraged. You’ll also experience great wins, meet wonderful people and discover new things about yourself. That’s the roller-coaster of job search. Consider Summary Sunday your resource for getting questions answered and showing […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 552 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 11:37:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fathers’ views on family and work after COVID-19 lockdowns</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/fathers-views-on-family-and-work-after-covid-19-lockdowns/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fathers-views-on-family-and-work-after-covid-19-lockdowns</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Fathers often want to be present for their children and contribute to household tasks, but they can lack opportunities and confidence; they may see themselves as “helpers” instead of parents. Australian fathers in our small study reported that they spent more time with their children during the COVID-19 lockdowns, and they […] The post Fathers’ views on family and work after COVID-19 lockdowns appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Meal Plan #4</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/weekly-menu-plan-4/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Take advantage of this weekly meal plan that has all the favorite recipes that families love! It is so easy…</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aglaonema Plant – Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/aglaonema-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Aglaonema, also called the Chinese Evergreen Plant, is an easy-care houseplant that lives happily in many lighting conditions – even a dark corner of our daughter’s room. There are dozens of different Aglaonema varieties, most with large tropical foliage and colors ranging from silvery-green, red, and even vibrant pink. They’re also tough to kill, so they’re a great option for forgetful plant owners or anyone looking for an easy win in the plant department. These truly have been very low maintenance for us. We purchased our two Aglaonemas (pronounced ag-lee-oh-neem-ah ) to put atop our daughter’s closet. It’s sometimes hard to distinguish different varieties, but we believe that’s an Aglaonema Silver (right) and either a Candy Cane or Princess Silver Queen (left). Aglaonema Quick Facts Here’s what you need to know about your Aglaonema at a glance: Latin name : Aglaonema is the genus under which there are 21 recognized species . Continue reading Aglaonema Plant – Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:47:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shell Season</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/shell-season/</link><description>Spring welcomes the captivating allure of shell season. As nature awakens and warmth spreads, ocean treasures inspire wardrobe choices. This… The post Shell Season appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:58:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Fall Became The Big Season in Book Publishing</title><link>https://bookriot.com/today-in-books-may-10-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Screenshot-2024-05-10-at-11.09.05 AM.png</image_url><description>How Fall Became The Big Season in Publishing, SHOGUN Season 2 news, a RED, WHITE, &amp; ROYAL BLUE sequel, and Amazon's Big Book Sale is Live...and Good.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 19:14:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Marcus Armstrong honors cancer patients with special livery for Indy Grand Prix</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/11/marcus-armstrong-honors-cancer-patients-with-special-livery-for-indy-grand-prix/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/10123734/indycar_indianapolis_auto_racing-2.jpeg</image_url><description>Filed under: Motorsports Continue reading Marcus Armstrong honors cancer patients with special livery for Indy Grand Prix Marcus Armstrong honors cancer patients with special livery for Indy Grand Prix originally appeared on Autoblog on Sat, 11 May 2024 10:30:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Do this 1 thing to curb your kid's anxiety today, says researcher behind 'The Anxious Generation'</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/11/do-this-1-thing-to-curb-your-kids-anxiety-today.html</link><description>If you want to make a change today that will positively impact your child's health start by talking to your kids' friends' parents.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>While a little competition in the workplace might help bring out the best in everyone involved, an atmosphere rooted in envy, fear, or jealousy can do the exact opposite. This post will help you recognize signs that your coworker is threatened by you, and help you navigate the situation. 1. They Don’t Want You Involved […] The post 10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:07:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Strong Latine Identity Supports U.S. Latine Children’s Well-Being</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/a-strong-latine-identity-supports-u-s-latine-childrens-well-being/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=a-strong-latine-identity-supports-u-s-latine-childrens-well-being</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key Takeaways for caregivers Children tend to have better health and well-being when they have a strong ethnic identity (affinity and adoption of ethnicity-based self-concept). A traditional Latine cultural value (familismo) that emphasizes family bonds is also associated with better developmental outcomes. Caregivers can support the development of U.S. Latine children (and possibly other children […] The post A Strong Latine Identity Supports U.S. Latine Children’s Well-Being appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 03:03:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Garlic Balsamic Mushrooms</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/garlic-balsamic-mushrooms/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>The depth of flavors in these garlic balsamic mushrooms is next level! Sauteed mushrooms are coated in a sweet balsamic…</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Corn Plant – Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/corn-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Corn plants ( Dracaena fragrans ) are popular low-maintenance houseplants you’ve probably seen at the nursery, home improvement store, or doctor’s office. I even had one in my college dorm room! You can recognize them by their spear-shaped leaves and woody, cane-line trunks that can grow up to 6 feet tall indoors. But did you know there are several varieties of corn plants? We didn’t! Heck, we didn’t even realize some of our smaller houseplants were in the same corn plant family! Currently, we own two smaller varieties of corn plants, pictured above. The one on the left is a Dracaena Limelight ( Dracaena fragrans ‘Limelight’ ) and the taller plant is a Draecanea Dorado ( Dracaena fragrans ‘Dorado’ ). We actually have several limelights around because we love their vibrant color on shelves, tabletops, and windowsills. Corn Plant Quick Facts Latin name : Dracaena fragrans Common names : Corn plant, cornstalk plant, false palms Light : Bright, indirect light but can tolerate lower-light conditions Watering : Keep soil moist, but not soggy. Continue reading Corn Plant – Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 17:37:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Discovering My Avaline Favorites</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/discovering-my-avaline-favorites/</link><description>Thank you to Avaline for sponsoring this post. Spring symbolizes fresh starts and cleaner living. In my quest to align… The post Discovering My Avaline Favorites appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:50:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paperbacks and Hardcovers On Sale On Amazon for 50% Off</title><link>https://bookriot.com/amazon-book-sale-may-10-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/amazon-books-on-sale.png</image_url><description>Emily Henry, Toni Morrison, J.R.R. Tolkien, Dr. Seuss and more books on sale for 50% off today!</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 19:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Colton Herta hopes to protect narrow points lead through IndyCar's biggest month</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/11/colton-herta-hopes-to-protect-narrow-points-lead-through-indycars-biggest-month/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/crop/3280x1845+0+57/resize/800x450!/format/jpg/quality/85/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/10122835/indycar_indianapolis_auto_racing1.jpeg</image_url><description>Filed under: Motorsports Continue reading Colton Herta hopes to protect narrow points lead through IndyCar's biggest month Colton Herta hopes to protect narrow points lead through IndyCar's biggest month originally appeared on Autoblog on Sat, 11 May 2024 10:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Photos from across the globe show spectacular displays of the aurora borealis</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/11/the-aurora-borealis-in-pictures-.html</link><description>The aurora borealis is typically only visible in high north latitudes, but this time, it stretched as far south as Louisiana.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 16:44:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 551</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-551/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-551</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Job search requires writing and marketing skills. It also requires strong verbal communication. If these skills are not part of your normal work function, you’ll want some help. That’s what this week’s Summary Sunday is all about. There’s no doubt that LinkedIn is one of THE most powerful tools in your career toolbox. It contains […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 551 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 11:37:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Children caught between highly conflicted divorced parents at greater risk of mental health problems</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/children-caught-between-conflicted-divorced-parents/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=children-caught-between-conflicted-divorced-parents</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Interparental conflict after divorce escalates the risk of mental health problems in children and adolescents. Elevated levels of conflict between parents can also induce fear and worry in children about their future and whether they will be adequately taken care of. In turn, a greater fear of abandonment puts children at […] The post Children caught between highly conflicted divorced parents at greater risk of mental health problems appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 08:59:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Creamy Cucumber Salad</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/creamy-cucumber-salad/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Creamy Cucumber Salad is a delicious and refreshing side dish. All it takes is a handful of fresh simple ingredients…</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Using Solid Stain In Our Outdoor Shower</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/solid-deck-stain-outdoor-shower/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>In all of our years of DIYing, I don’t think we’ve ever used a solid stain before. But we recently had a project that was *perfectly* suited for it and, well, solid stain quickly won us over. It was recommended by a professional house painter to us, specifically because he thought it would be great for our outdoor shower. And we found it easy to apply, it gave us great coverage, and we got an even-better-than-we-expected result (which is always the best kind!). So here’s a post that covers all the pros &amp; cons and hows &amp; whys of solid stain. As you can see, the “canvas” for this staining project was our outdoor shower. We gave it a mini-makeover right after moving in, but we knew it may need more attention and care down the line. Honestly, we dreaded the task of stripping and restaining it – so many nooks &amp; crannies! Continue reading Using Solid Stain In Our Outdoor Shower at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 17:46:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spring Slumber</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/spring-slumber/</link><description>In the gentle embrace of mid-spring, there’s a delightful charm in refreshing my sleepwear collection. I tend to gravitate towards… The post Spring Slumber appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 20:00:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Riot’s Deals of the Day for May 10, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/book-riots-deals-of-the-day-for-may-10-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/collage-ofdeals-for-5-10-2024.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>Viola Davis' Memoir, Lovecraft Country, E.L. James, Korean Independence, and More of Today's Best Book Deals</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 18:05:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nissan reports 92% jump in profit as sales surge</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/11/nissan-reports-92-jump-in-profit-as-sales-surge/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/10125027/japan-automobile-climate-energy.jpeg</image_url><description>Filed under: Earnings/Financials , Nissan Continue reading Nissan reports 92% jump in profit as sales surge Nissan reports 92% jump in profit as sales surge originally appeared on Autoblog on Sat, 11 May 2024 09:30:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This inflation-focused ETF may be in a sweet spot</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/11/inflation-etf-may-be-in-a-sweet-spot-even-if-fed-cuts-rates.html</link><description>Horizon Kinetics' James Davolos thinks his firm's inflation-focused ETF is "ideally positioned" for gains this year.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>15 Ways to Own Digital Terrain</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/15-ways-to-own-digital-terrain/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=15-ways-to-own-digital-terrain</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>It is now no longer optional…you must have an online presence! Your career stability and your job search demand it. Here are some tips to help you begin claiming digital terrain and brand it with your unique messaging! Why Should You Own Digital Terrain? You need to stake a claim by owning turf on the […] The post 15 Ways to Own Digital Terrain appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 15:56:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>“Why do they feel sad?” Shared book reading reveals how children learn about others’ emotions</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/shared-book-reading/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=shared-book-reading</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers: It is good for children to identify the emotions of others in conversations with caregivers because it scaffolds their ability to identify others’ emotions on their own. Children who use more emotion talk in parent-child conversations about emotions are more likely to have higher emotion knowledge one year later. Parents can […] The post “Why do they feel sad?” Shared book reading reveals how children learn about others’ emotions appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 08:19:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Beginner’s Guide to Baking Bread</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/beginners-guide-to-baking-bread/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>You want to make bread, but where do you start? My beginner’s guide to baking bread is here to save…</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ZZ Plant – Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/zz-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>The ZZ plant is another one of our favorite low-maintenance houseplants. They’re easy to care for, hard to kill, and always look full &amp; leafy. They’ve even earned the nickname “Eternity Plant” because they’re practically indestructible! That’s why they’re a top choice for commercial spaces, doctor’s offices, and busy homes like ours. Don’t you love a house plant you can forget about? ZZ plants are sold in a variety of sizes, meaning they’re great for shelves, tabletops, and small surfaces as well as larger statements on the floor. We have some that are over 3 feet tall with their pots! ZZ Plant Quick Facts Here’s what you need to know about your ZZ plant at a glance: Latin name : Zamioculcas zamiifolia Plant family : Araceae or Arums, which includes Philodendron , Alocasia, Aglaonema, Monstera , and Peace Lily Common name s: ZZ plant, Zanzibar Gem, Zuzu plant, Emerald Palm, Eternity plant Native to : East Africa Light : Medium indirect light, but is also low-light tolerant Watering : Every 2-3 weeks during its growing season Soil : Standard potting mix as long as it drains well Ideal Humidity : Average household humidity, ideally 40-50% Ideal Temperature : 65°F to 75°F Cold Hardiness : USDA Zones 9b-11 What Is A ZZ Plant? Continue reading ZZ Plant – Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 19:36:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coral Crush</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/coral-crush/</link><description>Outfit Details: Sir Top &amp; Skirt (also love the dress version), Loro Piana Hat, Prada Sunglasses Spring welcomes the delightful hue of coral, a color that perfectly… The post Coral Crush appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 05:00:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>