<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 06:58:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Macon Some Changes: SPHL’s Mayhem Unveil New Suite of Logos</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/01/macon-some-changes-sphls-mayhem-unveil-new-suite-of-logos/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Primary logo once again depicts a Viking, only this time just the head with a red beard and eyebrows and wearing a shiny silver horned helmet</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 23:36:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cardi B Announces She's Pregnant with Third Baby On Heels of Divorce News</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/01/cardi-b-pregnant-third-baby-after-filing-divorce-offset/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Cardi B is having another baby -- something she just announced online ... this hours after she filed for divorce from Offset. The rapper broke the news Thursday -- posting a photo of herself and her exposed belly on IG, and added a lengthy caption…</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 06:58:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Olympic Rings: Their Origin, History, and Meaning</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/01/the-olympic-rings-their-origin-history-and-meaning/other/olympics/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Olympic rings are synonymous with the peak of international sports achievement. Those five interlaced circles of equal size, each a different colour, absolutely dominate the sporting landscape around the globe for two straight weeks before vanishing as quickly as they appeared, hiding away until the next games, usually around</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 20:10:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Salma Hayek Rings In August With Bikini Thirst Trap</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/01/salma-hayek-bikini-thirst-trap-pool/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Salma Hayek is ringing in a new month with a good old-fashioned thirst trap ... and ya gotta see how she's looking these days in a two-piece swimsuit. The actress just shared a mini, poolside photoshoot on her social media ... and she's busting out…</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 06:58:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chicago Cubs to wear Motorola Ad on Uniform</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/01/chicago-cubs-to-wear-motorola-ad-on-uniform/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Chicago Cubs today became the 23rd Major League Baseball team to add an advertisement to their jersey sleeve, announcing that Motorola’s logo will live there for the foreseeable future. Chicago’s announcement comes just one day after the Philadelphia IBX Phillies announced their own jersey ad. The rather large patch</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 15:46:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Swifties' Fundraiser for Families of UK Stabbing Victims Nears Half A Million</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/01/taylor-swift-fans-fundraiser-uk-stabbing-victims-families/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>A fundraiser for the families of the 3 young girls who died at the Taylor Swift-themed dance party in Southport, England is picking up some major steam -- hitting almost half a million bucks. Cristina Jones and Holly Goldring from the Taylor Swift…</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 06:58:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Green Bay Packers Reveal White Alternate Helmets</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/01/green-bay-packers-reveal-white-alternate-helmets/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Confirming our report from April, the Green Bay Packers have revealed their new white alternate helmets, which will debut against the Houston Texans on Oct. 20.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 14:18:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kendall Jenner Says She's Cried Herself to Sleep Over Course of Modeling Career</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/01/kendall-jenner-remembers-loneliness-cried-herself-sleep-modeling/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Kendall Jenner's getting real about loneliness ... saying months of traveling around modeling left her in a dark place -- filled with tears just before drifting off to sleep. The reality star-turned-mogul opened up during a convo on Emma…</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 06:58:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MLB Jersey Ads by Team</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/31/mlb-jersey-ads-by-team/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>On April 1, 2022, Major League Baseball announced its teams would be permitted to wear advertisements on their in-game uniforms starting with Opening Day in 2023. As of August 1, 2024, twenty-three (77%) of the thirty MLB teams have advertisements on their uniforms. These ad patches can only be worn</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 20:58:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chris Paul Sells California Mansion For Over $15 Million, Saltwater Pool &amp; Home Theater!</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/01/chris-paul-california-mansion-house-sold/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Chris Paul unloaded his California mansion -- a massive estate with awesome amenities including a saltwater pool and home theater -- for over $15 million! The future Hall of Famer, who last played for the Warriors before signing with the San…</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 06:58:06 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>