<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 07:39:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Seeing Greene: Insurance and Taxes Killed My Cash Flow, Should I Sell?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-965</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Want a quicker way to buy rental properties? One that takes less cash, less time, and is beginner-friendly? Then you’re in the right place! In this Seeing Greene, we’re talking […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 07:02:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WndrCo officially gets into venture capital with fresh $450M across two funds</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/04/jeffrey-katzenberg-wndrco-450m-fund-venture-capital/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Jeffrey Katzenberg and Sujay Jaswa, along with three general partners, manage $1.5 billion in assets today through their Build, Venture and Seed strategies. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In St. Louis, a Racial Disparity in Whose Killings Get Solved</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/04/st-louis-police-unsolved-murders-race</link><description>In the past decade, police solved fewer than half of the homicide cases with Black victims and two-thirds of the cases with White ones.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Federal Experts Talk Bird Flu ‘What Ifs’ in WebMD Live Event</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/cold-and-flu/news/20240516/federal-experts-talk-bird-flu-what-ifs?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>WebMD brought together experts from four federal agencies to talk prevention, monitoring, and what the “what ifs” of bird flu might look like.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:50:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coast FI at 24 and a $99K Net Worth Thanks to a Few Years of Pure Hustle</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-534</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Could Coast FI be your BEST path to financial independence? Maybe you don’t want to retire early—not yet, at least. Hustle for a few years, invest your money, and watch […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 07:01:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Storyblok raises $80M to bring more AI into its ‘headless’ CMS aimed at non-technical people</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/04/storyblok-raises-80m-to-bring-more-ai-into-its-headless-cms-aimed-at-non-technical-people/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>If content is king, then the focus today is on how the king is expanding the empire: print and traditional media first got augmented by websites, and now websites are being augmented by an exponential landscape of apps, social media platforms, new kinds of screens, and content created not by humans, but by, artificial intelligence. […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 12:13:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How We Reported on Homicide Investigations in St. Louis</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/03/st-louis-police-unsolved-murders-methods</link><description>Getting and interpreting homicide clearance data involved litigation, complex analysis and patience.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What’s Next in Health Care for Older Adults: Questions and Answers With John Whyte, MD</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/blog-aging-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>As WebMD’s chief medical officer, John Whyte, MD, is in a unique position to see both the current state of medical care for America’s older adults and the way things are trending for the future. We asked him to share his insight on a few topics, along with a bit of advice.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:29:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Malta is a Hot, Stunning Island Market in Europe—Here’s How to Invest There</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/investing-in-malta-real-estate</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>While golden visas are sunsetting or significantly changing around Europe, there are still a few opportunities for Americans to buy international real estate, to live in or rent out, at […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 19:27:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘Star Wars’ lasers and waterfalls of molten salt: How Xcimer plans to make fusion power happen</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/04/star-wars-lasers-and-waterfalls-of-molten-salt-how-xcimer-plans-to-make-fusion-power-happen/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The startup has been pursuing a ground-up redesign of a well-understood technology. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why 1,000 Homicides in St. Louis Remain Unsolved</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/03/st-louis-police-unsolved-murders</link><description>In one of America’s deadliest cities, police have struggled to solve killings due to staffing shortages, shoddy detective work and lack of community trust.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Get the Care You Need in a COVID-19 World</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/covid-senior-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>What to expect at the doctor’s office, hospitals, and long-term care facilities, the future of telemedicine, and how to get the best care during COVID-19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 19:50:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Preferred Equity is an Alternative Asset Class You Can Buy in Real Estate Right Now—These Are the Four Types</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/four-types-of-preferred-equity-and-how-to-evaluate-each</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>“You’re investing in preferred equity? No thanks—I don’t invest in rescue capital!” I’ve heard this comment from prospective investors in different forms more than a few times in the past […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 19:16:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Travel app Sékr wants to help you plan your next road trip with its new AI tool</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/04/travel-app-sekr-wants-to-help-you-plan-your-next-road-trip-with-its-new-ai-tool/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Sékr, a startup that offers a mobile app for outdoor enthusiasts and campers, is launching a new AI tool for planning road trips. The new tool, called Copilot, is available on the startup’s updated website and app, which is used by more than 100,000 users. Sékr was founded in 2016 with the goal of helping […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Abortion’s Legal Landscape Post-Roe is Causing Fear and Confusion</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/01/abortion-supreme-court-roe-dobbs</link><description>We spoke with seven reproductive rights organizations — here’s what we found.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Personal Shopper: A Savvy Black Entrepreneur Guides You to Eczema-Friendly Clothes, Creams, Cosmetics, and More</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/savvy-black-entrepreneur-guides-eczema-friendly-clothes-creams-cosmetics?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>A savvy black entrepreneur guides you on an eczema-friendly shopping spree.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:54:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Much Should a State’s Landlord-Tenant Laws Affect Your Real Estate Investing Strategy?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/how-changing-landlord-tenant-laws-could-impact-your-real-estate-strategy</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>If you are a new investor with limited capital, having the misfortune of renting to a bad tenant in a tenant-friendly state can cripple you financially and put you off […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 18:47:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ChatGPT is down for some, OpenAI is working on a fix</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/04/chatgpt-is-down-for-several-users-openai-is-working-on-a-fix/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>OpenAI's chatbot ChatGPT has been down for several users across the globe for the last few hours. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 10:31:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I Recorded a Whole Hip-Hop Album on a Death Row Telephone</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/31/north-carolina-death-row-rapper-book-excerpt</link><description>In this new book excerpt, incarcerated rapper Alim “RRome Alone” Braxton describes his early attempts to record vocals over a phone in the dayroom.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Behind the Spike in Colorectal Cancer Among Young Americans</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/colorectal-cancer/news/20240515/behind-the-spike-in-colorectal-cancer-cases?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Colorectal cancer cases increased a whopping 333% among 15- to 19-year-olds and 185% among 20- to 24-year-olds from 1999 to 2020.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:59:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>