<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 07:27:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Investment Manager Selection Is Hotting Up. Are You Ready for the Tough Questions?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/25/investment-manager-selection-is-hotting-up-are-you-ready-for-the-tough-questions/</link><description>Investment managers are being caught off guard by tougher questions from an increasingly sophisticated allocator market. Are you prepared for your next beauty parade?</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 03:17:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>With 99 days to go, Trump’s camp is suddenly afraid that victory is slipping away</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/07/29/99-days-to-go-trump-camp-suddenly-afraid-victory-slipping-away/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/AP24210622885334.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>“The Democrats now have a candidate who can speak, who can attack. They have a weapon," said Republican National Committee member Henry Barbour. “They have a path.”</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 12:04:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Measuring Corporate Impact: The Gold Is in the Details</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/24/measuring-corporate-impact-the-gold-is-in-the-details/</link><description>Do the products and services of the companies you invest in create negative or positive material outcomes?</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 12:09:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Italy’s prime minister Meloni vows to reset relations with China and signs a three-year action plan in the midst of an EU-China trade war</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/07/29/italys-prime-minister-giorgia-meloni-vows-to-reset-relations-with-china-signs-three-year-action-plan-in-midst-of-eu-china-trade-war/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/GettyImages-2163686164-e1722249877650.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Her five-day visit comes several months after Italy dropped out of China's Belt and Road Initiative, a policy implemented by Chinese leader Xi Jinping, to develop global infrastructure power.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 11:56:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is Widespread Crypto Adoption Inevitable?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/22/is-widespread-crypto-adoption-inevitable/</link><description>New technologies always face resistance, but demographic shifts imply there is a fierce tailwind behind crypto adoption, politically, economically, and financially.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 12:38:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fed officials expected to cut rates only once in 2024 but now the market is betting on 3 cuts this year</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/07/29/fed-officials-expected-cut-rates-once-2024-market-betting-3-cuts-this-year/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/AP24208808911985-e1722249923104.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>A rate reduction this fall — the first since the pandemic — would amount to a momentous shift and a potential boost to the economy.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 11:55:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: Shocks, Crises, and False Alarms</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/19/book-review-shocks-crises-and-false-alarms/</link><description>Carlsson-Szlezak and Swartz attempt to add fresh thinking on framing macro shocks that may often prove to be false alarms. Any general reader will obtain some key fresh insights with this work, and CFA charterholders will be offered an alternative to the conventional Wall Street approach to macro discussions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 13:06:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Swiss pharma giant Roche is ‘fast-tracking’ development of an experimental Wegovy challenger pill for weight loss</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/07/29/swiss-pharma-giant-roche-fast-tracking-development-experimental-wegovy-challenger-pill-weight-loss-obesity/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/GettyImages-1968671907-e1722248165349.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Roche is working on bringing its weight-loss medications to patients "faster than anticipated,” making it yet another contender in the weight-loss drug market.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 11:45:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Preserving the Dollar: The Role of CBDCs in Securing Economic Stability for Future Generations</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/16/preserving-the-dollar-the-role-of-cbdcs-in-securing-economic-stability-for-future-generations/</link><description>As financial systems evolve, preserving the US dollar's dominance will require skillful policy management and the integration of cutting-edge technologies.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:24:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden presents Supreme Court overhaul that would let president appoint a justice every 2 years to 18-year terms</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/07/29/biden-supreme-court-overhaul-president-appoint-justice-18-year-terms/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/AP24210583134926-e1722248762959.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>He also wants Congress to establish a code of ethics for justices that would require justices to disclose gifts, refrain from public political activity and recuse themselves when they or their spouses have conflicts of interest.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 11:28:54 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>