<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 01:04:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Report: CFL’s Saskatchewan Roughriders to Add Fourth Uniform in 2024</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/27/report-cfls-saskatchewan-roughriders-to-add-fourth-uniform-in-2024/football/</link><description>Riders reportedly adding uniform that's predominantly a darker shade of green than usual; helmet to feature logo filed with Canadian trademark office in 2022</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 18:13:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sonny Vaccaro Says Caitlin Clark Deserved Michael Jordan-Esque Nike Deal</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/27/sonny-vaccaro-caitlin-clark-deserve-michael-jordan-nike-deal/</link><description>Sonny Vaccaro says he believes Caitlin Clark could have gotten a much better deal from Nike -- telling TMZ Sports he's sure the former Iowa superstar could've inked a pact similar to the one Michael Jordan got back in the day. The shoe industry…</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 01:04:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Madison Mallards declare, we are the Wurst</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/27/madison-mallards-declare-we-are-the-wurst/baseball/</link><description>Fresh off the successful unveiling of their Chris Farley–inspired Madison Motivational Speakers alternate identity, the collegiate summer level Madison Mallards unveiled a second temporary rebrand based on a meaty Wisconsin classic. The team will play one game as the Wisconsin Wurst for one game this summer. The identity is based</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 17:41:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Frank Grillo Says Sylvester Stallone Never Insulted 'Tulsa King' Extras</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/27/frank-grillo-sylvester-stallone-not-insult-tulsa-king-extras-craig-zisk-casting-director/</link><description>Frank Grillo's standing up for Sylvester Stallone ... saying Sly never insulted any extras on the "Tulsa King" set -- and the casting supervisor's lying because she didn't do her job. We caught up with Grillo -- who's starring in 'TK' season 2 --…</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 01:04:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Carolina Disco Turkeys change tune, to play as Yacht Rockers</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/27/carolina-disco-turkeys-change-tune-to-play-as-yacht-rockers/baseball/</link><description>The Carolina Disco Turkeys will trade their bell bottoms, polyester, and sparkly sequins for salmon polo shirts, ascots, and captain’s hats for one game this summer. The team announced this week that they’ll play as the Yacht Rockers, changing the vibe in the ballpark from Stayin’ Alive to Sailing. Yacht</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 15:38:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Girthmasterr Would Consider Yeezy Porn, Wants To Buy Mom A House</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/27/girthmasterr-consider-yeezy-porn-kanye-west-collab-mom-house/</link><description>Kanye West's Yeezy Porn has at least one famous OnlyFans star ready to talk turkey ... 'cause Girthmasterr says he's a big fan -- and, if the star calls, he'll certainly listen. The big-time porn star says Kanye's hit song, "Hey Mama," inspired…</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 01:04:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2024 MLB Armed Forces Day Caps Revealed</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/26/2024-mlb-armed-forces-day-caps-revealed/baseball/</link><description>Major League Baseball and New Era have released their Armed Forces Day ballcaps collection, to be worn across the league over the May 17-18-19 weekend. This year’s caps, crowns, buttons, and visors are black for every team. Each team’s typical cap logo is on the front but re-coloured army green</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 00:28:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Britney Spears Settles with Jamie, Gets No Money, Pays His Attorney's Fees</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/26/britney-spears-settles-dad-jamie-spears-money-attorneys-fees/</link><description>Britney Spears has settled her legal dispute with her dad, Jamie Spears, and in a stunning turn of events, Jamie isn't paying Britney a cent, but Britney is paying Jamie's legal bills ... TMZ has learned. Sources with direct knowledge tell TMZ ...…</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 01:04:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MLB Announces Return of Players’ Weekend in 2024, Custom Player Caps</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/26/mlb-announces-return-of-players-weekend-in-2024/baseball/</link><description>Major League Baseball is bringing back its Players’ Weekend this season, which will be held August 16-18, 2024, focusing on the players’ personalized gear. It’s the first time MLB will host its Players’ Weekend since 2019. As part of this year’s celebration, players will wear each player’s uniform number on</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 16:16:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bill Maher Says Many Pro-Palestinian Protestors Are Misguided Narcissists</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/27/bill-maher-pro-palestine-demonstrators-college-campuses-anti-israel-hamas/</link><description>Bill Maher came in hot Friday night, blasting college anti-Israel Protesters as self-involved, ill-informed, and mostly out-of-work narcissists. The 'Real Time' host lit into protesters who are blocking roads and bridges, along with those…</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 01:04:15 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>