<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 14:41:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Why the New T+1 Settlement Cycle Matters: A Global Index Provider’s Perspective</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/14/why-the-new-t1-settlement-cycle-matters-a-global-index-providers-perspective/</link><description>Shorter settlement periods are meant to protect market participants. But the new T+1 settlement cycle for US equities may have undesirable knock-on effects for financial market participants around the world, including index fund managers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 16:54:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jerome Powell says it’s ‘different this time’—and Americans and their mortgage rates are a key reason why</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/14/jerome-powell-economy-different-this-time-housing-mortgage-rates-inflation/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/AP24135552031795-e1715711718108.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>But the Fed chair "wouldn't call it hot," saying the wholesale inflation report was "sort of mixed."</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:38:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Leveraging AI to Identify and Predict Financial Crises</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/13/leveraging-ai-to-identify-and-predict-financial-crises/</link><description>Despite some current limitations, AI stands to offer significant advantages versus traditional approaches to identifying and predicting financial crises.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 14:39:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Florida’s migrant farming community jolted by bus crash that kills 8, injures dozens more</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/14/florida-bus-crash-migrant-farmers-8-dead/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/AP24135586923586.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Florida farms employ more H-2A workers than any other state, about 50,000 a year, according to the Florida Fruit &amp; Vegetable Association.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:29:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Your Portfolio Should Include Scarce Assets</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/10/why-your-portfolio-should-include-scarce-assets/</link><description>Portfolios that include both productive and scarce assets can deliver similar performance to the S&amp;P 500 with less risk than those that hold only productive assets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:34:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rich Gen Xers are outpacing baby boomers in buying vacation homes</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/14/housing-market-outlook-vacation-homes-housing-costs-redfin/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1144619544-e1715708934254.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Interest in second homes hasn’t been this low in almost a decade, according to Redfin.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:17:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coiled Tight: Smaller Companies Are Primed for Outperformance</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/08/coiled-tight-smaller-companies-are-primed-for-outperformance/</link><description>Small-cap companies are poised for a rebound. The sector is best approached through an active investment strategy where expertise and a deep understanding of the individual businesses and their risk-and-reward characteristics are necessary for success.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:40:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘Judge Judy’ sues National Enquirer parent company over misattributed quote in Menendez Brothers story</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/14/judge-judy-sues-national-enquirer-parent-company-menendez-brothers/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/AP24134678083837.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>“When you fabricate stories about me in order to make money for yourselves with no regard for the truth or the reputation I've spent a lifetime cultivating, it's going to cost you."</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:15:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Investment Returns Are NOT Random</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/07/investment-returns-are-not-random/</link><description>Are investment returns random across time as Burton Malkiel suggests in his book, A Random Walk Down Wall Street? There is notable disagreement on this topic. This research finds that practitioners may need to rethink their portfolio optimization routines.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:22:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Harvard protesters voluntarily withdraw after administration agrees to discuss endowment concerns</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/14/harvard-israel-gaza-middle-east-protests-divestment-endowment/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/AP24135530618360-e1715710080392.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Harvard interim President Alan Garber agreed to pursue a meeting between protesters and university officials regarding the students’ questions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:12:43 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>