<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from multiple RSS sources, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 23:55:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Google lays off workers, Tesla cans its Supercharger team and UnitedHealthcare reveals security lapses</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/04/google-lays-off-workers-tesla-cans-its-supercharger-team-and-unitedhealthcare-reveals-security-lapses/</link><description>Welcome, folks, to Week in Review (WiR), TechCrunch’s regular newsletter that recaps the week that was in tech. This edition’s a tad bittersweet for me — it’ll be my last (for a while, anyway). Soon, I’ll be shifting my attention to a new AI-focused newsletter, which I’m super thrilled about. Stay tuned! Now, on with […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 21:15:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weinstein Ruling Poses Quandary: Can #MeToo Coexist With Protections for Defendants?</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/04/sex-crimes-weinstein-me-too</link><description>Proving sex crimes often requires evidence that is generally excluded to protect the rights of the accused.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Normal Aging Process: Changes, Memory, Eyesight, Hearing, and More</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/normal-aging-changes-and-symptoms?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Curious if your body’s aging is normal? WebMD discusses healthy and normal signs of aging.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 14:30:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Human composting and timber marketplaces: talking “industrial” VC with investor Dayna Grayson</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/04/human-composting-and-timber-marketplaces-talking-industrial-vc-with-investor-dayna-grayson/</link><description>While the venture world is abuzz over generative AI, Dayna Grayson, a longtime venture capitalist who five years ago co-founded her own firm, Construct Capital, has been focused on comparatively boring software that can transform industrial sectors. Her mission doesn’t exclude AI, but it also doesn’t depend on it. Construct recently led a seed-stage round, […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 20:23:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mississippi Lawmakers Considered Modest Public Defense Reforms. They Rejected All of Them.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/02/mississippi-public-defense-legislative-reforms</link><description>With its refusal to impose oversight or consistent standards in local defense, Mississippi risks falling further behind rest of the U.S., critics say.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What to Eat as You Age</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/nutrition-for-seniors?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Your dietary needs change as you age. WebMD advises what should be on your grocery list.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 14:30:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Women in AI: Tara Chklovski is teaching the next generation of AI innovators</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/04/women-in-ai-tara-chklovski-is-teaching-the-next-generation-of-ai-innovators/</link><description>Tara Chklovski is the CEO and founder of Technovation, a nonprofit that helps teach young girls about technology and entrepreneurship.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 18:00:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In This Police Youth Program, a Trail of Sexual Abuse Across the U.S.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/01/police-explorer-sexual-abuse-boy-scouts</link><description>Explorer posts, overseen by the Boy Scouts, are supposed to foster an interest in policing. They have faced nearly 200 allegations of misconduct.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 18:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What's Behind Major Rise in Heart Failure Deaths?</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/heart-disease/heart-failure/news/20240503/heart-failure-mortality-rate-continues-to-rise?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>After falling for over a decade, the death rate climbed for several years and now is about the same as in 1999.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 18:36:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Farewell, dunks? Threads launches quote controls for all users</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/04/farewell-dunks-threads-launches-quote-controls-for-all-users/</link><description>Threads users can now exert more control over who can quote their posts. This builds on a feature that already allows Threads users to limit who can reply to their posts (competing services like X and Bluesky offer similar reply controls). Threads outlined its plans for quote controls last month, and last night Adam Mosseri […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 17:16:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Campus Protests Could Shape the 2024 Elections — And Not Just the Presidency</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/30/campus-protests-gaza-arrests-prosecutors-elections</link><description>With hundreds of arrests and more campus standoffs looming, local law enforcement officials could face consequences at the ballot box.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 21:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jump-Start Your Exercise With This Mindset Reset</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/fitness-exercise/news/20240429/jump-start-exercise-with-this-mindset-reset?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>There are far more powerful motivators than “get abs!” to help you start an exercise routine you’ll stick to.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 18:25:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deal Dive: Amae Health is building an in-person approach to mental healthcare in an increasingly digital space</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/04/deal-dive-amae-health-is-building-an-in-person-approach-to-mental-healthcare-in-an-increasingly-digital-space/</link><description>While many recent mental health-focused startups are digital first, Amae Health focuses on the importance of in-person care.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 17:00:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>They Killed Their Abusive Partners. Now Their Sentences Could Be Reconsidered.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/27/oklahoma-oregon-minnesota-domestic-violence</link><description>Oklahoma could re-examine how it punishes people whose crimes came after years of domestic abuse. Other states may follow.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When Does Old Age Start? It Depends on Who You Ask</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/news/20240502/when-does-old-age-start-many-disagree?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>The goalpost for old age has been moving. Until now.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 18:45:35 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>