<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 06:48:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>ECHL’s Tahoe Knight Monsters Unveil Uniforms For Inaugural Season</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/17/echls-tahoe-knight-monsters-unveil-uniforms-for-inaugural-season/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>All three jerseys have different Knight Monsters logos on the chest; club also announces affiliation agreement with AHL's Henderson Silver Knights and NHL's Vegas Golden Knights</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 20:50:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jon Jones Pleads Not Guilty To Charges Stemming From Drug Test Incident</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/17/jon-jones-pleads-not-guilty-charges-drug-test-incident/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>UFC heavyweight champion Jon Jones isn't tapping out in his ongoing legal battle ... entering a not-guilty plea for the two misdemeanor charges he's facing in relation to a drug test gone wrong earlier this year. Jones -- who appeared in New Mexico…</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 06:48:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MLB to Mull Over Return to Individual Team Uniforms For All-Star Game</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/17/mlb-to-mull-over-return-to-individual-team-uniforms-for-all-star-game/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>MLB Commissioner Rob Manfred tells Baseball Writers' Association of America that return to team uniforms is "something we’re going to have a conversation about"</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 18:02:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bam Margera's Ex Was Never His Wife Despite Wedding, Court Tentatively Rules</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/17/bam-margera-never-married-ex-nikki-boyd-custody-dispute-judge-ruling/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Bam Margera and Nikki Boyd were never husband and wife in the eyes of the law, despite going through a wedding ceremony -- that's the word from the judge in their ongoing custody battle. According to new legal docs, obtained by TMZ, the judge…</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 06:48:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chelsea Hope to Burn Bright in New Home Kit – Plus Other Recent European Kit Launches</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/16/chelsea-hope-to-burn-bright-in-new-home-kit-plus-other-recent-european-kit-launches/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Other clubs unveiling kits for 2024-25 include Juventus, Brighton &amp; Hove Albion, Nottingham Forest, U.S. Lecce, Como 1907, Stade Brestois 29, Real Sociedad, Mallorca, Leganés</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 18:38:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Thomas Matthew Crooks' Former Classmate Says He Was a Trump Hater</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/17/thomas-matthew-crooks-former-classmate-trump-hater/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Thomas Matthew Crooks wasn't a fan of Donald Trump years before attempting to assassinate the former Prez ... so says one of his former classmates. Vincent Taormina -- who went to high school with the would-be assassin -- spoke with FOX News about…</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 06:48:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MLS Reaches Into Its Past For Retro-Inspired Third Kits For Five Clubs</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/16/mls-reaches-into-its-past-for-retro-inspired-third-kits-for-five-clubs/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>MLS x Adidas Archive Collection includes jerseys, jackets and sneakers for Inter Miami, LA Galaxy, LAFC, Portland Timbers and Sporting Kansas City</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 17:14:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eric Trump Says 'Competent' Shooter Would've Hit Dad, Pissed at Security Lapses</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/17/eric-trump-competent-shooter-assassination-attempt-security-lapses-secret-service/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Eric Trump is furious with the security lapses leading up to the assassination attempt on his father ... and says a competent shooter wouldn't have missed his target. Donald Trump's son expanded on his father's brush with death in an interview with…</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 06:48:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Las Vegas Raiders Unveil 65th Season Logo</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/15/las-vegas-raiders-unveil-65th-season-logo/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Las Vegas Raiders will celebrate their 65th season this year with a commemorative logo, which the franchise unveiled on Monday afternoon.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 21:45:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Salt-N-Pepa's Sandra Denton Says Southwest Airlines Treated Her Like a Criminal</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/17/salt-n-pepa-sandra-denton-southwest-airlines-treated-like-criminal/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Sandra "Pepa" Denton, 1/2 of Salt-N-Pepa, is still shaken and confused by her encounter with Southwest Airlines this week, when she says she got treated like a criminal without displaying any criminal behavior!!! It's a perplexing tale, for sure --…</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 06:48:35 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>