<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 07:13:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Indianapolis Indians pay tribute to Pittsburgh with Young Bucs alternate</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/18/indianapolis-indians-pay-tribute-to-pittsburgh-with-young-bucs-alternate/baseball/</link><description>For six games this season, the Triple-A Indianapolis Indians will represent the colors of their parent club of 19 years, the Pittsburgh Pirates. The Indians will wear specialty “Young Bucs” jerseys and caps for Prospects Weekends in May and June. The Pittsburgh Pirates are often referred to as the Bucs,</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 04:32:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Porn Star Sophia Leone's Mom Told Cops She Drank, Had Suicidal Thoughts</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/18/porn-star-sophia-leone-death-mom-suicidal-thoughts-drinking-police-report/</link><description>Sophia Leone's death remains under investigation -- but we now know a bit more about what was relayed to cops when they found her body ... including the fact her mom said her daughter had been known to have suicidal thoughts. According to the…</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 07:13:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Minot Hot Tots honor Scandinavian roots with Berzerkers alternate</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/18/minot-hot-tots-honor-scandinavian-roots-with-berzerkers-alternate/baseball/</link><description>The collegiate summer level Minot Hot Tots’ identity does not exactly instill fear. Pretty much the worst thing the tater tot mascot can do to an opponent is cause elevated cholesterol levels. So when the team set out to create an alternate identity for a series of “What Might Have</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 03:53:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Vanderpump Rules' Star Scheana Shay Works a Shift at Chili's in Uniform</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/18/vanderpump-rules-scheana-shay-works-shift-chilis-selfies-guests/</link><description>Scheana Shay was slinging drinks somewhere other than SUR this week -- working a shift at a Chili's Grill &amp; Bar instead ... going back to her server roots, pre-fame! In videos obtained by TMZ, the "Vanderpump Rules" star was seen rocking a…</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 07:13:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Detroit Lions Officially Unveil New Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/18/detroit-lions-officially-unveil-new-uniforms-2/football/</link><description>While we caught our first glimpse of the jerseys thanks to a leak earlier in the day, the Detroit Lions officially unveiled their new uniforms on Thursday evening.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 00:45:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Frank Sinatra's Daughter Reacts to Scorsese Biopic, Seems A-OK With It</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/18/frank-sinatra-daughter-tina-react-martin-scorsese-dicaprio-biopic-approval/</link><description>Frank Sinatra's daughter is weighing in on Martin Scorsese's plans to turn the singer's life into a film -- and from the sounds of it ... she's more than fine with the project. ICYMI ... Martin is planning to make a biopic about Ol' Blue Eyes --…</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 07:13:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NHL to Utah, Coyotes “Inactive”. What will Utah NHL Team be Called?</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/18/nhl-expands-to-utah-coyotes-franchise-inactive-for-2024-25/hockey-2/</link><description>The National Hockey League today officially confirmed what had been rumoured all week. They have rendered the Arizona Coyotes franchise “inactive” and added a new franchise in Salt Lake City, Utah, to take their place starting in 2024-25. The new Utah franchise will be owned by the Smith Entertainment Group,</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 21:44:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Andy Cohen Not Negotiating Departure Package from Bravo, Reports Are BS</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/18/andy-cohen-not-negotiate-bravo-departure-package-report-rumor/</link><description>Andy Cohen's not leaving Bravo despite reports claiming he's negotiating a departure package amid legal troubles -- with a network rep blasting the unsubstantiated rumors. A spokesperson for Bravo tells TMZ ... there is absolutely no truth to the…</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 07:13:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Detroit Lions’ New Jerseys Leak In Promotional Post</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/18/detroit-lions-new-jerseys-leak-in-promotional-post/football/</link><description>Although they won't officially be unveiled until 7 p.m. ET tonight, the Detroit Lions' new jerseys were leaked in a since-deleted promotional post on Thursday morning.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 19:05:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Travis Scott Says Grammys Matter To Him, Frustrated He Hasn't Won Yet</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/18/travis-scott-grammys-matter-frustrated-not-won-award/</link><description>Travis Scott says while many of his contemporaries have turned their back on the Grammys -- he's still holding out hope he can snag one ... 'cause he still finds they hold value. The rapper got brutally honest on a new episode of LeBron James' show…</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 07:13:05 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>