<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 00:44:09 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The Most Popular Book Riot Stories of the Week</title><link>https://bookriot.com/best-of-book-riot-may-18-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/black-woman-reading-with-a-cup-of-coffee.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>Grab your coffee, kick up your feet, and dive into our best stuff from another eventful week in the world ...</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Junkyard Gem: 1994 Volvo 850 Turbo Wagon</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/18/junkyard-gem-1994-volvo-850-turbo-wagon/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/12122534/99-1994-Volvo-850-Turbo-in-Colorado-junkyard-photo-by-Murilee-Martin.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Volvo , Automotive History , Wagon , Performance , Classics Continue reading Junkyard Gem: 1994 Volvo 850 Turbo Wagon Junkyard Gem: 1994 Volvo 850 Turbo Wagon originally appeared on Autoblog on Sat, 18 May 2024 16:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>No ‘cop on the beat’: Why the SEC may deny new ether ETFs this month</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/18/crypto-fraud-and-poor-regulation-may-jeopardize-ether-etf-approval.html</link><description>The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission is expected to make a key decision on approving ether ETFs.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sharing Fun Facts About Yourself: 22 Examples &amp; Ideas</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/fun-facts-about-me/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fun-facts-about-me</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Asking to share some fun facts about yourself is a common icebreaker that’s used during job interviews. But the quality of your answer still matters. This guide will help you come up with some ideas for crafting a response that starts the interview on a good note. Table of contents Ideas for Sharing Fun Facts […] The post Sharing Fun Facts About Yourself: 22 Examples &amp; Ideas appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 15:26:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A case for public preschool: New study reveals preschool benefits to be longer-lasting and substantial</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/benefits-of-public-preschool/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=benefits-of-public-preschool</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Preschool lays a foundation for elementary school students to succeed. In the United States, as children approach kindergarten entry, it is increasingly common for 4-year-olds to be in non-parental group care and education, often in a center- or school-based setting where they can learn alongside peers. For children from low-income communities, […] The post A case for public preschool: New study reveals preschool benefits to be longer-lasting and substantial appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 08:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>California Burrito</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/california-burrito/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>This delicious California Burrito is filled with well-seasoned grilled steak, pepper jack cheese, French fries, pico de Gallo, sour cream…</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Weekend In New Orleans With Kids</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/new-orleans-with-kids/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Since our travel guides to Charleston with kids and Palm Springs with kids have elicited requests for more travel ideas with kids, we’re back with an overdue recap of our 3-night trip to New Orleans. We’d never been to The Big Easy before and were impressed by how family-friendly the city is. It’s not all booze, beads, and Bourbon Street! So here’s a look at where we stayed, what we did, and what we’re excited to do next time we go back – because we will definitely go back! The four of us (well, five if you count our chihuahua!) went to NOLA for 3 nights in November of 2022. At the time, our kids were 8 and 12 years old. So unfortunately we can’t vouch for our suggestions being a good fit for toddlers or younger children. Although I’m sure ours would’ve loved the Louisiana Children’s Museum and Storyland playground back in the day! Continue reading A Weekend In New Orleans With Kids at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 17:17:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wedding Guest Edit</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/wedding-guest-edit/</link><description>Outfit Details: Siedres Dress, JB x Jennifer Behr Necklace, Sherman Fields Necklace, Prada Bag, Hermes Bangles (similar, less expensive here) Wedding season… The post Wedding Guest Edit appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 05:00:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Riot’s YA Book Deals of the Day: May 18, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/book-riots-ya-book-deals-of-the-day-may-18-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Untitled-design-56.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>A dozen YA books across an array of genres, all coming in at under $3 today!</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Morocco’s automotive industry shifts gears to prep for electric vehicle era</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/18/moroccos-automotive-industry-shifts-gears-to-prep-for-electric-vehicle-era/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/17133232/morocco_car_industry.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Earnings/Financials , Government/Legal , Plants/Manufacturing , Green Automakers , Electric , Future Vehicles , Hybrid Continue reading Morocco’s automotive industry shifts gears to prep for electric vehicle era Morocco’s automotive industry shifts gears to prep for electric vehicle era originally appeared on Autoblog on Sat, 18 May 2024 14:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Study links talc use to ovarian cancer, adding a potential boon for lawsuits against J&amp;J</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/18/study-links-talc-to-ovarian-cancer-with-implications-for-jj-.html</link><description>The analysis, released Wednesday in the Journal of Clinical Oncology, found that applying talc powder to the genitals was associated with ovarian cancer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 15:29:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 553</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-553/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-553</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Tools and technology change rapidly. Yet as wonderful as technology can be, it doesn’t replace the need for human connection through interactions. Keep this in mind as you are searching for a new job. It’s your human connections that often open doors! In this week’s collection of news and tips for job seekers, you’ll find: […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 553 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 12:19:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fathers’ views on family and work after COVID-19 lockdowns</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/fathers-views-on-family-and-work-after-covid-19-lockdowns/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fathers-views-on-family-and-work-after-covid-19-lockdowns</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Fathers often want to be present for their children and contribute to household tasks, but they can lack opportunities and confidence; they may see themselves as “helpers” instead of parents. Australian fathers in our small study reported that they spent more time with their children during the COVID-19 lockdowns, and they […] The post Fathers’ views on family and work after COVID-19 lockdowns appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly Meal Plan #5</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/weekly-menu-plan-5/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Weekly meal plan #5 is made up of delicious comfort meals the whole family will love. I specifically included a…</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Easy Low-Light Indoor Plants</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/easy-low-light-indoor-plants/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>I used to think every houseplant needed a sunny corner or bright windowsill to thrive. But it turns out many of our favorite go-to houseplants do just fine in shady corners and low-light locations. So before you write off your house as too dark to sustain plant life, check out this list of the best indoor plants for low light. You might be surprised at how many good options there are! Our upstairs family room is the brightest room we’ve ever owned thanks to big unobstructed windows on all 4 sides. But most of our indoor plants live downstairs, where we get far less natural light. Luckily, that hasn’t stopped us from growing our collection of happy healthy houseplants. 9 Houseplants That Don’t Need A Lot Of Light Here are our favorite low-light indoor plants. We list a lot more info on them below, but here’s a quick list to bring on your next trip to the plant store: Snake Plant ZZ Plant Pothos Heartleaf Philodendron English Ivy Aglaonema Cast Iron Plant Monstera Parlor Palm Perhaps our favorite part of this list is that these aren’t ugly “consolation plants” that people begrudgingly buy for dark homes. Continue reading Easy Low-Light Indoor Plants at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 14:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pastel Palette Picks</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/pastel-palette-picks/</link><description>Outfit Details: Pucci Swimsuit, Janessa Leone Hat, Prada Sunglasses One of the joys of embracing spring and early summer in Charleston is… The post Pastel Palette Picks appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 21:30:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Riot’s Deals of the Day for May 18, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/book-riots-deals-of-the-day-for-may-18-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/deals-051824.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>A teen-created Satanic panic, a bruja with ever-growing magical abilities, and more of today's best book deals.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indy 500: When it starts, how to watch, betting odds for 'The Greatest Spectacle in Racing'</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/18/indy-500-when-it-starts-how-to-watch-betting-odds-for-the-greatest-spectacle-in-racing/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/17131047/indycar_indy_500_auto_racing.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Motorsports , Racing Vehicles Continue reading Indy 500: When it starts, how to watch, betting odds for 'The Greatest Spectacle in Racing' Indy 500: When it starts, how to watch, betting odds for 'The Greatest Spectacle in Racing' originally appeared on Autoblog on Sat, 18 May 2024 12:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Activist Corvex could take an amicable approach to help create value at Vestis. How it may unfold</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/18/corvex-could-take-an-amicable-approach-to-help-create-value-at-vestis.html</link><description>Corvex reveals a stake in uniform supplier Vestis. The firm is suggesting that it’s here for the long term.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 14:26:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 552</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-552/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-552</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>When you are searching for a job, you will inevitably run into unexpected scenarios. You will have questions, experience self-doubt and even feel discouraged. You’ll also experience great wins, meet wonderful people and discover new things about yourself. That’s the roller-coaster of job search. Consider Summary Sunday your resource for getting questions answered and showing […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 552 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 11:37:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Strong Latine Identity Supports U.S. Latine Children’s Well-Being</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/a-strong-latine-identity-supports-u-s-latine-childrens-well-being/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=a-strong-latine-identity-supports-u-s-latine-childrens-well-being</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key Takeaways for caregivers Children tend to have better health and well-being when they have a strong ethnic identity (affinity and adoption of ethnicity-based self-concept). A traditional Latine cultural value (familismo) that emphasizes family bonds is also associated with better developmental outcomes. Caregivers can support the development of U.S. Latine children (and possibly other children […] The post A Strong Latine Identity Supports U.S. Latine Children’s Well-Being appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 03:03:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best Swedish Meatballs</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/the-best-swedish-meatballs/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>These Swedish Meatballs are smothered in the most amazing rich and creamy gravy and packed with such delicious flavor. You…</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/how-to-remove-wallpaper/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Wallpaper has made a big comeback as a trendy home design choice. But despite its resurgence, there are still plenty of us dealing with dingy, dated, or downright ugly old wallpaper we don’t want. In our old home, we had to remove wallpaper in so many rooms: the kitchen, the dining room, the foyer, and two different bathrooms! As we traveled from room to room removing wallpaper, we tested 4 different methods, and today we’ll share what we learned. Removing wallpaper doesn’t require special tools or lots of money. It’s a totally doable project for any homeowner. However, it can be a tedious process that can take elbow grease and patience, depending on the size of your room and the stubbornness of your wallpaper. But having removed several rooms worth of decades-old wallpaper, we can confidently say it’s worth the effort! You can also check out more before and afters of our once-wallpapered rooms. Continue reading How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:21:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jet Set Ready With Net-A-Porter</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/jet-set-ready-with-net-a-porter/</link><description>Thank you to NET-A-PORTER for sponsoring this post. Jet Set Ready With Net-A-Porter emerges as your essential guide to traveling… The post Jet Set Ready With Net-A-Porter appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 05:00:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Riot’s Deals of the Day for May 17, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/book-riots-deals-of-the-day-for-may-17-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/deals-051724.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>Another mega-list of deals for you today - grab 'em while you can!</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 19:09:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Yeti coolers, drinkware and more are 20% off at REI's Anniversary Sale</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/article/yeti-coolers-drinkware-and-more-are-20-off-at-reis-anniversary-sale/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/15122608/61301101-b2fb-453b-a87b-72f150f81.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Commerce Continue reading Yeti coolers, drinkware and more are 20% off at REI's Anniversary Sale Yeti coolers, drinkware and more are 20% off at REI's Anniversary Sale originally appeared on Autoblog on Sat, 18 May 2024 11:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Some consumers are punting big purchases like pools and mattresses</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/18/some-consumers-are-punting-big-purchases-like-pools-and-mattresses.html</link><description>There are some signs that shoppers are holding off on big-ticket buys, the latest signal of the economy contracting at the hands of tighter monetary policy.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 14:22:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>While a little competition in the workplace might help bring out the best in everyone involved, an atmosphere rooted in envy, fear, or jealousy can do the exact opposite. This post will help you recognize signs that your coworker is threatened by you, and help you navigate the situation. 1. They Don’t Want You Involved […] The post 10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:07:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Children caught between highly conflicted divorced parents at greater risk of mental health problems</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/children-caught-between-conflicted-divorced-parents/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=children-caught-between-conflicted-divorced-parents</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Interparental conflict after divorce escalates the risk of mental health problems in children and adolescents. Elevated levels of conflict between parents can also induce fear and worry in children about their future and whether they will be adequately taken care of. In turn, a greater fear of abandonment puts children at […] The post Children caught between highly conflicted divorced parents at greater risk of mental health problems appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 08:59:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>No Bake Snickers Bar Pie</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/no-bake-snickers-bar-pie/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>No Bake Snickers Bar Pie is one of the easiest and most delicious no bake pies that you make. You…</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aglaonema Plant – Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/aglaonema-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Aglaonema, also called the Chinese Evergreen Plant, is an easy-care houseplant that lives happily in many lighting conditions – even a dark corner of our daughter’s room. There are dozens of different Aglaonema varieties, most with large tropical foliage and colors ranging from silvery-green, red, and even vibrant pink. They’re also tough to kill, so they’re a great option for forgetful plant owners or anyone looking for an easy win in the plant department. These truly have been very low maintenance for us. We purchased our two Aglaonemas (pronounced ag-lee-oh-neem-ah ) to put atop our daughter’s closet. It’s sometimes hard to distinguish different varieties, but we believe that’s an Aglaonema Silver (right) and either a Candy Cane or Princess Silver Queen (left). Aglaonema Quick Facts Here’s what you need to know about your Aglaonema at a glance: Latin name : Aglaonema is the genus under which there are 21 recognized species . Continue reading Aglaonema Plant – Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:47:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Crop Tops</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/crop-tops/</link><description>Outfit Details: Kilentar Top (similar here), Emporior Sirenuse Skirt, Emme Parsons Sandals, Prada Bag The crop top has earned its place as one of… The post Crop Tops appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:30:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best Sci-Fi, Fantasy, and Horror Books of the Summer</title><link>https://bookriot.com/best-of-book-riot-may-17-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/nebula.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>Here’s to wrapping up the week with a big serving of bookish goodness! 🍿 Less than a month until It ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>UAW loss in Alabama won't kill national organizing effort, analysts say</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/18/uaw-loss-in-alabama-wont-kill-national-organizing-effort-analysts-say/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/crop/3800x2138+0+81/resize/800x450!/format/jpg/quality/85/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/18095258/the_exterior_of_the_visitors_center_at_the_mercedes-benz__suv_manufacturing_plant_in_vance_.jpeg</image_url><description>Filed under: Plants/Manufacturing , UAW/Unions , Mercedes-Benz Continue reading UAW loss in Alabama won't kill national organizing effort, analysts say UAW loss in Alabama won't kill national organizing effort, analysts say originally appeared on Autoblog on Sat, 18 May 2024 10:30:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>These stocks and ETFs could benefit from AI's voracious appetite for energy</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/18/stocks-and-etfs-that-could-benefit-from-ais-insatiable-need-for-energy.html</link><description>The power required to operate large artificial intelligence programs could help these investments outside of technology, according to Bank of America.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 14:17:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 551</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-551/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-551</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Job search requires writing and marketing skills. It also requires strong verbal communication. If these skills are not part of your normal work function, you’ll want some help. That’s what this week’s Summary Sunday is all about. There’s no doubt that LinkedIn is one of THE most powerful tools in your career toolbox. It contains […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 551 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 11:37:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>“Why do they feel sad?” Shared book reading reveals how children learn about others’ emotions</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/shared-book-reading/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=shared-book-reading</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers: It is good for children to identify the emotions of others in conversations with caregivers because it scaffolds their ability to identify others’ emotions on their own. Children who use more emotion talk in parent-child conversations about emotions are more likely to have higher emotion knowledge one year later. Parents can […] The post “Why do they feel sad?” Shared book reading reveals how children learn about others’ emotions appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 08:19:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Easy Grilled Bourbon Chicken</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/grilled-bourbon-chicken/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>One bite of this grilled bourbon chicken and your tastebuds will be dancing with delight! It’s marinated in a flavorful…</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Corn Plant – Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/corn-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Corn plants ( Dracaena fragrans ) are popular low-maintenance houseplants you’ve probably seen at the nursery, home improvement store, or doctor’s office. I even had one in my college dorm room! You can recognize them by their spear-shaped leaves and woody, cane-line trunks that can grow up to 6 feet tall indoors. But did you know there are several varieties of corn plants? We didn’t! Heck, we didn’t even realize some of our smaller houseplants were in the same corn plant family! Currently, we own two smaller varieties of corn plants, pictured above. The one on the left is a Dracaena Limelight ( Dracaena fragrans ‘Limelight’ ) and the taller plant is a Draecanea Dorado ( Dracaena fragrans ‘Dorado’ ). We actually have several limelights around because we love their vibrant color on shelves, tabletops, and windowsills. Corn Plant Quick Facts Latin name : Dracaena fragrans Common names : Corn plant, cornstalk plant, false palms Light : Bright, indirect light but can tolerate lower-light conditions Watering : Keep soil moist, but not soggy. Continue reading Corn Plant – Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 17:37:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Punchy Prints</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/punchy-prints/</link><description>Outfit Details: Pucci Top &amp; Pants, Chanel Bag (similar, less expensive here), Dior Sandals (similar, less expensive here), Louis Abel Earrings (less expensive here) Punchy prints are a favorite of mine… The post Punchy Prints appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 05:00:44 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>