<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 16:43:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Twins Announce City Connect Unveil Plans, Water-Themed Uniform?</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/03/twins-announce-city-connect-unveil-plans-water-themed-uniform/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Minnesota Twins have announced some of the details surrounding the upcoming release of their 2024 Nike MLB City Connect uniform. The new uniform will be unveiled on Monday, June 10, during a special event at Target Plaza outside Target Field. The unveiling kicks off the Twins’ “City Connect Launch</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 21:38:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Commanders Cut Brandon McManus After Sexual Assault Allegations</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/03/commanders-cut-brandon-mcmanus-after-sexual-assault-allegations/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Brandon McManus -- a former Super Bowl champion who signed a big free-agent deal with Washington in March -- has just been cut by the Commanders ... following allegations he sexually assaulted two flight attendants last year. The women made the…</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 16:43:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSL’s AFC Toronto Unveils Name and Crest</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/03/nsls-afc-toronto-unveils-name-and-crest/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Northern Super League club will take to the pitch in 2025 inaugural season with maroon and vermillion color scheme and crest that aims to represent different parts of their city</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 16:44:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pat Sajak Wants Next Job to Be Grandpa After 'Wheel of Fortune' Exit</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/03/wheel-of-fortune-exit-pat-sajak-wants-next-job-grandpa/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Pat Sajak is already eyeing his next role ahead of his "Wheel of Fortune" exit ... telling his daughter, Maggie, he's ready to be a grandpa. The longtime game show host sat down with his daughter days before his exit from the game show, explaining…</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 16:43:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WooSox wonder what might have been with Ruby Legs fauxbacks</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/03/woosox-wonder-what-might-have-been-with-ruby-legs-fauxbacks/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>When the erstwhile Pawtucket Red Sox moved from Rhode Island to their current home in Worcester, Massachusetts, one of the names the team considered adopting was the Worcester Ruby Legs. The nickname is loosely associated with a short-lived National League team called the Worcester Worcesters, who played from 1880 to</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 13:56:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Karl-Anthony Towns Goes Shopping W/ Jordyn Woods, Retail Therapy After WCF Loss?</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/03/karl-anthony-towns-jordyn-woods-retail-therapy-nba-playoffs-timberwolves/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Seems Karl-Anthony Towns is hoping a little retail therapy will help him get over the Timberwolves' Western Conference finals loss ... 'cause the Minnesota star was seen going on a shopping spree Sunday -- one in which he appeared to buy loads of…</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 16:43:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IronPigs pay tribute to Lehigh Valley with Shoofly Pies alternate</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/03/ironpigs-pay-tribute-to-lehigh-valley-with-shoofly-pies-alternate/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Triple-A Lehigh Valley IronPigs will honor the Pennsylvania Dutch heritage of eastern Pennsylvania when they play as the Shoofly Pies this summer. While the name in the alternate identity suggests another minor league baseball food-based brand, the logo instead focuses on the fly that is being shooed away. Shoofly</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 13:16:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cheryl Burke Advises Celebs To Be Single If Competing On 'DWTS'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/03/dancing-with-the-stars-cheryl-burke-contestants-single-romance/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Cheryl Burke's dishing out her most crucial advice for prospective "Dancing With The Stars" competitors ... be single if you're gonna come on, 'cause you're bound to fall in love. The 'DWTS' alum explained on her "Sex, Lies, and Spray Tans" podcast…</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 16:43:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sources: Minnesota Vikings To Unveil “Winter Whiteout” Alternate Uniforms On June 7</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/02/sources-minnesota-vikings-to-unveil-winter-whiteout-alternate-uniforms-on-june-7/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>According to multiple sources, the Minnesota Vikings will unveil their new “Winter Whiteout” alternate uniforms this Friday.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 23:31:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alex Jones Lets Out War Cry &amp; Sobs on Show, Claims 'Infowars' Will Be Shut Down</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/03/alex-jones-war-cry-sob-claim-info-wars-shut-down-studio/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Alex Jones bawled his eyes out this weekend -- and in the same breath, he let out a scream straight from his bowels, all while claiming his show is on the verge of a shutdown. Check it out ... Alex was doing an impromptu "Infowars" broadcast this…</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 16:43:55 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>