<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 07:25:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Financial Freedom in 3 Years by Scaling with Small Multifamily</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-405</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>MANY people invest in real estate for financial freedom. Unfortunately, not all investors get there. The truth is that a little cash flow won’t allow you to quit your W2 […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 07:02:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Permira is taking Squarespace private in $6.6 billion deal</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/13/permira-is-taking-squarespace-private-in-6-6-billion-deal/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Website building software provider Squarespace is going private in an all-cash deal that values the company on equity basis at $6.6 billion, or a $6.9 billion enterprise valuation. The acquiring company is U.K.-based private equity firm Permira, which acquired a majority stake in Tel Aviv-based cybersecurity firm BioCatch just a couple of weeks ago. Founded in […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 12:15:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When Bad Cops Become Private Security Guards</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/11/police-private-guard-florida-chicago</link><description>There’s growing evidence that former officers with troubling histories of abuse can easily find second careers in private security.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 7-Hour Itch: 3 Women With Eczema Describe the Ways They Combat Nighttime Flare-Ups</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/seven-hour-itch-women-eczema-combat-nighttime-flares?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Three women with eczema describe how they combat nighttime flare-ups.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 09:09:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From Broke College Graduate to Financial Freedom While Living Abroad</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-952</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>You don’t have to race to financial independence to get there. Dave Meyer, VP of Market Intelligence at BiggerPockets, took his time building up passive income, and years later, it’s […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 07:02:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Buymeacoffee’s founder has built an AI-powered voice note app</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/13/buymeacoffees-founder-has-built-an-ai-powered-voice-note-app/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>AI-powered tools like OpenAI’s Whisper have enabled many apps to make transcription an integral part of their feature set for personal note-taking, and the space has quickly flourished as a result. Apps like AudioPen, Cleft Notes, and TalkNotes have proliferated across app stores and the Internet, but most offer a pretty limited feature set: They […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 08:51:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Rare Bright Spot for a Canine Lover Doing Time: Raising Puppies to Become Service Dogs</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/10/service-dogs-training-prison-essay</link><description>Adam Roberts reflects on the highs and occasional lows of training Labrador retrievers for the Puppies Behind Bars program.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Mother’s Love: The Challenges of Parenting a Child With Eczema</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/mothers-love-challenges-parenting-child-eczema?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Two moms reveal the great lengths they went to in their determination to give their children relief and good health.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 09:18:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Squatters’ Rights: What Lawyers Want Landlords to Know in 2024 w/Denise Medina and Patrick MacQueen</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-216</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Squatters’ rights have been a serious subject of debate over the past few years. It seems that more and more investors and even one-off landlords are dealing with squatters staying […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 07:02:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Google partners with Airtel to offer cloud and genAI products to Indian businesses</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/13/google-partners-with-airtel-to-offer-cloud-and-genai-products-to-indian-businesses/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Airtel, India's second-largest telco, is partnering with Google Cloud to develop and deliver cloud and GenAI solutions to Indian businesses. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 08:49:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Marshall Project Wins the Dart Award for “The Mercy Workers”</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/06/the-marshall-project-wins-the-dart-award-for-the-mercy-workers</link><description>Our feature on mitigation specialists who help save people from the death penalty was recognized for making “significant contributions to public understanding of trauma-related issues.”</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Working It Out: How to Minimize Eczema Flare-ups at the Gym and on the Job</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/minimize-eczema-flare-ups-gym-job?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Three keys to managing your eczema at the gym and then heading off to a productive and itch-free workday.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 07:30:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Florida Is the Perfect Rent-to-Own Market—Should You Take Advantage?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/why-florida-is-the-perfect-rent-to-own-market</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>The Sunshine State offers the exact combination of factors that make this investment option attractive.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 14:08:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Women in AI: Rep. Dar’shun Kendrick wants to pass more AI legislation</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/12/women-in-ai-rep-darshun-kendrick-wants-to-pass-more-ai-legislation/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>To give AI-focused women academics and others their well-deserved — and overdue — time in the spotlight, TechCrunch has been publishing a series of interviews focused on remarkable women who’ve contributed to the AI revolution. We’re publishing these pieces throughout the year as the AI boom continues, highlighting key work that often goes unrecognized. Read more profiles here. […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weinstein Ruling Poses Quandary: Can #MeToo Coexist With Protections for Defendants?</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/04/sex-crimes-weinstein-me-too</link><description>Proving sex crimes often requires evidence that is generally excluded to protect the rights of the accused.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cows Are Potential Spreaders of Bird Flu to Humans</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/food-recipes/food-poisoning/news/20240510/cows-are-potential-spreaders-bird-flu-humans?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Cow udders have the same receptors for flu viruses as humans and birds, raising concerns that cows could become “mixing vessels” that help the bird flu virus spread between people.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 19:36:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What If We Replaced Income Taxes with Property and Sales Taxes? Would Real Estate Investing Even Work?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/should-the-us-eliminate-income-taxes-and-replace-it-with-sales-and-property-tax</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>A few reasons for—and against—this proposed shift in U.S. tax laws.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:15:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A reckoning is coming for emerging venture funds, and that, VCs say, is a good thing</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/12/emerging-fund-venture-capital/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>We took the pulse of emerging fund managers about what it's been like for them during these post-ZERP, venture-capital-winter years. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mississippi Lawmakers Considered Modest Public Defense Reforms. They Rejected All of Them.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/02/mississippi-public-defense-legislative-reforms</link><description>With its refusal to impose oversight or consistent standards in local defense, Mississippi risks falling further behind rest of the U.S., critics say.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Age-Related Macular Degeneration: Putting a Hole in Our World</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/eye-health/news/20240510/age-related-macular-degeneration-putting-hole-our-world?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Estimates show that by 2040, age-related macular degeneration may affect nearly 300 million people worldwide. And we are very limited in our ability to treat or prevent it. Here's what to know.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 19:31:18 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>