<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 15:42:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>MLB Announces Return of Players’ Weekend in 2024, Custom Player Caps</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/26/mlb-announces-return-of-players-weekend-in-2024/baseball/</link><description>Major League Baseball is bringing back its Players’ Weekend this season, which will be held August 16-18, 2024, focusing on the players’ personalized gear. It’s the first time MLB will host its Players’ Weekend since 2019. As part of this year’s celebration, players will wear each player’s uniform number on</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 16:16:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gypsy Rose Loses Out on $6K From TikTok, Money Transferred to Her Ex</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/26/gypsy-rose-blanchard-lose-money-tiktok-transfer-ex-ryan-anderson/</link><description>Gypsy Rose is missing a pretty big bag from her TikTok account -- several thousand dollars that ended up in her estranged husband's hands when she deleted her account. Sources with direct knowledge tell TMZ ... Gypsy, who had over 9 million Tiktok…</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 15:42:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Moroccan Soccer Team Awarded Default Win After Kits Confiscated by Algerian Customs</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/25/moroccan-soccer-team-awarded-default-win-after-kits-confiscated-by-algerian-customs/soccer/</link><description>Kits feature map of Morocco on the chest that includes disputed Western Sahara territory</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 18:55:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Yeezy Porn' Will Be Unlike Anything In Industry, Says Stormy Daniels' Ex</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/26/stormy-daniels-yeezy-porn-nothing-we-ever-seen-kanye-west-mike-moz-ex-husband/</link><description>Kanye West plans to flex his creative muscles in his latest venture, which means you can expect his usual creative genius to be on display in the porn industry ... according to Stormy Daniels' ex, Mike Moz. Moz is a vet in adult films -- he…</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 15:42:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Glacier Range Riders, National Park Service Embroiled in Battle Over Arrowhead Logo</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/25/glacier-range-riders-national-park-service-embroiled-in-battle-over-arrowhead-logo/baseball/</link><description>NPS has filed protests with the U.S. Patent and Trademark Office over logo possible causing confusion that team is affiliated with service</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:56:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rose McGowan Speaks Out After Harvey Weinstein Conviction News</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/26/rose-mcgowan-speaks-out-harvey-weinstein-conviction-overturned/</link><description>Rose McGowan is slamming the fact Harvey Weinstein's NYC rape conviction was overturned ... and she's got an empowering message for all of his alleged victims. The actress posted a video Thursday in response to the Weinstein news -- with a caption…</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 15:42:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New York Jets: Their Logos, Their Name, Their Colours</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/25/new-york-jets-their-logos-their-name-their-colours/football/</link><description>From their early-sixties inception as the Titans of New York to their modern, throwback-inspired green and white logo, the New York Jets have had several distinctive looks over their 60-plus year history. This team has found itself navigating through different eras, frequently alternating between two primary logos and uniform styles</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:34:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kim Zolciak Fires Back at Critics of 'RIP' Kroy Post, She's Sick of BS</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/26/kim-zolciak-defends-kroy-biermann-rip-fake-death-post-daughter-ariana/</link><description>Kim Zolciak's over all the lies and accusations following her clickbait "RIP" post ... saying it wasn't about her estranged hubby Kroy Biermann dying, but actually about the death of their relationship. The 'RHOA' star kept the drama train chugging…</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 15:42:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Update on Utah’s NHL Team Name, Uniform Info, Tournament Coming?</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/24/update-on-utahs-nhl-team-name-uniform-info-tournament-coming/hockey-2/</link><description>Utah’s new National Hockey League team is starting to assemble their list of possible team names ahead of their inaugural (but not expansion) season this fall. DetroitHockey.Net’s Clark Rasmussen, the king of the trademark search, found two more names possibly trademarked by the group, bringing the total to nine that</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:51:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ex-New York Giant Korey Cunningham Dead At 28, Found In NJ Home</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/26/korey-cunningham-dead-found-home-new-york-giants-nfl/</link><description>Former Giants offensive tackle Korey Cunningham -- who also played for the Cardinals and Patriots -- was found dead in a New Jersey home on Thursday. He was only 28. The NYG confirmed the passing on Friday, the morning after the first round of the…</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 15:42:51 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>