<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 03:16:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Book Review: Enrich Your Future</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/18/book-review-enrich-your-future/</link><description>This engaging book is simultaneously memorable and humorous. The numerous sports analogies will have you smiling as you absorb Larry Swedroe's unforgettable investment precepts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 18:07:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Musk delays India visit and meeting with Modi as Tesla, SpaceX eye huge market</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/20/elon-musk-delays-india-visit-narendra-modi-tesla-earnings-spacex-starlink/</link><description>“Unfortunately, very heavy Tesla obligations require that the visit to India be delayed, but I do very much look forward to visiting later this year."</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 02:19:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CAPE Is High: Should You Care?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/17/cape-is-high-should-you-care/</link><description>A simple analysis shows that Robert Shiller's cyclically adjusted price-to-earnings ratio changed in the 1990s and that mean-reversion concerns may be misplaced. If CAPE changed three decades ago, however, there is nothing preventing it from doing so again.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 15:18:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Longtime Tesla bull hits panic button on robo-taxis vs. Model 2: 'It would be a disaster of epic proportions'</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/20/tesla-stock-warning-model-2-robo-taxi-elon-musk-q1-earnings-call/</link><description>"We've been through a lot of white-knuckle moments for Musk and Tesla," Ives said. "This is up there."</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 00:49:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI to the Rescue? Overhauling the US Power Grid on the Path to Net Zero</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/15/ai-to-the-rescue-overhauling-the-us-power-grid-on-the-path-to-net-zero/</link><description>Once known as secure and profitable investments, utilities are now viewed as enterprises fraught with financial risks. Investors should favor utilities that employ AI and other digital strategies to minimize damage from natural disasters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 21:24:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Luxury rental prices for Paris Olympics slashed by half or more as demand comes in weak</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/20/luxury-rental-prices-airbnb-vrbo-slashed-paris-olympics-demand-weak/</link><description>High-end, 1,100-square-foot residences are asking around €10,000 per week, down from €20,000 or €30,000 a few months ago.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 22:43:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Does a Stock’s Price Influence Its Risk Profile?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/12/does-a-stocks-price-influence-its-risk-profile/</link><description>As a stock falls in value, it becomes more sensitive to market movements and its total volatility increases.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HGTV's Property Brothers reveal the biggest mistakes new real estate investors make and predict the next hot housing market</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/20/hgtv-stars-property-brothers-real-estate-investing-biggest-mistakes-next-hot-housing-market/</link><description>"They get in over their heads because they've been watching those TikTok videos," said Drew Scott of the Property Brothers.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 22:04:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Managing Regret Risk: The Role of Asset Allocation</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/10/managing-regret-risk-the-role-of-asset-allocation/</link><description>Regret risk is a quantifiable phenomenon. The answer for some clients may be equally weighted portfolios.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 13:04:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>House passes $95 billion in aid for Ukraine, Israel and other U.S. allies</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/20/ukraine-israel-foreign-aid-bill-95-billion-passes-house-speaker/</link><description>The whole package will go to the Senate, where passage in the coming days is nearly assured.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 19:58:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>