<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 16:15:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Oregon Ducks Unveil Black “Generation O” Football Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/26/oregon-ducks-unveil-black-generation-o-football-uniforms/college/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Oregon unveiled the first combination of its new “Generation O” uniforms on Wednesday afternoon with an all-black option that blends various elements from the Ducks’ previous designs.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 20:55:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dave Matthews Band Alum Boyd Tinsley Arrested for DUI, Cop Interaction on Video</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/25/dave-matthews-band-alum-boyd-tinsley-arrested-suspicion-dui/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Boyd Tinsley is facing new legal woes -- 'cause the famous violinist was arrested for DUI after allegedly having a run-in with another car ... TMZ has learned. Law enforcement sources tell us the Dave Matthews Band alum was busted Monday in Rio, VA…</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 16:15:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mighty Big News: Anaheim Ducks Reveal New Logos &amp;  Uniforms, a Mix of Modern and Retro</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/26/mighty-big-news-anaheim-ducks-reveal-new-logos-uniforms-a-mix-of-modern-and-retro/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Welcome to Orange Country Today, the Anaheim Ducks took us all the way back, with one bright orange eye on the future, as the team officially unveiled its new logos and uniforms for the upcoming 2024-25 National Hockey League season. It’s a look heavily reminiscent of the old Mighty Ducks</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 18:12:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nicole Kidman and Keith Urban Celebrate 18 Years of Marriage</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/26/nicole-kidman-keith-urban-celebrate-anniversary-marriage/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Nicole Kidman and Keith Urban just celebrated 18 years of marriage -- and one stunning image captured their beautiful relationship. The legendary actress posted an Instagram photo Tuesday, showing herself barefoot in a patterned dress lying back…</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 16:15:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NHL, Fanatics Unveil New On-Ice Jerseys for 2024-25</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/26/nhl-fanatics-unveil-new-on-ice-jerseys-for-2024-25/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The National Hockey League and Fanatics officially unveiled the new Fanatics Authentic Pro NHL on-ice uniforms today. The uniforms will be worn on the ice for the first time during the 2024-25 season as Fanatics takes over from Adidas, the on-ice uniform provider since 2017. Fanatics has been designing and</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 14:31:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bill Belichick, 23-Year-Old Girlfriend Jordon Hudson Living Together For Months</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/26/bill-belichick-23-year-old-girlfriend-living-together-jordon-hudson/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Things between Bill Belichick and his 23-year-old girlfriend definitely appear to be serious ... as TMZ Sports has learned the couple has been living together for months. Sources close to the duo tell us ... Jordon Hudson moved in with 72-year-old…</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 16:15:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ole Miss Rebels Unveil Powder Blue-Accented Road Jersey</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/24/ole-miss-rebels-unveil-powder-blue-accented-road-jersey/college/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Ole Miss unveiled the first powder blue-accented road jersey in school history on Monday morning, granting the wishes of a large portion of the Rebels' fanbase.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 17:29:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Reds' Hunter Greene Vomits All Over Mound During Game</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/26/reds-hunter-greene-vomits-all-over-mound-during-game/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>MLB star Hunter Greene uncorked a fastball on Tuesday night ... and then he unloaded the contents of his stomach -- vomiting all over the mound right in the middle of the Reds' game. The nasty moment happened just minutes after the ace took the…</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 16:15:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Washington Capitals Celebrate 50th Anniversary With New Logos, Patches, and More</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/24/washington-capitals-celebrate-50th-anniversary-with-new-logos-jersey-patches-and-more/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Washington Capitals will celebrate their 50th anniversary in 2024-25 with a series of fun events, but most importantly (to us, anyway), a fantastic new series of commemorative anniversary logos and a jersey patch. The logo was designed in collaboration with FANBRANDZ. Over the past decade-plus, this agency has created</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 16:11:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New Tesla Cybertruck Driver Crashes Into Neighbor's Home, Video</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/26/tesla-cybertruck-crash-accelerator-steering/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>A Tesla Cybertruck driver careened into a neighbor's house after the driver lost control of the accelerator -- and it's all caught on security vid. The futuristic monster truck picked up speed down a narrow alley before slamming into a wall -- this…</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 16:15:48 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>