<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:39:41 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Report: Brazil Could Ditch Nike as Kit Supplier After Receiving Massive Offer</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/07/report-brazil-could-ditch-nike-as-kit-supplier-after-receiving-massive-offer/soccer/</link><description>Brazilian news outlet reports CBF has received an offer worth more than five times what Nike currently pays them from either Adidas or Puma</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:29:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pamela Anderson Attends First Met Gala Ever, Returns to Wearing Make-Up</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/07/pamela-anderson-attends-first-met-gala-makeup/</link><description>This qualifies as a shocker ... Pamela Anderson hit the Met Gala for the very first time ever, and she did it with a little twist – wearing makeup again! Since last year, the former "Baywatch" star has been going makeup-free – but at Monday…</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:39:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>USL’s Orange County Try to Capture Magic with New Cup Kit</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/06/usls-orange-county-sc-try-to-capture-some-magic-with-new-cup-kit/soccer/</link><description>Kit is inspired by designs worn in 1910s, when U.S. Open Cup started, and will be worn when OCSC takes on Loudoun United in Round of 32 on Tuesday, May 7</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 03:31:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kim Kardashian Stuns Everyone With Her Itty-Bitty Waist At Met Gala</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/07/kim-kardashian-tiny-waist-met-gala/</link><description>Kim Kardashian knows how to make an entrance ... but her appearance at Monday's Met Gala was a shocker ... not over something she said, but because of her teensy-weensy waist! KK strolled into the fashion world's biggest night at the Metropolitan…</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:39:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Panama Football Unveils New National Team Crest</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/06/panamanian-football-federation-unveils-new-national-team-crest/soccer/</link><description>Crest depicts a harpy eagle — the national bird of Panama — with each feather representing one of the country's 10 provinces</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WNBA's Angel Reese Stuns At Met Gala On Her 22nd Birthday</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/07/angel-reese-met-gala-wnba-chicago-sky/</link><description>Angel Reese traded in her kicks for heels on her 22nd birthday ... the WNBA star celebrated at the 2024 Met Gala -- and she looked amazing!!! The Chicago Sky forward pulled up to the iconic fashion event at The Metropolitan Museum of Art on Fifth…</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:39:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Snoop Dogg’s Gin &amp; Juice Brand Becomes Presenting Sponsor of Arizona Bowl</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/06/snoop-doggs-gin-juice-brand-becomes-presenting-sponsor-of-arizona-bowl/college/</link><description>The Arizona Bowl announced a multi-year partnership with 17-time Grammy Award winning artist Snoop Dogg that makes his alcohol brand, Gin &amp; Juice by Dre and Snoop, the game’s presenting sponsor.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 21:55:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gisele Bündchen Reportedly Pissed Over Divorce Jokes At Tom Brady Roast</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/07/gisele-bundchen-tom-brady-roast-kevin-hart/</link><description>While the divorce jokes at the Tom Brady roast had audiences in stitches, one person reportedly didn't find them funny at all ... TB12's ex, Gisele Bündchen. According to People, the supermodel was "deeply disappointed" by all the flippant…</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:39:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bayern Munich Goes All In On Red With 2024-25 Home Kits</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/06/bayern-munich-goes-all-in-on-red-with-2024-25-home-kits/soccer/</link><description>Sponsor logo on left sleeve contains QR code that fans can scan to participate in exclusive promotions throughout the 2024-25 season</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:48:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Celebrities Bust a Move at Met Gala After-Parties, Lots of Fashionable Stars</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/07/met-gala-after-parties-celebrities-stars-dance-fashion-outfits/</link><description>The stars were out and ready to boogie after this year's Met Gala -- and a ton of them ended up at the same after-parties ... including this one, where they looked real loose! Check out this video obtained by TMZ ... it shows a slew of celebs at…</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:39:41 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>