<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 23:15:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Inspections for Rental Properties: The Landlord Guide</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rental-property-inspections</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>As a landlord, conducting inspections is a big part of your business. Without these, you never truly know what’s happening inside your property.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 22:22:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>William Anders, astronaut who took the famous ‘Earthrise’ photo, dies at 90</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/09/william-anders-astronaut-who-took-the-famous-earthrise-photo-dies-at-90/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>William A. Anders, the astronaut behind perhaps the single most iconic photo of our planet, has died at the age of 90. On Friday morning, Anders was piloting a small plane that dove into the water near Roche Harbor, Wash. His son Greg confirmed his death. Anders retired from the Air Force Reserve as a […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 21:12:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>They Were in a Mental Health Crisis at a Hospital. This Is How They Landed in Jail.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/09/seattle-arrest-assault-mental-illness</link><description>In Washington, like most states, laws intended to protect health care workers are leading to prosecutions of people with severe mental illness.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Federal Experts Talk Bird Flu ‘What Ifs’ in WebMD Live Event</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/cold-and-flu/news/20240516/federal-experts-talk-bird-flu-what-ifs?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>WebMD brought together experts from four federal agencies to talk prevention, monitoring, and what the “what ifs” of bird flu might look like.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:50:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Crash or Correction? Home Prices Are Falling In These 15 Cities Across the Country</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/crash-or-correction-home-prices-are-falling-in-these-cities</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>After several years of escalating home prices amid tight inventory, as well as high interest rates that slammed the brakes on homebuying and investing, the first few dominoes appear to […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 19:15:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Startup Battlefield 200 applications close tomorrow</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/09/startup-battlefield-200-applications-close-tomorrow/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>You’re running out of time to join the Startup Battlefield 200, our curated showcase of top startups from around the world and across multiple industries. This elite cohort — 200 companies strong — absolutely owns (and slays) the exhibition floor at TechCrunch Disrupt. Tomorrow is the last day to apply to Startup Battlefield 200 We’re […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Some States are Trying to Get People Medicaid Before They Leave Prison</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/08/medicaid-reentry-waivers-prison-jail</link><description>People leaving prisons and jails are at greater risk of illness and death, but for years they couldn’t use the government health insurance program.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What’s Next in Health Care for Older Adults: Questions and Answers With John Whyte, MD</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/blog-aging-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>As WebMD’s chief medical officer, John Whyte, MD, is in a unique position to see both the current state of medical care for America’s older adults and the way things are trending for the future. We asked him to share his insight on a few topics, along with a bit of advice.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:29:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Would Happen to Real Estate If a Major War Broke Out? 8 Factors to Consider</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/what-would-happen-to-real-estate-if-a-major-war-started</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>It’s not as idle a question as we’d all like to believe. I’m no catastrophizer, but authoritarian regimes have grown bolder over the last few years. Look no further than […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 19:00:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New York moves to limit kids’ access to ‘addictive feeds’</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/09/new-york-moves-to-limit-kids-access-to-addictive-feeds/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>New York’s state legislature has passed a bill that would prohibit social media companies from showing so-called “addictive feeds” to children under 18, unless they obtain parental consent. The Stop Addictive Feeds Exploitation (SAFE) for Kids Act defines an addictive feed as one where the content is recommended or prioritized based on information about the […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 16:49:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>St. Louis Homicide Cases Often Go Unsolved. Victims’ Families Want Justice.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/07/st-louis-police-unsolved-murders-families</link><description>These St. Louis families have waited years for answers. They say police seem to have forgotten their loved ones.</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Get the Care You Need in a COVID-19 World</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/covid-senior-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>What to expect at the doctor’s office, hospitals, and long-term care facilities, the future of telemedicine, and how to get the best care during COVID-19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 19:50:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Advice for a Smooth Buying Process (From an Experienced Real Estate Investor)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/advice-for-a-smooth-buying-process</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>A well-defined buying process is vital for real estate investing. It reduces risks, avoids costly delays, and facilitates quick property acquisition once a suitable property is found. Here, I will […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cat-sitting startup Meowtel clawed its way to profitability despite trouble raising from dog-focused VCs</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/09/cat-sitting-startup-meowtel-clawed-its-way-to-profitability-despite-trouble-raising-from-dog-focused-vcs/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Dogs are the most popular pet in the U.S.: 65.1 million households have one, according to the American Pet Products Association. But while cats are not far off, with 46.5 million households with one, a lot of innovation in the pet category has focused exclusively on dogs. And even if the service serves both species, […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>As Murders Increased, St. Louis Police Struggled for Resources to Solve Cases</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/06/st-louis-police-unsolved-murders-budget</link><description>The city’s homicide unit has dealt with short staffing, long hours and a ballooning DNA backlog.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Personal Shopper: A Savvy Black Entrepreneur Guides You to Eczema-Friendly Clothes, Creams, Cosmetics, and More</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/savvy-black-entrepreneur-guides-eczema-friendly-clothes-creams-cosmetics?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>A savvy black entrepreneur guides you on an eczema-friendly shopping spree.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:54:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BiggerNews: Apartment Investing Took a Huge Hit, Is a Comeback On the Way?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-967</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Almost overnight, multifamily investing went from red-hot to something not even the most experienced investors would touch. After interest rates went up, rent growth stalled, and apartment supply flooded the […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 07:02:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anterior grabs $20M from NEA to expedite health insurance approvals with AI</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/08/anterior-grabs-20m-from-nea-at-95m-valuation-to-expedite-health-insurance-approvals-with-ai/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Anterior, a company that uses AI to expedite health insurance approval for medical procedures, has raised a $20 million Series A round at a $95 million post-money valuation led by NEA, according to two people familiar with the deal. Existing investors Sequoia, which led Anterior’s $3.2 million seed round last September, and Neo, an accelerator […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 22:03:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Some St. Louis Detectives May Have Botched Homicide Investigations</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/05/st-louis-police-unsolved-murders-officers</link><description>Several officers in the homicide unit faced internal complaints that they slept on the job, failed to get key evidence and lied to superiors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Behind the Spike in Colorectal Cancer Among Young Americans</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/colorectal-cancer/news/20240515/behind-the-spike-in-colorectal-cancer-cases?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Colorectal cancer cases increased a whopping 333% among 15- to 19-year-olds and 185% among 20- to 24-year-olds from 1999 to 2020.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:59:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>