<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 23:15:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Minnesota Golden Gophers Unveil New Football Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/08/minnesota-golden-gophers-unveil-new-football-uniforms/college/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Minnesota unveiled three new uniforms on Friday morning, marking the first significant overhaul to the Golden Gophers’ look since the 2018 season.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 16:30:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Guitarist Marty Friedman Slams Spotify CEO's Claim It's Cheap to Make Music</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/09/marty-friedman-guitarist-slams-spotify-ceo-close-to-zero-content-costs/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Ex-Megadeth guitarist Marty Friedman is ripping Spotify CEO Daniel Ek for saying the cost of making music nowadays is practically zilch ... telling us that just proves Ek is clueless about the industry. Daniel ruffled feathers among artists…</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 23:15:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MLB World Tour London 2024 Logos, Caps, and More – Mets vs. Phillies</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/08/mlb-world-tour-london-2024-logos-caps-and-more-mets-vs-phillies/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The New York Mets and Philadelphia Phillies are in England this weekend for a two-game series, the next stop on Major League Baseball’s 2024 World Tour. It’s the third time the league has gone to the United Kingdom for regular season baseball, having done so previously in 2019 with the</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 16:17:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Johnny Depp -- Good Genes or Good Docs?!</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/09/johnny-depp-good-genes-or-good-docs/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Johnny Depp turns 61 today ... and his looks over the years have proven to be sea-worthy! Here is a 40-year-old version of a youthful Depp at the "Once Upon A Time In Mexico" New York premiere back in 2003 (left). This was the same year he rose to…</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 23:15:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Newcastle United Make Long-Awaited Return to Adidas With 24-25 Home Kit</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/07/newcastle-united-make-long-awaited-return-to-adidas-with-24-25-home-kit/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Kit honors Magpies' traditional black and white vertical stripes and draws inspiration from kit Newcastle wore during the 2002-03 season</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 16:28:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Magic Johnson Praises Caitlin Clark, Angel Reese, 'Doing Great Things' For WNBA</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/09/magic-johnson-praise-caitlin-clark-angel-reese-wnba/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Magic Johnson tells TMZ Sports he's loving what he's seeing from Caitlin Clark and Angel Reese so far in the WNBA ... praising the rookies for how they're transitioning to the pros. We spoke briefly with the NBA legend out in L.A. this week as he…</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 23:15:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10 Smaller European Countries Get New 2024-26 Kits Thanks to UEFA Kit Assistance Scheme</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/07/10-smaller-european-countries-get-new-2024-26-kits-thanks-to-uefa-kit-assistance-scheme/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>In partnership with Italian manufacturer Erreà, program allows associations that lack bargaining power to get too-caliber kits for their national teams</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 16:04:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jennifer Lopez, Ben Affleck Selling Marital Home, Divorce Imminent</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/08/jennifer-lopez-ben-affleck-sell-marital-home-beverly-hills-divorce/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Jennifer Lopez and Ben Affleck are clearly heading down the path of divorce, because TMZ has learned they are quietly trying to sell the home they bought after they married. Multiple sources with direct knowledge tell TMZ, J Lo and Ben are using…</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 23:15:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jamaican National Teams, Adidas Roll Out Stunning New Home and Away Kits</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/06/jamaican-national-teams-adidas-roll-out-stunning-new-home-and-away-kits/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Pattern embossed on yellow home kit and in full color on black away kit features Jamaican national symbols like the doctor bird and lignum vitae</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 22:18:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eminem's New Music Video Gets Massive Praise From Adam West's Family</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/09/eminem-new-music-video-houdini-praise-adam-west-family-batman-robin/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Eminem's latest music video for the single "Houdini" is out, and among the millions viewing the banger is the family of the OG Batman Adam West, who loved the rapper's salute to his work. In the video for the track, which is part of Em's upcoming…</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 23:15:49 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>