<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from multiple RSS sources, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 13:15:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Home Prices Stagnate in The South and America’s New #1 Housing Market</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-213</link><description>Texas and Florida are seeing stagnating home prices as housing inventory booms while demand slips away. Housing is still expensive, but with more inventory, why is it staying that way? […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 07:02:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hyundai is spending close to $1 billion to keep self-driving startup Motional alive</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/02/hyundai-is-spending-close-to-1-billion-to-keep-self-driving-startup-motional-alive/</link><description>Hyundai has agreed to spend nearly $1 billion on Motional, an investment that will give the automaker a majority stake while providing the self-driving startup with the necessary capital to keep operating. The Korean automaker invested $475 million directly into Motional as part of a broader deal that includes buying out joint venture partner Aptiv. […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 17:48:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mississippi Lawmakers Considered Modest Public Defense Reforms. They Rejected All of Them.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/02/mississippi-public-defense-legislative-reforms</link><description>With its refusal to impose oversight or consistent standards in local defense, Mississippi risks falling further behind rest of the U.S., critics say.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prospects for Crohn's Relief Brighten With New Advancements</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/ibd-crohns-disease/crohns-disease/news/20240502/prospects-crohns-relief-brighten-with-new-advancements?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>More than 1 million Americans live with Crohn’s, a chronic and sometimes crippling bowel disease that affects the intestines and leads to digestive issues. But in 2024, breakthroughs could bring relief in different ways. Here's what to know.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 17:59:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Contractor Nightmares: 5 Red Flags to Watch For and How to Escape a Bad Hire</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/red-flags-to-avoid-with-contractors-and-how-to-escape-a-bad-hire</link><description>What’s easier to find, a unicorn or a rock star contractor? If you asked most value-add real estate investors, the answer would be obvious: “Unicorns, of course.” We all know the inherent […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 17:18:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TechCrunch Minute: Where CZ’s sentencing leaves the state of crypto</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/02/techcrunch-minute-where-czs-sentencing-leaves-the-state-of-crypto/</link><description>Four months behind bars and a massive fine, that’s what CZ is getting from the government for his crypto exchange’s misdeeds. Regardless of how you view the verdict — too much, too little, just right — his sentencing is a big deal for web3. Potentially in a positive way. There’s effort by some in crypto […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 17:05:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In This Police Youth Program, a Trail of Sexual Abuse Across the U.S.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/01/police-explorer-sexual-abuse-boy-scouts</link><description>Explorer posts, overseen by the Boy Scouts, are supposed to foster an interest in policing. They have faced nearly 200 allegations of misconduct.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 18:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Truth or TV: Is Grey's Anatomy's Parkinson's 'Cure' Real?</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/parkinsons-disease/features/is-greys-anatomys-parkinsons-cure-real?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>How realistic is the Grey’s Anatomy episode that shows a Parkinson’s disease cure? A neurosurgery professor weighs in.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 08:17:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Free Money? Can You Build a Real Estate Portfolio with Zero-Interest Credit Cards?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/can-you-build-a-real-estate-portfolio-with-zero-interest-credit-cards</link><description>Juggling 0% interest business credit cards is like juggling torches in a hay-covered barn. Drop one, and the whole place goes up in flames. However, if you are disciplined and […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 16:55:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Google will now show labels in Play Store to denote official government apps</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/02/google-will-now-show-labels-in-play-store-to-denote-official-government-apps/</link><description>After months of testing, Google is today rolling out labels in the Play Store to denote official state and federal government apps in more than 14 countries. This new label will help users rule out apps that masquerade as official apps to steal money or data. The company said that these badges currently cover more […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 17:00:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Campus Protests Could Shape the 2024 Elections — And Not Just the Presidency</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/30/campus-protests-gaza-arrests-prosecutors-elections</link><description>With hundreds of arrests and more campus standoffs looming, local law enforcement officials could face consequences at the ballot box.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 21:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Easing Marijuana Laws Doesn’t Mean the Drug Is Safer</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/mental-health/addiction/news/20240501/reclassification-of-marijuana-doesnt-mean-its-safer?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>You shouldn’t draw major conclusions about the safety of marijuana amid the recent announcement that federal regulators may reclassify the drug, experts are cautioning.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 23:29:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Solving the Housing Crisis: What Lawmakers Must Do to Support Investors and Boost Housing Supply</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/what-lawmakers-can-do-to-spur-housing-growth-and-help-investors</link><description>There’s a critical lack of affordable housing. This housing shortage began following the 2008 financial crisis and worsened during the pandemic, and now, not enough homes have been built to meet current […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 16:26:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>1 month left to submit nominations for Startup Battlefield 200</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/02/1-month-left-to-submit-nominations-for-startup-battlefield-200-2/</link><description>Here’s your shot across the bow — there’s a little over one month left to nominate your startup for Startup Battlefield 200 at Disrupt. Join this elite group for a new and awesome opportunity at TechCrunch Disrupt. It’s positively packed with perks and possibilities to get your company to the next level. Don’t delay: Apply to […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 17:00:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>They Killed Their Abusive Partners. Now Their Sentences Could Be Reconsidered.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/27/oklahoma-oregon-minnesota-domestic-violence</link><description>Oklahoma could re-examine how it punishes people whose crimes came after years of domestic abuse. Other states may follow.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Female Doctors Better? Here's What to Know</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/women/news/20240501/are-female-doctors-better-heres-what-to-know?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>A new study suggests female doctors may provide patients better care, especially when those patients are women. Here's what to know.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 18:11:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rookie Investor? Never Make This $40,000 Mistake</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-400</link><description>This episode could make you $40,000. Seriously, one property management mistake cost our own expert investor, Dave Meyer, anywhere from $30,000 to $40,000, BUT it’s easier to avoid than you […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 07:02:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spotify quietly moves lyrics behind a paywall</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/02/spotify-is-quietly-moves-lyrics-behind-a-paywall/</link><description>Following various reports citing frustrated posts from users on Reddit, Spotify is quietly confirming the change.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:49:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Being Trans in Prison Is Really Like</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/26/trans-prison-voices-gender-essay</link><description>Amid a wave of anti-trans legislation, and the violence that often follows, four people share their experiences in the criminal justice system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 11:00:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NIH’s Eliseo Pérez-Stable, MD, Talks Health Disparities, Biology, Behavior, and Culture</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/a-to-z-guides/features/nimhd-perez-stable-health-disparities?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Eliseo Pérez-Stable, MD, director of the National Institute on Minority Health and Health Disparities, talks about health disparities and how his studies aim to improve interventions in clinical settings and across communities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 22:06:41 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>