<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 01:07:09 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>State Capitalism in Private Markets: Mission Creep</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/03/state-capitalism-in-private-markets-mission-creep/</link><description>Governments relish mingling in markets. Yet, if past policies are any guide, taxpayers are being shortchanged.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 12:30:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>London's Royal Opera House plans a new renaissance starting with a name change — and potential Netflix series</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/04/londons-royal-opera-house-unveils-new-renaissance-name-change-potential-netflix-series-covent-garden/</link><description>To fill a multimillion-pound funding gap, the institution will begin streaming on social media sites such as YouTube and will team up with brands.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Implementation Shortfalls Hamstring Factor Strategies</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/01/implementation-shortfalls-hamstring-factor-strategies/</link><description>Smart rebalancing rules help portfolio managers capture more of the return that is inherent in their factor strategies. Concentrating on “priority best” trading improves factor portfolio performance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 11:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Europe’s largest smart city arises from the ashes of Greece’s debt crisis</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/04/greece-building-europes-largest-smart-city-ellinikon-after-debt-crisis/</link><description>Spread across 6,200 acres outside of Athens, Greece, Ellinikon will transform the coastline and the country.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IFRS Accounting Standard Will Support Better Investment Decisions</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/30/ifrs-accounting-standard-will-support-better-investment-decisions/</link><description>IFRS 18 responds to investors' concerns about challenges in comparing companies' financial performance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 11:34:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The U.K. economy could stare down long-term irrelevance without immigration</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/04/think-about-europe-but-everything-a-little-worse-the-u-k-economy-could-stare-down-long-term-irrelevance-without-immigration/</link><description>The U.K. is expected to grow more slowly than most of the world's developed nations this year, but it can save itself in the long run.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meir Statman: Your State of Mind Influences Your Investing Success</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/29/meir-statman-your-state-of-mind-influences-your-investing-success/</link><description>Meir Statman shares his insights on the broader aspects of financial well-being and its interconnection with life satisfaction.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 12:58:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>75% of Americans think mental health issues are treated worse than physical illness, new survey says. Here’s why</title><link>https://fortune.com/well/2024/05/03/gallup-poll-mental-health-vs-physical-illness/</link><description>The older the survey respondents, the more likely they were to think mental health issues are treated worse than physical ones.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 02:25:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: Trailblazers, Heroes, and Crooks</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/26/book-review-trailblazers-heroes-and-crooks/</link><description>Stephen Foerster, CFA, extracts lessons from exceptional episodes in financial history that ordinary investors and seasoned professionals alike can put to profitable use. The bonus is that you'll be entertained from start to finish.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Right, wrong, and a moment for clarity: Why universities must adopt a zero-tolerance policy</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/03/columbia-university-protests-palestinian-gaza-israel-antisemitism/</link><description>The right to protest does not equal the right to cause the chaos roiling Columbia and other universities, writes Capitolis CEO Gil Mandelzis.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 01:21:48 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>