<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 07:00:41 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The 8 Biggest Reasons I’m Excited About BPCON</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/reasons-to-attend-bpcon</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>This must-attend event features top real estate insights, unmatched networking, and a luxury all-inclusive experience.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 20:54:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nancy Pelosi criticizes California AI bill as ‘ill-informed’</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/17/nancy-pelosi-criticizes-california-ai-bill-as-ill-informed/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Congresswoman Nancy Pelosi issued a statement late yesterday laying out her opposition to SB 1047, a California bill that seeks to regulate AI. “The view of many of us in Congress is that SB 1047 is well-intentioned but ill-informed,” Pelosi said. She noted that other congresspeople from the Bay Area — Zoe Lofgren, Anna Eshoo, […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Prosecutors Fight Exonerations</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/17/wrongful-conviction-innocence-claims-missouri-st-louis</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>As laws are passed to support the wrongfully convicted, some officials in the legal system push back.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Investors: Make Sure to Capitalize On “Resolutions of Unacceptable Conditions”</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/dealing-with-resolutions-of-unacceptable-conditions</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Inspections are important because you need to know what you're getting into, but they're equally important for the negotiations that can occur after.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 19:52:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Palantir CEO Alex Karp is ‘not going to apologize’ for military work</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/17/palantir-ceo-alex-karp-is-not-going-to-apologize-for-military-work/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Data analytics company Palantir has faced criticism and even protests over its work with the military, police, and U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement, but co-founder and CEO Alex Karp isn’t interested in “the apology show.” In a lengthy New York Times profile, Karp told writer Maureen Dowd that the company has “a consistently pro-Western view” […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 22:11:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FAQ: How The Marshall Project Is Covering the 2024 Election</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/16/election-faq-crime-politics</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Learn more about who we are and how we choose what political stories to cover.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rookie Reply: Preparing for a Market Crash, Ending Leases, &amp; Building Teams</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-445</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>As a new investor, a strong real estate team is crucial to your success—especially when you’re looking to land your first deal, complete your first rehab project, or invest out-of-state. […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 10:00:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Porsche NA CEO Timo Resch is betting on ‘choice’ to survive the turbulent EV market</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/17/why-porsche-na-ceo-timo-resch-is-betting-on-choice-to-survive-the-turbulent-ev-market/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Timo Resch is basking in the sun. That’s literally true, as we speak on a gloriously clear California day at the Quail, one of Monterey Car Week’s most prestigious events. But it’s figuratively true as well, as Resch, who took the CEO role at Porsche Cars North America (PCNA) last November, is in a very […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 20:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Mother on a Mission for Full Police Transparency</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/16/police-beating-ulysses-wilkerson-mother-video</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Troy, Alabama, police severely beat Ulysses Wilkerson when he was 17. Seven years later, his mom, Angela Williams, is still fighting for answers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BiggerNews: What Happens if the Housing Market Crashes (&amp; What Will Cause It)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-1005</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Recession fears are increasing. The stock market has taken substantial hits, housing inventory is climbing, and bank account balances are starting to fall. So, with more economic turmoil, we have […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 10:00:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Google takes on OpenAI with Gemini Live</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/17/google-takes-on-openai-with-gemini-live/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Made by Google was this week, featuring a full range of reveals from Google’s biggest hardware event. Google unveiled its new lineup of Pixel 9 phones, including the $1,799 Pixel 9 Fold Pro; advanced AI-powered photo-editing tools; and the new Pixel Buds Pro 2, which are infused with Gemini AI. The company also announced Gemini […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 18:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How the 1968 DNC in Chicago Devolved into ‘Unrestrained and Indiscriminate Police Violence’</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/14/chicago-dnc-protests-police-reforms</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>As protesters prepare for the Democratic National Convention in Chicago next week, a half-century old report provides lessons for preventing chaos.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 11:00:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Retiring Early Before 30 and Why You DON’T Need Millions for FIRE</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-555</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>This might be the fastest path to FIRE we’ve ever seen. In just two years, Emily and James were able to retire early and travel the world full-time. They didn’t […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 07:01:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OpenAI’s new voice mode let me talk with my phone, not to it</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/17/openais-new-voice-mode-let-me-talk-with-my-phone-not-to-it/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>I’ve been playing around with OpenAI’s Advanced Voice Mode for the last week, and it’s the most convincing taste I’ve had of an AI-powered future yet. This week, my phone laughed at jokes, made them back to me, asked me how my day was, and told me it’s having “a great time.” I was talking […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aaron Sankin is The Marshall Project’s new Deputy Data Editor</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/13/aaron-sankin-is-the-marshall-projects-new-deputy-data-editor</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Sankin brings deep experience with ambitious data projects.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 20:00:24 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>