<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 13:51:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Rookie Reply: Build Your Portfolio OR Pay Off Debt &amp; Tenant Conflict 101</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-431</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Buying a house is a HUGE decision, whether you’re an experienced investor or a first-time homebuyer. The last thing you want is to get in over your head with a […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 07:02:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From Ethan Choi to Spencer Peterson, venture capitalists continue to play musical chairs</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/12/from-connie-chan-to-ethan-kurzweil-venture-capitalists-continue-to-play-musical-chairs/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>When Keith Rabois announced he was leaving Founders Fund to return to Khosla Ventures in January, it came as a shock to many in the venture capital ecosystem — and not just because Rabois is a big name in the industry. It was surprising because unlike in many other fields, venture capitalists don’t traditionally move […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 18:20:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jackson, Mississippi, Wants Curfew Centers to Cut Crime. Here’s What Other Cities Learned.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/09/jackson-mississippi-youth-curfew-centers</link><description>After a teen’s murder, city officials hope a curfew and youth centers will get kids off the street. Young people are skeptical.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 11:00:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BiggerNews: Rate Cut Chances Increase as New “Affordable” Markets Emerge</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-987</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Will the new jobs report finally prompt the Fed to cut rates, leading to you scoring a lower mortgage rate? With multifamily rents still falling, should we fear a nosediving […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 07:02:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Archer’s vision of an air taxi network could benefit from Southwest customer data</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/12/archers-vision-of-an-air-taxi-network-could-benefit-from-southwest-customer-data/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Archer Aviation and Southwest Airlines are teaming up to figure out what it will take to build out a network of electric air taxis at California airports. Southwest’s customer data is at the heart of it. The two companies signed a memorandum of understanding Friday, which sets the foundation for Archer to tap Southwest’s customer […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 17:39:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Love Beyond Bars: Miguel and Silvia</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/05/photo-essay-wrongful-conviction-love-story</link><description>While Miguel Solorio did 25 years for a crime he didn’t commit, his wife, Silvia, was right by his side. Here’s their California love story in pictures.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fat FI by 23: Building a 7-Figure Income &amp; 8-Figure Portfolio in 3 Years</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-545</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Fat FI and generational wealth in THREE years?! How is that possible? The sooner you forge good money habits, the sooner YOU can achieve your FI goal. Today’s guest wanted […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 07:01:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wikipedia’s mobile website finally gets a dark mode — here’s how to turn it on</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/12/wikipedias-mobile-website-finally-gets-a-dark-mode-heres-how-to-turn-it-on/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>If you visited the Wikipedia website on mobile this week, you might have seen a pop-up indicating that dark mode is ready for prime time. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 17:12:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Crime Rates and the 2024 Election: What You Need to Know</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/27/trump-and-biden-spar-over-crime-rates-ahead-of-their-debate-what-do-we-really-know</link><description>As crime data again becomes a flashpoint in the presidential campaign, experts push for better national statistics.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>These 11 Markets Used to Be America’s Hot Spots. Now They’ve Gone Cold.</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/11-formerly-hot-markets-that-are-not-so-hot-anymore</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>The pandemic-fueled explosion of growth has waned, and now these real estate hot spots have gotten icy.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 22:30:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What the AT&amp;T phone records data breach means for you</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/12/what-the-att-call-records-data-breach-means-for-you/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The giant U.S. telco lost the information of around 110 million customers. Here’s what you need to know. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 17:02:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Death Row Prisoner’s Parting Interview</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/24/texas-death-row-prisoner-final-interview</link><description>Days before his scheduled execution in Texas, Ramiro Gonzales speaks on faith, legacy — and apologizing to the family of his victim, Bridget Townsend.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Housing Market “Stuck” Until 2026 as Insurance Prices Rise, Rents Slow</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-233</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>See Dave, Henry, James, and Kathy at BPCon2024 in Cancún, Mexico! Grab your ticket here! The housing market is “stuck” and may stay that way for the next two years. […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 07:02:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TechCrunch Minute: FTC finds ‘dark patterns’ in subscription apps</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/video/techcrunch-minute-ftc-finds-dark-patterns-in-subscription-apps/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>A new study from the Federal Trade Commission looks at the “dark patterns” that subscription apps and websites use to get more money or data from their users. “Dark pattern” is actually the term used in the FTC report, and it refers to manipulative design techniques that are supposed to make users do something they […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The New Battle Over an Old Institution: Forced Prison Labor</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/22/prison-slavery-forced-labor-lawsuits-bills</link><description>Inside the latest legal and legislative efforts to close state constitutional loopholes that allow slavery as punishment for a crime.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>