<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 07:21:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>I See a Summer Rally Coming</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/i-see-a-summer-rally-coming/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, Ross here. Welcome to a new trading week where some see stalling, I see a set stage for a summer rally. Just last week, the market triggered a Power Trend—a strong indicator developed by experts at Investors Business Daily, now pointing us towards significant upward momentum. This isn’t just another fluke; it’s a rare occurrence, the third in the last five years, and it’s showing all the signs of an impending rally similar to the one last November that saw the market soar relentlessly. Ready to capitalize on this? Join me at 11 a.m. Eastern for a masterclass where I’ll dive into how to position yourself with the top corporate insiders for what could be the run of the season. We'll uncover high-potential stocks with insider secrets that are poised for a takeoff. Don’t wait—spots are filling up. The post I See a Summer Rally Coming appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What's an old-school guy like me doing with a Tesla Cybertruck?</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/29/whats-an-old-school-guy-like-me-doing-with-a-tesla-cybertruck/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/crop/1569x883+0+204/resize/800x450!/format/jpg/quality/85/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/23122119/Kirbys-fleet-hi-res.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Green , Tesla , Truck , Electric , Special and Limited Editions Continue reading What's an old-school guy like me doing with a Tesla Cybertruck? What's an old-school guy like me doing with a Tesla Cybertruck? originally appeared on Autoblog on Wed, 29 May 2024 06:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stay-at-Home Mom to “Accidental” Investor with a $600K/Year Business</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-412</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Want to invest but fear you don’t have enough money to get started? Building a profitable real estate business could be the answer. This strategy allowed today’s guest to not […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 07:02:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>8 YA Books for Fans of Greek Mythology</title><link>https://bookriot.com/ya-books-for-fans-of-greek-mythology/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Untitled-design-2024-05-28T111318.124.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>Which Greek mythological stories do you love to see retold?</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sharing Fun Facts About Yourself: 22 Examples &amp; Ideas</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/fun-facts-about-me/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fun-facts-about-me</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Asking to share some fun facts about yourself is a common icebreaker that’s used during job interviews. But the quality of your answer still matters. This guide will help you come up with some ideas for crafting a response that starts the interview on a good note. Table of contents Ideas for Sharing Fun Facts […] The post Sharing Fun Facts About Yourself: 22 Examples &amp; Ideas appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 15:26:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Becoming Confident in Parenting Abilities</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/confidence-in-parenting/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=confidence-in-parenting</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Parental self-efficacy (i.e., a parent’s confidence in their own ability to care for their infant and respond to the infant’s needs) is the first step to a good parent-child relationship. Research has explored the development of maternal self-efficacy beginning during pregnancy and continuing after childbirth. Mothers who have previous childbirth and […] The post Becoming Confident in Parenting Abilities appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 10:06:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ConocoPhillips to buy Marathon Oil in $17.1 billion all-stock deal that bolsters shale assets</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/29/conocophillips-to-buy-marathon-oil-in-17point1-billion-all-stock-deal-that-bolsters-shale-assets.html</link><description></description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 12:11:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dance Moms' Kelly Hyland Reveal Breast Cancer Diagnosis</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1402471/dance-moms-kelly-hyland-reveals-breast-cancer-diagnosis?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>For Dance Moms' Kelly Hyland, it was a series of compliments that initially set off internal alarm bells. "The first red flag was my significant weight loss," the reality TV alum told E! News in...</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rethinking Retirement Planning Amidst Aging Demographic Frontiers</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/28/rethinking-retirement-planning-amidst-aging-demographic-frontiers/</link><description>Forward-thinking approaches to policy and wealth management are needed to ensure a better financial future across generations and income brackets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 20:32:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Inflation's persistence is killing hope for a Fed rate cut in 2024</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/29/inflations-persistence-killing-hope-fed-reserve-interest-rate-cut-2024/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/AP24149743155138-e1716979098496.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The Fed's mandate is to strike a balance between keeping rates high enough to control inflation yet not so high as to damage the job market.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 12:06:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Print Mixing For Summer</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/print-mixing-for-summer/</link><description>Outfit Details: Bode Top, Zimmermann Skirt (longer version here &amp; dress version here), Prada Sandals, Chanel Bag (similar here), Marisa Klass Necklace I’ve always embraced the art of… The post Print Mixing For Summer appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 18:30:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The ear is wormed</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/a87YWed</link><description>Tags: germany , outlander , europe , together 8644 points, 849 comments.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 12:20:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Canada’s New Women’s Soccer League Unveils Name, Logo</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/28/canadas-new-womens-soccer-league-unveils-name-logo/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Northern Super League will play its inaugural season in 2025 with teams in Ottawa, Montréal, Vancouver, Calgary, Toronto and Halifax</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 21:39:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Clean Energy Ventures avoided the pandemic bubble and raised a $305M fund</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/29/how-clean-energy-ventures-avoided-the-pandemic-bubble-and-raised-a-305m-fund/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>When other firms were investing and raising eye-popping sums, Clean Energy Ventures took a different approach. It appears to be paying off. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Legal Doctrine That Shields Police From Many Lawsuits May Be Losing Support</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/25/police-mississippi-courts-judges-qualified-immunity</link><description>A federal judge in Mississippi joined other courts in recently rejecting police arguments that qualified immunity protected their actions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Strawberry Salsa (5 Ingredients)</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/strawberry-salsa/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Add a burst of fresh, fruity flavor to your table with this Strawberry Salsa. This quick and easy recipe combines…</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kim Kardashian Tells People to Follow Mason Disick, Who's Now on Instagram</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/28/kim-kardashian-tells-fans-follow-mason-disick-instagram-account/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Kim Kardashian is welcoming one important family member back into the spotlight -- pointing the fact that her nephew, Mason Disick, is finally on Instagram ... and sending folks to his page. The SKIMS founder took to her IG Stories Tuesday,…</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 07:21:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Federal Experts Talk Bird Flu ‘What Ifs’ in WebMD Live Event</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/cold-and-flu/news/20240516/federal-experts-talk-bird-flu-what-ifs?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>WebMD brought together experts from four federal agencies to talk prevention, monitoring, and what the “what ifs” of bird flu might look like.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:50:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Best Air Purifying Plants</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/best-air-purifying-plants/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>We love any excuse to buy more plants, and you may have heard they can improve your home’s indoor air quality. But before you blow your paycheck in the name of a healthier home, let’s dive deeper into plants’ air purifying powers. We’ll share which plants we recommend and what benefits you can actually expect from them. We’ve heard for years about how plants act as natural air filters for your home. So let’s dive a little deeper, shall we? 7 Air Purifying Plants If you just came here for a list, our favorite air purifying houseplants are bulleted below. The best part is these are all beautiful, low-maintenance plants. Many also appear on our best low-light indoor plants list too! Dracaena (including Corn Plant ) Snake Plant Aglaonema English Ivy Pothos Bamboo Palm Spider Plant There are certainly more that could be included here, but we narrowed it to the ones that are most often cited by experts AND the plants that we think look best too. Continue reading Best Air Purifying Plants at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 14:15:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Did This Market Move Catch You by Surprise?</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/did-this-market-move-catch-you-by-surprise/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, Ross here. Did yesterday's market dip catch you off guard? It erased last week's gains, but from a technical standpoint, it's a typical response after hitting new all-time highs. Now, the real question is how the support from March's highs will hold up. Even if it breaks, expect some sideways movement—no need to panic. Remember, markets need to shake out the overeager traders to climb higher, and that's exactly what we're seeing. It's the perfect setup for my Stealth Trades strategy, which leverages the moves of big institutional money. In fact, this Memorial Day, I’m offering a special on my strategy for just 99 cents for a full year. Don't miss out on this opportunity to align with the big players and position for the next surge. Grab it before the weekend! The post Did This Market Move Catch You by Surprise? appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2025 BMW 3 Series adopts mild-hybrid power across the board</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/28/2025-bmw-3-series-refresh-update-reveal/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/28141231/P90549616-copy.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: BMW , Hybrid , Luxury , Sedan Continue reading 2025 BMW 3 Series adopts mild-hybrid power across the board 2025 BMW 3 Series adopts mild-hybrid power across the board originally appeared on Autoblog on Tue, 28 May 2024 18:45:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 23:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Buy a Home (or Entire Neighborhood) With Your Friends and Family</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-962</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Imagine living in a home where your next-door neighbors are your best friends or family members. We know you’ve thought about it before—starting a compound with all the people you […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 07:02:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2024 Summer Reading Clubs for Kids and Teens</title><link>https://bookriot.com/summer-reading-clubs-for-kids-and-teens-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/image-of-children-reading-outside-in-the-grass.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>Looking for free summer reading clubs for kids and teens? This guide offers a range of clubs, including those from Half Price Books, Pizza Hut, and more.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 553</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-553/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-553</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Tools and technology change rapidly. Yet as wonderful as technology can be, it doesn’t replace the need for human connection through interactions. Keep this in mind as you are searching for a new job. It’s your human connections that often open doors! In this week’s collection of news and tips for job seekers, you’ll find: […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 553 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 12:19:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A case for public preschool: New study reveals preschool benefits to be longer-lasting and substantial</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/benefits-of-public-preschool/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=benefits-of-public-preschool</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Preschool lays a foundation for elementary school students to succeed. In the United States, as children approach kindergarten entry, it is increasingly common for 4-year-olds to be in non-parental group care and education, often in a center- or school-based setting where they can learn alongside peers. For children from low-income communities, […] The post A case for public preschool: New study reveals preschool benefits to be longer-lasting and substantial appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 08:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Saudi Aramco to reportedly sell $10 billion to $20 billion worth of shares in new offering</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/29/saudi-aramco-to-sell-stock-in-new-offering-report.html</link><description>The reported new offering would come at an opportune time for the kingdom, which is spending heavily on megaprojects while seeing lower oil revenue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 12:04:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 40 Most Popular Amazon Items E! Readers Bought This Month</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1402539/the-40-most-popular-amazon-items-e-readers-bought-this-month-bracelets-garbage-disposal-cleaner-more?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>We independently selected these products because we love them, and we think you might like them at these prices. E! has affiliate relationships, so we may get a commission if you purchase...</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: The New World Economy in 5 Trends</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/24/book-review-the-new-world-economy-in-5-trends/</link><description>A diligent economist and an eclectic bookworm serve up an analysis of megatrends that will have the greatest impact on economies and investments: innovation, productivity, climate, multiglobalization, debt, and aging.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 12:22:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Russia-linked cyber attacks on Europe have doubled since 2023, top EU cybersecurity official says</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/29/russia-cyber-attacks-europe-doubled-since-2023-eu-cybersecurity-official/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2007336257-e1716978157711.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Juhan Lepassaar, head of the European Union Agency for Cybersecurity, said that attack methods — while mostly unsuccessful — were often tried out in Ukraine before being expanded to EU countries.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 11:50:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Week’s Favorites From Amazon</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/amazon-sundays-5-19-24/</link><description>Welcome to our latest favorites from Amazon that I’m especially excited to share! This week includes an array of colorful… The post This Week’s Favorites From Amazon appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 05:00:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Women: \u2615\ufe0f</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/azxEjvx</link><description>Tags: indonesia , wtf , random , funny , anime 3412 points, 239 comments.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 12:20:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Baylor Bears Unveil New Football Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/28/baylor-bears-unveil-new-football-uniforms/college/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Baylor unveiled new football uniforms on Tuesday morning, marking the first overhaul to the Bears' look since the 2019 season.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 20:00:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OpenAI signs 100K PwC workers to ChatGPT’s enterprise tier as PwC becomes its first resale partner</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/29/openai-signs-on-100k-pwc-workers-to-its-chatgpt-enterprise-tier-as-the-consultant-becomes-its-first-resale-partner/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>PwC, the management consulting giant, will become OpenAI’s biggest customer to date, covering 100,000 users. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 09:59:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Out of the Blue: The Rise and Fall of a Black Cop</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/23/black-police-officers-cleveland-black-shield</link><description>After Cleveland officer Vincent Montague shot a Black man, he got promoted. Then he allied with Black Lives Matter, and his life went off the rails.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zesty BBQ Chicken (5 Ingredients)</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/zesty-bbq-chicken/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>This zesty BBQ chicken is an easy crockpot recipe that only takes 5 ingredients to make! The slow-cooked tender pulled…</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Molly Ringwald Details Being 'Taken Advantage of' By 'Predators'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/28/molly-ringwald-taken-advantage-predators-hollywood/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Molly Ringwald is opening up about her experiences as a teen star ... sharing her time in Hollywood was more daunting than fans realize, 'cause she says she was preyed upon. The 'Breakfast Club' actress reflected on her early career during the…</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 07:21:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What’s Next in Health Care for Older Adults: Questions and Answers With John Whyte, MD</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/blog-aging-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>As WebMD’s chief medical officer, John Whyte, MD, is in a unique position to see both the current state of medical care for America’s older adults and the way things are trending for the future. We asked him to share his insight on a few topics, along with a bit of advice.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:29:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Weekend In New Orleans With Kids</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/new-orleans-with-kids/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Since our travel guides to Charleston with kids and Palm Springs with kids have elicited requests for more travel ideas with kids, we’re back with an overdue recap of our 3-night trip to New Orleans. We’d never been to The Big Easy before and were impressed by how family-friendly the city is. It’s not all booze, beads, and Bourbon Street! So here’s a look at where we stayed, what we did, and what we’re excited to do next time we go back – because we will definitely go back! The four of us (well, five if you count our chihuahua!) went to NOLA for 3 nights in November of 2022. At the time, our kids were 8 and 12 years old. So unfortunately we can’t vouch for our suggestions being a good fit for toddlers or younger children. Although I’m sure ours would’ve loved the Louisiana Children’s Museum and Storyland playground back in the day! Continue reading A Weekend In New Orleans With Kids at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 17:17:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Big of a Problem is Inflation Really?</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/how-big-of-a-problem-is-inflation-really/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, Ross here. As we navigate through the bull market, one looming question persists: How big of a problem is inflation really? Despite the alarm bells rung by bears and the media, our latest data shows a decrease in the number of S&amp;P 500 companies concerned about inflation during their earnings calls. This signals a potentially overstated issue, with corporate earnings—key market drivers—still on solid ground. If you're watching the market meander sideways and finding it "boring," you might be missing out. Sideways markets are ripe for strategic positioning, often preceding significant movements. Join me tomorrow at 10 a.m. Eastern for a masterclass where I'll delve into insider trading insights, showing you how to distinguish between high and low signal trades and uncover the top-performing insiders. Plus, I'll share an exclusive opportunity that's just come onto my radar. Don’t miss this chance to learn from the insiders—reserve your spot now! The post How Big of a Problem is Inflation Really? appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2025 BMW M3 bakes in 3 Series updates; Competition xDrive gets power bump</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/28/2025-bmw-m3-bakes-in-3-series-updates-competition-xdrive-gets-power-bump/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/28134125/P90551006.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: BMW , Luxury , Performance , Sedan Continue reading 2025 BMW M3 bakes in 3 Series updates; Competition xDrive gets power bump 2025 BMW M3 bakes in 3 Series updates; Competition xDrive gets power bump originally appeared on Autoblog on Tue, 28 May 2024 18:30:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 23:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Prepare Your Rental Property for Tenants</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/how-to-prepare-rental-property-for-tenants</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Rehabbing a home isn’t the same as preparing a home for rental, though. Not all homes require rehabbing, but all rental properties must be prepared for prospective renters.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 04:59:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>8 Spectacular Backlist Sci-Fi and Fantasy Series Worth Reading</title><link>https://bookriot.com/backlist-sci-fi-and-fantasy-series-worth-reading/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Untitled-design-2024-05-28T104048.144.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>"This list is a pretty balanced blend of science fiction and fantasy, spanning cultures and space, past and future, authors familiar and under-the-radar."</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 552</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-552/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-552</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>When you are searching for a job, you will inevitably run into unexpected scenarios. You will have questions, experience self-doubt and even feel discouraged. You’ll also experience great wins, meet wonderful people and discover new things about yourself. That’s the roller-coaster of job search. Consider Summary Sunday your resource for getting questions answered and showing […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 552 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 11:37:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fathers’ views on family and work after COVID-19 lockdowns</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/fathers-views-on-family-and-work-after-covid-19-lockdowns/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fathers-views-on-family-and-work-after-covid-19-lockdowns</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Fathers often want to be present for their children and contribute to household tasks, but they can lack opportunities and confidence; they may see themselves as “helpers” instead of parents. Australian fathers in our small study reported that they spent more time with their children during the COVID-19 lockdowns, and they […] The post Fathers’ views on family and work after COVID-19 lockdowns appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dick's Sporting Goods raises guidance, says shoppers are spending more on sneakers and athletic gear</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/29/dicks-sporting-goods-dks-earnings-q1-2024.html</link><description>Dick's Sporting Goods saw sales grow well ahead of estimates, following behind other retailers that said consumers are spending on new clothes and shoes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 12:02:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Brittany Cartwright Claps Back at Comments About Son Cruz's Well-Being</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1402567/brittany-cartwright-claps-back-at-comments-on-well-being-of-her-and-jax-taylors-son-cruz?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>Brittany Cartwright is shutting down her haters. After splitting with estranged husband Jax Taylor in February, the Valley star shared an emotional message slamming people for speculating...</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 03:06:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Factor Strategies Belong in Your Completion Portfolio Toolkit</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/23/factor-strategies-belong-in-your-completion-portfolio-toolkit/</link><description>Why wouldn't you include factor strategies in your completion portfolio? A review of the two commonly used approaches for managing institutional assets highlights their symbiotic nature.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 19:09:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Uber gears up for Paris Olympics by offering free cruises across the Seine and discounts to ease the load on public transport networks</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/29/uber-paris-olympics-free-cruises-seine-river-discounts-public-transport/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1602763816-e1716975585733.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Paris is expecting 30% more visitors this summer than usual—and Uber's support may help the city's public transport systems cope with the strain.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 11:39:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Warm Weather Hair Care</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/warm-weather-hair-care/</link><description>Outfit Details: Cala de la Cruz Dress, Emme Parsons Sandals, Saint Laurent Sunglasses One of the essential parts of summer… The post Warm Weather Hair Care appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 05:00:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Took her a while</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/azxEVAN</link><description>Tags: wholesome 4863 points, 427 comments.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 12:20:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Looking Back at the Dodgers and Giants Move from N.Y. to California</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/28/looking-back-at-the-dodgers-and-giants-move-from-n-y-to-california/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>On May 28, 1957, the National League approved one of the most significant relocations in the history of professional sports: the simultaneous move of the New York Giants and Brooklyn Dodgers to California. The decision marked the beginning of a new era of baseball, bringing the sport’s top talent to</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 19:14:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>72 hours left of the Disrupt early-bird sale</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/29/72-hours-left-disrupt-early-bird-sale/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Tech enthusiasts and entrepreneurs, the clock is ticking! With just 72 hours remaining until the early-bird ticket deadline for TechCrunch Disrupt 2024, now is the time to secure your spot and save big on this premier tech event. Don’t miss out on the opportunity to join us in San Francisco for an unforgettable experience filled […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Marshall Project Wins Prestigious Robert F. Kennedy Journalism Award for Criminal Justice</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/21/marshall-project-rfk-award</link><description>The award recognizes our 2023 investigation exposing lax prison discipline for abusive guards in New York state prisons.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Key Lime Pie Bars</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/key-lime-pie-bars/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key lime pie bars are classic key lime pie flavors baked into delightful little bars. They have a buttery graham…</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jason Kelce Claps Back At Social Media Troll, Says Wife Isn't 'Homemaker'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/28/jason-kelce-claps-back-social-media-troll-wife-not-homemaker-harrison-butker-commencement-speech/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Jason Kelce is adamant his wife isn't "a homemaker" ... saying in response to a social media troll this week that he considers Kylie Kelce his partner and his "equal" when it comes to raising their family. Kelce faced off with the heckler on X on…</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 07:21:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Get the Care You Need in a COVID-19 World</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/covid-senior-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>What to expect at the doctor’s office, hospitals, and long-term care facilities, the future of telemedicine, and how to get the best care during COVID-19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 19:50:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Easy Low-Light Indoor Plants</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/easy-low-light-indoor-plants/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>I used to think every houseplant needed a sunny corner or bright windowsill to thrive. But it turns out many of our favorite go-to houseplants do just fine in shady corners and low-light locations. So before you write off your house as too dark to sustain plant life, check out this list of the best indoor plants for low light. You might be surprised at how many good options there are! Our upstairs family room is the brightest room we’ve ever owned thanks to big unobstructed windows on all 4 sides. But most of our indoor plants live downstairs, where we get far less natural light. Luckily, that hasn’t stopped us from growing our collection of happy healthy houseplants. 9 Houseplants That Don’t Need A Lot Of Light Here are our favorite low-light indoor plants. We list a lot more info on them below, but here’s a quick list to bring on your next trip to the plant store: Snake Plant ZZ Plant Pothos Heartleaf Philodendron English Ivy Aglaonema Cast Iron Plant Monstera Parlor Palm Perhaps our favorite part of this list is that these aren’t ugly “consolation plants” that people begrudgingly buy for dark homes. Continue reading Easy Low-Light Indoor Plants at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 14:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Don’t Wait for This to Happen</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/dont-wait-for-this-to-happen/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Markets are soaring to new all-time highs, and the bears are out in full force. But don't be fooled—this bull market extends beyond the U.S. Today's chart highlights the All-Country World Index, showcasing the global market's performance. It’s at an all-time high too, proving the American bull market is not an outlier. Tune in at 3 p.m. Eastern for my live masterclass, where I'll show you how to position yourself for super performance by following corporate insiders. Don't miss this opportunity! The post Don’t Wait for This to Happen appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 15:55:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SUVs account for a quarter of all new demand for oil, 20% of the increase in emissions</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/28/suvs-account-for-a-quarter-of-all-new-demand-for-oil-20-of-the-increase-in-emissions/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/crop/5616x3159+0+239/resize/800x450!/format/jpg/quality/85/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/28175458/costco_gas_station.jpeg</image_url><description>Filed under: Government/Legal , Green , Emissions , Fuel Efficiency , SUV Continue reading SUVs account for a quarter of all new demand for oil, 20% of the increase in emissions SUVs account for a quarter of all new demand for oil, 20% of the increase in emissions originally appeared on Autoblog on Tue, 28 May 2024 17:55:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 22:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>5 Insights on the Current State of Commercial Real Estate That Investors Must Know About</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/5-insights-on-the-current-state-of-commercial-real-estate-that-investors-must-know-about</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>This article is presented by Walker &amp; Dunlop. Read our editorial guidelines for more information. If you are, or thinking about, investing in commercial real estate, what should you know about the […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 20:36:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>9 of the Best Bookish Tote Bags for Beach Reads on the Go</title><link>https://bookriot.com/best-bookish-tote-bags-for-beach-reads-on-the-go/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/chairs.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>Tell the truth: do you have any overdue library books right now? If so, we have the *perfect* tote bag for you. - CJ Connor</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>While a little competition in the workplace might help bring out the best in everyone involved, an atmosphere rooted in envy, fear, or jealousy can do the exact opposite. This post will help you recognize signs that your coworker is threatened by you, and help you navigate the situation. 1. They Don’t Want You Involved […] The post 10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:07:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Strong Latine Identity Supports U.S. Latine Children’s Well-Being</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/a-strong-latine-identity-supports-u-s-latine-childrens-well-being/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=a-strong-latine-identity-supports-u-s-latine-childrens-well-being</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key Takeaways for caregivers Children tend to have better health and well-being when they have a strong ethnic identity (affinity and adoption of ethnicity-based self-concept). A traditional Latine cultural value (familismo) that emphasizes family bonds is also associated with better developmental outcomes. Caregivers can support the development of U.S. Latine children (and possibly other children […] The post A Strong Latine Identity Supports U.S. Latine Children’s Well-Being appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 03:03:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Clean Energy Ventures raises $305 million to back early-stage climate startups</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/29/clean-energy-ventures-raises-305-million-to-back-early-stage-climate-startups.html</link><description>Clean energy stocks may be underperforming in the public market, but in private markets there is still appetite for companies focused on decarbonization.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 12:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>20 Cooling Products for People Who Are Always Hot</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1354231/cooling-products-for-people-who-are-always-hot?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>We independently selected these deals and products because we love them, and we think you might like them at these prices. E! has affiliate relationships, so we may get a commission if you...</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 03:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>For the Analyst: Peer Benchmarking Methods to Improve Earnings Forecasts</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/21/for-the-analyst-peer-benchmarking-methods-to-improve-earnings-forecasts/</link><description>Peer benchmarking is a vexing task for financial analysts but one that is critical for forecasting earnings. This straightforward measure can help find peers for relative performance, compensation, and valuation benchmarking.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 12:47:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ONS dealing with 20% staf exodus weeks after facing strikes over return to office orders</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/29/ons-stats-body-strike-remote-work-20-staff-exodus/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1308902643-e1716976967537.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Headcount has dipped at the ONS at the same time as the stats body fights with staff over office attendance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 11:23:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coastal Breeze Style</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/coastal-breeze-style/</link><description>Outfit Details: EPHEMERA Bikini, Zankov Dress, Loro Piana Hat, Marni Bag, Hermes Bangles (similar here, less expensive here), Bottega Venita Sunglasses The weather has… The post Coastal Breeze Style appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 05:00:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>All hail Denmark</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/aLnPBOA</link><description>Tags: savage , dark humor , humor , lol , awesome 18762 points, 750 comments.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 12:20:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Utah NHL Team Logos, Colours, and Possible Uniforms for Year One</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/27/utah-nhl-team-logos-colours-and-possible-uniforms-for-year-one/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Utah’s new National Hockey League team, set to debut for the upcoming 2024-25 NHL season, will reportedly start without a permanent name or logo. However, a look at some of the early merchandise being prepared for the team has revealed what appears to be a temporary design featuring “UTAH” in</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 17:51:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Avendus, India’s top venture advisor, confirms it’s looking to raise a $350 million fund</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/28/avendus-indias-top-venture-advisor-confirms-its-looking-to-raise-a-350-million-fund/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Avendus, the top investment bank for venture deals in India, confirmed on Wednesday it is looking to raise up to $350 million for its new private equity fund. The new fund, called Future Leaders Fund III, will enable the Mumbai-headquartered firm to write larger checks and maintain a meaningful position in the startups it backs, […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 03:03:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Police Tactics at Some Pro-Palestine Protests Ignore Past Lessons</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/18/police-israel-palestine-campus-protests</link><description>While some universities have sought peaceful approaches, others have used aggressive policing that bucks research from the protests following George Floyd’s murder.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Salmon Marinade</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/salmon-marinade/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>A great salmon marinade makes your fish flavorful, tender, and juicy! This recipe gives each filet the perfect balance of…</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bam Margera Gets Married Again to Fiancée Dannii Marie</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/28/bam-margera-gets-married-again-fiancee-dannii-marie/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>4:57 PM PT -- Bam Margera announced there will be ANOTHER wedding! Just minutes ago he posted a pic of his bride, Dannii, with the caption, "Danielle Marie MARGERA, it’s official. To all family and friends there will be a November wedding in…</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 07:21:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Personal Shopper: A Savvy Black Entrepreneur Guides You to Eczema-Friendly Clothes, Creams, Cosmetics, and More</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/savvy-black-entrepreneur-guides-eczema-friendly-clothes-creams-cosmetics?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>A savvy black entrepreneur guides you on an eczema-friendly shopping spree.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:54:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/how-to-remove-wallpaper/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Wallpaper has made a big comeback as a trendy home design choice. But despite its resurgence, there are still plenty of us dealing with dingy, dated, or downright ugly old wallpaper we don’t want. In our old home, we had to remove wallpaper in so many rooms: the kitchen, the dining room, the foyer, and two different bathrooms! As we traveled from room to room removing wallpaper, we tested 4 different methods, and today we’ll share what we learned. Removing wallpaper doesn’t require special tools or lots of money. It’s a totally doable project for any homeowner. However, it can be a tedious process that can take elbow grease and patience, depending on the size of your room and the stubbornness of your wallpaper. But having removed several rooms worth of decades-old wallpaper, we can confidently say it’s worth the effort! You can also check out more before and afters of our once-wallpapered rooms. Continue reading How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:21:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Data-Backed Glimpse of the Market’s Future</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/a-data-backed-glimpse-of-the-markets-future/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>The bears keep insisting this bull market can't last, but let's dive into the data. The S&amp;P 500 has surged about 48% since its October 2022 lows. Historically, the average gain two years in is 57%, suggesting even more upside by October 2024. Ignore the naysayers and focus on the facts. Join me at 11 a.m. ET for a live masterclass where I'll show you how to align with top corporate insiders. Learn their winning strategies and spot a hot insider opportunity. Don't miss out—secure your spot now! The post A Data-Backed Glimpse of the Market’s Future appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2025 Acura MDX prices rise thanks to new tech and audio</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/28/2025-acura-mdx-prices-rise-thanks-to-new-tech-and-audio/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/28115019/2025_acura_mdx_001.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Acura , Car Buying , Crossover , SUV Continue reading 2025 Acura MDX prices rise thanks to new tech and audio 2025 Acura MDX prices rise thanks to new tech and audio originally appeared on Autoblog on Tue, 28 May 2024 16:34:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 21:34:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seeing Greene: How to Avoid High Down Payments and When to BRRRR vs. Buy New</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-961</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>One of the biggest hurdles to rental property investing? High down payments. Most lenders want you to come to the table with twenty to thirty percent down, but with home […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 07:02:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>120 Book Recommendations for Every Summer Reading Mood</title><link>https://bookriot.com/summer-book-recommendations-by-mood/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/reading-on-the-beach.png</image_url><description>How do you define "summer reading"?</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 19:26:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 551</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-551/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-551</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Job search requires writing and marketing skills. It also requires strong verbal communication. If these skills are not part of your normal work function, you’ll want some help. That’s what this week’s Summary Sunday is all about. There’s no doubt that LinkedIn is one of THE most powerful tools in your career toolbox. It contains […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 551 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 11:37:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Children caught between highly conflicted divorced parents at greater risk of mental health problems</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/children-caught-between-conflicted-divorced-parents/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=children-caught-between-conflicted-divorced-parents</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Interparental conflict after divorce escalates the risk of mental health problems in children and adolescents. Elevated levels of conflict between parents can also induce fear and worry in children about their future and whether they will be adequately taken care of. In turn, a greater fear of abandonment puts children at […] The post Children caught between highly conflicted divorced parents at greater risk of mental health problems appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 08:59:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weekly mortgage demand drops to three-month low, as rates begin climbing again</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/29/weekly-mortgage-demand-drops-to-three-month-low-as-rates-climb-again.html</link><description>After a brief pullback during much of May, mortgage rates began rising again last week.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Viral Boucle Furniture Trend &amp; How to Style It</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1402249/the-boucle-furniture-trend-is-taking-over-the-internet-heres-how-to-style-it-in-your-home?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>The products featured in this article are from brands that are available in the NBCUniversal Checkout Marketplace. If you purchase something through our links, we get a commission. Just like...</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 03:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Building LLMs in the Open-Source Community: A Call to Action for Investment Professionals</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/20/building-llms-in-the-open-source-community-a-call-to-action-for-investment-professionals/</link><description>Large language models like ChatGPT are changing the way we think about investing and reshaping roles in the investment profession.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 16:26:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The future is a state of mind: What it takes to build a future-ready company</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/29/future-ready-company-leadership-traits-bcg/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2153485379-e1716499507886.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The best and most future-ready CEOs and leaders know how to balance prudence and patience with ambition and experimentation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 10:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Colors Of The Sea</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/colors-of-the-sea/</link><description>Outfit Details: Show Me Your Mumu Coverup (also similar here), Good American Swimsuit, Miu Miu Sandals, Valentino Hat, Prada Sunglasses, Hanna Andersson Dress, Teva Sandals &amp; Stella Kids… The post Colors Of The Sea appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 05:00:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Burger</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/aZZxpNQ</link><description>Tags: wtf , humor , meme , amerimutt , random 1234 points, 255 comments.</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 12:20:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blue Jays to Unveil City Connect Uniform Thursday, Wear it Thrice for “City Week”</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/27/blue-jays-to-unveil-city-connect-uniform-thursday-wear-it-thrice-for-city-week/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Today, the Toronto Blue Jays announced some details surrounding their upcoming Nike MLB City Connect uniform release and the accompanying “City Week” promotion, which will run during their next homestand from May 31 through June 6. Things get underway on Thursday night when the Blue Jays unveil the new look</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 14:54:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>China’s $47B semiconductor fund puts chip sovereignty front and center</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/28/chinas-47b-semiconductor-fund-puts-chip-sovereignty-front-and-center/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>China has closed a third state-backed investment fund to bolster its semiconductor industry and reduce reliance on other nations, both for using and for manufacturing wafers — prioritizing what is called chip sovereignty. China’s National Integrated Circuit Industry Investment Fund, also known simply as ‘the Big Fund,’ had two previous vintages: Big Fund I (2014 […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 22:15:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Susan Chira to Step Down as The Marshall Project’s Editor-in-Chief in January</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/16/susan-chira-eic-step-down</link><description>Under her stewardship, the news nonprofit more than doubled in size, opened local newsrooms and won its second Pulitzer Prize.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>John Wayne Casserole</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/john-wayne-casserole/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>This delicious John Wayne Casserole is Mexican comfort food at its finest! Layers of seasoned ground beef, creamy cheddar cheese…</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Texas Chainsaw' Star Bill Moseley Struck by Cyclist in Hit-and-Run, Hospitalized</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/28/texas-chainsaw-massacre-actor-bill-moseley-hit-bicyclist-hospitalized/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Bill Moseley -- known for 'The Texas Chainsaw Massacre' franchise -- got an unwelcome scare of his own last week after being slammed into by a cyclist ... who apparently took off. The actor's rep tells TMZ ... it all went down in Raleigh, NC Friday…</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 07:21:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Behind the Spike in Colorectal Cancer Among Young Americans</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/colorectal-cancer/news/20240515/behind-the-spike-in-colorectal-cancer-cases?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Colorectal cancer cases increased a whopping 333% among 15- to 19-year-olds and 185% among 20- to 24-year-olds from 1999 to 2020.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:59:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aglaonema Plant – Complete Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/aglaonema-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Aglaonema, also called the Chinese Evergreen Plant, is an easy-care houseplant that lives happily in many lighting conditions – even a dark corner of our daughter’s room. There are dozens of different Aglaonema varieties, most with large tropical foliage and colors ranging from silvery-green, red, and even vibrant pink. They’re also tough to kill, so they’re a great option for forgetful plant owners or anyone looking for an easy win in the plant department. These truly have been very low maintenance for us. We purchased our two Aglaonemas (pronounced ag-lee-oh-neem-ah ) to put atop our daughter’s closet. It’s sometimes hard to distinguish different varieties, but we believe that’s an Aglaonema Silver (right) and either a Candy Cane or Princess Silver Queen (left). Aglaonema Quick Facts Here’s what you need to know about your Aglaonema at a glance: Latin name : Aglaonema is the genus under which there are 21 recognized species . Continue reading Aglaonema Plant – Complete Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:47:48 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>