<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 06:50:40 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Is the Outright Ban on a US Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC) a Mistake?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/06/20/is-the-outright-ban-on-a-us-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc-a-mistake/</link><description>Instead of outright banning a US CBDC, wouldn’t it be preferrable to establish clear and enforceable legislative guardrails?</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 17:00:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump proposed excluding tips from federal taxes.  Here’s what that would mean for workers’ take-home pay—and budget deficits</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/06/21/trump-excluding-tips-federal-taxes-workers-take-home-pay-budget-deficits/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/AP24170801520926-e1718964303726.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The Committee for a Responsible Federal Budget, a fiscal watchdog group, has estimated that exempting tips from both income and payroll taxes would reduce federal revenues by $150-$250 billion over the next decade.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 11:16:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Concerned About Market Concentration and Lofty Valuations? Consider Small Caps</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/06/19/concerned-about-market-concentration-and-lofty-valuations-consider-small-caps/</link><description>Investors are showing increased concern about large-cap stocks due to high market concentration and lofty stock valuations. Other factors combine to make a compelling case for small caps.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 17:16:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In Spain, where one in five toddlers aged 3 or 4 owns a smartphone, thousands of parents have united to say ‘no’</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/06/21/europe-one-in-five-toddlers-3-or-4-owns-smartphonethese-parents-have-united-to-say-no-spain-deepfakes-ai/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/GettyImages-904540638-e1718962260724.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The push to control smartphones in Spain comes amid a surge in cases of children viewing online pornography, sharing videos of sexual violence, or in creating deepfakes.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 10:49:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Is Systems Thinking? A Primer with Applications for Sustainable Investing</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/06/18/what-is-systems-thinking-a-primer-with-applications-for-sustainable-investing/</link><description>Systems thinking is gaining in popularity in many fields including economics, finance, and investment management. Learn what it means and how it's being applied to sustainable investing.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 16:33:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Martha’s Vineyard rentals have gotten so expensive a correctional officer switched to cleaning to earn less so she didn’t lose access to low-income housing</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/06/21/marthas-vineyard-expensive-correctional-officer-cleaning-access-low-income-housing/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/AP24172675659386-e1718962844574.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Landlords stand to make far more money from short-term tourists than from year-round residents. And many island homes are almost always vacant, their wealthy owners uninterested in renting them between fleeting visits.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 10:42:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: My Value Creation Journey</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/06/14/book-review-my-value-creation-journey/</link><description>Bartley J. Madden has produced a book that challenges business leaders and investment professionals to think outside the box systematically to solve difficult problems.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 18:04:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mothers are back at work. Here’s why we shouldn’t be too quick to celebrate</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/06/21/mothers-back-work-celebrate-labor-jobs-women-economy/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/GettyImages-1520603528-e1718962183926.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>In the absence of a social safety net, moms end up filling low-wage, no-benefit, dead-end jobs in retail, food service, home health, and childcare.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 10:36:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Private Markets’ Governance: A New Era</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/06/14/private-markets-governance-a-new-era/</link><description>Now that the SEC Private Fund Adviser rules have been struck down, it's incumbent on the industry to demonstrate how private ordering can work.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 17:49:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why going cashless has turned Sweden from one of the safest countries into a high-crime nation</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/06/21/why-going-cashless-has-turned-sweden-from-one-of-the-safest-countries-into-a-high-crime-nation/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/GettyImages-1037652702-e1718960722760.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>In just a decade fraud has almost doubled from just under 9,000 to over 23,000 in 2023.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 10:21:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>