<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 07:19:40 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>May the Books Be With You: 10 New SFF Books Out May 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/new-sci-fi-fantasy-books-may-2024/</link><description>A reluctant dragon catcher, a magebike courier in the wastelands, and more of the best SFF out this month.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Miami Grand Prix F1 Race: Everything you need to know before you go</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/article/miami-grand-prix-f1-race-everything-you-need-to-know-before-you-go/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/02/13131425/night_photo_formula_one_f1_grand_prix_race_miami_hard_rock_stadium-1.jpeg</image_url><description>Filed under:
					    Motorsports,Commerce
Continue reading Miami Grand Prix F1 Race: Everything you need to know before you go
Miami Grand Prix F1 Race: Everything you need to know before you go originally appeared on Autoblog on Wed, 1 May 2024 17:15:00 EDT.  Please see our terms for use of feeds.
Permalink | 
						Email this | 
					    Comments</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 22:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Peloton CEO Barry McCarthy to step down, company to lay off 15% of staff</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/02/peloton-ceo-barry-mccarthy-steps-down-15percent-of-staff-laid-off.html</link><description>Peloton announced Thursday that CEO Barry McCarthy will be stepping down just over two years after he took over from founder John Foley.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 12:12:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 553</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-553/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-553</link><description>Tools and technology change rapidly. Yet as wonderful as technology can be, it doesn’t replace the need for human connection through interactions. Keep this in mind as you are searching for a new job. It’s your human connections that often open doors! In this week’s collection of news and tips for job seekers, you’ll find: […]
The post Summary Sunday: Issue 553 appeared first on Career Sherpa.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 12:19:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Addicting Bean Dip</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/bean-dip/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/cheesiest_bean_dip.jpg</image_url><description>Bring out the chips and start dipping because this is the most addicting bean dip you will ever have! It’s…</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Using Solid Stain In Our Outdoor Shower</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/solid-deck-stain-outdoor-shower/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2024/04/Sherry-In-Outdoor-Shower-Featured-Image-650x542.jpg</image_url><description>In all of our years of DIYing, I don’t think we’ve ever used a solid stain before. But we recently had a project that was *perfectly* suited for it and, well, solid stain quickly won us over. It was recommended by a professional house painter to us, specifically because he thought it would be great for our outdoor shower. And we found it easy to apply, it gave us great coverage, and we got an even-better-than-we-expected result (which is always the best kind!). So here’s a post that covers all the pros &amp; cons and hows &amp; whys of solid stain. 
As you can see, the “canvas” for this staining project was our outdoor shower. We gave it a mini-makeover right after moving in, but we knew it may need more attention and care down the line. Honestly, we dreaded the task of stripping and restaining it – so many nooks &amp; crannies!
Continue reading Using Solid Stain In Our Outdoor Shower at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 17:46:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spring Clean &amp; Organize</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/spring-clean-organize/</link><description>In our household, spring cleaning is more than a seasonal task; it’s about embracing a system that keeps our home…
The post Spring Clean &amp; Organize appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 05:00:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>8 of the Best New Graphic Novels and Comics Out in May 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/new-graphic-novels-may-2024/</link><description>What's the next graphic novel on your TBR?</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aston Martin's losses balloon ahead of new model ramp-up</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/01/aston-martin-losses-balloon-ahead-of-new-model-ramp-up/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/01162819/Aston-Martin-Vantage_011.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under:
					    Earnings/Financials,Aston Martin
Continue reading Aston Martin's losses balloon ahead of new model ramp-up
Aston Martin's losses balloon ahead of new model ramp-up originally appeared on Autoblog on Wed, 1 May 2024 16:29:00 EDT.  Please see our terms for use of feeds.
Permalink | 
						Email this | 
					    Comments</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 21:29:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wayfair's losses narrow by more than $100 million after layoffs, even as sales dip</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/02/wayfair-w-earnings-q1-2024.html</link><description>Wayfair's sales fell in the first quarter, but the furniture retailer narrowed its losses by over $100 million after cutting 13% of its staff.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 12:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 552</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-552/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-552</link><description>When you are searching for a job, you will inevitably run into unexpected scenarios. You will have questions, experience self-doubt and even feel discouraged. You’ll also experience great wins, meet wonderful people and discover new things about yourself. That’s the roller-coaster of job search. Consider Summary Sunday your resource for getting questions answered and showing […]
The post Summary Sunday: Issue 552 appeared first on Career Sherpa.</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 11:37:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Bake with Yeast</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/how-to-bake-with-yeast/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/how-to-bake-with-yeast-1.jpg</image_url><description>You asked for help with yeast, so I have created a “How to Bake with Yeast” guide just for you!…</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ZZ Plant – Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/zz-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2024/04/ZZ-Plant-Close-Up-Horiztonal-650x475.jpg</image_url><description>The ZZ plant is another one of our favorite low-maintenance houseplants. They’re easy to care for, hard to kill, and always look full &amp; leafy. They’ve even earned the nickname “Eternity Plant” because they’re practically indestructible! That’s why they’re a top choice for commercial spaces, doctor’s offices, and busy homes like ours. Don’t you love a house plant you can forget about?
ZZ plants are sold in a variety of sizes, meaning they’re great for shelves, tabletops, and small surfaces as well as larger statements on the floor. We have some that are over 3 feet tall with their pots!
ZZ Plant Quick Facts
Here’s what you need to know about your ZZ plant at a glance:

Latin name: Zamioculcas zamiifolia
Plant family: Araceae or Arums, which includes Philodendron, Alocasia, Aglaonema, Monstera, and Peace Lily
Common names: ZZ plant, Zanzibar Gem, Zuzu plant, Emerald Palm, Eternity plant
Native to: East Africa
Light: Medium indirect light, but is also low-light tolerant
Watering: Every 2-3 weeks during its growing season
Soil: Standard potting mix as long as it drains well
Ideal Humidity: Average household humidity, ideally 40-50%
Ideal Temperature: 65°F to 75°F
Cold Hardiness: USDA Zones 9b-11

What Is A ZZ Plant?
Continue reading ZZ Plant – Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 19:36:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Introducing the JB x Jennifer Behr Collection</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/04/introducing-the-jb-x-jennifer-behr-collection/</link><image_url>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240312-julia-berolzheimer-jennifer-behr-turquoisenecklace-greenskirt-1002614-1024x1536.jpg</image_url><description>Image Details: JB x Jennifer Behr Necklace &amp; Earrings, Goop Top, Aje Skirt (similar here), Chanel Sandals (similar here), I…
The post Introducing the JB x Jennifer Behr Collection appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 15:00:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paul Auster, Author of The New York Trilogy, Has Died</title><link>https://bookriot.com/paul-auster-has-died/</link><description>Paul Auster made a mark in literature as an inventive superstar. Have you read any of his books?</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 18:21:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gear up without breaking the bank with REI's latest 50% off clearance sale</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/article/gear-up-without-breaking-the-bank-with-reis-latest-50-off-clearance-sale/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/01143503/REI-Tents4.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under:
					    Commerce
Continue reading Gear up without breaking the bank with REI's latest 50% off clearance sale
Gear up without breaking the bank with REI's latest 50% off clearance sale originally appeared on Autoblog on Wed, 1 May 2024 15:34:00 EDT.  Please see our terms for use of feeds.
Permalink | 
						Email this | 
					    Comments</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 20:34:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Moderna loses less than expected as Covid vaccine sales beat estimates, cost cuts take hold</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/02/moderna-mrna-earnings-q1-2024.html</link><description>The company reiterated its full-year 2024 sales guidance of roughly $4 billion, which includes revenue from the expected launch of its RSV vaccine.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:35:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you</link><description>While a little competition in the workplace might help bring out the best in everyone involved, an atmosphere rooted in envy, fear, or jealousy can do the exact opposite. This post will help you recognize signs that your coworker is threatened by you, and help you navigate the situation. 1. They Don’t Want You Involved […]
The post 10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You appeared first on Career Sherpa.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:07:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Monster Cookies</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/monster-cookies/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/05/monster-cookies-4.jpg</image_url><description>Monster cookies are slightly crisp on the outside, and soft and chewy in the center. They are loaded with peanut…</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Star Jasmine – Plant Growing &amp; Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/star-jasmine-plant-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2024/04/Star-Jasmine-Flower-Close-Up-650x488.jpg</image_url><description>Star jasmine is a fast-growing and fragrant evergreen vine that not only gives you great coverage &amp; privacy as a climbing or creeping vine, it also bursts into blooms with incredible-smelling flowers in the spring. The plant is native to Asia, but is incredibly popular in the Southeastern United States and areas of California. In warm environments like these, star jasmine is also super easy to care for and grow. Just another reason we love it!
Star jasmine can grow as a dense ground cover, but we prefer to use it as a climbing vine. This does require a trellis, pergola, stakes, or some other structure for it to grow up. Those are easy to make and we have DIY tutorials for a wire trellis on a wall as well as a freestanding privacy trellis. 
Star Jasmine Quick Facts
Here’s what you need to know about star jasmine at a glance:

Latin name: Trachelospermum jasminoides
Plant type: Evergreen climbing vine
Flowers: White star-shaped blooms in late spring &amp; early summer
Sun exposure: Full sun to part shade
Growth rate: Fast-growing (3 to 6 feet per year)
Mature size: Up to 20 feet
Soil: Well-draining loamy soil.

Continue reading Star Jasmine – Plant Growing &amp; Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:02:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Workout Refresh</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/04/workout-refresh/</link><image_url>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240429-jb-workoutrefresh-1-1024x1280.jpg</image_url><description>Outfit Details: Beyond Yoga Sports Bra &amp; Leggings, Marni Bag, Hermes Sandals As spring unfolds, my commitment to working out…
The post Workout Refresh appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 05:00:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best Book Club Books Out in May</title><link>https://bookriot.com/the-best-book-club-books-out-in-may/</link><description>Make your book club spicy with a time-traveling romance, a funny queer-coming-of-age novel with messy family details, and more.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tesla abandons quest for one-piece ‘gigacasting’</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/01/tesla-abandons-quest-for-one-piece-gigacasting/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/crop/3991x2245+0+185/resize/800x450!/format/jpg/quality/85/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/01151158/ol_9000_cs_gigapress_machine_is_pictured_at_the_idra_group_plant_in_travagliato-2.jpeg</image_url><description>Filed under:
					    Plants/Manufacturing,Tesla
Continue reading Tesla abandons quest for one-piece ‘gigacasting’
Tesla abandons quest for one-piece ‘gigacasting’ originally appeared on Autoblog on Wed, 1 May 2024 15:12:00 EDT.  Please see our terms for use of feeds.
Permalink | 
						Email this | 
					    Comments</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 20:12:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Thursday's analyst calls: Discount retailers upgraded, more good news for Carvana, tough outlook for CVS</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/02/thursdays-analyst-calls-discount-retailers-upgraded-more-good-news-for-carvana-tough-outlook-for-cvs.html</link><description>This is CNBC Pro's live coverage of Thursday's analyst calls and Wall Street chatter.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:21:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 551</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-551/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-551</link><description>Job search requires writing and marketing skills. It also requires strong verbal communication. If these skills are not part of your normal work function, you’ll want some help. That’s what this week’s Summary Sunday is all about. There’s no doubt that LinkedIn is one of THE most powerful tools in your career toolbox. It contains […]
The post Summary Sunday: Issue 551 appeared first on Career Sherpa.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 11:37:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Homemade Teriyaki Sauce</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/teriyaki-sauce-recipe/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/homemadeteriyakisauce.jpg</image_url><description>Teriyaki Sauce is super easy, takes only 10 minutes to make and is way better than store-bought! Made with simple…</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best Greige Paint Colors (According To Experts)</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/best-greige-paint-colors/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2024/04/Best-Greige-Paint-Square-Graphic-650x614.jpg</image_url><description>“Greige” is that sweet spot between gray &amp; beige, and it’s a paint color that’s both trendy and timeless. In fact, we’ve been on the greige bandwagon for nearly 20 years – well before we’d even heard that term! But finding the perfect greige can be daunting. There are 100s of neutral paint colors that could be considered greige, so we’ve waded through dozens of expert round-ups to see what colors come up over and over again. (Yes, I made a spreadsheet. And yes, I liked it). 
We weren’t surprised to see our favorite greige paint show up on this Iist, but the color that ranked #1 was a bit of a shock to us! 
What Is Greige?
Greige is an umbrella term for any color that dances the line between gray and beige (gray + beige = greige).
Continue reading The Best Greige Paint Colors (According To Experts) at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 17:43:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amazon Sundays</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/04/amazon-sundays-4-21-24/</link><description>Outfit Details: My Swimsuit, Girls’ Swimsuits, Goggles Welcome to Amazon Sundays, filled with the latest from Amazon that I’m especially…
The post Amazon Sundays appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 05:00:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Title: Book Riot’s Romance Deals for May 1, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/title-book-riots-romance-deals-for-may-1-2024/</link><description>Cozy Sci-Fi Romance, Dark Bargains, Fated Alphas, and More of the Best Romance Deals of the Day</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 17:53:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>South Carolina's 'Carolina Squat' ban gets enforced May 10</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/01/south-carolina-begins-giving-tickets-to-carolina-squat-drivers/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/01131336/Screenshot-2024-05-01-at-1.12.42 PM.png</image_url><description>Filed under:
					    Auto News,Aftermarket,Weird Car News,Safety
Continue reading South Carolina's 'Carolina Squat' ban gets enforced May 10
South Carolina's 'Carolina Squat' ban gets enforced May 10 originally appeared on Autoblog on Wed, 1 May 2024 14:07:00 EDT.  Please see our terms for use of feeds.
Permalink | 
						Email this | 
					    Comments</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 19:07:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>World's largest olive oil producer says the industry faces one of its toughest moments ever</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/02/spains-deoleo-says-olive-oil-sector-faces-one-of-its-toughest-moments.html</link><description>Spain's Deoleo says the industry must undergo a "profound transformation" as it grapples with one of the most challenging moments in its history.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 10:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>15 Ways to Own Digital Terrain</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/15-ways-to-own-digital-terrain/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=15-ways-to-own-digital-terrain</link><description>It is now no longer optional…you must have an online presence! Your career stability and your job search demand it. Here are some tips to help you begin claiming digital terrain and brand it with your unique messaging!   Why Should You Own Digital Terrain? You need to stake a claim by owning turf on the […]
The post 15 Ways to Own Digital Terrain appeared first on Career Sherpa.</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 15:56:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bang Bang Shrimp Tacos</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/bang-bang-shrimp-tacos/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/bang-bang-shrimp-tacos-.jpg</image_url><description>These Bang Bang Shrimp Tacos are made with deliciously crunchy shrimp cooked to perfection and coated in a special sauce…</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Golden Pothos – Plant Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/golden-pothos-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2024/04/Golden-Pothos-Overhead-650x455.jpg</image_url><description>Pothos are easily our #1 favorite houseplant and the golden pothos is by far the most popular variety. They’re loved by beginners and plant experts alike because they’re affordable, attractive, and easy to care for. They’re quick-growing plants with beautiful trailing vines that add loads of life and color to any space. We have pothos in nearly EVERY room of our house!
There are over a dozen kinds of pothos (Epipremnum aureum), most of which share similar characteristics and care instructions as the golden pothos. You can read more about other varieties we love, like the marble queen pothos and neon pothos.
Golden Pothos Quick Facts
Here’s what you need to know about your golden pothos at a glance:

Latin name: Epipremnum aureum
Common names: Golden pothos, devil’s ivy, devil’s vine, hunter’s rove
Mistaken for: Neon pothos, marble queen pothos
Light: Prefers medium, indirect light but is low-light tolerant
Watering: Every 7-10 days during its growing season, or if the soil is dry &amp; leaves are drooping
Soil: Standard potting mix as long as it drains well
Ideal Humidity: Average household humidity, ideally 50-70%
Ideal Temperature: 65°F to 85°F
Cold Hardiness: USDA Zones 10-12

What Is A Golden Pothos?
Continue reading Golden Pothos – Plant Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mother’s Day Gift Ideas</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/04/mothers-day-gift-ideas-3/</link><image_url>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/20240412-jb-boden-1001895-1024x1536.jpg</image_url><description>Image Details: Boden Dress, Chanel Flats (similar here), Illesteva Sunglasses, Boden Dresses on C &amp; M Mother’s Day always feels…
The post Mother’s Day Gift Ideas appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 05:00:29 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>