<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 06:52:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Is Widespread Crypto Adoption Inevitable?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/22/is-widespread-crypto-adoption-inevitable/</link><description>New technologies always face resistance, but demographic shifts imply there is a fierce tailwind behind crypto adoption, politically, economically, and financially.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 12:38:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>South Korea arrests the founder of one of its biggest internet companies over a K-pop stock rigging scandal</title><link>https://fortune.com/asia/2024/07/23/south-korea-arrests-brian-kim-founder-kakao-k-pop-stock-rigging-scandal/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/GettyImages-1739890063-e1721723445464.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>South Korean authorities have arrested Kakao Corp. founder Brian Kim over allegations of market manipulation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 11:42:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: Shocks, Crises, and False Alarms</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/19/book-review-shocks-crises-and-false-alarms/</link><description>Carlsson-Szlezak and Swartz attempt to add fresh thinking on framing macro shocks that may often prove to be false alarms. Any general reader will obtain some key fresh insights with this work, and CFA charterholders will be offered an alternative to the conventional Wall Street approach to macro discussions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 13:06:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway cuts its stake in EV giant BYD to under 5%, dropping below Hong Kong’s disclosure threshold</title><link>https://fortune.com/asia/2024/07/23/warren-buffett-berkshire-hathaway-cuts-byd-stake-china-ev/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/GettyImages-2157258913-e1721726634683.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The days of calling BYD a “Buffett-backed” company may soon be coming to a close.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 11:40:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Preserving the Dollar: The Role of CBDCs in Securing Economic Stability for Future Generations</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/16/preserving-the-dollar-the-role-of-cbdcs-in-securing-economic-stability-for-future-generations/</link><description>As financial systems evolve, preserving the US dollar's dominance will require skillful policy management and the integration of cutting-edge technologies.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:24:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Finance guru Dave Ramsey believes spousal interviews should be part of the hiring process: ‘Discover if your candidate is married to crazy’</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/07/23/dave-ramsey-spousal-interviews-dinner-hiring-process/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/GettyImages-837536120-e1721728542614.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>"As the spouse hears about your culture and the job role, they’re usually eager to share whether they think the position fits."</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 11:23:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Can Equal Weight Solve Our Concentration Crisis? Not So Fast…</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/15/can-equal-weight-solve-our-concentration-crisis-not-so-fast/</link><description>Mega-cap concentration has exploded since 2015. The corollary to an increasingly top-heavy benchmark is that market diversification and breadth have never been more limited. A multifactor methodology can be a restorative balance to US equities when more traditional measures fall short.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 22:43:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The global M&amp;A market’s big-deal bravado is losing steam as rates stay high in 2024</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/07/23/global-ma-merger-markets-big-deal-bravado-losing-steam-rates-stay-high-2024/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/GettyImages-2161548269.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The largest sector for M&amp;A globally was technology, with deal volume up 37% year on year, of which North America made up some 66% of the total.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 11:18:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In Search of the Elusive Neutral Interest Rate</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/10/in-search-of-the-elusive-neutral-interest-rate/</link><description>With Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell's semiannual address to the Senate Banking Committee this week fresh in mind, it is an ideal time to consider the drivers of r*.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 12:17:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>European cities are trying to shun young ‘drunk’ tourists in favor of big spenders, but there are concerns the move could be classist</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/07/23/european-cities-barcelona-shun-young-drunk-tourists-big-spenders-classist/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/GettyImages-2160673457-e1721728818376.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>“We don’t want the tourists who come to do what they can’t do in their own countries,” says Mateu Hernández, director-general of Turisme de Barcelona.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 11:14:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>