<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 16:32:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Meir Statman: Your State of Mind Influences Your Investing Success</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/29/meir-statman-your-state-of-mind-influences-your-investing-success/</link><description>Meir Statman shares his insights on the broader aspects of financial well-being and its interconnection with life satisfaction.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 12:58:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to write an MBA resume that’ll help you get into business school</title><link>https://fortune.com/education/articles/mba-resume/</link><description>MBA resumes are similar to traditional job resumes, with a couple of key differences. Experts detail how to write one, what to avoid—and why.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 21:18:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: Trailblazers, Heroes, and Crooks</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/26/book-review-trailblazers-heroes-and-crooks/</link><description>Stephen Foerster, CFA, extracts lessons from exceptional episodes in financial history that ordinary investors and seasoned professionals alike can put to profitable use. The bonus is that you'll be entertained from start to finish.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden backs off long-awaited ban on menthol cigarettes</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/29/biden-menthol-cigarettes-ban-tobacco-meetings-white-house/</link><description>“This decision prioritizes politics over lives, especially Black lives,” said Yolonda Richardson of the Campaign for Tobacco-Free Kids, in an emailed statement.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 21:05:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Price Risk? Unpacking the Equity Risk Premium</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/24/what-price-risk-unpacking-the-equity-risk-premium/</link><description>Stocks are a good wager over the long term, on favorable odds. But stocks remain a bet, and investors must grasp how much returns can vary over long time horizons.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Business travel survives the Zoom era, as leaders jump back on flights</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/29/business-travel-trends-pre-pandemic-levels-zoom-era-corporate-flights/</link><description>Even with Zoom’s implementation, employee travel bounds back to pre-pandemic levels.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 20:53:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Equity Income Investing Redux</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/22/equity-income-investing-redux/</link><description>No doubt the past year has been difficult for equity income investors. But history, inherent biases, mean reversion, and the current market backdrop point to a comeback.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 17:19:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Millennials have it better than everyone thinks, accumulating wealth faster than anyone else since the pandemic, new data shows</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/29/millennials-accumulating-wealth-vs-other-generations-pandemic-recession-center-american-progress/</link><description>“This historic growth is without parallel in recent decades,” according to an analysis from the Center for American Progress.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 20:49:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: Enrich Your Future</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/18/book-review-enrich-your-future/</link><description>This engaging book is simultaneously memorable and humorous. The numerous sports analogies will have you smiling as you absorb Larry Swedroe's unforgettable investment precepts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 18:07:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MedMen’s spectacular collapse is complete: Just five years after earning a whopping $3 billion valuation, the one-time legal cannabis darling has declared bankruptcy</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/29/medmen-cannabis-unicorn-bankrupt-legal-california-retail-adam-bierman-alan-brochstein/</link><description>“MedMen has been ‘DeadMen’ to most investors for a long time,” one industry analyst told Fortune.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 20:26:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>