<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:15:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>What Price Risk? Unpacking the Equity Risk Premium</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/24/what-price-risk-unpacking-the-equity-risk-premium/</link><description>Stocks are a good wager over the long term, on favorable odds. But stocks remain a bet, and investors must grasp how much returns can vary over long time horizons.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 10 best secured credit cards for 2024</title><link>https://fortune.com/recommends/credit-cards/the-best-secured-credit-cards/</link><description>We compared dozens of secured credit cards across numerous financial institutions and weighed minimum account deposits, annual fees, credit limits, rewards, and more.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:10:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Equity Income Investing Redux</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/22/equity-income-investing-redux/</link><description>No doubt the past year has been difficult for equity income investors. But history, inherent biases, mean reversion, and the current market backdrop point to a comeback.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 17:19:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Want a risk-free investment that earns you more than 5% a year? Try these CDs.</title><link>https://fortune.com/recommends/banking/the-best-cd-rates/</link><description>The best CD rates are now well over 5%.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:05:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: Enrich Your Future</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/18/book-review-enrich-your-future/</link><description>This engaging book is simultaneously memorable and humorous. The numerous sports analogies will have you smiling as you absorb Larry Swedroe's unforgettable investment precepts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 18:07:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Luxury buyers are spending an extra $1 million to add pickleball courts to vacation homes</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/24/luxury-vacation-home-buyers-pickleball-courts-million-dollars/</link><description>Buyers are willing to spend an extra seven figures for the needed space.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:03:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CAPE Is High: Should You Care?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/17/cape-is-high-should-you-care/</link><description>A simple analysis shows that Robert Shiller's cyclically adjusted price-to-earnings ratio changed in the 1990s and that mean-reversion concerns may be misplaced. If CAPE changed three decades ago, however, there is nothing preventing it from doing so again.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 15:18:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'War-time mode' Musk restores investor faith in Tesla’s growth story by accelerating plans to launch new models</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/24/elon-musk-tesla-first-quarter-earnings-low-cost-car-new-models/</link><description>The Tesla CEO scrapped plans to build his low-cost car using a revolutionary new technique, opting to save money and bring the model to market sooner to reignite growth.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:43:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI to the Rescue? Overhauling the US Power Grid on the Path to Net Zero</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/15/ai-to-the-rescue-overhauling-the-us-power-grid-on-the-path-to-net-zero/</link><description>Once known as secure and profitable investments, utilities are now viewed as enterprises fraught with financial risks. Investors should favor utilities that employ AI and other digital strategies to minimize damage from natural disasters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 21:24:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Choose the Best 10-Year CD Rate for You</title><link>https://fortune.com/recommends/banking/the-best-10-year-cd-rates/</link><description>A 10-year CD is a long-term commitment, but locking in a high APY can lead to a big payoff. Here are the top rates this month.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:31:34 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>