<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:39:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Gold and Inflation: An Unstable Relationship</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/06/05/gold-and-inflation-an-unstable-relationship/</link><description>While there are periods when gold has hedged inflation quite well, beware blanket claims of gold's inflation-hedging utility.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 12:07:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IRS says it will refund taxes extracted from Ohioans who got financial assistance after Norfolk Southern derailment disaster</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/06/05/irs-refund-taxes-disaster-ohio-brown/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/GettyImages-1247414116-e1717631611331.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>“I don’t know why they didn’t do that from the very beginning,” East Palestine resident Misti Allison said.</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 00:54:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Monetary Policy and Financial Conditions: Meaningful Relationship?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/06/03/monetary-policy-and-financial-conditions-meaningful-relationship/</link><description>An analysis of the Fed's recent rounds of quantitative tightening (QT) and quantitative easing (QE) yields actionable insights about the relationship between monetary policy and financial conditions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 12:01:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zero percent down mortgages might help more first-time homebuyers break into the housing market—but there are caveats</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/06/05/zero-percent-down-mortgages-first-time-homebuyers/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/GettyImages-1179761508-e1717621514926.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>United Wholesale Mortgage announced a 0% down program last month, and since then it’s been all the rage, but people are split: Does it eliminate a barrier or will it launch us into another subprime mortgage crisis?</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 22:46:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Five Quotes from Financial History to Guide Trustees</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/31/five-quotes-from-financial-history-to-guide-trustees/</link><description>If you serve as a trustee of an institutional investment plan, these five quotes may help guide your decisions for the benefit of those who depend on your stewardship.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 13:59:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kansas politicians relaunch effort to steal Kansas City Chiefs from neighboring Missouri after a $1 billion taxpayer-funded plan fizzled</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/06/05/kansas-city-chiefs-missouri-politicians/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/GettyImages-2154748918-e1717623269871.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>After an earlier stadium-financing plan fell through, Kansas legislators are trying a new tactic to bring the Chiefs across the state border.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 22:37:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stocks for the Long Run? Setting the Record Straight</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/30/stocks-for-the-long-run-setting-the-record-straight/</link><description>Stocks are a good investment long-term, providing that you dial in your expectations. New historical findings provide a richer, more complete understanding of international returns.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 16:55:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Short seller Scorpion Capital accuses Japan’s most actively traded company of being the ‘largest outright fraud in the world’</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/06/05/short-seller-scorpion-capital-lasertec-japan-semiconductors-chips-euv-fraud-allegations/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/GettyImages-1245621798-e1717621891973.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Hedge fund targets niche semiconductor company that’s rode AI demand for huge gains since 2019.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 22:29:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rethinking Retirement Planning Amidst Aging Demographic Frontiers</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/28/rethinking-retirement-planning-amidst-aging-demographic-frontiers/</link><description>Forward-thinking approaches to policy and wealth management are needed to ensure a better financial future across generations and income brackets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 20:32:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New York governor abruptly cancels nation's first 'congestion pricing' system that would have charged $15 to drive into midtown Manhattan</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/06/05/new-york-congestion-pricing-governor/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/GettyImages-1498297146-e1717620869191.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The $15 charge "can break the budget of a hardworking or middle class household," Kathy Hochul said.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 22:25:17 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>