<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from multiple RSS sources, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 06:59:12 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Seeing Greene: Stolen Properties and Why Your Rate Doesn’t (Really) Matter</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-945</link><description>There’s a silent threat out there that most real estate investors have no idea about. It’s a threat that could take away all your cash flow, ruin your real estate […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 07:02:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Devastated by his image being posted to a porn site, this founder hit on an AI startup idea</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/30/devastated-by-his-image-being-posted-to-a-porn-site-this-founder-hit-on-an-ai-startup-idea/</link><description>Realising that a former partner had, unbeknownst to him, put previously private, intimate videos of them onto a porn site, tech founder Dan Purcell felt devastated. He resolved to come up with a solution to help prevent such violations happening again. His Ceartas startup has now raised $4.5 million in a Seed round from European […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 10:48:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>They Killed Their Abusive Partners. Now Their Sentences Could Be Reconsidered.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/27/oklahoma-oregon-minnesota-domestic-violence</link><description>Oklahoma could re-examine how it punishes people whose crimes came after years of domestic abuse. Other states may follow.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>You Give Me (Spring) Fever</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/women/features/you-give-me-spring-fever?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>New Season Brings Boost of Energy, but Also Unplanned Pregnancies</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 16:57:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lessons From the Rich That Took Me from $0 to a $1,000,000+ Business</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-524</link><description>Want to be a millionaire or build a business that brings in seven figures? Want generational wealth and to be debt-free? Want to know that you have enough money to […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 07:01:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nigeria’s YC-backed Chowdeck hopes to scale food delivery, a notoriously tough market, with $2.5M funding</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/30/chowdeck-hopes-to-scale-notoriously-tough-food-delivery-market/</link><description>Food is significant to Nigerians, with households spending nearly 60% of their income on it, the highest globally, according to official reports. This strong affinity for food, coupled with the rise of online shopping, sets the stage for Nigeria’s food delivery market to potentially reach $2 billion to $3 billion by 2032. Despite the promising […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 09:11:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Being Trans in Prison Is Really Like</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/26/trans-prison-voices-gender-essay</link><description>Amid a wave of anti-trans legislation, and the violence that often follows, four people share their experiences in the criminal justice system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 11:00:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Older Adults: 9 Nutrients You May Be Missing</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/missing-nutrients?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>With age, your body doesn’t absorb nutrients well, so every calorie you consume must be packed with nutrition. Here are 9 nutrients older adults often need more of.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 16:57:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tenant Not Paying Rent? Here’s What to Do</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/tenant-not-paying-rent</link><description>A tenant not paying rent can turn your profit upside down. Should you find yourself in this situation, there are several key steps you must take.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 04:43:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>neuroClues wants to put high speed eye tracking tech in the doctor’s office</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/30/neuroclues/</link><description>The eyes aren’t just a window into the soul; tracking saccades can help doctors pick up a range of brain health issues. That’s why French-Belgian medtech startup neuroClues is building accessible, high-speed eye-tracking technology that incorporates AI-driven analysis. It wants to make it easier for healthcare service providers to use eye tracking to support the […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 08:00:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Enduring Use of Solitary, and New Proposed Limits That Will Likely Fail (Again)</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/20/solitary-confinement-reform-oklahoma-washington-florida</link><description>Isolation’s damaging effects are widely known. But many facilities confine people — even youth — virtually all day, sometimes in shower stalls.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Immunity Challenge: How aging affects your immune system</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/seniors-boost-immunity?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>How does getting older affect your immune system? How can you keep those effects to a minimum? Your answers are here.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 16:57:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Property Management Checklist (What Needs to Be Done, and When)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/property-management-checklist</link><description>With this guidance, you can create a property management checklist that guides you throughout the year.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 04:30:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>As VC firms invest more in B2B startups, Intuition is a new VC fund focusing on consumer tech</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/29/as-vc-firms-invest-more-in-b2b-startups-intuition-is-a-new-vc-fund-focusing-on-consumer-tech/</link><description>In 2024, it’s hard to wake up without reading about yet another large funding round in an enterprise AI company. Intuition, a new VC firm based in Paris, is doing something radical and betting on consumer tech exclusively. Behind the scenes, Hugo Amsellem (pictured left) and Etienne Boutan (pictured right) will be the general partners […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 07:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Officials Failed to Act When COVID Hit Prisons. A New Study Shows the Deadly Cost.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/18/covid-prison-deaths-data</link><description>People in prison died at 3.4 times the rate of the free population, with the oldest hit hardest. New data holds lessons for preventing future deaths.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Helps When It’s Hard to Chew and Swallow?</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/eating-problems?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Trouble chewing and swallowing? WebMD shares six ways to make everything go down a little easier.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 16:57:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>U.S. Immigration Crisis: What It Really Means for Housing Markets and Investors</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/how-the-immigration-crisis-impacts-real-estate</link><description>A record 300,000 migrants entered the U.S. through the southern border in December. Rather than trying to sneak past border agents, many surrendered to apply for asylum.  Overwhelmed immigration courts take years to […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 21:00:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Solo GP fund Andrena Ventures hopes to carry startup talent onto its next challenges</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/29/andrena-ventures-solo-gp/</link><description>Gideon Valkin's solo VC firm Andrena Ventures is raising $12 million from backers including several VCs and entrepreneurs, and made its first investment into AI startup Nustom.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 07:01:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Parents Paying for Their Children’s Crimes</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/13/michigan-school-shooting-parents</link><description>Experts warn about a wave of legal consequences for parents like the Crumbleys, while some states consider prosecutions for kids as young as 10.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Foods to Keep You Healthy as You Age</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/longevity-foods?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Staying healthy as you enter your golden years has a lot to do with your diet. Here are some foods that are good for your heart, your brain, your bones, and your muscles.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 16:57:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>