<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from multiple RSS sources, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:50:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The New Reform That Could Unlock $1B+ for Affordable Housing w/Sharon Cornelissen</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-211</link><description>America is in need of affordable housing; we’re all aware. Buying your first home has become increasingly challenging for everyday people. This is where housing subsidies come in. Federal housing […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 07:02:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RevenueCat raises $12M Series C as it expands its subscription management to the web</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/25/revenuecat-raises-12m-series-c-as-it-expands-its-subscription-management-to-the-web/</link><description>With RevenueCat Billing, essentially a web SDK, developers can accept subscription payments from any website.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:03:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Enduring Use of Solitary, and New Proposed Limits That Will Likely Fail (Again)</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/20/solitary-confinement-reform-oklahoma-washington-florida</link><description>Isolation’s damaging effects are widely known. But many facilities confine people — even youth — virtually all day, sometimes in shower stalls.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rise and Shine: A Carefully Considered Morning Ritual That Can Brighten Your Day</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/rise-shine-carefully-considered-morning-ritual-brighten-your-day?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Strategies for getting ready to be at your best each morning</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 10:31:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sunbelt Surge: 15 Cities Dominating the Growth Charts</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/best-sunbelt-markets-for-growth</link><description>Simply investing in any metro Sunbelt market is not a recipe for success. To catch a cresting wave of appreciation and cash flow, you’ll need to dive deep into the metrics […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:48:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paystand acquires Teampay to be DeFi version of ‘Venmo for B2B payments’</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/25/paystand-teampay-defi-venmo-b2b-payments/</link><description>“Teampay represents this new class of fintech companies that came up,” said Paystand CEO Jeremy Almond.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 14:30:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Officials Failed to Act When COVID Hit Prisons. A New Study Shows the Deadly Cost.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/18/covid-prison-deaths-data</link><description>People in prison died at 3.4 times the rate of the free population, with the oldest hit hardest. New data holds lessons for preventing future deaths.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Considering a Clinical Trial When You Have COPD</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/lung/copd/features/clinical-trials-copd?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Thinking about joining a clinical trial to help your COPD? Jean Rommes shares some of what to expect.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 22:21:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Warning: These States and Cities Are Becoming Uninvestable Due to Politics</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/how-politics-is-making-these-states-and-cities-uninvestable</link><description>Taxes and regulations impact your bottom line as an investor—and not always in direct or obvious ways. Unfortunately, as soon as you start talking about either one, the average person closes their […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 18:27:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The impact of TikTok’s ban in other countries could signal what’s ahead for the US</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/25/the-impact-of-tiktoks-ban-in-other-countries-could-signal-whats-ahead-for-the-u-s/</link><description>On April 24, U.S. President Joe Biden signed a bill that would ban TikTok if its owner ByteDance doesn’t sell the app. The bill requires ByteDance to secure a deal within nine months, with a 90-day extension available to close it. After this deadline, the U.S. will bar app stores from listing the app. TikTok […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 14:29:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Parents Paying for Their Children’s Crimes</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/13/michigan-school-shooting-parents</link><description>Experts warn about a wave of legal consequences for parents like the Crumbleys, while some states consider prosecutions for kids as young as 10.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Treating and Managing Mild COPD</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/lung/copd/features/treat-mild-copd?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Learn how to treat and manage mild COPD.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 22:07:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The BEST Ways to Protect Your Rental Property and Keep Your Tenants Safe</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-397</link><description>If you own a rental property, it’s YOUR responsibility to provide a safe environment for tenants. This starts with things like tenant screening, security upgrades, and most importantly, acting swiftly […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:02:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Petlibro’s new smart refrigerated wet food feeder is what your cat deserves</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/25/petlibros-new-smart-refrigerated-wet-food-feeder-is-what-your-cat-deserves/</link><description>Petlibro, pet tech startup that designs automatic food dispensers for cats, launched its first refrigerated smart feeder.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 14:00:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I Had a Tough Job at My Brooklyn Jail: Keeping Men From Taking Their Own Lives</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/12/brooklyn-jail-suicide-prevention-aide</link><description>As a suicide prevention aide, I had to make sure my fellow detainees didn’t harm themselves. It was surprisingly easy to get such a complex job.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Manage Your COPD Flares</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/lung/copd/features/manage-copd-episodes?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>If you have chronic obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD), you’re probably no stranger to flares. If you take steps to address symptoms early and find ways to minimize triggers, you can dramatically lower your risk of flares.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 21:54:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Building Wealth with OLD Homes and How to Keep Tenants for Longer</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-942</link><description>How do you find investment properties nobody else is looking for—the ones with cash flow potential, equity upside, and wealth-building qualities all the other investors overlook? Simple: buy what nobody […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 07:02:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Carv raises $10M Series A to help gamers monetize their data</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/25/carv-raises-10m-series-a-to-help-gaming-and-ai-firms-monetize-data/</link><description>Carv, a data layer platform that lets web3 gaming and AI companies, as well as gamers, control and monetize their data, has raised a $10 million Series A round led by Tribe Capital and IOSG Ventures.  Carv’s new round comes approximately five months after it received a strategic investment led by HashKey Capital. The startup […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 14:00:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Supreme Court Case on Homelessness May Limit Prisoner Rights and Expand Executions</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/10/supreme-court-homeless-grants-pass-originalism</link><description>In Grants Pass v. Johnson, a town in Oregon asks the court to reconsider what constitutes “cruel and unusual punishments.”</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Lifestyle Changes Helped Minimize My COPD Episodes</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/lung/copd/features/copd-lifestyle-changes?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Edi Mesa  made these lifestyle changes in order to keep COPD episodes to a minimum.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 21:51:41 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>