<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:16:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Washington Commanders Reintroduce Gold Pants To Uniform Rotation</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/09/washington-commanders-reintroduce-gold-pants-to-uniform-rotation/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Washington Commanders are reintroducing gold pants to their uniform rotation this season, an option that has not been available since they rebranded in 2022.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 21:36:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Woman Gets Instant Karma in Road Rage Incident, Car Crashes into SUV</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/09/karen-road-rage-karma-video-car-park-brake-crash-drunk/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Getting out of your car in the middle of a road rage incident is always a dicey move, especially when your car's not in park ... which this woman found out when her car rolled into another vehicle! Ya gotta see the video of this instant karma…</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:16:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trio of Premier League Kits Highlight Recent Launches From Europe’s Top Leagues</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/09/trio-of-premier-league-kits-highlight-recent-launches-from-europes-top-leagues/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Ipswich Town, Leicester City and West Ham lead the way in England; other clubs unveiling 24-25 kits include Stade Brestois 29, Nice, Lille, Fiorentina, Galatasaray and Ajax</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 18:00:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Teresa Giudice Reveals Reason for Her Larsa Pippen Photoshop Fail</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/09/teresa-giudice-photoshop-fail-beach-reason/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Teresa Giudice's caught up in a Photoshop scandal for the ages -- her severely mocked birthday wish for Larsa Pippen -- but now, she's trying to have some fun with it. We caught up with Teresa Tuesday at ABC Studios in NYC ... and she said the…</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:16:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NHL, New Era Announce Headwear and Apparel Deal</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/09/nhl-new-era-announce-headwear-and-apparel-deal/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>New multiyear agreement grants New Era rights to produce and distribute globally headwear and apparel for the League and its 32 teams</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 16:21:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kamala Harris Visits Team USA Basketball Practice In Vegas</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/09/kamala-harris-visits-team-usa-basketball-practice-las-vegas/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>All eyes in the political world are on Kamala Harris right now, but the Vice President made time to hang out with the Team USA basketball squad ... meeting up with a ton of NBA superstars!! Harris -- who walked in alongside head coach Steve Kerr --…</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:16:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Brooklyn Nets Subtly Update Logos, Introduce New Secondary Mark For 2024-25 Season</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/07/brooklyn-nets-subtly-update-logos-introduce-new-secondary-mark-for-2024-25-season/basketball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Brooklyn Nets have made several changes to their logo set for the 2024-25 season, including introducing a new secondary logo that depicts a stylized net.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 19:12:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kanye West Says He's Quitting Rap Despite New Collabs Dropping</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/09/kanye-west-quitting-rap-consequence-rich-the-kid/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Kanye West is having a change of heart regarding his rap career and he's been texting his closest collaborators that the end may be near!!! On Tuesday, Rich The Kid shared a text sent by Ye informing them he's run outta gas ... "I am retiring from…</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:16:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PSG Pay Homage to Eiffel Tower With New Away Kit – Plus More European Kit Launches</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/05/psg-pay-homage-to-eiffel-tower-with-new-away-kit-plus-more-european-kit-launches/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Other clubs unveiling 2024-25 kits include Napoli, Wolves, West Ham, Stade de Reims, Mallorca, Real Betis, Villarreal, Bochum, Stuttgart, Mainz 05 and Union Berlin</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 20:20:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Katy Perry Shares Risqué Teaser Clip For New Single 'Woman's World'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/09/katy-perry-sexy-womans-world-teaser/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Katy Perry's shared a teaser video for her upcoming pop anthem, "Woman's World" -- getting super racy ... all in the name of female empowerment, of course. Check it out -- the singer gave feminist icon Rosie the Riveter a sexy twist with that…</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:16:25 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>