<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 01:49:36 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Book Review: The New World Economy in 5 Trends</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/24/book-review-the-new-world-economy-in-5-trends/</link><description>A diligent economist and an eclectic bookworm serve up an analysis of megatrends that will have the greatest impact on economies and investments: innovation, productivity, climate, multiglobalization, debt, and aging.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 12:22:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ferrari 296 GTS Hybrid Review: ‘Arresting, uncanny beauty’ with $366,139 price tag</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/26/ferrari-296-gts-hybrid-review-beauty-366139-price/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/cropped-Ferrari-GTS-hybrid-martyn-lucy-GettyImages-1947682592-e1716215162910.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>As Ferrari rolls toward its first all-electric car, arriving next year, it makes sense that it would also make a hybrid or two.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Factor Strategies Belong in Your Completion Portfolio Toolkit</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/23/factor-strategies-belong-in-your-completion-portfolio-toolkit/</link><description>Why wouldn't you include factor strategies in your completion portfolio? A review of the two commonly used approaches for managing institutional assets highlights their symbiotic nature.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 19:09:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Janet Yellen warns higher outlook for rates will make it harder to keep deficits and debt expenses under control</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/25/deficit-debt-warning-janet-yellen-higher-rate-outlook-interest-expenses/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2153651062-e1716681638211.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The White House sees 10-year Treasury yields at 3.7% in the early 2030s — almost a full percentage point higher than three years ago.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 01:12:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>For the Analyst: Peer Benchmarking Methods to Improve Earnings Forecasts</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/21/for-the-analyst-peer-benchmarking-methods-to-improve-earnings-forecasts/</link><description>Peer benchmarking is a vexing task for financial analysts but one that is critical for forecasting earnings. This straightforward measure can help find peers for relative performance, compensation, and valuation benchmarking.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 12:47:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Could drugs like Ozempic and Wegovy help people live longer? Some experts see them as potential longevity pills</title><link>https://fortune.com/well/article/ozempic-glp1-help-people-live-longer-longevity/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1499754635.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>“The singular most effective and consistent way of extending lifespan in animals is caloric restriction.”</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Building LLMs in the Open-Source Community: A Call to Action for Investment Professionals</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/20/building-llms-in-the-open-source-community-a-call-to-action-for-investment-professionals/</link><description>Large language models like ChatGPT are changing the way we think about investing and reshaping roles in the investment profession.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 16:26:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tesla shareholders should reject Elon Musk’s ‘excessive’ pay package, proxy advisor says, noting ‘extraordinarily time-consuming projects’ unrelated to EV maker</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/25/tesla-shareholders-elon-musk-pay-package-proxy-advisor-glass-lewis/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2151265017-e1716680351499.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>“Mr. Musk’s slate of extraordinarily time-consuming projects unrelated to the Company was well-documented before the 2018 grant, and only expanded with his high-profile purchase of the company now known as X,” said Glass Lewis.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:49:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sustainability Reporting: Navigating Assurance Practices</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/17/sustainability-reporting-navigating-assurance-practices/</link><description>Don't be lulled into a false sense of security by the word "assurance" when evaluating sustainability reports. Assurance practices vary, and investors would be wise to learn more about the different levels of coverage.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 17:57:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Top assassin for the Sinaloa drug cartel, once described as ‘a complete psychopath’ with long history of gruesome acts, is extradited to U.S.</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/25/sinaloa-drug-cartel-assassin-el-nini-extradited-el-chapo-guzman-chapitos/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1251816769-e1716679229306.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Nestor Isidro Pérez Salas, also known as “El Nini,” is a leader of a group that provided security for the sons of imprisoned drug lord Joaquín “El Chapo” Guzmán, federal investigators said.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:29:43 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>