<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 12:04:52 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Hedge Funds: A Poor Choice for Most Long-Term Investors?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/06/26/hedge-funds-a-poor-choice-for-most-long-term-investors/</link><description>By allocating to a diversified pool of hedge funds, many institutional investors are unwittingly reducing their equity holdings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 13:31:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sam’s Club is going after Costco through the hearts and wallets of Gen Z shoppers. ‘That generation believes it’s cool to save money,’ CEO says</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/06/27/sams-club-costco-gen-z-store-brand-kirkland/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/GettyImages-1410188362-e1719436491181.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The Walmart-owned retailer’s digital strategies and budget brands have struck a chord with tech-savvy and deal-driven Gen Z.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:58:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Did Inflation Kill the CAPM?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/06/25/did-inflation-kill-the-capm/</link><description>While the immediate future may not be promising for the equity premium, it looks bright for factor premiums.</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 13:51:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Doctors in Idaho can now provide emergency abortions, SCOTUS rules, after pregnant women were airlifted out of the state for emergency care</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/06/27/idaho-emergency-abortions-supreme-court/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/GettyImages-2149407061-e1719499809547.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The ruling came a day after an opinion was briefly posted on the court's website accidentally and quickly taken down, but not before it was obtained by Bloomberg News.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:51:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Behavior of Crowds not Wisdom of Crowds</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/06/21/behavior-of-crowds-not-wisdom-of-crowds/</link><description>When behavioral crowds are roiling the markets, as they are now, best idea active equity has an excellent chance of outperforming.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 17:54:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ellevest’s founder went to Wall Street after being rejected by her first choice. Now her $2 billion empire is helping women build their own wealth</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/06/27/sallie-krawcheck-ellevest-ceo-secrets-to-success/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/Sallie-5.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The investing industry tends to look past women and mostly serve men, longtime Wall Street executive Sallie Krawcheck says. That's what led her to build Ellevest.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:50:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is the Outright Ban on a US Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC) a Mistake?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/06/20/is-the-outright-ban-on-a-us-central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc-a-mistake/</link><description>Instead of outright banning a US CBDC, wouldn’t it be preferrable to establish clear and enforceable legislative guardrails?</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 17:00:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Supreme Court just rejected a deal with the maker of OxyContin that would have shielded the billionaire Sackler family from liability—but provided billions of dollars to fight opioids</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/06/27/supreme-court-rejects-purdue-pharma-oxycontin-bankruptcy-settlement-sackler-family-opioid-epidemic/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/GettyImages-1824551962-e1719501501140.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Had the bankruptcy been approved, the Sacklers would have contributed up to $6 billion and given up ownership of the company but retained billions more.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:46:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Concerned About Market Concentration and Lofty Valuations? Consider Small Caps</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/06/19/concerned-about-market-concentration-and-lofty-valuations-consider-small-caps/</link><description>Investors are showing increased concern about large-cap stocks due to high market concentration and lofty stock valuations. Other factors combine to make a compelling case for small caps.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 17:16:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cybersecurity is now a ‘team sport’ amid a wave of generative AI-based attacks, say tech experts</title><link>https://fortune.com/asia/2024/06/27/cybersecurity-is-team-sport-amid-generative-ai-based-attacks-tech-experts-accenture/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/GettyImages-2022975324-e1719480883691.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>AI "is available to both our friends and foes," warned Maria Milosavljevic, group CISO at ANZ Banking Group, at a Fortune conversation Wednesday.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:45:58 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>