<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 00:44:03 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Chicago Bears Add George S. Halas’ Initials To 1936 Throwback Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/18/chicago-bears-add-george-s-halas-initials-to-1936-throwback-uniforms/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Chicago Bears have subtly added the initials of late founder, owner and coach George S. Halas to the left sleeve of their 1936 throwback uniforms, matching their navy blue home, white road and orange alternate jerseys.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 22:34:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gayle King Embraces WW &amp; Exercise For Weight Loss, Unlike Pal Oprah</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/18/gayle-king-embrace-weightwatchers-exercise-sports-illustrated-oprah-weight-loss-drugs/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Gayle King is dishing on how she got cover ready for her photo shoot with Sports Illustrated ... giving cred to the very company her pal Oprah Winfrey just ditched, at least professionally. We caught up with Gayle in NYC, where the CBS News anchor…</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 00:44:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fanatics and NFLPA Reveal 2024 NFL Rookie Jerseys</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/18/fanatics-and-nflpa-reveal-2024-nfl-rookie-jerseys/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Last night, Fanatics and the NFLPA held a special “Jersey Reveal” event in Los Angeles to unveil the official game jerseys for 39 NFL rookies during the NFLPA Rookie Premiere. Several high-profile 2024 NFL Draft picks and rookies attended the event, including Caleb Williams and Rome Odunze of the Chicago</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 17:58:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kanye West and Bianca Censori Dine at Denny's Amid Major Yeezy Changes</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/18/kanye-west-bianca-censori-dennys-yeezy-mass-exodus-employees/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Kanye West and Bianca Censori chowing down at America's Diner isn't something you'd expect, but their affordable meal comes as a major shakeup goes down at Ye's company. New video obtained by TMZ shows Kanye -- with a white hoodie tight around his…</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 00:44:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Carolina Disco Turkeys to play as Camel City Humps</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/18/carolina-disco-turkeys-to-play-as-camel-city-humps/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The town of Winston-Salem, North Carolina, is called “Camel City” because since 1875 it has been home to the R.J. Reynolds Tobacco Company, which produces Camel brand cigarettes. The town of Winston-Salem is also home to the collegiate summer level Carolina Disco Turkeys, who will put a new twist on</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 17:29:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Billionaire Juices Speech with $1,000 to Each UMass Dartmouth Graduate</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/18/billionaire-robert-hale-jr-speech-1000-dollars-umass-dartmouth-graduation/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Oprah Winfrey's got nothing on Robert Hale Jr., a telecom billionaire, who didn't hand out car keys to UMass Dartmouth grads ... but, instead, handed them cold hard cash -- for themselves and others. You could say Hale spiced up his commencement…</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 00:44:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>All MLB Teams are Wearing Black Camo Caps Today</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/17/all-mlb-teams-are-wearing-black-camo-caps-today/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Why are all the Major League Baseball teams wearing black and green camouflage hats today? Well, that’s because MLB and New Era are in the midst of their annual Armed Forces Day ballcap celebration; here in 2024, the caps will be worn across the league over the May 17-18-19 weekend.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 23:44:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jennifer Lopez, Ben Affleck's Separate Lives, Not Together on Mother's Day</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/18/jennifer-lopez-ben-affleck-separate-lives-mothers-day/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Jennifer Lopez and Ben Affleck are living such separate lives right now, they reportedly did not celebrate Mother's Day together. As we reported, Ben has moved out of their Beverly Hills mansion, and into a home he's renting in Brentwood -- not far…</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 00:44:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Borussia Dortmund Aims for  a Modern Classic With 2024-25 Home Kits – Plus 3 Other European Kit Launches</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/17/borussia-dortmund-aims-for-a-modern-classic-with-2024-25-home-kits-plus-3-other-european-kit-launches/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>ACF Fiorentina leans hard into signature purple color; Bologna FC calls new home kits 'an act of love'; Athletic Bilbao goes with the flow with new away kit</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 15:54:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Britney Spears Rants About Mexico Trip, Claims Injured Foot Healed</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/18/britney-spears-instagram-rant-mexico-trip-injure-foot-heal/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Britney Spears says she's healing all on her own after a trip to Mexico -- which she says included cursing out strangers -- but visuals of her battered foot seem to tell a drastically different story. Late Friday, the pop star posted a disturbing…</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 00:44:03 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>