<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 06:59:08 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Building LLMs in the Open-Source Community: A Call to Action for Investment Professionals</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/20/building-llms-in-the-open-source-community-a-call-to-action-for-investment-professionals/</link><description>Large language models like ChatGPT are changing the way we think about investing and reshaping roles in the investment profession.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 16:26:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scarlett Johansson says she's 'shocked, angered and in disbelief' over Sam Altman using a copycat voice for his new ChatGPT bot</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/21/scarlett-johansson-new-chatgpt-bot-sam-altman-openai/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1707035409-e1716250143129.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>OpenAI said it is “working to pause” Sky — the name of one of five voices that ChatGPT users can chose to speak with.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 11:52:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sustainability Reporting: Navigating Assurance Practices</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/17/sustainability-reporting-navigating-assurance-practices/</link><description>Don't be lulled into a false sense of security by the word "assurance" when evaluating sustainability reports. Assurance practices vary, and investors would be wise to learn more about the different levels of coverage.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 17:57:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden and Trump united on heavy import tariffs as election approaches</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/21/biden-trump-united-heavy-import-tariffs-election-deciding-states-pennsylvania-michigan-wisconsin/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/AP24141751493463-e1716287736438.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Trump and Biden agree on essentially nothing else, from taxes and climate change to immigration and regulation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 11:37:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Power of Clicks, Likes, and Shares: Promote the Right Kind of Financial Content</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/16/the-power-of-clicks-likes-and-shares-promote-the-right-kind-of-financial-content/</link><description>Not all financial content creators on social media are created equal. A broad differentiation can be made between influencers, knowledge sharers, and aspiring thought leaders.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 14:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gen Zers walk into the workplace with one foot out the door—slandering them won’t solve the future-of-work conundrum</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/21/gen-zers-workplace-slander-future-of-work-careers/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-200416661-005-e1716286410847.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>In a society where possibilities are endless, it shouldn’t come as a shock that there is an appeal in betting on yourself if your values are being ignored.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 11:15:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why the New T+1 Settlement Cycle Matters: A Global Index Provider’s Perspective</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/14/why-the-new-t1-settlement-cycle-matters-a-global-index-providers-perspective/</link><description>Shorter settlement periods are meant to protect market participants. But the new T+1 settlement cycle for US equities may have undesirable knock-on effects for financial market participants around the world, including index fund managers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 16:54:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump’s Truth Social company lost more than $300 million in its first quarter as a public company</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/21/trump-truth-social-trump-media-and-technology-group-q1-earnings/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2144465619-e1716285465674.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>At this early stage in the Company’s development, TMTG remains focused on long-term product development, rather than quarterly revenue,” Trump Media said.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 10:58:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Leveraging AI to Identify and Predict Financial Crises</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/13/leveraging-ai-to-identify-and-predict-financial-crises/</link><description>Despite some current limitations, AI stands to offer significant advantages versus traditional approaches to identifying and predicting financial crises.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 14:39:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Drone pilots don't have First Amendment right to offer mapping services</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/21/drone-pilot-first-amendment-right-mapping-services-state-surveyors-license-court/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/AP24141777684666-e1716285009681.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The panel of the 4th U.S. Circuit Court of Appeals, in upholding a trial court’s decision, found the free-speech protections of Michael Jones and his 360 Virtual Drone Services business weren't violated.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 10:55:54 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>