<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 01:49:32 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Did This Market Move Catch You by Surprise?</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/did-this-market-move-catch-you-by-surprise/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, Ross here. Did yesterday's market dip catch you off guard? It erased last week's gains, but from a technical standpoint, it's a typical response after hitting new all-time highs. Now, the real question is how the support from March's highs will hold up. Even if it breaks, expect some sideways movement—no need to panic. Remember, markets need to shake out the overeager traders to climb higher, and that's exactly what we're seeing. It's the perfect setup for my Stealth Trades strategy, which leverages the moves of big institutional money. In fact, this Memorial Day, I’m offering a special on my strategy for just 99 cents for a full year. Don't miss out on this opportunity to align with the big players and position for the next surge. Grab it before the weekend! The post Did This Market Move Catch You by Surprise? appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Junkyard Gem: 1977 Dodge Aspen Wagon</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/25/junkyard-gem-1977-dodge-aspen-wagon/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/08155153/99-1977-Dodge-Aspen-Station-wagon-in-Colorado-junkyard-photo-by-Murilee-Martin.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Dodge , Automotive History , Wagon , Classics Continue reading Junkyard Gem: 1977 Dodge Aspen Wagon Junkyard Gem: 1977 Dodge Aspen Wagon originally appeared on Autoblog on Sat, 25 May 2024 12:30:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>High Interest Rates Are Forcing Big-Time Investors to Cut Their Losses—Is a Bust Coming?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/high-interest-rates-are-forcing-big-time-investors-to-sell</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>The sudden increase in interest rates has left many experienced commercial real estate owners gasping for air. It’s a tsunami of woe for landlords who own office and retail space and never […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 17:29:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Most Popular Posts of the Week</title><link>https://bookriot.com/the-most-popular-posts-of-the-week/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/summer-2024-books-to-read.webp</image_url><description>Pets eating books, exciting books to read this summer, horror short story collections, and more in this week's most popular posts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 18:05:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sharing Fun Facts About Yourself: 22 Examples &amp; Ideas</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/fun-facts-about-me/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fun-facts-about-me</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Asking to share some fun facts about yourself is a common icebreaker that’s used during job interviews. But the quality of your answer still matters. This guide will help you come up with some ideas for crafting a response that starts the interview on a good note. Table of contents Ideas for Sharing Fun Facts […] The post Sharing Fun Facts About Yourself: 22 Examples &amp; Ideas appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 15:26:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Becoming Confident in Parenting Abilities</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/confidence-in-parenting/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=confidence-in-parenting</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Parental self-efficacy (i.e., a parent’s confidence in their own ability to care for their infant and respond to the infant’s needs) is the first step to a good parent-child relationship. Research has explored the development of maternal self-efficacy beginning during pregnancy and continuing after childbirth. Mothers who have previous childbirth and […] The post Becoming Confident in Parenting Abilities appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 10:06:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Grayson Murray dies at age 30 a day after withdrawing from Colonial, PGA Tour says</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/25/grayson-murray-dies-at-age-30-a-day-after-withdrawing-from-colonial-pga-tour-says.html</link><description>Two-time PGA Tour winner Grayson Murray died Saturday morning at age 30, one day after he withdrew from the Charles Schwab Cup Challenge at Colonial.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 21:21:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nicki Minaj Detained by Police in Amsterdam and Livestreams Incident</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1402426/nicki-minaj-detained-by-police-at-amsterdam-airport-and-livestreams-incident?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>Dutch military police temporarily detained Nicki Minaj in the Netherlands for an alleged drug offense and her fans got a front row look. The "Anaconda" rapper, who maintained her innocence while...</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 01:34:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: The New World Economy in 5 Trends</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/24/book-review-the-new-world-economy-in-5-trends/</link><description>A diligent economist and an eclectic bookworm serve up an analysis of megatrends that will have the greatest impact on economies and investments: innovation, productivity, climate, multiglobalization, debt, and aging.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 12:22:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ferrari 296 GTS Hybrid Review: ‘Arresting, uncanny beauty’ with $366,139 price tag</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/26/ferrari-296-gts-hybrid-review-beauty-366139-price/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/cropped-Ferrari-GTS-hybrid-martyn-lucy-GettyImages-1947682592-e1716215162910.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>As Ferrari rolls toward its first all-electric car, arriving next year, it makes sense that it would also make a hybrid or two.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Warm Weather Hair Care</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/warm-weather-hair-care/</link><description>Outfit Details: Cala de la Cruz Dress, Emme Parsons Sandals, Saint Laurent Sunglasses One of the essential parts of summer… The post Warm Weather Hair Care appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 05:00:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tesla in self driving mode</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/aVvQn52</link><description>Tags: cars , tesla , wtf 1689 points, 275 comments.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 06:45:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Our Chat with Cards’ President Bill DeWitt III About New City Connect Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/25/our-chat-with-cards-president-bill-dewitt-iii-about-new-city-connect-uniforms/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The St. Louis Cardinals brand new Nike MLB City Connect uniforms will be making their on-field début this afternoon. The red jerseys with “The Lou” scripted across the chest, inspired by the hit song from Nelly, were unveiled on Monday to an overall positive reaction from fans and media alike.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 17:17:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The ups and downs of investing in Europe, with VCs Saul Klein and Raluca Ragab</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/25/the-ups-and-downs-of-investing-in-europe-with-vcs-saul-klein-and-raluca-ragab/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>When it comes to the world of venture-backed startups, some issues are universal, and some are very dependent on where the startups and its backers are located. It’s something we talked about this week in London, when TechCrunch took its StrictlyVC series of more intimate, more investor-focused events on the road. Sitting down with Saul […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:20:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Legal Doctrine That Shields Police From Many Lawsuits May Be Losing Support</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/25/police-mississippi-courts-judges-qualified-immunity</link><description>A federal judge in Mississippi joined other courts in recently rejecting police arguments that qualified immunity protected their actions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Salmon Marinade</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/salmon-marinade/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>A great salmon marinade makes your fish flavorful, tender, and juicy! This recipe gives each filet the perfect balance of…</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adam Silver Says NBA's Negotiations W/ TNT Not Dead Yet, 'We're All Still Talking'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/25/adam-silver-says-nbas-negotiations-w-tnt-not-dead-yet-we-re-all-still-talking/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Fill in the gravesite and call off the funeral ... Adam Silver says despite all the perception of doom and gloom surrounding the NBA's current negotiations with TNT -- the talks between the sides are NOT dead yet. The Association's commissioner…</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 01:49:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Federal Experts Talk Bird Flu ‘What Ifs’ in WebMD Live Event</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/cold-and-flu/news/20240516/federal-experts-talk-bird-flu-what-ifs?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>WebMD brought together experts from four federal agencies to talk prevention, monitoring, and what the “what ifs” of bird flu might look like.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:50:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Weekend In New Orleans With Kids</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/new-orleans-with-kids/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Since our travel guides to Charleston with kids and Palm Springs with kids have elicited requests for more travel ideas with kids, we’re back with an overdue recap of our 3-night trip to New Orleans. We’d never been to The Big Easy before and were impressed by how family-friendly the city is. It’s not all booze, beads, and Bourbon Street! So here’s a look at where we stayed, what we did, and what we’re excited to do next time we go back – because we will definitely go back! The four of us (well, five if you count our chihuahua!) went to NOLA for 3 nights in November of 2022. At the time, our kids were 8 and 12 years old. So unfortunately we can’t vouch for our suggestions being a good fit for toddlers or younger children. Although I’m sure ours would’ve loved the Louisiana Children’s Museum and Storyland playground back in the day! Continue reading A Weekend In New Orleans With Kids at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 17:17:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Big of a Problem is Inflation Really?</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/how-big-of-a-problem-is-inflation-really/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, Ross here. As we navigate through the bull market, one looming question persists: How big of a problem is inflation really? Despite the alarm bells rung by bears and the media, our latest data shows a decrease in the number of S&amp;P 500 companies concerned about inflation during their earnings calls. This signals a potentially overstated issue, with corporate earnings—key market drivers—still on solid ground. If you're watching the market meander sideways and finding it "boring," you might be missing out. Sideways markets are ripe for strategic positioning, often preceding significant movements. Join me tomorrow at 10 a.m. Eastern for a masterclass where I'll delve into insider trading insights, showing you how to distinguish between high and low signal trades and uncover the top-performing insiders. Plus, I'll share an exclusive opportunity that's just come onto my radar. Don’t miss this chance to learn from the insiders—reserve your spot now! The post How Big of a Problem is Inflation Really? appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New cars in California could alert drivers for breaking the speed limit</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/25/new-cars-in-california-could-alert-drivers-for-breaking-the-speed-limit/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/23132949/us-transport.jpeg</image_url><description>Filed under: Government/Legal , Safety Continue reading New cars in California could alert drivers for breaking the speed limit New cars in California could alert drivers for breaking the speed limit originally appeared on Autoblog on Sat, 25 May 2024 11:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Brian Took the Easy Way Out—Here’s Why He Made a Big Mistake and Why I’m Never Selling My Properties</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/brian-took-the-easy-way-out-why-im-never-selling-my-properties</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>A very “good” problem many investors have is whether they should sell or rent their primary residence when it comes time to move out. I have been blessed with this problem […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 17:05:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Riot’s YA Book Deals of the Day for May 25, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/book-riots-ya-book-deals-of-the-day-for-may-25-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Untitled-design-58.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>A teen living through the Kuala Lumpur race riots, a magical historical fantasy, a mission to Jupiter's moon, and more of today's best YA book deals.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 553</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-553/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-553</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Tools and technology change rapidly. Yet as wonderful as technology can be, it doesn’t replace the need for human connection through interactions. Keep this in mind as you are searching for a new job. It’s your human connections that often open doors! In this week’s collection of news and tips for job seekers, you’ll find: […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 553 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 12:19:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A case for public preschool: New study reveals preschool benefits to be longer-lasting and substantial</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/benefits-of-public-preschool/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=benefits-of-public-preschool</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Preschool lays a foundation for elementary school students to succeed. In the United States, as children approach kindergarten entry, it is increasingly common for 4-year-olds to be in non-parental group care and education, often in a center- or school-based setting where they can learn alongside peers. For children from low-income communities, […] The post A case for public preschool: New study reveals preschool benefits to be longer-lasting and substantial appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 08:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elon Musk plans xAI supercomputer, The Information reports</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/25/elon-musk-plans-xai-supercomputer-the-information-reports.html</link><description>Musk founded xAI last year as a challenger to Microsoft-backed OpenAI and Alphabet's Google.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 20:11:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 77 Best Memorial Day Fashion Deals: J.Crew, Michael Kors &amp; More</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1402335/the-best-memorial-day-2024-fashion-deals-j-crew-banana-republic-old-navy-michael-kors-gap-more?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>We independently selected these products and deals because we love them, and we think you might like them at these prices. E! has affiliate relationships, so we may get a commission if you...</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Factor Strategies Belong in Your Completion Portfolio Toolkit</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/23/factor-strategies-belong-in-your-completion-portfolio-toolkit/</link><description>Why wouldn't you include factor strategies in your completion portfolio? A review of the two commonly used approaches for managing institutional assets highlights their symbiotic nature.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 19:09:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Janet Yellen warns higher outlook for rates will make it harder to keep deficits and debt expenses under control</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/25/deficit-debt-warning-janet-yellen-higher-rate-outlook-interest-expenses/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2153651062-e1716681638211.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The White House sees 10-year Treasury yields at 3.7% in the early 2030s — almost a full percentage point higher than three years ago.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 01:12:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coastal Breeze Style</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/coastal-breeze-style/</link><description>Outfit Details: EPHEMERA Bikini, Zankov Dress, Loro Piana Hat, Marni Bag, Hermes Bangles (similar here, less expensive here), Bottega Venita Sunglasses The weather has… The post Coastal Breeze Style appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 05:00:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Today it randomly snowed in mexico (puebla)\u2026 in the summer\u2026 during a heatwave. It melted immediately and people\u2019s homes are getting flooded</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/aW40zwK</link><description>Tags: wtf 6344 points, 565 comments.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 06:45:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ligue 1’s Lille OSC Put Unique Spin on Traditional Chevron for 2024-25 Home Kits</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/24/ligue-1s-lille-osc-put-unique-spin-on-traditional-chevron-for-2024-25-home-kits/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Club's traditional chevron, which they've used in some form since the 1940s, appears on new kits made up of several tonal mini-chevrons</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 22:01:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scarlett Johansson brought receipts to the OpenAI controversy</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/25/scarlett-johansson-brought-receipts-to-the-openai-controversy/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Welcome back to TechCrunch’s Week in Review — TechCrunch’s newsletter recapping the week’s biggest news. Want it in your inbox every Saturday? Sign up here. OpenAI announced this week that it’s removing Sky, one of the voices used by its new GPT-4o model, after users found it sounded eerily similar to Scarlett Johansson’s AI character […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 21:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Out of the Blue: The Rise and Fall of a Black Cop</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/23/black-police-officers-cleveland-black-shield</link><description>After Cleveland officer Vincent Montague shot a Black man, he got promoted. Then he allied with Black Lives Matter, and his life went off the rails.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>John Wayne Casserole</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/john-wayne-casserole/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>This delicious John Wayne Casserole is Mexican comfort food at its finest! Layers of seasoned ground beef, creamy cheddar cheese…</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Selling the OC' Sean Palmieri Fires Back at Ex-Castmates, Villain Label</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/25/sean-palmieri-selling-the-oc-fires-back-castmates-villian-label/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Former "Selling the OC" star Sean Palmieri's going scorched earth on his ex-colleagues ... firing off a barrage of critiques -- and, telling fans who think he's the villain to look at everyone else's behavior. We caught up with Palmieri on Rodeo…</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 01:49:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What’s Next in Health Care for Older Adults: Questions and Answers With John Whyte, MD</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/blog-aging-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>As WebMD’s chief medical officer, John Whyte, MD, is in a unique position to see both the current state of medical care for America’s older adults and the way things are trending for the future. We asked him to share his insight on a few topics, along with a bit of advice.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:29:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Easy Low-Light Indoor Plants</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/easy-low-light-indoor-plants/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>I used to think every houseplant needed a sunny corner or bright windowsill to thrive. But it turns out many of our favorite go-to houseplants do just fine in shady corners and low-light locations. So before you write off your house as too dark to sustain plant life, check out this list of the best indoor plants for low light. You might be surprised at how many good options there are! Our upstairs family room is the brightest room we’ve ever owned thanks to big unobstructed windows on all 4 sides. But most of our indoor plants live downstairs, where we get far less natural light. Luckily, that hasn’t stopped us from growing our collection of happy healthy houseplants. 9 Houseplants That Don’t Need A Lot Of Light Here are our favorite low-light indoor plants. We list a lot more info on them below, but here’s a quick list to bring on your next trip to the plant store: Snake Plant ZZ Plant Pothos Heartleaf Philodendron English Ivy Aglaonema Cast Iron Plant Monstera Parlor Palm Perhaps our favorite part of this list is that these aren’t ugly “consolation plants” that people begrudgingly buy for dark homes. Continue reading Easy Low-Light Indoor Plants at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 14:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Don’t Wait for This to Happen</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/dont-wait-for-this-to-happen/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Markets are soaring to new all-time highs, and the bears are out in full force. But don't be fooled—this bull market extends beyond the U.S. Today's chart highlights the All-Country World Index, showcasing the global market's performance. It’s at an all-time high too, proving the American bull market is not an outlier. Tune in at 3 p.m. Eastern for my live masterclass, where I'll show you how to position yourself for super performance by following corporate insiders. Don't miss this opportunity! The post Don’t Wait for This to Happen appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 15:55:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Explore new trails with up to $1,688 off Cannondale eBikes: Exclusive discounts at REI's Anniversary Sale</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/article/explore-new-trails-with-up-to-1688-off-cannondale-ebikes-exclusive-discounts-at-reis-anniversary-sale/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/22140705/male_mountain_biker_pauses_on_mountain_top.jpeg</image_url><description>Filed under: Commerce Continue reading Explore new trails with up to $1,688 off Cannondale eBikes: Exclusive discounts at REI's Anniversary Sale Explore new trails with up to $1,688 off Cannondale eBikes: Exclusive discounts at REI's Anniversary Sale originally appeared on Autoblog on Sat, 25 May 2024 10:30:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BiggerNews: 2024 Housing Market Update and Why Prices Are Still Rising</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-959</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>The 2024 housing market isn’t turning out how most of us thought. At the beginning of the year, real estate investors were hopeful that mortgage rates would fall, affordability would […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 07:02:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Riot’s Deals of the Day for May 25, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/book-riots-deals-of-the-day-for-may-25-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/deals-052524.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>A beautiful beekeeper, different ways to experience time, Ghanian email scams, and more of today's best book deals.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 552</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-552/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-552</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>When you are searching for a job, you will inevitably run into unexpected scenarios. You will have questions, experience self-doubt and even feel discouraged. You’ll also experience great wins, meet wonderful people and discover new things about yourself. That’s the roller-coaster of job search. Consider Summary Sunday your resource for getting questions answered and showing […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 552 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 11:37:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fathers’ views on family and work after COVID-19 lockdowns</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/fathers-views-on-family-and-work-after-covid-19-lockdowns/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fathers-views-on-family-and-work-after-covid-19-lockdowns</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Fathers often want to be present for their children and contribute to household tasks, but they can lack opportunities and confidence; they may see themselves as “helpers” instead of parents. Australian fathers in our small study reported that they spent more time with their children during the COVID-19 lockdowns, and they […] The post Fathers’ views on family and work after COVID-19 lockdowns appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>European banks in Russia face 'awful lot of risk', Yellen says</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/25/european-banks-in-russia-face-awful-lot-of-risk-yellen-says.html</link><description>President Biden's new secondary sanctions allow the Treasury to cut off banks from the U.S. financial system if they assist Russia's invasion of Ukraine.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 17:13:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sophia Bush Reacts After Ashlyn Harris Photos Spark Engagement Rumors</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1402415/sophia-bush-responds-after-new-pics-with-ashlyn-harris-spark-engagement-rumors?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>Sophia Bush wants these rumors to go the way of John Tucker. The One Tree Hill alum is showing her hand, literally, after photos of herself and partner Ashlyn Harris, 38, on a trip to...</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 23:57:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>For the Analyst: Peer Benchmarking Methods to Improve Earnings Forecasts</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/21/for-the-analyst-peer-benchmarking-methods-to-improve-earnings-forecasts/</link><description>Peer benchmarking is a vexing task for financial analysts but one that is critical for forecasting earnings. This straightforward measure can help find peers for relative performance, compensation, and valuation benchmarking.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 12:47:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Could drugs like Ozempic and Wegovy help people live longer? Some experts see them as potential longevity pills</title><link>https://fortune.com/well/article/ozempic-glp1-help-people-live-longer-longevity/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1499754635.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>“The singular most effective and consistent way of extending lifespan in animals is caloric restriction.”</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Colors Of The Sea</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/colors-of-the-sea/</link><description>Outfit Details: Show Me Your Mumu Coverup (also similar here), Good American Swimsuit, Miu Miu Sandals, Valentino Hat, Prada Sunglasses, Hanna Andersson Dress, Teva Sandals &amp; Stella Kids… The post Colors Of The Sea appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 05:00:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Life hacks</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/aZZWGWz</link><description>Tags: Random life hacks , random 4230 points, 279 comments.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 06:45:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Memorial Cup Host Saginaw Spirit Unveil Commemorative Jersey for Tourney Opener</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/24/memorial-cup-host-saginaw-spirit-unveil-commemorative-jersey-for-tourney-opener/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Like the Memorial Cup itself, Spirit jersey for Friday's opening game against the Moose Jaw Warriors honors fallen military personnel</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 15:34:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deal Dive: Can blockchain make weather forecasts better? WeatherXM thinks so</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/25/deal-dive-can-blockchain-make-weather-forecasts-better-weatherxm-thinks-so/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Accurate weather forecasts are critical to industries like agriculture, and they’re also important to help prevent and mitigate harm from inclement weather events or natural disasters. But getting forecasts right is extremely difficult. That’s why the founders of WeatherXM have been looking to make weather forecasts more accurate for the past 12 years. In 2012, […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Marshall Project Wins Prestigious Robert F. Kennedy Journalism Award for Criminal Justice</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/21/marshall-project-rfk-award</link><description>The award recognizes our 2023 investigation exposing lax prison discipline for abusive guards in New York state prisons.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Memorial Day Menu Plan</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/memorial-day-menu-plan/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>This Memorial Day Menu Plan makes holiday planning a breeze! I’ve even included a shopping list, so you can spend…</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Diddy's Walk of Fame Star Cannot Be Removed</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/25/diddy-no-discussion-remove-walk-of-fame-star-downfall/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Calls to remove Diddy's Hollywood Walk of Fame star are gaining traction amid his downfall -- but the team behind the honor has made no such move. A Hollywood Chamber of Commerce spokesperson tells TMZ ... they have not discussed it and the org is…</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 01:49:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Get the Care You Need in a COVID-19 World</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/covid-senior-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>What to expect at the doctor’s office, hospitals, and long-term care facilities, the future of telemedicine, and how to get the best care during COVID-19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 19:50:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/how-to-remove-wallpaper/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Wallpaper has made a big comeback as a trendy home design choice. But despite its resurgence, there are still plenty of us dealing with dingy, dated, or downright ugly old wallpaper we don’t want. In our old home, we had to remove wallpaper in so many rooms: the kitchen, the dining room, the foyer, and two different bathrooms! As we traveled from room to room removing wallpaper, we tested 4 different methods, and today we’ll share what we learned. Removing wallpaper doesn’t require special tools or lots of money. It’s a totally doable project for any homeowner. However, it can be a tedious process that can take elbow grease and patience, depending on the size of your room and the stubbornness of your wallpaper. But having removed several rooms worth of decades-old wallpaper, we can confidently say it’s worth the effort! You can also check out more before and afters of our once-wallpapered rooms. Continue reading How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:21:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Data-Backed Glimpse of the Market’s Future</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/a-data-backed-glimpse-of-the-markets-future/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>The bears keep insisting this bull market can't last, but let's dive into the data. The S&amp;P 500 has surged about 48% since its October 2022 lows. Historically, the average gain two years in is 57%, suggesting even more upside by October 2024. Ignore the naysayers and focus on the facts. Join me at 11 a.m. ET for a live masterclass where I'll show you how to align with top corporate insiders. Learn their winning strategies and spot a hot insider opportunity. Don't miss out—secure your spot now! The post A Data-Backed Glimpse of the Market’s Future appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Austin Pedal Car reemerges in new, bespoke form</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/25/austin-pedal-car-reemerges-in-new-bespoke-form/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/21182114/Screenshot-2024-05-21-at-18.11.53.png</image_url><description>Filed under: Toys/Games , Automotive History , Classics Continue reading Austin Pedal Car reemerges in new, bespoke form Austin Pedal Car reemerges in new, bespoke form originally appeared on Autoblog on Sat, 25 May 2024 09:30:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fundamentals of Funding: How to Finance Real Estate Without the Big Banks</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-410</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Private money is a “secret weapon” for real estate investing, allowing you to dodge the major banks and fund real estate deals on your terms. But just how easy is […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 07:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Number of Independent Bookstores in the U.S. Has Doubled in the Last 8 Years</title><link>https://bookriot.com/today-in-books-may-24-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Screenshot-2024-05-24-at-7.32.26 AM.png</image_url><description>Today's links include the continued rise in independent bookstores, a master bookseller on bookselling, and more.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 20:41:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>While a little competition in the workplace might help bring out the best in everyone involved, an atmosphere rooted in envy, fear, or jealousy can do the exact opposite. This post will help you recognize signs that your coworker is threatened by you, and help you navigate the situation. 1. They Don’t Want You Involved […] The post 10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:07:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Strong Latine Identity Supports U.S. Latine Children’s Well-Being</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/a-strong-latine-identity-supports-u-s-latine-childrens-well-being/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=a-strong-latine-identity-supports-u-s-latine-childrens-well-being</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key Takeaways for caregivers Children tend to have better health and well-being when they have a strong ethnic identity (affinity and adoption of ethnicity-based self-concept). A traditional Latine cultural value (familismo) that emphasizes family bonds is also associated with better developmental outcomes. Caregivers can support the development of U.S. Latine children (and possibly other children […] The post A Strong Latine Identity Supports U.S. Latine Children’s Well-Being appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 03:03:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 'absolute worst' of times for car buying are over</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/25/the-absolute-worst-of-times-for-car-buying-are-over.html</link><description>The “absolute worst” of times for car buying are over as dealerships slash prices heading into the summer, analysts say.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 16:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PGA Tour Winner Grayson Murray Dead at 30</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1402423/pga-tour-winner-grayson-murray-dead-at-30?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>The golf world is in mourning. Two-time PGA Tour winner Grayson Murray died March 25. He was 30. "We were devastated to learn—and are heartbroken to share—that PGA TOUR player Grayson Murray...</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 22:22:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Building LLMs in the Open-Source Community: A Call to Action for Investment Professionals</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/20/building-llms-in-the-open-source-community-a-call-to-action-for-investment-professionals/</link><description>Large language models like ChatGPT are changing the way we think about investing and reshaping roles in the investment profession.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 16:26:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tesla shareholders should reject Elon Musk’s ‘excessive’ pay package, proxy advisor says, noting ‘extraordinarily time-consuming projects’ unrelated to EV maker</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/25/tesla-shareholders-elon-musk-pay-package-proxy-advisor-glass-lewis/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2151265017-e1716680351499.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>“Mr. Musk’s slate of extraordinarily time-consuming projects unrelated to the Company was well-documented before the 2018 grant, and only expanded with his high-profile purchase of the company now known as X,” said Glass Lewis.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:49:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Walmart Summer Fashion Under $50</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/walmart-summer-fashion-under-50/</link><description>Thank you to Walmart for sponsoring this post. I have a passion for finding beautiful fashion pieces for women and… The post Walmart Summer Fashion Under $50 appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 05:00:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Just a prank bro</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/a9yMQPo</link><description>Tags: Rich 3967 points, 676 comments.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 06:45:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Announcing Player 97: Our New Brand Vision, Research, Consulting Company</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/24/player-97-consulting-brand-vision-historical-research/misc/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Today, I’m excited to announce the official launch of Player 97, the new consulting, research, and branding company managed by the same friendly faces that have been running SportsLogos.Net. After many years of helping teams, leagues, designers, and other companies, I decided to finally make it official—folks, I am here</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 14:39:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spyware app pcTattletale was hacked and its website defaced</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/25/spyware-app-pctattletale-was-hacked-and-its-website-defaced/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>pcTattletale's website was briefly defaced and contained links containing files from the spyware maker's servers, before going offline. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 16:29:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Police Tactics at Some Pro-Palestine Protests Ignore Past Lessons</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/18/police-israel-palestine-campus-protests</link><description>While some universities have sought peaceful approaches, others have used aggressive policing that bucks research from the protests following George Floyd’s murder.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Grilled Tilapia</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/grilled-tilapia/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Fire up the grill! This grilled tilapia is deliciously seasoned and has the best flaky texture. Mix a few simple…</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Island Boys' Franky Venegas Arrested For Driving Offenses in Florida</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/25/island-boys-franky-venegas-florida-arrested-driving-offenses/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Franky Venegas – one half of the viral hip hop duo The Island Boys – has been busted in Florida for driving-related offenses. The tattooed TikTok star --who shares the limelight with his twin brother Alex – was arrested in Fort Lauderdale…</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 01:49:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Personal Shopper: A Savvy Black Entrepreneur Guides You to Eczema-Friendly Clothes, Creams, Cosmetics, and More</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/savvy-black-entrepreneur-guides-eczema-friendly-clothes-creams-cosmetics?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>A savvy black entrepreneur guides you on an eczema-friendly shopping spree.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:54:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aglaonema Plant – Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/aglaonema-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Aglaonema, also called the Chinese Evergreen Plant, is an easy-care houseplant that lives happily in many lighting conditions – even a dark corner of our daughter’s room. There are dozens of different Aglaonema varieties, most with large tropical foliage and colors ranging from silvery-green, red, and even vibrant pink. They’re also tough to kill, so they’re a great option for forgetful plant owners or anyone looking for an easy win in the plant department. These truly have been very low maintenance for us. We purchased our two Aglaonemas (pronounced ag-lee-oh-neem-ah ) to put atop our daughter’s closet. It’s sometimes hard to distinguish different varieties, but we believe that’s an Aglaonema Silver (right) and either a Candy Cane or Princess Silver Queen (left). Aglaonema Quick Facts Here’s what you need to know about your Aglaonema at a glance: Latin name : Aglaonema is the genus under which there are 21 recognized species . Continue reading Aglaonema Plant – Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:47:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Profit from the Market’s Appetite</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/profit-from-the-markets-appetite/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, Ross here. Last week showed us that even after a brief slowdown, the markets are still on an upward trajectory—and it's clear from today's Bitcoin chart that we're just getting started. The bull flag pattern I highlighted is unfolding right before our eyes, with Bitcoin surging nearly 10% in just four days. This movement isn't just about Bitcoin; it reflects a broader market craving for risk, and today, I'll show you how to leverage this appetite to your advantage. Ready to join the insiders who are already capitalizing on this trend? Join me tomorrow at 11 a.m. Eastern for a can’t-miss masterclass. The post Profit from the Market’s Appetite appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 14:46:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Embrace the elements with the Arc'teryx Beta LT Jacket, now 30% off</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/article/embrace-the-elements-with-the-arcteryx-beta-lt-jacket-now-30-off/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/22130959/488e8b30-72f5-40e4-9172-17df0195-1.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Commerce Continue reading Embrace the elements with the Arc'teryx Beta LT Jacket, now 30% off Embrace the elements with the Arc'teryx Beta LT Jacket, now 30% off originally appeared on Autoblog on Sat, 25 May 2024 09:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Financial Freedom in 9 Steps: The Money Guy’s Financial Order of Operations</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-531</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>If you follow these nine steps, you will reach financial independence. How do we know? Well, The Money Guy Show’s Brian Preston and Bo Hanson have tested it hundreds of […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 07:01:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Riot’s Deals of the Day for May 24, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/book-riots-deals-of-the-day-for-may-24-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/deals-052424.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>A twist on Cinderella, the myth of Psyche and Eros, a Danish port town epic, and more of today's best book deals.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 16:18:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 551</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-551/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-551</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Job search requires writing and marketing skills. It also requires strong verbal communication. If these skills are not part of your normal work function, you’ll want some help. That’s what this week’s Summary Sunday is all about. There’s no doubt that LinkedIn is one of THE most powerful tools in your career toolbox. It contains […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 551 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 11:37:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Children caught between highly conflicted divorced parents at greater risk of mental health problems</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/children-caught-between-conflicted-divorced-parents/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=children-caught-between-conflicted-divorced-parents</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Interparental conflict after divorce escalates the risk of mental health problems in children and adolescents. Elevated levels of conflict between parents can also induce fear and worry in children about their future and whether they will be adequately taken care of. In turn, a greater fear of abandonment puts children at […] The post Children caught between highly conflicted divorced parents at greater risk of mental health problems appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 08:59:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>U.S. screens record 2.95 million airline passengers in single day</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/25/us-screens-record-2point95-million-airline-passengers-in-single-day.html</link><description>The U.S. Transportation Security Administration (TSA) said it screened 2.95 million airline passengers on Friday, the highest number ever on a single day.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 16:26:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BaubleBar Memorial Day Sale: $10 Jewelry, Plus Extra 20% Off Necklaces</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1402260/baublebar-memorial-day-sale-score-s10-jewelry-plus-an-extra-20-off-bestselling-necklaces-more?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>We independently selected these deals and products because we love them, and we think you might like them at these prices. E! has affiliate relationships, so we may get a commission if you...</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sustainability Reporting: Navigating Assurance Practices</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/17/sustainability-reporting-navigating-assurance-practices/</link><description>Don't be lulled into a false sense of security by the word "assurance" when evaluating sustainability reports. Assurance practices vary, and investors would be wise to learn more about the different levels of coverage.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 17:57:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Top assassin for the Sinaloa drug cartel, once described as ‘a complete psychopath’ with long history of gruesome acts, is extradited to U.S.</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/25/sinaloa-drug-cartel-assassin-el-nini-extradited-el-chapo-guzman-chapitos/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1251816769-e1716679229306.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Nestor Isidro Pérez Salas, also known as “El Nini,” is a leader of a group that provided security for the sons of imprisoned drug lord Joaquín “El Chapo” Guzmán, federal investigators said.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:29:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summer Ready With Saks Designer Sale</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/summer-ready-with-saks-designer-sale/</link><description>Thank you to Saks Fifth Avenue for sponsoring this post. Summer is just around the corner, making it the perfect… The post Summer Ready With Saks Designer Sale appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 05:00:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Welcome to China, a living utopia</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/a87bR11</link><description>Tags: wtf , china , insane 1383 points, 285 comments.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 06:45:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Football in Their DNA: AC Milan Launches 2024-25 Home Kit</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/23/football-in-their-dna-ac-milan-launches-2024-25-home-kit/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Tonal segmented stripes inside red stripes are a visual representation of the human genome; patch on back collar celebrates club's 125th anniversary</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 16:11:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Synapse, backed by a16z, has collapsed, and 10 million consumers could be hurt</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/25/with-a16z-backed-synapses-collapse-baas-fintech-is-a-mess-and-10-million-consumers-could-be-hurt/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Synapse's bankruptcy shows just how treacherous things are for the often-interdependent fintech world when one key player hits trouble. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Susan Chira to Step Down as The Marshall Project’s Editor-in-Chief in January</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/16/susan-chira-eic-step-down</link><description>Under her stewardship, the news nonprofit more than doubled in size, opened local newsrooms and won its second Pulitzer Prize.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best Burger and Secret Sauce</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/the-best-burger-and-secret-sauce-recipe/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Get ready for the ultimate burger experience topped with my irresistible Secret Sauce. The flavor packed into this burger is…</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Millie Bobby Brown, Jake Bongiovi Flaunt Rings, First Pics Since Wedding</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/24/millie-bobby-brown-jake-bongiovi-seem-to-confirm-marriage-rings-new-photos/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Millie Bobby Brown and Jake Bongiovi are lookin' very newlywed ... tooling around the Hamptons and flashing their rings in the first shots of them since their reported secret wedding. The happy couple were out and about Friday doing some shopping…</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 01:49:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Behind the Spike in Colorectal Cancer Among Young Americans</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/colorectal-cancer/news/20240515/behind-the-spike-in-colorectal-cancer-cases?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Colorectal cancer cases increased a whopping 333% among 15- to 19-year-olds and 185% among 20- to 24-year-olds from 1999 to 2020.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:59:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Corn Plant – Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/corn-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Corn plants ( Dracaena fragrans ) are popular low-maintenance houseplants you’ve probably seen at the nursery, home improvement store, or doctor’s office. I even had one in my college dorm room! You can recognize them by their spear-shaped leaves and woody, cane-line trunks that can grow up to 6 feet tall indoors. But did you know there are several varieties of corn plants? We didn’t! Heck, we didn’t even realize some of our smaller houseplants were in the same corn plant family! Currently, we own two smaller varieties of corn plants, pictured above. The one on the left is a Dracaena Limelight ( Dracaena fragrans ‘Limelight’ ) and the taller plant is a Draecanea Dorado ( Dracaena fragrans ‘Dorado’ ). We actually have several limelights around because we love their vibrant color on shelves, tabletops, and windowsills. Corn Plant Quick Facts Latin name : Dracaena fragrans Common names : Corn plant, cornstalk plant, false palms Light : Bright, indirect light but can tolerate lower-light conditions Watering : Keep soil moist, but not soggy. Continue reading Corn Plant – Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 17:37:33 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>