<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 06:56:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Chicago Bears Add George S. Halas’ Initials To 1936 Throwback Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/18/chicago-bears-add-george-s-halas-initials-to-1936-throwback-uniforms/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Chicago Bears have subtly added the initials of late founder, owner and coach George S. Halas to the left sleeve of their 1936 throwback uniforms, matching their navy blue home, white road and orange alternate jerseys.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 22:34:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Diddy's Former Media Co. Revolt 'Disturbed' by Cassie Beating Video</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/19/revolt-media-diddy-statement-cassie-ventura-beating-video/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Diddy's former employees at Revolt, the media company he co-founded, are reacting to the horrific video of him assaulting Cassie. The company posted a statement saying, "We are deeply saddened and disturbed by the recent video circulation of our…</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 06:56:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fanatics and NFLPA Reveal 2024 NFL Rookie Jerseys</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/18/fanatics-and-nflpa-reveal-2024-nfl-rookie-jerseys/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Last night, Fanatics and the NFLPA held a special “Jersey Reveal” event in Los Angeles to unveil the official game jerseys for 39 NFL rookies during the NFLPA Rookie Premiere. Several high-profile 2024 NFL Draft picks and rookies attended the event, including Caleb Williams and Rome Odunze of the Chicago</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 17:58:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ben Affleck's Wedding Ring Is Back, Jen Garner Visits Amid J Lo Marriage Drama</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/19/ben-affleck-jen-garner-wedding-ring-jennifer-lopez-split/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Ben Affleck's wedding ring found its way back on to his hand, just one day after it vanished right in the middle of his marriage drama with Jennifer Lopez. Ben's left hand went platinum (or silver) again Saturday ... the ring was visible as he…</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 06:56:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Carolina Disco Turkeys to play as Camel City Humps</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/18/carolina-disco-turkeys-to-play-as-camel-city-humps/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The town of Winston-Salem, North Carolina, is called “Camel City” because since 1875 it has been home to the R.J. Reynolds Tobacco Company, which produces Camel brand cigarettes. The town of Winston-Salem is also home to the collegiate summer level Carolina Disco Turkeys, who will put a new twist on</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 17:29:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Travis Kelce Looks Rejuvenated &amp; Happier Than Ever After Taylor Swift Getaway</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/19/travis-kelce-jam-event-happier-than-ever-taylor-swift/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Travis Kelce looks like he's feeling pretty damn good after his whirlwind trip to Europe with Taylor Swift ... bringing a renewed energy to his music festival this weekend, and letting everyone know just how freakin' happy he is. The NFL star was…</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 06:56:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>All MLB Teams are Wearing Black Camo Caps Today</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/17/all-mlb-teams-are-wearing-black-camo-caps-today/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Why are all the Major League Baseball teams wearing black and green camouflage hats today? Well, that’s because MLB and New Era are in the midst of their annual Armed Forces Day ballcap celebration; here in 2024, the caps will be worn across the league over the May 17-18-19 weekend.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 23:44:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Selena Gomez Gets Emotional During Cannes Standing Ovation</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/19/selena-gomez-cannes-crying-standing-ovation-emilia-perez/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Selena Gomez is taking yet another step back toward her acting roots, 'cause a movie she's in just premiered at Cannes and people loved it -- getting on their feet for her ... making for some light waterworks. The singer was spotted wiping away…</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 06:56:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Borussia Dortmund Aims for  a Modern Classic With 2024-25 Home Kits – Plus 3 Other European Kit Launches</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/17/borussia-dortmund-aims-for-a-modern-classic-with-2024-25-home-kits-plus-3-other-european-kit-launches/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>ACF Fiorentina leans hard into signature purple color; Bologna FC calls new home kits 'an act of love'; Athletic Bilbao goes with the flow with new away kit</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 15:54:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Diddy Posts Apology Video for Cassie Beating</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/19/diddy-posts-apology-video-for-cassie-beating/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Diddy's uttering his first words about the videotaped beating of Cassie ... saying he "takes full responsibility for his actions," and claims he's already gone to rehab. He posted a video Sunday morning, looking directly into camera, he said, "It's…</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 06:56:25 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>