<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 06:36:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Bankruptcy to Financial Freedom in Under 10 Years with a $1M+ Net Worth</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-449</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>From bankruptcy to financial freedom in just ten years?! Today’s guest is living proof that past money mistakes don’t disqualify you from building wealth with real estate. Whether you’re neck-deep […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 10:00:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Loft Orbital forms joint venture with UAE-based firm to scale satellite production in the Middle East</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/25/loft-orbital-forms-joint-venture-with-uae-based-firm-to-scale-satellite-production-in-the-middle-east/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>A holding company affiliated with an Emirati royal family is injecting a new joint venture between Abu Dhabi-based Marlan Space and startup Loft Orbital with over $100 million to grow the region’s domestic satellite manufacturing capabilities. The joint venture, called Orbitworks, will be the first commercial firm in the United Arab Emirates to mass manufacture […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How a Drop in Border Crossings May Change the Presidential Campaign</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/24/kamala-harris-dnc-border-donald-trump</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>The Democratic National Convention sought to address one of the party’s biggest weaknesses with voters.</description><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>August Mortgage Rate Update &amp; Should You Buy/Refi Now?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-246</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Mortgage rates are falling, but the Fed hasn’t made any rate cuts yet. What’s the deal? We’re explaining it all in this August mortgage rate update with repeat guest and […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 10:00:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In 2024, it really is better to run a startup in San Francisco, according to data and founders who’ve relocated</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/25/in-2024-it-really-is-better-to-run-a-startup-in-san-francisco-according-to-data-and-founders-whove-relocated/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>San Francisco’s AI startup boom is so big, even international founders who don’t run AI startups are relocating there to help their companies grow, according to several founders who recently moved. This is largely because the tech talent and investor money is still overwhelmingly concentrated there, according to new data that VC firm SignalFire exclusively […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Prosecutors Fight Exonerations</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/17/wrongful-conviction-innocence-claims-missouri-st-louis</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>As laws are passed to support the wrongfully convicted, some officials in the legal system push back.</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>8 Rental Units in 2.5 Years (While Working 6 Jobs!)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-1009</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Don’t have enough money to buy rentals? Neither did Brandon Tilson. As a social worker, he was never on the higher end of the income scale, but thanks to some […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 10:00:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Y Combinator backs its first defense startup, Ares Industries</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/25/y-combinator-backs-its-first-defense-startup-ares-industries/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>The first defense startup to receive backing from Y Combinator, Ares Industries, launched earlier this week. In a post on the YC website, the startup outlined a vision to build low-cost cruise missiles that will be compatible with existing launch platforms, saying it will “deliver the capabilities that the [Department of Defense] wants in a […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 22:21:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FAQ: How The Marshall Project Is Covering the 2024 Election</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/16/election-faq-crime-politics</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Learn more about who we are and how we choose what political stories to cover.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Our Team Is Passively Investing With Private Partnerships</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/why-our-team-is-passively-investing-with-private-partnerships</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Brian's team is shifting from syndications to private partnerships, focusing on high-return, low-risk opportunities by vetting partner trustworthiness, leverage, and regulatory risks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 20:54:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Telegram founder Pavel Durov arrested in France</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/25/telegram-founder-pavel-durov-reportedly-arrested-in-france/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Pavel Durov, founder and CEO of messaging app Telegram, was arrested on Saturday evening while leaving his private jet at France’s Le Bourget airport, as initially reported by French television network TF1. Durov’s arrest sparked widespread discussion and speculation on social media, including on Telegram itself, though news reports have been largely based on unnamed […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Mother on a Mission for Full Police Transparency</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/16/police-beating-ulysses-wilkerson-mother-video</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Troy, Alabama, police severely beat Ulysses Wilkerson when he was 17. Seven years later, his mom, Angela Williams, is still fighting for answers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The 10 Best Markets for Your First House Hack</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/best-markets-for-first-house-hack</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Rising prices and crushed affordability have made house hacking an even better way to start your investment journey. These 10 markets offer the best opportunities.</description><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 20:41:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Port of Seattle and Sea-Tac Airport say they’ve been hit by ‘possible cyberattack’</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/25/the-port-of-seattle-and-sea-tac-airport-say-theyve-been-hit-by-possible-cyberattack/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>The Port of Seattle, which also operates the Seattle-Tacoma International Airport, said it was hit with a “possible cyberattack” that appeared to affect websites and phone systems. The port first noted the outages via social media on Saturday morning, with the airport then posting that it had “experienced certain system outages indicating a possible cyberattack.” […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 17:49:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How the 1968 DNC in Chicago Devolved into ‘Unrestrained and Indiscriminate Police Violence’</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/14/chicago-dnc-protests-police-reforms</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>As protesters prepare for the Democratic National Convention in Chicago next week, a half-century old report provides lessons for preventing chaos.</description><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 11:00:44 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>