<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 14:57:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Los Angeles Kings Unveil New Logos, Modernized Take on ’90s Classic</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/20/los-angeles-kings-unveil-new-logos-modernized-take-on-90s-classic/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Los Angeles Kings are goin’ back to the ’90s, kids! This morning, the Kings unveiled their new, old logo via their social media channels, one day after posting a teaser graphic simply showing the outline of the logo. It’s a throwback, mostly, to what the club wore from 1988</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 17:13:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Celeb Hologram Creator Hit with $900 Million Sexual Assault Verdict</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/19/alki-david-900-million-verdict-sexual-assault-lawsuit-celeb-hologram-creator/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Alki David -- the tycoon who famously created Tupac and Michael Jackson holograms -- just took a huge loss in court ... 'cause a jury hit him with a huge 9-figure verdict in a sexual assault lawsuit. A jury of Alki's peers decided he oughta pay a…</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 14:57:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Here’s A Visual Guide to the Colors on the Euro 2024 Logo</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/20/heres-a-visual-guide-to-the-colors-on-the-euro-2024-logo/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>If you've been watching Euro 2024 this summer, you may have noticed the dizzying number of colors in the tournament logo and television graphics. But those colors are there and arranged the way there for a good reason.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 16:50:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Swan in 'The Warriors' 'Memba Him?!</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/20/swan-in-the-warriors-memba-him/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>American actor Michael Beck was 30 years old when he played Swan -- the smart and dreamy gang leader living in Coney Island, Brooklyn -- in the action/thriller film "The Warriors" back in 1979. Joining Beck included a cult of characters including…</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 14:57:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Los Angeles Kings Tease New Logo, Returning to an Old Favourite, for 2024-25</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/20/los-angeles-kings-tease-new-logo-returning-to-an-old-favourite-for-2024-25/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>There’s room for teasin’ from two Southern California teams in the NHL this week. Just two days after the Anaheim Ducks did so, the Los Angeles Kings have decided to join in. Last night, the Kings—wildly rumoured to be getting a new logo—changed their profile photo to show just the</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 15:43:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TMZ TV Hot Takes: Justin Timberlake Arrest, Jacob Elordi, Roger Federer</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/20/tmz-tv-hot-takes-justin-timberlake-fighting-dwi-arrest-jacob-elordi-deepfake-roger-federer-comeback/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Justin Timberlake's planning to fight his DWI arrest, Jacob Elordi's got an issue with AI and Roger Federer downplays a comeback ... all this and more on TMZ Hot Takes. First up on "TMZ Live" Harvey and Charles explain how Justin's lawyer is…</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 14:57:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NFL Second, Third Helmet Concept Series – AFC East</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/19/nfl-second-third-helmet-concept-series-afc-east/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Our newest concept series creates second and/or third helmet designs for every NFL team, starting with the AFC East.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 14:24:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Deductive Logic' Author Stoked Book Helped Spark Bill Belichick's New Romance</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/20/deductive-logic-author-pumped-book-helped-spark-bill-belichick-s-new-romance/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>A textbook on logic helped bring Bill Belichick and Jordon Hudson together ... and the man who wrote it tells TMZ Sports he couldn't be happier!! We broke the story ... the literary piece -- titled "Deductive Logic" -- was what first drew Belichick…</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 14:57:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>An Apparent Leak of the New Anaheim Ducks Uniforms &amp; Logo?</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/18/apparent-leak-of-new-anaheim-ducks-uniforms-logo/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Just one day after the Anaheim Ducks dropped a tantalizing teaser, an eager Reddit user may have spoiled the party. Thanks to a few dozen folks sending me messages, we learned that earlier today, Reddit user The_Illa_Vanilla posted an image to the Reddit/Hockey boards purportedly showing the new Anaheim Ducks</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 21:50:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Courtney Stodden Newly Engaged Days After Flushing Ex's Ring Down Toilet</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/20/courtney-stodden-engaged-boyfriend-days-flushing-ring-toilet/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Courtney Stodden is living the diamond life once again ... she's engaged to be married, and we've learned her new fiance popped the question just days after she sent her ex-fiancé's engagement ring down the toilet! Sources close to the couple tell…</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 14:57:27 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>