<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 07:19:12 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Ope! Madison Mallards unveil another alternate</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/02/ope-madison-mallards-unveil-another-alternate/baseball/</link><description>There are a lot of theories about the origins of the quirky exclamation “Ope!”—none of which stand up to any real scrutiny. More onomatopoeia than actual word, the term has been likened to “oops” or “oh” plus the letter P, and associated with most anywhere human beings have made inadvertent</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 12:07:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alfred Molina Chokes Up Talking About Dad Who Rebuffed His Acting Dream</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/01/alfred-molina-chokes-up-tears-talk-about-dad-rebuff-acting-career/</link><description>Here's your tearjerker moment of the week -- Alfred Molina is talking about his dad, who didn't approve of him being an actor ... even though he kept tabs on his boy in private. The veteran thespian sat down for an interview with Vanity Fair, and…</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 07:19:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tri-City Chili Peppers to play “Cosmic Baseball” under black lights</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/01/tri-city-chili-peppers-to-play-cosmic-baseball-under-black-lights/baseball/</link><description>Nearly a century after the Negro Leagues’ Kansas City Monarchs became the first professional baseball team to host a baseball game under artificial lights, the Coastal Plain League’s Tri-City Chili Peppers are putting their own spin on that innovation. The team will play “Cosmic Baseball” under powerful black lights that</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 02:45:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elisabeth Moss Says 'Girl, Interrupted' Split Cast, Angelina vs. Winona</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/01/elisabeth-moss-girl-interrupted-split-cast-angelina-jolie-winona-ryder/</link><description>Elisabeth Moss says filming "Girl, Interrupted" was more like a real-life "Mean Girls," as the set split into 2 camps ... with Angelina Jolie and Winona Ryder each calling shots. The two-time Golden Globe winner -- who played Polly in the 1999…</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 07:19:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rockford Rivets to rebrand as Screw City Sock Monkeys</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/01/rockford-rivets-to-rebrand-as-screw-city-sock-monkeys/baseball/</link><description>The collegiate summer level Rockford Rivets will pay tribute to their hometown’s textile and manufacturing heritage when they take to the field as the Screw City Sock Monkeys for two games this season. The Sock Monkeys nickname derives from Rockford, Illinois’s claim to “Home of the Sock Monkey”—a term the</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 02:03:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Big Boy Says Drake is Primed to Respond to Kendrick Lamar's Latest Diss</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/01/big-boy-drake-ready-respond-kendrick-lamar-diss-hip-hop-beef/</link><description>Big Boy says he's heard through the grapevine that Drake is geared up to respond to Kendrick Lamar (again) after the latter's latest harsh diss ... and the DJ loves it! The legendary Real 92.3 radio host hopped on "TMZ Live" Wednesday to give his…</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 07:19:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>First Look at the 2024 World Series and MLB Postseason Logos</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/01/first-look-at-the-2024-world-series-and-mlb-postseason-logos/baseball/</link><description>It might still be the beginning of May, but today, we’re looking forward all the way to October with the release of Major League Baseball’s 2024 Postseason Logos. First, let’s take a look at the whole package: Yes, they do feel awfully similar to last season. However, there are some</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 23:43:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Canelo Alvarez Rips 'F***ing Asshole," "P****" Oscar De La Hoya</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/01/canelo-alvarez-rips-asshole-oscar-de-la-hoya-promoter-golden-boy/</link><description>Canelo Alvarez is fighting on Saturday, but perhaps an opponent change is in order ... 'cause Saul went scorched earth on Oscar De La Hoya, as the legendary fighter sat just feet away. "He's a f***ing asshole. That's what I say. He's a f***ing…</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 07:19:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wyoming Cowboys Unveil New Gold Alternate Football Jerseys</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/01/wyoming-cowboys-unveil-new-gold-alternate-football-jerseys/college/</link><description>Wyoming recently unveiled new gold alternate jerseys that put the state and one of its most notable geographical features at the forefront of the design.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 19:31:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sammy Hagar Surprised By Chad Smith At Hollywood Walk of Fame Ceremony</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/01/sammy-hagar-surprised-chad-smithhollywood-walk-of-fame/</link><description>Sammy Hagar received one spicy surprise during his Hollywood Walk of Fame ceremony this week ... 'cause his 'Red Hot' buddy Chad Smith showed his love in person. Sources with direct knowledge tell TMZ ... Smith -- the longtime drummer for the Red…</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 07:19:12 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>