<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:28:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Mother’s Day 2024: Pink Caps, Pink Ribbons as MLB Salutes Mom</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/11/mothers-day-2024-pink-caps-pink-ribbons-as-mlb-salutes-mom/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>It’s Mother’s Day here in North America, which means we’ll see pink-themed baseball caps and ribbons on the uniforms of Major League Baseball players, coaches, managers, and umpires during games played on Sunday, May 12th. SHOP: 2024 MLB Mother’s Day team caps available right now This will be the eighth</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:07:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What's The Big Frigin' Difference?!</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/11/whats-the-big-frigin-difference/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>WHAT'S POPPIN' ya'll?! You ready to take on the sneaky switcharoos in these two images of rapper-singer Jack Harlow? It may be hard to keep your eyes off this stunna, but while you're at it take a peek at the pottery. Fresh off the Met Gala earlier…</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:28:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>EA Sports’ College Football 25 Deluxe Edition Cover Revealed</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/10/ea-sports-college-football-25-deluxe-edition-cover-revealed/college/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The deluxe edition cover of EA Sports' College Football 25 was revealed in an update to the PlayStation Store on Friday morning, generating even more excitement for the long-awaited video game ahead of its summer release.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 19:00:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FaZe Banks Says Miami Grand Prix Felt 'Bigger Than Super Bowl,' So Many Celebs!</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/11/faze-banks-says-miami-grand-prix-felt-bigger-than-super-bowl-so-many-celebs/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>The Formula One Miami Grand Prix blew the Super Bowl outta the water in the VIP department ... so says gamer FaZe Banks, who tells TMZ Sports last weekend's event was "insane!!" Folks like Patrick and Brittany Mahomes, Kendall Jenner, Steve Aoki,…</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:28:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New USL Super League Team Dallas Trinity FC Unveils Name, Logo</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/10/new-usl-super-league-team-dallas-trinity-fc-unveils-name-logo/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>New professional women's soccer team in North Texas will begin inaugural season in August and play out of historic Cotton Bowl stadium</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 16:10:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Matisyahu Says Macklemore's 'Hind's Hall' Is Antisemitic, Won't Free Palestine</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/11/matisyahu-macklemore-hinds-hall-antisemitic-not-free-palestine-israel-hamas/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Matisyahu says Macklemore's new track isn't about freeing Palestine, as Mack claims -- instead, it only sows deeper discord by pushing what he sees as antisemitic tropes. We caught up with the Jewish singer-songwriter in L.A., and he tells TMZ he's…</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:28:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paris Saint-Germain Draws From Urban Art Scene for 2024-25 Home Kit</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/10/paris-saint-germain-draws-from-urban-art-scene-for-2024-25-home-kit/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Traditional red-and-white Hechter stripe returns to center of jersey, but is "reinterpreted with a fluid and dynamic brushstroke style"</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 15:29:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aoki Simmons Posts Response to Kimora's Embarrassment Over Her Older BF</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/11/aoki-simmons-responds-kimora-lee-simmons-kissing-older-man-vittorio-assaf/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>The Simmons family mother-daughter standoff is getting more public ... as Aoki appears to be firing back at her mom Kimora Lee Simmons for commenting about Aoki's brief fling with much older restaurateur Vittorio Assaf. Aoki posted a quote Friday…</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:28:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Report: WNBA Expanding to Toronto for 2026</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/10/report-wnba-expanding-to-toronto-for-2026/basketball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The WNBA is crossing the border! According to a CBC report, Toronto will be getting a Women’s National Basketball Association expansion franchise for the 2026 WNBA season. Kilmer Sports Inc., led by Toronto billionaire Larry Tanenbaum, will own the franchise. The report says the league’s official announcement is expected to</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 14:25:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Christy Martin Honored by Sydney Sweeny Casting, Wants to Train with Her</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/11/christy-martin-honored-sydney-sweeny-casting-want-train-boxing-biopic/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Christy Martin's happy Sydney Sweeney's lacing up her boxing gloves ... saying she's thrilled Syd's playing her in a new biopic, and she wants to make sure her ring moves look authentic. The boxing legend tells TMZ ... she's excited for Syd's…</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:28:13 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>