<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:33:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Colorado Buffaloes’ New Football Jerseys Leaked By CTESPN</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/06/colorado-buffaloes-new-football-jerseys-leaked-by-ctespn/college/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Colorado is set to unveil new football uniforms ahead of the 2024 season, and former NFL wide receiver Antonio Brown gave us a sneak peek at the jersey design over the weekend.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 06:35:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nancy Pelosi Hasn't Spoken to President Biden in Weeks</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/06/nancy-pelosi-joe-biden-not-spoken-weeks-since-dropped-out/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Nancy Pelosi clearly pissed off President Joe Biden ... because they haven't spoken in weeks, and it all goes back to her putting pressure on the Prez to withdraw from the race. The former House speaker stopped by CNN Monday, and Pelosi awkwardly…</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:33:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Premier League Away Kits Dominate Recent Unveilings From Around Europe</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/02/premier-league-away-kits-dominate-recent-unveilings-from-around-europe/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Clubs launching kits include Liverpool, Brighton, Fulham, Bournemouth, Nottingham Forest, Wolves, Le Havre, Stade de Reims, Montepellier, Roma, Parma, RB Leipzig, VFB Stuttgart, Girona</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 21:41:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zac Efron Hit Bottom of Swimming Pool On Dive, Ingested Water Into Lungs</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/05/zac-efron-swimming-pool-dive-hit-bottom-ingest-water-lungs-hospital-ibiza/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Zac Efron's swimming pool incident started when he dove into the water ... the dive was so deep, he hit the bottom of the pool and ingested water into his lungs ... TMZ has learned. Sources close to the situation tell us Zac went for a swim with…</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:33:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Carolina Panthers Add 30th Season Logo To Jerseys</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/02/carolina-panthers-add-30th-season-logo-to-jerseys/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Carolina Panthers will celebrate their 30th season this fall with a commemorative logo, which they quietly unveiled back in May and added to their jerseys ahead of Thursday's Fan Fest at Clemson's Memorial Stadium.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 17:02:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Olympic Swimmer Luana Alonso Says She Was Not Booted From Olympic Village</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/06/olympic-swimmer-luana-alonso-responds-inappropriate-behavior-claims-axed-games/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Paraguayan hottie Luana Alonso is firing back at claims she got kicked out of her Olympic digs for alleged "inappropriate behavior" ... making it damn clear that's not what happened. In an IG Story Monday, she cleared things up in a statement ...…</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:33:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Macon Some Changes: SPHL’s Mayhem Unveil New Suite of Logos</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/01/macon-some-changes-sphls-mayhem-unveil-new-suite-of-logos/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Primary logo once again depicts a Viking, only this time just the head with a red beard and eyebrows and wearing a shiny silver horned helmet</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 23:36:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Serena Williams Gets Answer from Peninsula Hotel In Paris, You Weren't Denied Service</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/06/serena-williams-denied-service-at-peninsulahotel-paris-olympics/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Serena Williams' fight with a fancy Paris hotel is in standoff mode, after the establishment pushed back on claims it denied her service. The Peninsula Paris issued a statement Monday in response to the tennis legend accusing the rooftop restaurant…</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:33:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Olympic Rings: Their Origin, History, and Meaning</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/01/the-olympic-rings-their-origin-history-and-meaning/other/olympics/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Olympic rings are synonymous with the peak of international sports achievement. Those five interlaced circles of equal size, each a different colour, absolutely dominate the sporting landscape around the globe for two straight weeks before vanishing as quickly as they appeared, hiding away until the next games, usually around</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 20:10:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>British Swimmer Adam Peaty Claims Worms Found In Olympic Village Food</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/06/adam-peaty-olympic-village-food-worms-fish/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>***Warning: Finish your Cheerios before reading*** The food in Olympic Village is straight-up crap, according to a British swimmer ... who says the nasuea-inducing grub's so gross, athletes have literally found WORMS in the fish! Adam Peaty -- who…</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:33:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>