<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 11:55:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Detroit Tigers Get Their Motor Runnin’, Unveil City Connect Uniform</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/06/detroit-tigers-get-their-motor-runnin-unveil-city-connect-uniform/baseball/</link><description>The Detroit Tigers today joined the Nike Cool Kids Club™ with the official unveiling of their new City Connect uniform, the 24th of the 30 Major League Baseball teams to release one thus far. As expected, the uniform leans into Detroit’s “Motor City” heritage and its ties to the automobile</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 15:08:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kate Beckinsale Blasts Trolls For Claiming She Had Plastic Surgery</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/05/kate-beckinsale-blast-trolls-claim-she-plastic-surgery-actress-hospital-gala/</link><description>Kate Beckinsale's fed up with trolls claiming she's had work done ... firing back in a lengthy Instagram caption and letting people know their bullying's taken a toll. The actress took to the popular social media site early Sunday morning to…</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 11:55:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Warren Moon Has Issue With Houston Texans’ New Oilers-Inspired Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/04/warren-moon-has-issue-with-houston-texans-new-oilers-inspired-uniforms/football/</link><description>While fans in Houston are happy with the Texans adding "H-Town" blue to their new uniforms, former Oilers quarterback Warren Moon doesn’t feel the same way.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 17:23:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kristi Noem Admits She Never Met Kim Jong Un Despite Book Claim</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/05/kristi-noem-admits-never-met-kim-jong-un-book-claims-dog-cricket-kill/</link><description>Kristi Noem's book's landed her in hot water again ... this time resulting from a factual error claiming she met Kim Jong Un -- even though the meet never happened. The South Dakota Governor went on CBS' "Face The Nation" Sunday morning to talk…</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 11:55:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>West Virginia Mountaineers Reveal Coal Mining-Inspired Alternate Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/03/west-virginia-mountaineers-reveal-coal-mining-inspired-alternate-uniforms/college/</link><description>On Thursday, just days after it unveiled an entirely new uniform set, West Virginia revealed a black alternate design that pays homage to the state's coal mining history.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 02:25:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Teyana Taylor Performs Sexy Cabaret Show, Star-Studded Audience Attends</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/05/teyana-taylor-perform-sexy-sultry-cabaret-show-private-event-met-gala/</link><description>BTW ... sources close to the show tell us the guest list far exceeds Leo wasn't the only celeb in attendance -- with Colman Domingo, Glen Powell, Savannah James, Winnie Harlow, Kyle Kuzma, Joan Smalls, Vittoria Ceretti, Tyrod Taylor, Lena Waithe,…</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 11:55:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MLB, Nike Announces Return of Larger Player Names, Fix to Grey Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/03/mlb-nike-announces-return-of-larger-player-names-fix-to-grey-uniforms/baseball/</link><description>Major League Baseball and Nike today announced they will fix some of the problems with the new uniforms introduced for the 2024 season. The decision follows feedback from players and clubs and months of fan and media complaints, which pointed to several areas needing improvement. Starting in the 2025 season,</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 20:58:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Model Claims Met Gala Fired Him Because He Upstaged Kylie Jenner</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/05/kylie-jenner-italian-model-claim-met-gala-fired-him-upstage-background-photos/</link><description>The Met Gala's allegedly rescinded one person's invitation already ... 'cause a model's claiming he just got fired from his gig there -- after he stole Kylie Jenner's spotlight. Here's the deal ... Eugenio Casnighi -- who says he's a model in his…</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 11:55:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nats, Orioles to Play in MLB’s First-Ever All-City Connect Uniform Game</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/03/nats-orioles-to-play-in-mlbs-first-ever-all-city-connect-uniform-game/baseball/</link><description>For the first time in Major League Baseball history, two teams will wear their Nike MLB City Connect uniforms in the same game. This morning, the Washington Nationals announced they will don their cherry blossom-themed City Connect uniforms when they host the Baltimore Orioles on Tuesday, May 7 for the</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 15:40:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kourtney Kardashian Details Postpartum Struggles at Work</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/05/kourtney-kardashian-emotional-post-not-ready-kardashians-shoot-while-postpartum/</link><description>Kourtney Kardashian's ready to talk about her emotional struggles after her son was born ... revealing she felt weird at work -- even though she had Rocky with her. The reality television star posted to Instagram Saturday, sharing behind-the-scenes…</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 11:55:35 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>