<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 07:21:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Canada’s New Women’s Soccer League Unveils Name, Logo</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/28/canadas-new-womens-soccer-league-unveils-name-logo/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Northern Super League will play its inaugural season in 2025 with teams in Ottawa, Montréal, Vancouver, Calgary, Toronto and Halifax</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 21:39:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kim Kardashian Tells People to Follow Mason Disick, Who's Now on Instagram</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/28/kim-kardashian-tells-fans-follow-mason-disick-instagram-account/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Kim Kardashian is welcoming one important family member back into the spotlight -- pointing the fact that her nephew, Mason Disick, is finally on Instagram ... and sending folks to his page. The SKIMS founder took to her IG Stories Tuesday,…</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 07:21:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Baylor Bears Unveil New Football Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/28/baylor-bears-unveil-new-football-uniforms/college/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Baylor unveiled new football uniforms on Tuesday morning, marking the first overhaul to the Bears' look since the 2019 season.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 20:00:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Molly Ringwald Details Being 'Taken Advantage of' By 'Predators'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/28/molly-ringwald-taken-advantage-predators-hollywood/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Molly Ringwald is opening up about her experiences as a teen star ... sharing her time in Hollywood was more daunting than fans realize, 'cause she says she was preyed upon. The 'Breakfast Club' actress reflected on her early career during the…</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 07:21:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Looking Back at the Dodgers and Giants Move from N.Y. to California</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/28/looking-back-at-the-dodgers-and-giants-move-from-n-y-to-california/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>On May 28, 1957, the National League approved one of the most significant relocations in the history of professional sports: the simultaneous move of the New York Giants and Brooklyn Dodgers to California. The decision marked the beginning of a new era of baseball, bringing the sport’s top talent to</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 19:14:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jason Kelce Claps Back At Social Media Troll, Says Wife Isn't 'Homemaker'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/28/jason-kelce-claps-back-social-media-troll-wife-not-homemaker-harrison-butker-commencement-speech/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Jason Kelce is adamant his wife isn't "a homemaker" ... saying in response to a social media troll this week that he considers Kylie Kelce his partner and his "equal" when it comes to raising their family. Kelce faced off with the heckler on X on…</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 07:21:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Utah NHL Team Logos, Colours, and Possible Uniforms for Year One</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/27/utah-nhl-team-logos-colours-and-possible-uniforms-for-year-one/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Utah’s new National Hockey League team, set to debut for the upcoming 2024-25 NHL season, will reportedly start without a permanent name or logo. However, a look at some of the early merchandise being prepared for the team has revealed what appears to be a temporary design featuring “UTAH” in</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 17:51:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bam Margera Gets Married Again to Fiancée Dannii Marie</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/28/bam-margera-gets-married-again-fiancee-dannii-marie/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>4:57 PM PT -- Bam Margera announced there will be ANOTHER wedding! Just minutes ago he posted a pic of his bride, Dannii, with the caption, "Danielle Marie MARGERA, it’s official. To all family and friends there will be a November wedding in…</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 07:21:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blue Jays to Unveil City Connect Uniform Thursday, Wear it Thrice for “City Week”</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/27/blue-jays-to-unveil-city-connect-uniform-thursday-wear-it-thrice-for-city-week/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Today, the Toronto Blue Jays announced some details surrounding their upcoming Nike MLB City Connect uniform release and the accompanying “City Week” promotion, which will run during their next homestand from May 31 through June 6. Things get underway on Thursday night when the Blue Jays unveil the new look</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 14:54:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Texas Chainsaw' Star Bill Moseley Struck by Cyclist in Hit-and-Run, Hospitalized</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/28/texas-chainsaw-massacre-actor-bill-moseley-hit-bicyclist-hospitalized/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Bill Moseley -- known for 'The Texas Chainsaw Massacre' franchise -- got an unwelcome scare of his own last week after being slammed into by a cyclist ... who apparently took off. The actor's rep tells TMZ ... it all went down in Raleigh, NC Friday…</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 07:21:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>