<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from multiple RSS sources, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 07:11:22 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>How “Switching Costs” Hold the Housing Market in Limbo w/Lance Lambert</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-215</link><description>The housing market has seen unprecedented home price growth in the 2020s. Already, we’ve almost beat the past three decades, and we aren’t even halfway through our own. And now, […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 07:02:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>India weighs delaying caps on UPI market share in win for PhonePe, Google Pay</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/09/india-weighs-delaying-caps-on-upi-market-share-in-win-for-phonepe-google-pay/</link><description>India’s mobile payments regulator is likely to extend the deadline for imposing market share caps on the popular UPI payments rail by one to two years, sources familiar with the matter told TechCrunch. The National Payments Corporation of India (NPCI), a special unit of the Reserve Bank of India, plans to extend the deadline for […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:18:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Marshall Project Wins the Dart Award for “The Mercy Workers”</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/06/the-marshall-project-wins-the-dart-award-for-the-mercy-workers</link><description>Our feature on mitigation specialists who help save people from the death penalty was recognized for making “significant contributions to public understanding of trauma-related issues.”</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Taking Racism out of the Kidney Disease Equation</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/a-to-z-guides/features/end-of-racist-kidney-math?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Kidney care in the U.S. is at a watershed moment of moving past a deeply entrenched, institutionally racist equation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 04:17:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best Appliances to Boost Your Rental Property’s Value—and Bonus Tips For Saving Money</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/best-appliances-to-raise-property-value</link><description>Rental properties come in all shapes, sizes, and prices, as do many of the appliances that go in them. Assuming, however, that your rental is not a sprawling Beverly Hills […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:55:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Thai food delivery app Line Man Wongnai weighs IPO in Thailand, US in 2025</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/08/thai-food-delivery-app-line-man-wongnai-weighs-ipo-in-thailand-us-in-2025/</link><description>Line Man Wongnai, an on-demand food delivery service in Thailand, is considering an initial public offering on a Thai exchange or the U.S. in 2025.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Weinstein Ruling Poses Quandary: Can #MeToo Coexist With Protections for Defendants?</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/04/sex-crimes-weinstein-me-too</link><description>Proving sex crimes often requires evidence that is generally excluded to protect the rights of the accused.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Plant-Powered Sleep: Vegan, Vegetarian Diets Unlock Extra ZZZs</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/sleep-disorders/news/20240508/plant-powered-sleep-vegan-vegetarian-diet-unlocks-extra-zzzs?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Vegans and vegetarians sleep around 30 more minutes per night than average and up to 90% of them report good or excellent sleep quality, according to a new survey published by the Sleep Foundation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 19:12:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Before You Buy: 3 Key Strategies for Investing in Turnkey Properties</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/three-tips-for-turnkey-property-analysis</link><description>Turnkey investing is one of the more controversial forms of investing in real estate. Depending on who you ask, you may hear that turnkey is one of the best forms of […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:50:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple’s ‘Crush’ ad is disgusting</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/08/apples-crush-ad-is-disgusting/</link><description>The problem is not the media, but the message.
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 22:15:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mississippi Lawmakers Considered Modest Public Defense Reforms. They Rejected All of Them.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/02/mississippi-public-defense-legislative-reforms</link><description>With its refusal to impose oversight or consistent standards in local defense, Mississippi risks falling further behind rest of the U.S., critics say.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anorexia: The Body Neglected</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/mental-health/eating-disorders/anorexia-nervosa/features/anorexia-body-neglected?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>What, exactly, does anorexia nervosa do inside the human body? The heart and bones suffer the most.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump May Consider Shaking Up the Federal Reserve If Elected—Here’s What That Could Look Like</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/trump-allies-draft-federal-reserve-changes-that-could-replace-powell</link><description>A group of former officials and other allies of Former President Donald Trump has drafted a document outlining suggested policy changes that would impact the authority and independence of the Federal Reserve. While […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:28:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OpenAI offers a peek behind the curtain of its AI’s secret instructions</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/08/openai-offers-a-peek-behind-the-curtain-of-its-ais-secret-instructions/</link><description>Ever wonder why conversational AI like ChatGPT says “Sorry, I can’t do that” or some other polite refusal? OpenAI is offering a limited look at the reasoning behind its own models’ rules of engagement, whether it’s sticking to brand guidelines or declining to make NSFW content. Large language models (LLMs) don’t have any naturally occurring […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 20:52:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In This Police Youth Program, a Trail of Sexual Abuse Across the U.S.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/01/police-explorer-sexual-abuse-boy-scouts</link><description>Explorer posts, overseen by the Boy Scouts, are supposed to foster an interest in policing. They have faced nearly 200 allegations of misconduct.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 18:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Postpartum PTSD: Right Diagnosis Can Help Mothers and Babies</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/mental-health/news/20240506/postpartum-ptsd-right-diagnosis-can-help-mothers-and-babies?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Many new mothers aren’t aware that postpartum PTSD even exists, but it’s far from rare. Here's what to know.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:19:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Avoid My Mistakes: Single-Family Renovation Lessons I Learned the Hard Way</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/single-family-renovation-lessons-i-learned-the-hard-way</link><description>I want to share a few tips and lessons (some are costly) so you don’t repeat my mistakes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>US Patent and Trademark Office confirms another leak of filers’ address data</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/08/us-patent-and-trademark-office-confirms-another-leak-of-filers-address-data/</link><description>The federal government agency responsible for granting patents and trademarks is alerting thousands of filers whose private addresses were exposed following a second data spill in as many years. The U.S. Patent and Trademark Office (USPTO) said in an email to affected trademark applicants this week that their private domicile address — which can include […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 20:44:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Campus Protests Could Shape the 2024 Elections — And Not Just the Presidency</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/30/campus-protests-gaza-arrests-prosecutors-elections</link><description>With hundreds of arrests and more campus standoffs looming, local law enforcement officials could face consequences at the ballot box.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 21:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Living With Major Depressive Disorder</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/depression/features/live-with-mdd?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>See how one person manages the ups and downs of major depressive disorder -- and how her depression inspired her career as a therapist.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 17:45:12 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>