<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 07:15:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Would You Vote for Any of These Market-Changing Economic Policies?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-251</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>No matter who wins your vote during the presidential debates, odds are, the housing market will still have its problems. We’ve got high building costs, low inventory, and slow bureaucratic […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 10:00:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Google’s GenAI facing privacy risk assessment scrutiny in Europe</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/12/googles-genai-facing-privacy-risk-assessment-scrutiny-in-europe/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Google’s lead privacy regulator in the European Union has opened an investigation into whether or not it has complied with the bloc’s data protection laws in relation to use of people’s information for training generative AI. Specifically it’s looking into whether the tech giant needed to carry out a data protection impact assessment (DPIA) in […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 10:19:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Not ‘Mini-Adult Court’: Lawyers Lacking Qualifications Defended 1,200 Cuyahoga County Kids</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/09/12/cuyahoga-juvenile-courts-appointed-public-defender</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Juvenile Court judges will now track qualifications, but insist the state system creates barriers keeping experienced attorneys from defending kids.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Eviction Diversion Programs Are Driving Rates (and Costs) Down</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/how-eviction-diversion-programs-are-driving-eviction-rates-down</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>If there’s a downside to investing in real estate, it’s dealing with nonpaying tenants. Many people prefer to put their money in the stock market because even with diligent screening, […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 22:04:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Consumer group sues to ban purchases inside games like Fortnite and Minecraft in Europe</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/12/bad-credits-consumer-group-files-eu-suit-over-manipulative-payments-in-games-like-fortnite-and-minecraft-calls-for-a-ban/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Video games are some of the most lucrative apps in the world, in part because of how they lure people into spending money on credits to buy digital goodies, to the tune of more than $50 billion annually worldwide. But a powerful consumer group in Europe believes games publishers are “purposefully tricking consumers,” especially children, […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 09:46:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>She Ate a Poppy Seed Salad Just Before Giving Birth. Then They Took Her Baby Away.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/09/09/drug-test-pregnancy-pennsylvania-california</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Hospitals use drug tests that return false positives from poppy seed bagels, decongestants and Zantac. Yet newborns are being taken from parents based on the results.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A 40-Year Mortgage Won’t Be as Bad for Homebuyers as I Originally Thought</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/40-year-mortgages-wont-be-as-bad-for-homeowners-as-i-originally-thought</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>A 40-year mortgage offers pros and cons for buyers, depending on their goals.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 20:45:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WhatsApp brings Meta Verified, customized messages to small businesses in India</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/12/whatsapp-brings-meta-verified-customized-messages-to-small-businesses-in-india/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>WhatsApp is now letting small businesses in India sign up for a Meta Verified badge and giving them the ability to send customized messages to customers. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 08:44:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Seemingly Endless Cycle of Reforms in Juvenile Justice</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/09/07/the-seemingly-endless-cycle-of-reforms-in-juvenile-justice</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>As Ohio considers closing youth detention facilities, recent efforts in other states have hit roadblocks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Team-Building Lessons: 5 Pitfalls I Encountered and How to Avoid Them</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/team-building-lessons</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>Learn how to avoid common team-building pitfalls with tips on improving communication, documenting processes, fostering leadership, and inspiring collaboration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Drama at OpenWeb, as a new CEO is announced – and the founding CEO says he’s staying</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/11/drama-at-openweb-as-a-new-ceo-is-announced-and-the-founding-ceo-says-hes-staying/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>OpenWeb, a New York startup whose tools help publishers engage users, has a unique problem. Its co-founding CEO reportedly won’t leave, even though it announced a new CEO. According to CTech, on Tuesday, OpenWeb’s chairman, Tim Harvey, sent an email to employees, saying he’s becoming CEO and thanking longtime CEO Nadav Shoval for his “incredible […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 05:32:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>You’re About to Deliver Your Baby. This Faulty Drug Test Could Take Your Newborn Away.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/09/07/drug-test-hospital-pregnancy</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Listen to our investigation into how hospitals use unreliable test results to report parents to child welfare agencies.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 08:01:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scaling to 10 Rentals in 2 Years &amp; $6K/Month Cash Flow with Low Money Down</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-456</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>What’s stopping you from investing in real estate? Money? What if there was a profitable rental you could buy with just $500 down? Well, today’s guest has found the perfect […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 10:00:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adam Neumann’s crypto comeback company is reportedly refunding investors</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/11/adam-neumanns-crypto-comeback-company-is-reportedly-refunding-investors/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>In a development that will surprise few, former WeWork CEO Adam Neumann’s climate/crypto/carbon-credit startup Flowcarbon appears to be in the process of curling up to die, Forbes reported today. Buyers of the outfit’s “Goddess Nature Token,” pitched as the first step in putting carbon credits on the blockchain, have reportedly been contacted about receiving refunds […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Serious Case of Prison Visit Blues</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/09/06/tariq-maqbool-prison-visit-pandemic-covid-19</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Tariq MaQbool reflects on disruptive COVID-era visitation restrictions that remain in effect at New Jersey State Prison.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>