<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 07:26:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Scenario Planning, Foresight, and the Power of Imagination: Navigating an Uncertain Future</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/08/05/scenario-planning-foresight-and-the-power-of-imagination-navigating-an-uncertain-future/</link><description>By fostering resilience through the consideration of various outcomes, investment practitioners can better anticipate and manage the complexities and disruptions that characterize today's dynamic environment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 17:28:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bosses are losing the ‘return-to-office’ war as the WFH pyjama army forces them to go hybrid</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/08/07/data-bosses-return-to-office-mandatestheyre-downsizing-instead/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/GettyImages-691574605-e1723026865666.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Despite all the noise around bosses ditching remote working for good, the world's largest hybrid workspace provider just reported record revenue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:19:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Private Equity: In Essence, Plunder?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/08/02/private-equity-in-essence-plunder/</link><description>To understand what private equity is at its worst is a call to action, personally and professionally.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 16:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DBS’s next CEO will be Tan Su Shan, the first woman to lead Southeast Asia’s largest bank</title><link>https://fortune.com/asia/2024/08/07/dbs-next-ceo-tan-su-shan-first-woman-lead-southeast-asia-largest-bank/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/53906974501_448d78f4b8_o-e1723027155367.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Tan Su Shan will become the first woman CEO in DBS' history when she assumes the top job come March 2025.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:16:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Small Caps, Large Caps, and Interest Rates</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/08/01/small-caps-large-caps-and-interest-rates/</link><description>The relationship between stocks and interest rates is not reliably stable. There are periods when equities are highly rate sensitive, and periods when they aren't.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 12:39:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elon Musk’s backing of Donald Trump is hurting Tesla’s struggling EV business in Europe</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/08/07/elon-musk-support-donald-trump-hurting-tesla-ev-business-europe-rossmann/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/GettyImages-2162688843_ab398f-e1723028149304.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>German drugstore chain Rossmann said that Elon Musk's support for Donald Trump, the Republican candidate who calls climate change a hoax, goes against Tesla's mission—and it wants out.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:15:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Well Does the Market Predict Volatility?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/31/how-well-does-the-market-predict-volatility/</link><description>How accurate is VIX on a realized basis and when does it diverge with the market?</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 13:22:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Exploding Mercedes-Benz EV prompts parking garage electric vehicle bans in South Korea</title><link>https://fortune.com/asia/2024/08/07/exploding-mercedes-benz-ev-parking-garage-bans-south-korea/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/GettyImages-2163004125.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>More than 700 residents were evacuated due to water and power outages and the blaze damaged some 140 cars.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:12:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Do Experts Really Know? Embracing the Unknown</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/29/what-do-experts-really-know-embracing-the-unknown/</link><description>Confidence is a necessary but insufficient factor in long-term investing success. Raising the metaknowledge quotient of the investment team can help protect against the surprises that lurk in left-tail events and remain unknown, until they’re known.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 16:08:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cathay Pacific is buying up to 60 Airbus jets in $11 billion deal as travel approaches pre-COVID numbers</title><link>https://fortune.com/asia/2024/08/07/cathay-pacific-buying-60-airbus-jets-11-billion-travel-pre-covid-numbers/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/GettyImages-2165152336-e1723025863617.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Cathay announced that its passenger count had reached 80 percent of its pre-pandemic levels and it hoped to hit 100 percent in early 2025.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 11:20:09 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>