<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 02:22:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Premier League’s Everton FC Leaves Hummel, Signs Kit ‘Landmark’ Deal With Castore</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/14/premier-leagues-everton-fc-leaves-hummel-signs-kit-landmark-deal-with-castore/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>British sportswear brand also becomes first founding partner of Everton's new stadium, slated to open in time for the 2024-25 Premier League season</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:56:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kate Middleton Offers Cancer Treatment Update, Attending Trooping of Colour</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/14/kate-middleton-cancer-treatement-update-confirms-attending-trooping-of-colour/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Kate Middleton just came out and confirmed TMZ's reporting -- namely, that her cancer treatments are going well ... and more importantly, that she'll be out in public tomorrow. The Princess of Wales just posted a lengthy statement, in which she…</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 02:22:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bowling Green Falcons Unveil New Throwback-Inspired Football Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/14/bowling-green-falcons-unveil-new-throwback-inspired-football-uniforms/college/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Bowling Green recently unveiled mockups of three new uniforms for this season that are reminiscent of the Falcons' look during the 1980s and 1990s.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 19:17:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jonathan Majors' Girlfriend Meagan Good in New Movie About Domestic Abuse</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/14/jonathan-majors-girlfriend-meagan-good-new-movie-domestic-abuse-assault-trial/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Meagan Good is starring in a new movie about domestic violence -- and it's a little awkward considering what her boyfriend Jonathan Majors just went through in real life. The actress is the lead actress in Tyler Perry's latest drama, "Divorce in…</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 02:22:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Utah Hockey Club Unveils Logos, Uniforms, Colours, and Name for 2024-25</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/13/utah-hockey-club-unveils-logos-uniforms-colours-and-name-for-2024-25/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>It’s officially official: Utah has an NHL team… and a name, logo, colours, and uniform (even if those last four are just temporary). Today, the National Hockey League made it official by announcing the Utah Hockey Club would join the league in time for the 2024-25 season, absorbing the roster,</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 01:30:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elderly Woman Knocked Out In Road Rage Fight at LAX</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/14/lax-road-rage-fight-video-elderly-woman-knocked-out/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>A violent road rage fight at LAX caused some serious collateral damage ... in the form of an elderly woman getting knocked out cold ... and it's all on video. Brutal footage shows the moment from late last month -- when an old lady minding her…</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 02:22:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rising Tides: Halifax NSL Club Unveils Name, Crest</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/13/rising-tides-halifax-nsl-club-unveils-name-crest/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Nova Scotia-based club is third of Northern Super League's six teams for inaugural season in 2025 to unveil their visual identity system</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 00:28:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Deadliest Catch' Star Nick Mavar Dead at 59 After Medical Emergency</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/14/deadliest-catch-star-nick-mavar-dead-dies-medical-emergency/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Nick Mavar -- who was once a deckhand on the F/V Northwestern on "Deadliest Catch" -- has died ... TMZ has learned. The Police Chief of Bristol Bay Borough Police Department in Alaska tells TMZ ... the ex-Discovery Channel star died Thursday…</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 02:22:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MLB Releases Fourth of July Caps for 2024</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/13/mlb-releases-fourth-of-july-caps-for-2024/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Major League Baseball and New Era have unveiled the stars-and-stripes-themed caps that players, managers, coaches, and umpires will wear on-field for Independence Day in the United States on Thursday, July 4, 2024. This year, all 30 clubs will wear a cream-coloured crown, with teams again having the option of a</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 20:03:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Darren Criss Trolled After Revealing Newborn Son's Name is Brother</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/14/darren-criss-trolled-newborn-son-named-brother/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Darren Criss really stepped in it as he ventures into fatherhood -- at least that's what the internet is saying after learning what he named his baby ... who's most definitely a Bro. The "Glee" star is being low-key roasted on social media for the…</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 02:22:28 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>