<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 15:16:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Ranking the Possible 2024 Stanley Cup Final Uniform Matchups</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/21/ranking-the-possible-2024-stanley-cup-final-uniform-matchups/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The 2024 Stanley Cup Playoffs are winding down, and with that comes a good sense of who will face off in this year’s Stanley Cup Final. At the moment, we’re left with just the Dallas Stars and Edmonton Oilers in the Western Conference and the Florida Panthers and New York</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 19:27:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TMZ TV Hot Takes: Taylor Swift, Ben Affleck &amp; J.Lo, Tom Brady &amp; Jay-Z</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/21/tmz-tv-hot-takes-taylor-swift-ben-affleck-j-lo-tom-brady-jay-z/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>It's a new week, so you know what that means ... a new set of TMZ TV hot takes to unpack. First up, on "TMZ Live," Harvey and Charles discuss Taylor Swift's concert in Stockholm, Sweden ... where she sported a very interesting accessory -- a love…</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 15:16:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aston Villa, Adidas Announce Kit Deal Starting in 2024-25 Season</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/21/aston-villa-adidas-announce-kit-deal-starting-in-2024-25-season/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Deal marks first time Aston Villa has been outfitted by German sportswear giant; announcement confirms new crest that matches January leaks</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 15:51:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ricky Stenhouse Jr., Kyle Busch Get Celebrity Boxing Offer To Hash Out Beef In Ring</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/21/ricky-stenhouse-jr-kyle-busch-celebrity-boxing-offer-hash-out-beef/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>If Ricky Stenhouse Jr. and Kyle Busch wanna take their beef from garages and pit roads to an actual squared circle ... TMZ Sports has learned Celebrity Boxing is more than willing to put on the bout for them. Damon Feldman -- the honcho of the…</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 15:16:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>St Louis Cardinals Unveil New “The Lou” City Connect Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/20/st-louis-cardinals-unveil-new-the-lou-city-connect-uniforms/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>They’re from “The Lou,” and they’re proud. This morning, the St. Louis Cardinals became the 26th team to unveil their new Nike MLB City Connect uniform, doing so with the help of Grammy Award-winning hip-hop artist Nelly, a St. Louis native. It’s the first time in franchise history that the</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 13:59:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Four Seasons Orlando Reacts to Viral Baby TikTok, Open to Collaborating</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/21/four-seasons-orlando-reacts-viral-baby-tiktok-collab/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>A baby who's gone viral for precociously expressing her excitement for the Four Seasons ... just might have a future in the travel biz, because the luxury hotel's pumped about the shout out. The manager for the Four Seasons Orlando tells TMZ ……</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 15:16:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chicago Bears Add George S. Halas’ Initials To 1936 Throwback Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/18/chicago-bears-add-george-s-halas-initials-to-1936-throwback-uniforms/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Chicago Bears have subtly added the initials of late founder, owner and coach George S. Halas to the left sleeve of their 1936 throwback uniforms, matching their navy blue home, white road and orange alternate jerseys.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 22:34:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jennifer Lopez Goes Solo to Film Premiere Amid Breakup Rumors</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/21/jennifer-lopez-movie-premiere-solo-ben-affleck-film-set-breakup-split-rumors/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Jennifer Lopez went all by herself to her film premiere in L.A. Monday night – one day after she was seen smiling on a drive with her husband Ben Affleck, creating even more confusion about their relationship status. J Lo hit the red carpet for…</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 15:16:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fanatics and NFLPA Reveal 2024 NFL Rookie Jerseys</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/18/fanatics-and-nflpa-reveal-2024-nfl-rookie-jerseys/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Last night, Fanatics and the NFLPA held a special “Jersey Reveal” event in Los Angeles to unveil the official game jerseys for 39 NFL rookies during the NFLPA Rookie Premiere. Several high-profile 2024 NFL Draft picks and rookies attended the event, including Caleb Williams and Rome Odunze of the Chicago</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 17:58:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Law Enforcement Investigating Matthew Perry Death, Source of Ketamine</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/21/cops-investigating-matthew-perry-death-origins-ketamine/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Matthew Perry's death has, publicly, been considered an open and shut case -- but, as far as the authorities go, they're still digging into how he got one particular drug ... TMZ has learned. Law enforcement sources tell us there is an ongoing…</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 15:16:56 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>