<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 06:58:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Stocks for the Long Run? Setting the Record Straight</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/30/stocks-for-the-long-run-setting-the-record-straight/</link><description>Stocks are a good investment long-term, providing that you dial in your expectations. New historical findings provide a richer, more complete understanding of international returns.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 16:55:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Renault links up with Chinese partner to build $22,000 EV after VW broadside</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/31/renault-china-ev-partner-volkswagen/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1715552858-e1717152185979.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Renault CEO Luca de Meo was critical of Volkswagen after talks over a joint affordable EV imploded.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 11:52:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rethinking Retirement Planning Amidst Aging Demographic Frontiers</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/28/rethinking-retirement-planning-amidst-aging-demographic-frontiers/</link><description>Forward-thinking approaches to policy and wealth management are needed to ensure a better financial future across generations and income brackets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 20:32:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lab-grown meat isn’t on grocery store shelves yet, but Florida and Arizona have already banned it</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/31/lab-grown-meat-ban-alabama-iowa-florida/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/AP24150634014062-e1717081977201.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Some cultivated meat companies say they’re considering legal action, and some states—like Tennessee—shelved proposed bans after lawmakers argued they would restrict consumers’ choices.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 11:35:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: The New World Economy in 5 Trends</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/24/book-review-the-new-world-economy-in-5-trends/</link><description>A diligent economist and an eclectic bookworm serve up an analysis of megatrends that will have the greatest impact on economies and investments: innovation, productivity, climate, multiglobalization, debt, and aging.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 12:22:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Women’s health has been ignored for most of history. Here’s why that’s changing—and why it’s time to double down</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/31/womens-health-ignored-changing-venture-capital-startups-unicorns-maven-clinic/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/IMG_1172-1-e1717108336933.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Women’s health could be poised to enter an era of equity—but only if founders, funders, and public partners continue to support innovation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Factor Strategies Belong in Your Completion Portfolio Toolkit</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/23/factor-strategies-belong-in-your-completion-portfolio-toolkit/</link><description>Why wouldn't you include factor strategies in your completion portfolio? A review of the two commonly used approaches for managing institutional assets highlights their symbiotic nature.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 19:09:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mark Zuckerberg’s request to be dropped from a Meta lawsuit is granted by New Mexico judge</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/31/mark-zuckerbergs-meta-child-safety-lawsuit-new-mexico/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2036333677-e1717150196366.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The case is one of many filed by states, school districts and parents against Meta and its platforms over concerns about child exploitation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 11:13:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>For the Analyst: Peer Benchmarking Methods to Improve Earnings Forecasts</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/21/for-the-analyst-peer-benchmarking-methods-to-improve-earnings-forecasts/</link><description>Peer benchmarking is a vexing task for financial analysts but one that is critical for forecasting earnings. This straightforward measure can help find peers for relative performance, compensation, and valuation benchmarking.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 12:47:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amazon gets FAA approval to expand Prime Air drone deliveries for online orders</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/31/amazon-faa-approval-expand-prime-air-drone-deliveries-online-orders/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/AP24134500545938-e1717148730104.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Amazon said that the FAA has given its Prime Air delivery service the OK to operate drones “beyond visual line of sight,” removing a barrier that has prevented its drones from traveling longer distances.</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 10:55:25 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>