<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 02:37:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Book Review: Shocks, Crises, and False Alarms</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/19/book-review-shocks-crises-and-false-alarms/</link><description>Carlsson-Szlezak and Swartz attempt to add fresh thinking on framing macro shocks that may often prove to be false alarms. Any general reader will obtain some key fresh insights with this work, and CFA charterholders will be offered an alternative to the conventional Wall Street approach to macro discussions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 13:06:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Four travel gems in France: A guide through lavender fields, sleepy ski villages, and the region’s ‘Hamptons’</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/07/20/four-travel-gems-in-france-bordeaux-alps-chateau/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/GettyImages-1397067169-e1721381630106.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The following four regions are no secret; the French, and some smart Brits, have long understood their appeal.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Preserving the Dollar: The Role of CBDCs in Securing Economic Stability for Future Generations</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/16/preserving-the-dollar-the-role-of-cbdcs-in-securing-economic-stability-for-future-generations/</link><description>As financial systems evolve, preserving the US dollar's dominance will require skillful policy management and the integration of cutting-edge technologies.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:24:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Affordable travel is to blame for Europe’s overtourism problem, spoiling its most sought-after cities like Barcelona, Amsterdam and Athens</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/07/20/affordable-travel-europe-overtourism-social-environment-cities-barcelona-amsterdam-athens-airports-tiktok-trends/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/GettyImages-2161473448-e1721383556774.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Mass tourism isn't a new phenomenon, but it’s reached a tipping point in Europe where locals are increasingly bearing the brunt of it.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Can Equal Weight Solve Our Concentration Crisis? Not So Fast…</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/15/can-equal-weight-solve-our-concentration-crisis-not-so-fast/</link><description>Mega-cap concentration has exploded since 2015. The corollary to an increasingly top-heavy benchmark is that market diversification and breadth have never been more limited. A multifactor methodology can be a restorative balance to US equities when more traditional measures fall short.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 22:43:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CEO at cybersecurity firm that caused a global outage forgot to apologize</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/07/19/ceo-at-cybersecurity-firm-that-caused-a-global-outage-forgot-to-apologize/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/GettyImages-1177538342-e1721436967942.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The lack of contrition likely stems from the IT sector’s longstanding struggle to relate in a more personalized and less robotic way with the general public.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 02:00:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In Search of the Elusive Neutral Interest Rate</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/10/in-search-of-the-elusive-neutral-interest-rate/</link><description>With Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell's semiannual address to the Senate Banking Committee this week fresh in mind, it is an ideal time to consider the drivers of r*.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 12:17:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Billionaire’s son resolves feud over inheritance</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/07/19/billionaires-son-resolves-feud-over-inheritance/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/GettyImages-1214624883-e1721436474926.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Alberto Safra claimed his father, who suffered from Parkinson’s disease, lacked the mental capacity to execute the three new wills that disinherited him</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 01:48:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Commodities for the Long Run?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/08/commodities-for-the-long-run/</link><description>Asset classes such as commodities have historically had notable diversification benefits for longer-term investors who are concerned with inflation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 21:50:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple and Walmart banking partner Green Dot fined $44 million by the Federal Reserve</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/07/19/apple-and-walmart-banking-partner-green-dot-fined-44-million-by-the-federal-reserve/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/GettyImages-2158705289.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Green Dot Bank, the banking-as-a-Service partner to some of America’s biggest companies agreed to pay the fine for policies they say they fixed years ago.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 00:45:59 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>