<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 13:32:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Crystal Palace, Valencia Headline Recent Kit Launches From Around Europe</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/21/crystal-palace-valencia-headline-recent-kit-launches-from-around-europe/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Other clubs releasing 2024-25 kits recently include: Getafe CF, Borussia Mönchengladbach, Stade Rennais, RC Lens, FC Nantes, SL Benfica, FC Porto</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 15:16:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Carol Burnett Honored in Star-Studded Hollywood Handprint Ceremony</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/20/carol-burnett-honor-hollywood-handprint-ceremony-dick-van-dyke/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Carol Burnett's a living legend who's going to live on forever ... 'cause she got the cement treatment at TCL Chinese Theater while some of Hollywood's biggest stars looked on. The actress-comedian dipped her hands and feet into wet cement outside…</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 13:32:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Washington Wizards Unveil 2024-25 Statement Edition Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/21/washington-wizards-unveil-2024-25-statement-edition-uniforms/basketball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Washington Wizards unveiled their 2024-25 Statement Edition uniforms early Friday morning, replacing the set they've worn since the 2019-20 season.</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 14:55:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Guess Who This Curly Cutie Turned Into!</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/21/guess-who-this-curly-cutie-turned-into/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Before this sweetie pie in her fancy schmancy headband turned into a talented pop superstar, she was just a kiddo growing up in Edison, New Jersey with her two younger bros and playing the violin, viola, cello and guitar! Growing up, she looked up…</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 13:32:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>San Fransico Giants Add #24 Memorial Patch for Willie Mays</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/20/san-fransico-giants-add-24-memorial-patch-for-willie-mays/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The San Francisco Giants have added a memorial patch to the front of their uniform’s jersey in honour of the great Willie Mays. The patch shows Mays’ legendary number 24 in orange on a black circle, his name “MAYS” arched above in orange. There’s an additional orange outline around the</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 22:25:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TMZ TV Hot Takes: Dana White on Cancel Culture, Bianca Censori, Jon Jones</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/21/tmz-tv-hot-takes-dana-white-bianca-censori-jon-jones/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Dana White compared cancel culture to coming out, Bianca Censori bounced around in another risque outfit and Jon "Bones" Jones cracked a joke about his cocaine usage ... all this and more on TMZ's hot takes. On "TMZ Live," Harvey and Charles…</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 13:32:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Los Angeles Kings Unveil New Logos, Modernized Take on ’90s Classic</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/20/los-angeles-kings-unveil-new-logos-modernized-take-on-90s-classic/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Los Angeles Kings are goin’ back to the ’90s, kids! This morning, the Kings unveiled their new, old logo via their social media channels, one day after posting a teaser graphic simply showing the outline of the logo. It’s a throwback, mostly, to what the club wore from 1988</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 17:13:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Al Horford Guarantees Return To Celtics, I Want Another Title!</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/21/al-horford-guarantees-return-celtics-wants-another-title/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>It took Al Horford 17 years to win his first NBA title ... but he's hoping he can double his ring collection next season -- telling TMZ Sports he's 100% NOT retiring and is returning to the Boston Celtics. We spoke with the longtime vet fresh off…</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 13:32:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Here’s A Visual Guide to the Colors on the Euro 2024 Logo</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/20/heres-a-visual-guide-to-the-colors-on-the-euro-2024-logo/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>If you've been watching Euro 2024 this summer, you may have noticed the dizzying number of colors in the tournament logo and television graphics. But those colors are there and arranged the way there for a good reason.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 16:50:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RFK Jr. Campaign Paid Russell Brand's Production Co. $68K for Appearance</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/21/rfk-jr-campaign-paid-russell-brand-production-company-68k-appearance/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Russell Brand's production company got paid a nice chunk of change for performing at a Robert F. Kennedy Jr. event earlier this year ... and we're talking tens of thousands. TMZ pulled Team Kennedy's FEC filings ... and it shows the campaign…</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 13:32:59 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>