<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 17:28:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Coiled Tight: Smaller Companies Are Primed for Outperformance</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/08/coiled-tight-smaller-companies-are-primed-for-outperformance/</link><description>Small-cap companies are poised for a rebound. The sector is best approached through an active investment strategy where expertise and a deep understanding of the individual businesses and their risk-and-reward characteristics are necessary for success.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:40:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How a NASM certification can kickstart your personal training career</title><link>https://fortune.com/education/articles/nasm-certification/</link><description>As the need for fitness trainers and instructors grows, a NASM certification can be your entry point into a dynamic and in-demand field.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:58:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Investment Returns Are NOT Random</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/07/investment-returns-are-not-random/</link><description>Are investment returns random across time as Burton Malkiel suggests in his book, A Random Walk Down Wall Street? There is notable disagreement on this topic. This research finds that practitioners may need to rethink their portfolio optimization routines.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:22:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A 35-year-old junior Bank of America associate suddenly died—and it’s ignited discussions about Wall Street’s intense working conditions</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/08/leo-lukenas-iii-bank-of-america-junior-investment-banker-death-wall-street-working-conditions/</link><description>Leo Lukenas III, a former Green Beret, joined Bank of America as an investment banker last summer. He died on May 2.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:50:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Generational Wealth: Does the Apple Fall Far From the Tree?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/06/generational-wealth-does-the-apple-fall-far-from-the-tree/</link><description>There is strong evidence that most “rich families” will be poorer after several generations. Some of the reasons for this are systemic like taxes. But most factors that diminish a family’s wealth over generations are the choices that heirs make.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 12:37:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CEO Dara Khosrowshahi wants more workers to return to the office—preferably in an Uber</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/08/uber-ceo-dara-khosrowshahi-wants-more-workers-to-return-to-the-office/</link><description>After a full year of profitability, Uber reported a first quarter loss and its CEO blames a lack of commuters post-pandemic.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:43:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>State Capitalism in Private Markets: Mission Creep</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/03/state-capitalism-in-private-markets-mission-creep/</link><description>Governments relish mingling in markets. Yet, if past policies are any guide, taxpayers are being shortchanged.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 12:30:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Panera is ditching its Charged Lemonade after 2 customers died—but Gen Z is still thirsting for dangerous snacks and drinks</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/08/panera-charged-lemonade-end-discontinued-gen-z-one-chip-challenge-celsius-prime/</link><description>A 30-ounce Charged Lemonade reportedly contained 390 milligrams of caffeine, the equivalent of about five Red Bulls.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:35:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Implementation Shortfalls Hamstring Factor Strategies</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/01/implementation-shortfalls-hamstring-factor-strategies/</link><description>Smart rebalancing rules help portfolio managers capture more of the return that is inherent in their factor strategies. Concentrating on “priority best” trading improves factor portfolio performance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 11:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The UK’s second-richest man is demanding Manchester United workers return to the office—’If you don’t like it, please seek alternative employment’</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/08/jim-ratcliffe-manchester-united-return-to-office/</link><description>Even if workers prefer flexibility, executives are getting impatient.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 21:05:24 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>