<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 01:49:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>High Interest Rates Are Forcing Big-Time Investors to Cut Their Losses—Is a Bust Coming?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/high-interest-rates-are-forcing-big-time-investors-to-sell</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>The sudden increase in interest rates has left many experienced commercial real estate owners gasping for air. It’s a tsunami of woe for landlords who own office and retail space and never […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 17:29:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The ups and downs of investing in Europe, with VCs Saul Klein and Raluca Ragab</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/25/the-ups-and-downs-of-investing-in-europe-with-vcs-saul-klein-and-raluca-ragab/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>When it comes to the world of venture-backed startups, some issues are universal, and some are very dependent on where the startups and its backers are located. It’s something we talked about this week in London, when TechCrunch took its StrictlyVC series of more intimate, more investor-focused events on the road. Sitting down with Saul […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:20:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Legal Doctrine That Shields Police From Many Lawsuits May Be Losing Support</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/25/police-mississippi-courts-judges-qualified-immunity</link><description>A federal judge in Mississippi joined other courts in recently rejecting police arguments that qualified immunity protected their actions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Federal Experts Talk Bird Flu ‘What Ifs’ in WebMD Live Event</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/cold-and-flu/news/20240516/federal-experts-talk-bird-flu-what-ifs?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>WebMD brought together experts from four federal agencies to talk prevention, monitoring, and what the “what ifs” of bird flu might look like.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:50:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Brian Took the Easy Way Out—Here’s Why He Made a Big Mistake and Why I’m Never Selling My Properties</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/brian-took-the-easy-way-out-why-im-never-selling-my-properties</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>A very “good” problem many investors have is whether they should sell or rent their primary residence when it comes time to move out. I have been blessed with this problem […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 17:05:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scarlett Johansson brought receipts to the OpenAI controversy</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/25/scarlett-johansson-brought-receipts-to-the-openai-controversy/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Welcome back to TechCrunch’s Week in Review — TechCrunch’s newsletter recapping the week’s biggest news. Want it in your inbox every Saturday? Sign up here. OpenAI announced this week that it’s removing Sky, one of the voices used by its new GPT-4o model, after users found it sounded eerily similar to Scarlett Johansson’s AI character […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 21:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Out of the Blue: The Rise and Fall of a Black Cop</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/23/black-police-officers-cleveland-black-shield</link><description>After Cleveland officer Vincent Montague shot a Black man, he got promoted. Then he allied with Black Lives Matter, and his life went off the rails.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What’s Next in Health Care for Older Adults: Questions and Answers With John Whyte, MD</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/blog-aging-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>As WebMD’s chief medical officer, John Whyte, MD, is in a unique position to see both the current state of medical care for America’s older adults and the way things are trending for the future. We asked him to share his insight on a few topics, along with a bit of advice.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:29:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BiggerNews: 2024 Housing Market Update and Why Prices Are Still Rising</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-959</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>The 2024 housing market isn’t turning out how most of us thought. At the beginning of the year, real estate investors were hopeful that mortgage rates would fall, affordability would […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 07:02:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deal Dive: Can blockchain make weather forecasts better? WeatherXM thinks so</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/25/deal-dive-can-blockchain-make-weather-forecasts-better-weatherxm-thinks-so/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Accurate weather forecasts are critical to industries like agriculture, and they’re also important to help prevent and mitigate harm from inclement weather events or natural disasters. But getting forecasts right is extremely difficult. That’s why the founders of WeatherXM have been looking to make weather forecasts more accurate for the past 12 years. In 2012, […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Marshall Project Wins Prestigious Robert F. Kennedy Journalism Award for Criminal Justice</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/21/marshall-project-rfk-award</link><description>The award recognizes our 2023 investigation exposing lax prison discipline for abusive guards in New York state prisons.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Get the Care You Need in a COVID-19 World</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/covid-senior-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>What to expect at the doctor’s office, hospitals, and long-term care facilities, the future of telemedicine, and how to get the best care during COVID-19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 19:50:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fundamentals of Funding: How to Finance Real Estate Without the Big Banks</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-410</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Private money is a “secret weapon” for real estate investing, allowing you to dodge the major banks and fund real estate deals on your terms. But just how easy is […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 07:02:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spyware app pcTattletale was hacked and its website defaced</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/25/spyware-app-pctattletale-was-hacked-and-its-website-defaced/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>pcTattletale's website was briefly defaced and contained links containing files from the spyware maker's servers, before going offline. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 16:29:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Police Tactics at Some Pro-Palestine Protests Ignore Past Lessons</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/18/police-israel-palestine-campus-protests</link><description>While some universities have sought peaceful approaches, others have used aggressive policing that bucks research from the protests following George Floyd’s murder.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Personal Shopper: A Savvy Black Entrepreneur Guides You to Eczema-Friendly Clothes, Creams, Cosmetics, and More</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/savvy-black-entrepreneur-guides-eczema-friendly-clothes-creams-cosmetics?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>A savvy black entrepreneur guides you on an eczema-friendly shopping spree.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:54:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Financial Freedom in 9 Steps: The Money Guy’s Financial Order of Operations</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-531</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>If you follow these nine steps, you will reach financial independence. How do we know? Well, The Money Guy Show’s Brian Preston and Bo Hanson have tested it hundreds of […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 07:01:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Synapse, backed by a16z, has collapsed, and 10 million consumers could be hurt</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/25/with-a16z-backed-synapses-collapse-baas-fintech-is-a-mess-and-10-million-consumers-could-be-hurt/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Synapse's bankruptcy shows just how treacherous things are for the often-interdependent fintech world when one key player hits trouble. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Susan Chira to Step Down as The Marshall Project’s Editor-in-Chief in January</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/16/susan-chira-eic-step-down</link><description>Under her stewardship, the news nonprofit more than doubled in size, opened local newsrooms and won its second Pulitzer Prize.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Behind the Spike in Colorectal Cancer Among Young Americans</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/colorectal-cancer/news/20240515/behind-the-spike-in-colorectal-cancer-cases?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Colorectal cancer cases increased a whopping 333% among 15- to 19-year-olds and 185% among 20- to 24-year-olds from 1999 to 2020.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:59:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>