<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 02:37:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Why Your Portfolio Should Include Scarce Assets</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/10/why-your-portfolio-should-include-scarce-assets/</link><description>Portfolios that include both productive and scarce assets can deliver similar performance to the S&amp;P 500 with less risk than those that hold only productive assets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:34:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Which 2023 vintage wines should you buy? A trip through Bordeaux's vineyards</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/11/which-2023-vintage-wines-buy-bordeaux-vineyards/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1440497281-e1715335233534.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Should you buy now? The short answer is yes—if the price is right. But pick carefully.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 06:09:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coiled Tight: Smaller Companies Are Primed for Outperformance</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/08/coiled-tight-smaller-companies-are-primed-for-outperformance/</link><description>Small-cap companies are poised for a rebound. The sector is best approached through an active investment strategy where expertise and a deep understanding of the individual businesses and their risk-and-reward characteristics are necessary for success.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:40:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fitness influencer gets candid out about having stage 4 colon cancer</title><link>https://fortune.com/well/article/colon-cancer-younger-people-maria-kang/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-903934188-e1715372078754.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>"I want to create awareness that it can happen to anyone," says Maria Kang, 43.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 03:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Investment Returns Are NOT Random</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/07/investment-returns-are-not-random/</link><description>Are investment returns random across time as Burton Malkiel suggests in his book, A Random Walk Down Wall Street? There is notable disagreement on this topic. This research finds that practitioners may need to rethink their portfolio optimization routines.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:22:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Financial stress is making us mentally and physically ill. Here’s how to cope</title><link>https://fortune.com/well/article/financial-stress-mental-health-physical-illness/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1076802112-e1715365105446.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The latest research on the connection between money and the mind finds our finances even take a toll on our physical health. It’s a vicious cycle.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 02:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Generational Wealth: Does the Apple Fall Far From the Tree?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/06/generational-wealth-does-the-apple-fall-far-from-the-tree/</link><description>There is strong evidence that most “rich families” will be poorer after several generations. Some of the reasons for this are systemic like taxes. But most factors that diminish a family’s wealth over generations are the choices that heirs make.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 12:37:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>One of the most shorted stocks on the market just leapt 99%, putting a ‘rib-crunching’ squeeze on bearish bettors</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/10/novavax-stock-nvax-short-seller-squeeze-sanofi-covid-flu-vaccine/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1241112231-e1715383076862.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Friday’s stock surge delivered paper losses of about $255 million to short sellers, according to data from S3 Partners LLC.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 00:41:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>State Capitalism in Private Markets: Mission Creep</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/03/state-capitalism-in-private-markets-mission-creep/</link><description>Governments relish mingling in markets. Yet, if past policies are any guide, taxpayers are being shortchanged.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 12:30:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Flavor Flav is the official hype man for the US women's water polo team in the Paris Olympics</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/10/flavor-flav-public-enemy-us-women-water-polo-team-paris-olympics/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/AP24131603544960-e1715378316858.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>“One thing about me, I know what it feels like to want to see a dream come true,” Flavor Flav said.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 23:11:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>