<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 06:57:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Clinton LumberKings to play as Shadflies as prank becomes reality</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/17/clinton-lumberkings-to-play-as-shadflies-as-prank-becomes-reality/baseball/</link><description>When the collegiate summer level Clinton LumberKings announced earlier this month that they planned to rebrand as the Shadflies for Friday night games this season, fans recognized the April Fool’s prank right away. Shadflies, also called mayflies, are short-lived flying insects that live near waterways—like the Mississippi, which flows right</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 04:59:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Real Housewives' Alum Siggy Flicker's Stepson Arrested Over Jan. 6 Riot</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/17/real-housewives-siggy-flicker-stepson-arrested-january-6-capitol-riot/</link><description>Siggy Flicker's stepson has been arrested -- now facing charges for his alleged role in the Jan. 6 Capitol riot after authorities say his stepmom posted pics of him in the building. Tyler Campanella -- the former 'Real Housewives' star's stepson --…</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 06:57:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Las Vegas Aviators to play as Gamblers</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/17/las-vegas-aviators-to-play-as-gamblers/baseball/</link><description>Since 1983, the Triple-A franchise that plays in Las Vegas, Nevada, has had three monikers, which have highlighted celebrities, aliens, and the aviation industry. None of those brands has featured what the city is best known for—the gaming industry. In a promotional video unveiling a new alternate identity this week,</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 04:37:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jessica Chastain's 'Murph' Baby Name Boom Not as Common as She Thinks</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/17/jessica-chastain-baby-name-claim-debunk-murph-interstellar/</link><description>Jessica Chastain's claim about a popular baby name isn't holdin' water -- while she says lots of fans are naming kids after her "Interstellar" character ... Babynames.com says that's not the case. The online database for baby names tells TMZ ...…</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 06:57:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Flying Squirrels pay tribute to Mighty James with River City alternate</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/17/flying-squirrels-pay-tribute-to-mighty-james-with-river-city-alternate/baseball/</link><description>As the James River flows 444 miles from its headwaters in the Appalachian Mountains to the Chesapeake Bay, it rolls through Virginia’s state capital, Richmond, where it is central to the city’s history, economy, and contemporary culture and recreation. The Double-A Richmond Flying Squirrels will pay tribute to the Mighty</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 03:55:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Halle Bailey Still Together with DDG Despite Breakup Rumors</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/17/halle-bailey-still-with-ddg-together-despite-breakup-rumors/</link><description>Halle Bailey and DDG, the father of her child, have not gone their separate ways and are not broken up -- even though the internet certainly seems to think they did ... TMZ has learned. The singer's rep tells us Halle and DDG are still together and…</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 06:57:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CFL’s Montréal Alouettes to Mark 50th Anniversary of 1974 Grey Cup Win With ‘One-Of-A-Kind’ Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/17/cfls-montreal-alouettes-to-mark-50th-anniversary-of-1974-grey-cup-win-with-one-of-a-kind-uniforms/football/</link><description>Alouettes to celebrate 50th anniversary of Grey Cup victory over Edmonton in August with alumni in the house and special uniforms</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 18:29:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>O.J. Simpson Officially Cremated, Attorney &amp; Others Present as Witnesses</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/17/oj-simpson-officially-cremated-attorney-others-present-witness/</link><description>O.J. Simpson has officially been cremated -- and it sounds like there were only a select few people around to bear witness ... including his attorney-turned-executor of his estate. Malcolm LaVergne confirms to TMZ that his longtime client's body…</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 06:57:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cleveland Browns Update Helmets, Logo For 2024</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/04/17/cleveland-browns-update-helmets-and-logo-for-2024/football/</link><description>The Cleveland Browns announced on Wednesday morning they are returning to white facemasks and a glossy finish on their helmets and updating their logo to reflect the change.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 15:03:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coachella Weekend 1 Arrests Down 20 Percent From 2023</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/04/17/coachella-weekend-arrests-down-20-percent-last-year/</link><description>It looks like people were better behaved at Coachella Weekend 1 this year ... because arrests were down significantly compared to last year, TMZ has learned. Indio PD released their data from the festival's first installment ... and they say they…</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 06:57:17 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>