<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 01:04:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Book Review: Trailblazers, Heroes, and Crooks</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/26/book-review-trailblazers-heroes-and-crooks/</link><description>Stephen Foerster, CFA, extracts lessons from exceptional episodes in financial history that ordinary investors and seasoned professionals alike can put to profitable use. The bonus is that you'll be entertained from start to finish.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Should you sleep in socks? Experts say this hack might be the secret to falling asleep faster and waking up less</title><link>https://fortune.com/well/article/sleep-in-socks/</link><description>Socks aren't just for daytime.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 01:25:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Price Risk? Unpacking the Equity Risk Premium</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/24/what-price-risk-unpacking-the-equity-risk-premium/</link><description>Stocks are a good wager over the long term, on favorable odds. But stocks remain a bet, and investors must grasp how much returns can vary over long time horizons.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'We expect Powell to make a hawkish pivot'—Fed meeting to headline busy week for global markets</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/27/jerome-powell-hawkish-pivot-fed-meeting-interest-rates-global-market/</link><description>"At the minimum, he’ll likely indicate the median FOMC participant now expects ‘less’ cuts this year."</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 23:58:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Equity Income Investing Redux</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/22/equity-income-investing-redux/</link><description>No doubt the past year has been difficult for equity income investors. But history, inherent biases, mean reversion, and the current market backdrop point to a comeback.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 17:19:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Police bust 'very sophisticated' burglary ring that used Wi-Fi jammers to stea $4 million in jewels</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/27/burglary-ring-jewel-thieves-4-million-wi-fi-jammers-gold-cash-diamonds/</link><description>The Providence-based theft crew broke into homes in 25 Massachusetts communities between July 21, 2018 and March 30.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 23:42:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: Enrich Your Future</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/18/book-review-enrich-your-future/</link><description>This engaging book is simultaneously memorable and humorous. The numerous sports analogies will have you smiling as you absorb Larry Swedroe's unforgettable investment precepts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 18:07:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>U.S. Secretary of State buys Taylor Swift album in China to wrap up key visit after warning on EV overproduction, Russia</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/27/secretary-of-state-antony-blinken-taylor-swift-album-china-ev-overproduction-russia/</link><description>Antony Blinken stopped at a Beijing record store where he bought albums by Taylor Swift and Chinese rocker Dou Wei in a symbolic nod to cross-cultural exchanges.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 23:23:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CAPE Is High: Should You Care?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/17/cape-is-high-should-you-care/</link><description>A simple analysis shows that Robert Shiller's cyclically adjusted price-to-earnings ratio changed in the 1990s and that mean-reversion concerns may be misplaced. If CAPE changed three decades ago, however, there is nothing preventing it from doing so again.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 15:18:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>It's time to talk about the 'dirty word' on Wall Street as 'whiffs of stagflation' intrude on markets, chief strategist says</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/27/stagflation-warning-q1-gdp-pce-inflation-bond-yields-stock-market-correction/</link><description>"And that's why it was kind of shocking to see bond yields rise on a day where GDP was a big miss."</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 22:45:22 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>