<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 07:23:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The Midwest All-Stars, an MLB Team that Lasted Just One Game in 1970</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/19/the-midwest-all-stars-an-mlb-team-that-lasted-just-one-game-in-1970/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>What happens when a league’s schedule makers forget to include a team for an entire weekend? In 1970, the American League was forced to solve that exact problem when they inadvertently left the Boston Red Sox off the Grapefruit League schedule entirely over the weekend of March 7-8. Of course,</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 20:30:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bianca Censori Wears Nearly-Naked Look to Shop With Mom &amp; Sisters</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/19/bianca-censori-naked-outfit-shopping/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Bianca Censori seems like she's toning down her nearly-naked style lately ... but even wearing pants and a top, there's not much left to the imagination. The Yeezy architect stepped out for a shopping outing on Melrose Ave with her mother,…</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 07:23:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NFL Second, Third Helmet Concept Series – AFC West</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/18/nfl-second-third-helmet-concept-series-afc-west/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Our newest concept series that creates second and/or third helmet designs for every NFL team continues with the AFC West.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 17:07:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TikTok Star Nicky Champa Files For Divorce From Pierre Boo</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/19/tiktok-couple-nicky-champa-pierre-boo-divorce/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>TikTok star Nicky Champa is pulling the plug on his marriage ... he just filed for divorce from his famous partner. Nicky beelined it to court bright and early Monday morning and filed for divorce from fellow TikTok star Pierre Boo after 2 years of…</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 07:23:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>First Look at the 2025 MLB Spring Training Logos</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/17/first-look-at-the-2025-mlb-spring-training-logos/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Is it that time of the year already? This week, Major League Baseball released its new official logos for its 2025 Spring Training schedule. This year’s logos for the annual six-week slate of exhibition games include an all-new primary mark, a slightly modified alternate design, and designs for both the</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 16:08:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shiloh Jolie Officially Drops Pitt From Last Name</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/19/shiloh-jolie-pitt-name-change-approved/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Shiloh Jolie has officially dropped dad Brad Pitt's surname from her moniker ... the 18-year-old has been granted a name change, TMZ has learned. In new court documents ... Angelina Jolie's daughter received court approval to drop "Pitt" from her…</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 07:23:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2024-25 European Football Kit Preview: Serie A</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/17/2024-25-european-football-kit-preview-serie-a/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>123rd season of top-flight soccer in Italy kicks off on Saturday, August 17, with defending champs Inter Milan taking on Genoa CFC</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sexyy Red Launches NSFW Lip Gloss Names</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/19/sexyy-red-nsfw-lip-gloss/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Sexyy Red is heating up summer with a new business venture ... a line of NSFW lip glosses, seemingly channeling her "Pound Town" anthem. The rapper revealed the sexually-charged makeup brand online Monday, called "Sexyy," by posing for a series of…</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 07:23:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CFL Running Back Becomes First Pro Football Player to Wear Guardian Cap in Regular Season Game</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/16/cfl-running-back-becomes-first-pro-football-player-to-wear-guardian-cap-in-regular-season-game/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Saskatchewan Roughriders running back Thomas Bertrand-Hudon wears concussion prevention cover in game against Montreal Alouettes on Friday, August 16</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 03:05:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Flavor Flav Parties With USA Women's Water Polo Team In Vegas After Olympics</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/19/flavor-flav-parties-water-polo-team/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>The USA women's water polo team took the party from Paris to Sin City this month -- jet-setting to Vegas following their run in the Olympics -- and their hype man and sponsor, Flavor Flav, was right there by their side for the festivities!! Maggie…</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 07:23:51 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>