<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:28:37 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>New USL Super League Team Dallas Trinity FC Unveils Name, Logo</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/10/new-usl-super-league-team-dallas-trinity-fc-unveils-name-logo/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>New professional women's soccer team in North Texas will begin inaugural season in August and play out of historic Cotton Bowl stadium</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 16:10:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Andy Cohen Cleared in Bravo Misconduct Investigation, 'WWHL' Renewed</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/09/andy-cohen-cleared-bravo-misconduct-investigation-wwhl-renewed/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Andy Cohen's position at Bravo has been secured for the foreseeable future ... not long after being cleared in a misconduct investigation, TMZ has learned. The network confirmed Thursday that Andy and "Watch What Happens Live" will continue on…</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:28:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paris Saint-Germain Draws From Urban Art Scene for 2024-25 Home Kit</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/10/paris-saint-germain-draws-from-urban-art-scene-for-2024-25-home-kit/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Traditional red-and-white Hechter stripe returns to center of jersey, but is "reinterpreted with a fluid and dynamic brushstroke style"</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 15:29:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zayn Malik Says He Doesn't Think He's Been In Love, Shading Gigi Hadid?</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/09/zayn-malik-doesnt-think-ever-been-in-love-shading-gigi-hadid/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Zayn Malik might've just thrown an unintentional dig at Gigi Hadid ... saying he's not sure he's ever fallen in love with someone -- which seems to apply to the mother of his child. The One Direction star lifted the lid on his past relationships on…</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:28:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Report: WNBA Expanding to Toronto for 2026</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/10/report-wnba-expanding-to-toronto-for-2026/basketball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The WNBA is crossing the border! According to a CBC report, Toronto will be getting a Women’s National Basketball Association expansion franchise for the 2026 WNBA season. Kilmer Sports Inc., led by Toronto billionaire Larry Tanenbaum, will own the franchise. The report says the league’s official announcement is expected to</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 14:25:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Joe Biden Flubs Aces Championship Speech, Calls Candace Parker Greatest 'Coach'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/09/president-joe-biden-candace-parker-aces-white-house-visit-wnba/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>President Joe Biden has suffered yet another gaffe at a podium ... this time, he incorrectly ID'ed WNBA superstar Candace Parker as a "coach." The flub happened as Biden was hosting Parker's Las Vegas Aces at the White House to celebrate their 2023…</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:28:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Report: Fanatics NHL Jerseys to Debut in June</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/10/report-fanatics-nhl-jerseys-to-debut-in-june/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The NHL’s shift to Fanatics on-ice jerseys could be revealed as soon as next month, according to former NFL quarterback Boomer Esiason. While on his morning Boomer and Gio radio program, Esiason revealed that the new Fanatics NHL jerseys for all 32 teams (Utah too?) would be revealed sometime in</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:55:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bear Attack Caught on Video, Rushes Car and Smashes Windshield</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/09/bear-attackr-car-smashes-windshield-new-video-shows-caught-japan/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>A couple foragers ended up in a hairy situation out in Japan -- speeding down the road in a forest when a bear attacked their car, cracking their window ... and it's all on camera. Check out this wild footage out out of Hokkaido last week ... the…</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:28:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New England Patriots Subtly Reveal New Secondary Logo</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/09/new-england-patriots-subtly-reveal-new-secondary-logo/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Following a recent visit to Gillette Stadium, former New England Patriots linebacker Brandon Spikes posted a photo of what appears to be the franchise’s new secondary logo prominently displayed inside the facility.</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 20:58:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Real-Life 'Baby Reindeer' Martha Says She Sent Gadd Less Than 10 Emails</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/09/real-life-baby-reindeer-martha-fiona-harvey-sent-gadd-10-emails/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>The real-life woman behind the villain in "Baby Reindeer" -- who's portrayed as a stalker -- just went on TV to deny how she was depicted ... insisting she only sent a few emails. Fiona Harvey appeared as a guest on Piers Morgan's show Thursday --…</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:28:37 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>