<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 22:38:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Book Review: Shocks, Crises, and False Alarms</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/19/book-review-shocks-crises-and-false-alarms/</link><description>Carlsson-Szlezak and Swartz attempt to add fresh thinking on framing macro shocks that may often prove to be false alarms. Any general reader will obtain some key fresh insights with this work, and CFA charterholders will be offered an alternative to the conventional Wall Street approach to macro discussions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 13:06:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Junk bonds are now in high demand as Wall Street bets on another Trump presidency</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/07/20/junk-bonds-donald-trump-trade-corporate-tax-cuts-tariffs-election/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/GettyImages-2162000451_2d93e9-e1721516063158.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>“US high yield is the trade. It is more domestic-focused and exposed to US economic activity.”</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 00:01:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Preserving the Dollar: The Role of CBDCs in Securing Economic Stability for Future Generations</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/16/preserving-the-dollar-the-role-of-cbdcs-in-securing-economic-stability-for-future-generations/</link><description>As financial systems evolve, preserving the US dollar's dominance will require skillful policy management and the integration of cutting-edge technologies.</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:24:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The worst IT catastrophe ever hit less than 1% of all Microsoft Windows devices</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/07/20/crowdstrike-global-outage-less-than-1-percent-all-microsoft-windows-devices/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/GettyImages-2162656140-e1721515317401.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>A faulty software update from cybersecurity firm CrowdStrike affected 8.5 million devices globally that rely on the Microsoft Windows operating system.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 23:49:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Can Equal Weight Solve Our Concentration Crisis? Not So Fast…</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/15/can-equal-weight-solve-our-concentration-crisis-not-so-fast/</link><description>Mega-cap concentration has exploded since 2015. The corollary to an increasingly top-heavy benchmark is that market diversification and breadth have never been more limited. A multifactor methodology can be a restorative balance to US equities when more traditional measures fall short.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 22:43:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Phishing attempts rise as scam artists try to exploit the CrowdStrike global tech outage</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/07/20/crowdstrike-outage-phishing-attempts-scam-artists-microsoft-windows-cybersecurity/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/AP24202623575279-e1721514368759.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>“We know that adversaries and bad actors will try to exploit events like this,” CrowdStrike CEO George Kurtz said.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 23:34:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>In Search of the Elusive Neutral Interest Rate</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/10/in-search-of-the-elusive-neutral-interest-rate/</link><description>With Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell's semiannual address to the Senate Banking Committee this week fresh in mind, it is an ideal time to consider the drivers of r*.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 12:17:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gunman in Trump assassination attempt flew a drone over the rally site ahead of shooting, official says</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/07/20/trump-assassination-attempt-gunman-drone-campaign-rally-site-shooting/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/AP24198007342884-e1721513346169.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>More details about the investigation are expected to be made public in the coming week when FBI Director Chris Wray appears before the House Judiciary Committee.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 23:17:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Commodities for the Long Run?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/08/commodities-for-the-long-run/</link><description>Asset classes such as commodities have historically had notable diversification benefits for longer-term investors who are concerned with inflation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 21:50:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘Black Swan’ investor warns the ‘greatest bubble in human history’ is about to pop and stocks could lose more than half their value</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/07/20/black-swan-investor-mark-spitznagel-greatest-bubble-human-history-stock-market-crash-recession/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/GettyImages-693466508-e1721506424565.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The federal government will have less capacity to respond, and the economy could enter a recession by the end of this year, Mark Spitznagel predicted.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 22:36:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>