<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 11:55:36 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Generational Wealth: Does the Apple Fall Far From the Tree?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/06/generational-wealth-does-the-apple-fall-far-from-the-tree/</link><description>There is strong evidence that most “rich families” will be poorer after several generations. Some of the reasons for this are systemic like taxes. But most factors that diminish a family’s wealth over generations are the choices that heirs make.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 12:37:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Howard Schultz urges Starbucks to 'fix' U.S. stores after big earnings miss</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/06/howard-schultz-starbucks-disappointing-earnings/</link><description>“The company’s fix needs to begin at home:”</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:38:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>State Capitalism in Private Markets: Mission Creep</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/03/state-capitalism-in-private-markets-mission-creep/</link><description>Governments relish mingling in markets. Yet, if past policies are any guide, taxpayers are being shortchanged.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 12:30:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cesar Luis Menotti, the ‘thin one’ who led Argentina to its first World Cup in 1978, has died at 85</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/06/cesar-luis-menotti-obituary-argentina-world-cup-coach-soccer-football/</link><description>The longtime smoker once talked of meeting the great writer Jorge Luis Borges: "When I asked him if it bothered him that I smoked, he told me: ‘What intoxicates me is not the cigarette, but the stupid conversations.’”</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 15:49:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Implementation Shortfalls Hamstring Factor Strategies</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/01/implementation-shortfalls-hamstring-factor-strategies/</link><description>Smart rebalancing rules help portfolio managers capture more of the return that is inherent in their factor strategies. Concentrating on “priority best” trading improves factor portfolio performance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 11:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Columbia cancels university-wide commencement amid protests but will hold smaller ceremonies 5 miles away from the main campus</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/06/columbia-cancels-university-wide-commencement-israel-hamas-gaza-protests/</link><description>“Our students emphasized that these smaller-scale, school-based celebrations are most meaningful to them and their families."</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 15:44:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IFRS Accounting Standard Will Support Better Investment Decisions</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/30/ifrs-accounting-standard-will-support-better-investment-decisions/</link><description>IFRS 18 responds to investors' concerns about challenges in comparing companies' financial performance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 11:34:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kim Godwin, first Black female network news chief, leaves ABC News</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/06/kim-godwin-retires-abc-news-disney-first-black-female-network-head/</link><description>After working at ABC, CBS and NBC, Godwin said she's quitting the business. “I leave with my head held high and wish the entire team continued success."</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 15:42:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meir Statman: Your State of Mind Influences Your Investing Success</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/29/meir-statman-your-state-of-mind-influences-your-investing-success/</link><description>Meir Statman shares his insights on the broader aspects of financial well-being and its interconnection with life satisfaction.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 12:58:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tesla may charge Model Y owners to unlock the full potential of their batteries</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/06/model-y-tesla-charge-battery-full-range-musk/</link><description>That could bump the cost up another $2,000</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 15:32:12 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>