<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 02:34:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>US Economic Outlook Significantly Stronger Than You’d Think</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-253</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>The US economy isn’t doing as well as you think—it’s doing even better. While mainstream media outlets and grocery prices may make you feel that the US economy is struggling, […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 10:00:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>India’s Physics Wallah raises $210M at $2.8B valuation even as edtech funding remains scarce</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/19/indias-physics-wallah-raises-210m-at-2-8b-valuation-even-as-edtech-funding-remains-scarce/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>An Indian edtech startup has secured $210 million in fresh financing amid a tough funding environment for edtech companies in the country. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 07:34:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How We Survived Extreme Heat in Prison</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/09/19/prison-journalists-how-to-survive-extreme-heat</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Incarcerated journalists detail the first signs of a heat wave in prison — and how they’ve coped with record-breaking temperatures.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What It Takes to Master Airbnb Accounting and Bookkeeping</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/mastering-airbnb-accounting-and-bookkeeping</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Accurate accounting and meticulous bookkeeping are vital to maintaining a profitable rental operation, especially when STRs are even more scrutinized than typical rentals.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 21:57:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>John Mulaney skewers San Francisco tech crowd at Dreamforce</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/19/john-mulaney-skewers-san-francisco-at-dreamforce/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Attendees of the giant, annual Dreamforce conference in San Francisco love being the butt of the joke. Last year, Seth Myers entertained them during a 40-minute set that poked fun at the tech industry’s liberal use of self-affirmations. “You are achieving, you are amplifying, you are accelerating,” Myers said. “‘Architect?’ I saw ‘architect’ used as […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 06:28:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Marshall Project to Host Inaugural Sing Sing Prison Film Festival</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/09/19/the-marshall-project-to-host-inaugural-sing-sing-prison-film-festival</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Incarcerated jury will choose best criminal justice documentary.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Federal Reserve Cuts Rates By 0.50%, a Bigger Cut Than Expected</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/federal-reserve-cuts-rates-for-first-time-since-2020</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>It finally happened: Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell announced that the Fed will, in fact, cut rates, ending months of speculation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 21:33:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian filmmaker Ram Gopal Varma abandons human musicians for AI-generated music</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/19/indian-filmmaker-ram-gopal-varma-abandons-human-musicians-for-ai-generated-music/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Indian filmmaker Ram Gopal Varma is ditching human musicians for artificial intelligence, saying he’ll use only AI-generated tunes in future projects, a move that underscores AI’s growing reach in creative industries. The filmmaker and screenwriter, known for popular Bollywood movies including Company, Rangeela, Sarkar, and Satya has launched a venture, called RGV Den Music, that […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 05:59:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Robert Roberson’s Death Penalty Case Shows How Justice System Fails People With Autism</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/09/18/texas-autism-death-penalty-roberson</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>He was convicted in his daughter’s death. Those who believe he’s innocent argue his diagnosis helps explain how he ended up facing execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Don’t Do What I Did On Your Next Property…w/Craig Curelop</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-1019</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Can your mistakes make you a millionaire? If you’re like Craig Curelop and learn from what went wrong, then yes! Craig is now financially free, with millions of dollars in […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 10:00:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Here is what’s illegal under California’s 8 (and counting) new AI laws</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/19/here-is-whats-illegal-under-californias-8-and-counting-new-ai-laws/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>California Governor Gavin Newsom is currently considering 38 AI-related bills, including the highly contentious SB 1047, which the state’s legislature sent to his desk for final approval. These bills try to address the most pressing issues in artificial intelligence: everything from futuristic AI systems creating existential risk, deepfake nudes from AI image generators, to Hollywood […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 00:41:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Could People Facing the Death Penalty Lose the Right to Tell Juries Their Life Stories?</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/09/17/supreme-court-death-penalty-jury-overturn-precedent</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Some defense lawyers fear that a conservative Supreme Court could overturn that precedent.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 11:00:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Passive Investing 101: A Passive Path to Profit, Appreciation, &amp; Tax Benefits</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-459</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Visit PassivePockets, your resource for passive investing with syndications. Do you want to get into real estate without managing rentals and dealing with tenants? Passive real estate investing could be […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 10:00:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gaming Lyft’s Citi Bike algos was a lucrative side hustle for a while</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/19/gaming-lyfts-citi-bike-algos-was-a-lucrative-side-hustle-for-a-while/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>A New York Times article Thursday highlighted a lucrative side hustle that is emblematic of the times we live in: gaming algorithms to earn money. In this case, folks figured out they could maximize the payout from Lyft’s Citi Bike “Bike Angels” program by taking advantage of a company algorithm used to meet its supply-and-demand […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 23:29:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>5 Things to Know About How the Parkland Shooter’s Life Was Spared</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/09/17/how-nikolas-cruz-avoided-death-penalty-takeaways</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways from our investigation into how Nikolas Cruz’s defense team convinced jurors not to impose the death penalty.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 11:00:22 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>