<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 01:13:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Shining A Light: QMJHL’s Rimouski Oceanic Unveil 30th Anniversary Logo</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/09/shining-a-light-qmjhls-rimouski-oceanic-unveil-30th-anniversary-logo/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Anniversary logo depicts historic lighthouse at nearby Pointe-au-Père in front of ship's porthole; lighter blue behind represents St. Lawrence River</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 21:01:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shawn Mendes Sings About Pregnancy Scare in New Song</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/09/shawn-mendes-pregnancy-scare/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Shawn Mendes is making it clear he's in no way ready to become a father ... sharing his fears in a new song after one tense pregnancy scare. The singer dropped "Why Why Why" late on Thursday, addressing for the first time how he almost became a…</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 01:13:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Utah Hockey Club Reveals Inaugural Season Logo, Centre Ice Design</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/09/utah-hockey-club-reveals-inaugural-season-logo-centre-ice-design/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Utah Hockey Club is just a few weeks away from playing its first-ever game in the National Hockey League. While it may not have a proper name, logo, uniform, or sensible franchise timeline yet, it does now have a commemorative inaugural season logo. The Hockey Club released the special</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 20:54:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jake Paul Plans To Compete For Boxing Gold Medal At 2028 Olympics</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/09/jake-paul-boxing-2028-olympics/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Jake Paul is taking matters into his own hands to bring USA Boxing back to the top of the Olympic podium -- he just announced his plans to compete at the 2028 Games in Los Angeles!! El Gallo dropped the surprising news on his "BS W/ Jake Paul"…</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 01:13:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oklahoma Sooners Unveil 1946-56 Throwback Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/09/oklahoma-sooners-unveil-1946-56-throwback-uniforms/college/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Oklahoma will celebrate the 100th season of Gaylord Family-Oklahoma Memorial Stadium this fall by wearing 1946-56 throwback uniforms against Houston on Sept. 7.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 17:53:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Donald Trump Claims He Took Helicopter Ride With Kamala's Ex, He Calls BS</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/09/donald-trump-helicopter-willie-brown/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Donald Trump's got a future career as a fantasy writer ... so says the former mayor of San Francisco, who's calling Trump's tale about the two of them a piece of "creative fiction." Here's the deal ... during Trump's news conference with reporters…</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 01:13:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MLB Announces Speedway Classic ’25 at Bristol, Unveils Logo</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/09/mlb-announces-speedway-classic-25-at-bristol-unveils-logo/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Before the Atlanta Braves and Cincinnati Reds take the field on Saturday, August 2, 2025, the home plate umpire will have a tough decision to make… “should I yell ‘play ball!’ or ‘It’s time to start your engines’?” This morning, Major League Baseball announced that they would play a game</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 16:17:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>T.I. Has No Grudges Against Cops Who Falsely Arrested Him</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/09/ti-mistaken-identity-arrest-reaction/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>T.I.'s putting his mistaken identity arrest in his rearview, and though cops ultimately put him through the wringer unnecessarily ... he's treating it like water under the bridge. TMZ Hip Hop caught up with Tip Thursday in Bev. Hills, where he…</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 01:13:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Colourful Player Numbers on Caps for MLB’s 2024 Players’ Weekend</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/08/colourful-player-numbers-on-caps-for-mlbs-2024-players-weekend/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Next weekend is Players’ Weekend across Major League Baseball. The series of games played from August 16-18 will be the first time MLB will host a Players’ Weekend since 2019. As part of this year’s celebration, each player’s uniform number will be worn on the right side of their cap</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 03:07:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stassi Schroeder Returns to Reality TV, Joins 'Vanderpump Villa' Season 2</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/09/stassi-schroeder-returns-vanderpump/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Stassi Schroeder is gearing up for a reality TV comeback .... as the "Vanderpump Rules" alum has reunited with Lisa Vanderpump for a new role. The Bravo personalities made the big announcement on Friday, when they confirmed that Stassi would be…</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 01:13:18 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>