<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 15:28:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>When the Dallas Stars Shifted to Green and Silver in 2013</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/04/when-the-dallas-stars-shifted-to-green-and-silver-in-2013/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Eleven years ago today, the Dallas Stars unveiled their current logo and uniform, marking the most significant shift in the franchise’s visual identity in over two decades. The Dallas Stars revealed their new logo and uniforms at a press event in Dallas on June 4, 2013, just two weeks after</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 19:00:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Christina Applegate Talks Depression Battle Over MS, 'Trapped In Darkness'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/04/christina-applegate-depression-multiple-sclerosis-diagnosis-trapped-darkness/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Christina Applegate's always been open about her MS struggles ... and now she's also revealing her battle with deep depression, which has left her with no joy in living. On the latest 'MeSsy' podcast episode, Christina told her buddy Jamie-Lynn…</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 15:28:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Back in Black: CFL’s Ottawa REDBLACKS Launch New Home Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/04/back-in-black-cfls-ottawa-redblacks-launch-new-home-uniforms/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Team's new home uniforms feature striping on helmets and shoulders that borrows heavily from old Ottawa Rough Riders franchise</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 17:55:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rodeo Star Spencer Wright's 3-Year-Old Son Dies After Toy Tractor Accident</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/04/spencer-kallie-wright-son-dead-toy-tractor-river-incident/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Rodeo star Spencer Wright's three-year-old son tragically passed away on Sunday ... two weeks after he was left in critical condition following a toy tractor accident. A friend of the Wright family confirmed the heartbreaking news to People ...…</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 15:28:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tottenham Hotspur Ready to Rise in New Home Kits — Plus Other Launches From Around Europe</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/04/tottenham-hotspur-ready-to-rise-in-new-home-kits-plus-other-launches-from-around-europe/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>FC St. Pauli returns to Bundesliga with Puma home kits; Celta Vigo switches manufacturers; Nantes celebrates 94-95 title team; Rangers mark 125th anniversary of Ibrox</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 17:20:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Michael Richards Says He's Less Angry Nearly 20 Years After N-Word Rant</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/04/michael-richards-less-angry-years-after-n-word-rant-new-book-today/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Michael Richards is making a comeback of sorts -- releasing a new book, and in the same breath, reflecting on his n-word rant ... saying he's a better person nearly 20 years later. The ex-"Seinfeld" star has just released a memoir called "Entrances…</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 15:28:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Twins Announce City Connect Unveil Plans, Water-Themed Uniform?</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/03/twins-announce-city-connect-unveil-plans-water-themed-uniform/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Minnesota Twins have announced some of the details surrounding the upcoming release of their 2024 Nike MLB City Connect uniform. The new uniform will be unveiled on Monday, June 10, during a special event at Target Plaza outside Target Field. The unveiling kicks off the Twins’ “City Connect Launch</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 21:38:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Friday the 13th' Actor Erich Anderson Dead at 67 After Cancer Battle</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/04/erich-anderson-dead-dies-cancer-battle-friday-13th-felicity/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Actor Erich Anderson, best known for his roles in "Friday the 13th: The Final Chapter" and "Felicity," has died. Erich's devastated wife, Saxon Trainor, confirmed the tragic news over the weekend ... revealing in a social media post, he had passed…</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 15:28:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NSL’s AFC Toronto Unveils Name and Crest</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/03/nsls-afc-toronto-unveils-name-and-crest/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Northern Super League club will take to the pitch in 2025 inaugural season with maroon and vermillion color scheme and crest that aims to represent different parts of their city</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 16:44:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pro Skier Jean Daniel Pession, GF Dead After Falling 2,300 Feet Off Mountain</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/04/jean-daniel-pession-world-cup-skier-dead-girlfriend-elisa-arlian-fall-off-mountain-zerbion/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>World Cup Skier Jean Daniel Pession, along with girlfriend Elisa Arlian, tragically died after the couple fell 2,300 feet off of a mountain in Italy. The Italian Winter Sports Federation confirmed the awful incident happened June 1 on Mount…</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 15:28:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>