<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 06:54:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Rookie Reply: Build Your Portfolio OR Pay Off Debt &amp; Tenant Conflict 101</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-431</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Buying a house is a HUGE decision, whether you’re an experienced investor or a first-time homebuyer. The last thing you want is to get in over your head with a […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 07:02:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AT&amp;T says criminals stole phone records of ‘nearly all’ customers in new data breach</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/12/att-phone-records-stolen-data-breach/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The stolen data includes 110 million AT&amp;T customer phone numbers, calling and text records, and some location-related data. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 11:27:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jackson, Mississippi, Wants Curfew Centers to Cut Crime. Here’s What Other Cities Learned.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/09/jackson-mississippi-youth-curfew-centers</link><description>After a teen’s murder, city officials hope a curfew and youth centers will get kids off the street. Young people are skeptical.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 11:00:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BiggerNews: Rate Cut Chances Increase as New “Affordable” Markets Emerge</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-987</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Will the new jobs report finally prompt the Fed to cut rates, leading to you scoring a lower mortgage rate? With multifamily rents still falling, should we fear a nosediving […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 07:02:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>EU’s AI Act gets published in bloc’s Official Journal, starting clock on legal deadlines</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/12/eus-ai-act-gets-published-in-blocs-official-journal-starting-clock-on-legal-deadlines/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The full and final text of the EU AI Act, the European Union’s landmark risk-based regulation for applications of artificial intelligence, has been published in the bloc’s Official Journal. In 20 days’ time, on August 1, the new law will come into force and in 24 months — so by mid-2026 — its provisions will […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 09:51:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Love Beyond Bars: Miguel and Silvia</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/05/photo-essay-wrongful-conviction-love-story</link><description>While Miguel Solorio did 25 years for a crime he didn’t commit, his wife, Silvia, was right by his side. Here’s their California love story in pictures.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fat FI by 23: Building a 7-Figure Income &amp; 8-Figure Portfolio in 3 Years</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-545</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Fat FI and generational wealth in THREE years?! How is that possible? The sooner you forge good money habits, the sooner YOU can achieve your FI goal. Today’s guest wanted […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 07:01:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Waymo cameras capture footage of person charged in alleged robotaxi tire slashings</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/11/waymo-cameras-capture-footage-of-man-charged-in-alleged-robotaxi-tire-slashings/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>A Castro Valley resident was charged Thursday for allegedly slashing the tires of 17 Waymo robotaxis in San Francisco between June 24 and June 26, according to the city’s district attorney. Prosecutors say the tire slashings were captured by cameras installed on the exterior of Waymo’s robotaxis. This is the latest incident of Waymo vandalism […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 02:49:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Crime Rates and the 2024 Election: What You Need to Know</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/27/trump-and-biden-spar-over-crime-rates-ahead-of-their-debate-what-do-we-really-know</link><description>As crime data again becomes a flashpoint in the presidential campaign, experts push for better national statistics.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Housing Market “Stuck” Until 2026 as Insurance Prices Rise, Rents Slow</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-233</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>See Dave, Henry, James, and Kathy at BPCon2024 in Cancún, Mexico! Grab your ticket here! The housing market is “stuck” and may stay that way for the next two years. […]</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 07:02:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SoftBank acquires UK AI chipmaker Graphcore</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/11/softbank-acquires-uk-ai-chipmaker-graphcore/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>While the figure of $500 million has been bandied around in various reports for months, in a press briefing early Thursday morning, Graphcore co-founder and CEO Nigel Toon remained coy on the details. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Death Row Prisoner’s Parting Interview</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/24/texas-death-row-prisoner-final-interview</link><description>Days before his scheduled execution in Texas, Ramiro Gonzales speaks on faith, legacy — and apologizing to the family of his victim, Bridget Townsend.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>These 11 Markets Used to Be America’s Hot Spots. Now They’ve Gone Cold.</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/11-formerly-hot-markets-that-are-not-so-hot-anymore</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>The pandemic-fueled explosion of growth has waned, and now these real estate hot spots have gotten icy.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 22:30:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>X is building a ‘dislike’ button for downvoting replies</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/11/x-is-building-a-dislike-button-for-downvoting-replies/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Elon Musk’s X, formerly Twitter, is continuing to develop a downvoting feature that will be used to improve how replies are ranked. Although the company has not yet officially announced its plans, more recent findings indicate the downvote feature may actually resemble a “dislike” button instead of a Reddit-style downvote icon. Code references found in […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 23:17:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The New Battle Over an Old Institution: Forced Prison Labor</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/22/prison-slavery-forced-labor-lawsuits-bills</link><description>Inside the latest legal and legislative efforts to close state constitutional loopholes that allow slavery as punishment for a crime.</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>