<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 07:10:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Did This Market Move Catch You by Surprise?</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/did-this-market-move-catch-you-by-surprise/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, Ross here. Did yesterday's market dip catch you off guard? It erased last week's gains, but from a technical standpoint, it's a typical response after hitting new all-time highs. Now, the real question is how the support from March's highs will hold up. Even if it breaks, expect some sideways movement—no need to panic. Remember, markets need to shake out the overeager traders to climb higher, and that's exactly what we're seeing. It's the perfect setup for my Stealth Trades strategy, which leverages the moves of big institutional money. In fact, this Memorial Day, I’m offering a special on my strategy for just 99 cents for a full year. Don't miss out on this opportunity to align with the big players and position for the next surge. Grab it before the weekend! The post Did This Market Move Catch You by Surprise? appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>South Korea May Build Lithium Reserves to Aid Battery Sector</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/27/south-korea-may-build-lithium-reserves-to-aid-battery-sector/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/23160643/u_s__treasury_secretary_janet_yellen_visits_the_plant_of_u_s__lithium_producer_albemarle.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Green , Plants/Manufacturing , Electric Continue reading South Korea May Build Lithium Reserves to Aid Battery Sector South Korea May Build Lithium Reserves to Aid Battery Sector originally appeared on Autoblog on Mon, 27 May 2024 14:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Seeing Greene: How to Avoid High Down Payments and When to BRRRR vs. Buy New</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-961</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>One of the biggest hurdles to rental property investing? High down payments. Most lenders want you to come to the table with twenty to thirty percent down, but with home […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 07:02:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best New Book Releases Out May 28, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/best-new-book-releases-out-may-28-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/fair-skinned-person-readinng-a-book-with-a-mug-in-their-hand-theyre-on-a-very-scenic-cliff.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>Nonfiction on magic in the 1600s, sapphic romance, running from the Devil, and more await you in today's new releases. Which one are you trying to read first?</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sharing Fun Facts About Yourself: 22 Examples &amp; Ideas</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/fun-facts-about-me/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fun-facts-about-me</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Asking to share some fun facts about yourself is a common icebreaker that’s used during job interviews. But the quality of your answer still matters. This guide will help you come up with some ideas for crafting a response that starts the interview on a good note. Table of contents Ideas for Sharing Fun Facts […] The post Sharing Fun Facts About Yourself: 22 Examples &amp; Ideas appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 15:26:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Becoming Confident in Parenting Abilities</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/confidence-in-parenting/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=confidence-in-parenting</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Parental self-efficacy (i.e., a parent’s confidence in their own ability to care for their infant and respond to the infant’s needs) is the first step to a good parent-child relationship. Research has explored the development of maternal self-efficacy beginning during pregnancy and continuing after childbirth. Mothers who have previous childbirth and […] The post Becoming Confident in Parenting Abilities appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 10:06:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>5 things to know before the stock market opens Tuesday</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/28/5-things-to-know-before-the-stock-market-opens-tuesday-may-28.html</link><description>Here are the most important news items that investors need to start their trading day.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 12:04:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>These Top-Rated Small Appliances on Amazon Make Great Graduation Gifts</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1329291/these-10-small-appliances-with-thousands-of-amazon-reviews-make-great-graduation-gifts?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>We independently selected these products because we love them, and we hope you do too at these prices. Shop with E! has affiliate relationships, so we may get a commission if you purchase...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: The New World Economy in 5 Trends</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/24/book-review-the-new-world-economy-in-5-trends/</link><description>A diligent economist and an eclectic bookworm serve up an analysis of megatrends that will have the greatest impact on economies and investments: innovation, productivity, climate, multiglobalization, debt, and aging.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 12:22:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bill Gates said he wished he learned this lesson from Warren Buffett sooner: The power of an 'intentionally light' calendar</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/28/bill-gates-warren-buffett-calendar-lesson/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2151357685-e1716892204682.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>"In hindsight, it’s a lesson I could have learned a lot sooner had I taken more peeks at Warren Buffett’s intentionally light calendar."</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 11:40:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>This Week’s Favorites From Amazon</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/amazon-sundays-5-19-24/</link><description>Welcome to our latest favorites from Amazon that I’m especially excited to share! This week includes an array of colorful… The post This Week’s Favorites From Amazon appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 05:00:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Can't they see how cool this style is?</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/aNDZeWb</link><description>Tags: random , meme , memes 5726 points, 450 comments.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 12:05:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Utah NHL Team Logos, Colours, and Possible Uniforms for Year One</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/27/utah-nhl-team-logos-colours-and-possible-uniforms-for-year-one/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Utah’s new National Hockey League team, set to debut for the upcoming 2024-25 NHL season, will reportedly start without a permanent name or logo. However, a look at some of the early merchandise being prepared for the team has revealed what appears to be a temporary design featuring “UTAH” in</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 17:51:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>More neobanks are becoming mobile networks — and Nubank wants a piece of the action</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/28/more-neobanks-are-becoming-mobile-networks-and-nubank-wants-a-piece-of-the-action/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Nubank is taking its first tentative steps into the mobile network realm, as the NYSE-traded Brazilian neobank rolls out an eSIM (embedded SIM) service for travelers. The service will give customers access to 10GB of free roaming internet in more than 40 countries without having to switch out their own existing physical SIM card or […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Legal Doctrine That Shields Police From Many Lawsuits May Be Losing Support</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/25/police-mississippi-courts-judges-qualified-immunity</link><description>A federal judge in Mississippi joined other courts in recently rejecting police arguments that qualified immunity protected their actions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zesty BBQ Chicken (5 Ingredients)</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/zesty-bbq-chicken/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>This zesty BBQ chicken is an easy crockpot recipe that only takes 5 ingredients to make! The slow-cooked tender pulled…</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kelly Rowland's Cannes Security Guard Also Had Run-In with South Korean Actress</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/27/cannes-film-festival-security-guard-third-incident-kelly-rowland-yoona-discrimination/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>11:58 AM PT -- Another Cannes' attendee has called out the same security guard ... Ukrainian model Sawa Pontyjska -- better known as Miss Europe 2023 -- shared a clip where she ended up in a bear hug by security. Unclear exactly what led up to the…</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 07:10:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Federal Experts Talk Bird Flu ‘What Ifs’ in WebMD Live Event</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/cold-and-flu/news/20240516/federal-experts-talk-bird-flu-what-ifs?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>WebMD brought together experts from four federal agencies to talk prevention, monitoring, and what the “what ifs” of bird flu might look like.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:50:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Weekend In New Orleans With Kids</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/new-orleans-with-kids/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Since our travel guides to Charleston with kids and Palm Springs with kids have elicited requests for more travel ideas with kids, we’re back with an overdue recap of our 3-night trip to New Orleans. We’d never been to The Big Easy before and were impressed by how family-friendly the city is. It’s not all booze, beads, and Bourbon Street! So here’s a look at where we stayed, what we did, and what we’re excited to do next time we go back – because we will definitely go back! The four of us (well, five if you count our chihuahua!) went to NOLA for 3 nights in November of 2022. At the time, our kids were 8 and 12 years old. So unfortunately we can’t vouch for our suggestions being a good fit for toddlers or younger children. Although I’m sure ours would’ve loved the Louisiana Children’s Museum and Storyland playground back in the day! Continue reading A Weekend In New Orleans With Kids at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 17:17:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Big of a Problem is Inflation Really?</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/how-big-of-a-problem-is-inflation-really/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, Ross here. As we navigate through the bull market, one looming question persists: How big of a problem is inflation really? Despite the alarm bells rung by bears and the media, our latest data shows a decrease in the number of S&amp;P 500 companies concerned about inflation during their earnings calls. This signals a potentially overstated issue, with corporate earnings—key market drivers—still on solid ground. If you're watching the market meander sideways and finding it "boring," you might be missing out. Sideways markets are ripe for strategic positioning, often preceding significant movements. Join me tomorrow at 10 a.m. Eastern for a masterclass where I'll delve into insider trading insights, showing you how to distinguish between high and low signal trades and uncover the top-performing insiders. Plus, I'll share an exclusive opportunity that's just come onto my radar. Don’t miss this chance to learn from the insiders—reserve your spot now! The post How Big of a Problem is Inflation Really? appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Junkyard Gem: Customized 1994 Chevrolet Caprice Classic LS Sedan</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/27/junkyard-gem-custom-1994-chevrolet-caprice-sedan/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/15120137/19-1994-Chevrolet-Caprice-Classic-LS-in-Colorado-junkyard-photo-by-Murilee-Martin.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Chevrolet , Automotive History , Sedan Continue reading Junkyard Gem: Customized 1994 Chevrolet Caprice Classic LS Sedan Junkyard Gem: Customized 1994 Chevrolet Caprice Classic LS Sedan originally appeared on Autoblog on Mon, 27 May 2024 13:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Building Generational Wealth? Don’t Lose It with This ONE Critical Mistake</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-532</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>You’re working hard to build wealth, but without estate planning, your assets could easily land in the wrong hands, causing your family a great deal of trouble. No one likes […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 07:01:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Top 10 Summer Manga To Pack In Your Beach Bag</title><link>https://bookriot.com/summer-manga/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/manga-at-the-beach.png</image_url><description>Summer has almost arrived in Japan — you can tell by the stacks of summer manga reading spilling out of beach bags, backpacks, and picnic baskets.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 553</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-553/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-553</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Tools and technology change rapidly. Yet as wonderful as technology can be, it doesn’t replace the need for human connection through interactions. Keep this in mind as you are searching for a new job. It’s your human connections that often open doors! In this week’s collection of news and tips for job seekers, you’ll find: […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 553 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 12:19:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A case for public preschool: New study reveals preschool benefits to be longer-lasting and substantial</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/benefits-of-public-preschool/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=benefits-of-public-preschool</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Preschool lays a foundation for elementary school students to succeed. In the United States, as children approach kindergarten entry, it is increasingly common for 4-year-olds to be in non-parental group care and education, often in a center- or school-based setting where they can learn alongside peers. For children from low-income communities, […] The post A case for public preschool: New study reveals preschool benefits to be longer-lasting and substantial appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 08:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GameStop shares rise 25% in premarket trading after $933 million stock sale</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/28/gamestop-shares-rise-21percent-in-early-trade-after-completing-stock-sale.html</link><description>Shares in GameStop gained in premarket trading on Tuesday after the company announced Friday that it had made $933 million from a stock sale.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 11:17:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nordstrom Rack's Clear The Rack Sale Has $3 Tops &amp; More Up to 93% Off</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1402093/snag-up-to-93-off-at-nordstrom-racks-clear-the-rack-sale-s3-tops-s11-jeans-s78-designer-bags-more?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>We independently selected these deals and products because we love them, and we think you might like them at these prices. E! has affiliate relationships, so we may get a commission if you...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 02:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Factor Strategies Belong in Your Completion Portfolio Toolkit</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/23/factor-strategies-belong-in-your-completion-portfolio-toolkit/</link><description>Why wouldn't you include factor strategies in your completion portfolio? A review of the two commonly used approaches for managing institutional assets highlights their symbiotic nature.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 19:09:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>While American companies go quiet on climate change, Europeans keep banging the drum</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/28/american-companies-quiet-climate-change-europeans-keep-banging-drum/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Danone-CEO-GettyImages-2149552913-e1716890807828.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>One-pager: Concerns over culture wars and ESG investment backlash are stronger factors in the U.S. than Europe, which may lead to further divergence on net zero trajectories.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 11:37:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Warm Weather Hair Care</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/warm-weather-hair-care/</link><description>Outfit Details: Cala de la Cruz Dress, Emme Parsons Sandals, Saint Laurent Sunglasses One of the essential parts of summer… The post Warm Weather Hair Care appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 05:00:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stable Diffusion users and NSFW</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/azxE71m</link><description>Tags: humor , funny , stable diffusion , family guy , glenn quagmire 3207 points, 427 comments.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 12:05:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blue Jays to Unveil City Connect Uniform Thursday, Wear it Thrice for “City Week”</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/27/blue-jays-to-unveil-city-connect-uniform-thursday-wear-it-thrice-for-city-week/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Today, the Toronto Blue Jays announced some details surrounding their upcoming Nike MLB City Connect uniform release and the accompanying “City Week” promotion, which will run during their next homestand from May 31 through June 6. Things get underway on Thursday night when the Blue Jays unveil the new look</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 14:54:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MARS doubles down on India’s Infra.Market with new $50M investment</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/28/mars-doubles-down-on-indias-infra-market-with-new-50m-investment/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Infra.Market, an Indian startup that helps construction and real estate firms procure materials, has raised $50M from MARS Unicorn Fund. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 08:03:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Out of the Blue: The Rise and Fall of a Black Cop</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/23/black-police-officers-cleveland-black-shield</link><description>After Cleveland officer Vincent Montague shot a Black man, he got promoted. Then he allied with Black Lives Matter, and his life went off the rails.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Key Lime Pie Bars</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/key-lime-pie-bars/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key lime pie bars are classic key lime pie flavors baked into delightful little bars. They have a buttery graham…</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Diddy's Sean John Frames Pulled From America's Best Contacts and Eyeglasses</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/27/diddy-sean-john-pull-america-best-contacts-eyeglasses-frames/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Diddy's wallet's about to take a hit ... 'cause his famed Sean John frames are out at a huge eyewear retailer while his legal troubles mount. America's Best Contacts &amp; Eyeglasses has halted sales of Diddy's company's frames, TMZ has learned ...…</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 07:10:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What’s Next in Health Care for Older Adults: Questions and Answers With John Whyte, MD</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/blog-aging-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>As WebMD’s chief medical officer, John Whyte, MD, is in a unique position to see both the current state of medical care for America’s older adults and the way things are trending for the future. We asked him to share his insight on a few topics, along with a bit of advice.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:29:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Easy Low-Light Indoor Plants</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/easy-low-light-indoor-plants/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>I used to think every houseplant needed a sunny corner or bright windowsill to thrive. But it turns out many of our favorite go-to houseplants do just fine in shady corners and low-light locations. So before you write off your house as too dark to sustain plant life, check out this list of the best indoor plants for low light. You might be surprised at how many good options there are! Our upstairs family room is the brightest room we’ve ever owned thanks to big unobstructed windows on all 4 sides. But most of our indoor plants live downstairs, where we get far less natural light. Luckily, that hasn’t stopped us from growing our collection of happy healthy houseplants. 9 Houseplants That Don’t Need A Lot Of Light Here are our favorite low-light indoor plants. We list a lot more info on them below, but here’s a quick list to bring on your next trip to the plant store: Snake Plant ZZ Plant Pothos Heartleaf Philodendron English Ivy Aglaonema Cast Iron Plant Monstera Parlor Palm Perhaps our favorite part of this list is that these aren’t ugly “consolation plants” that people begrudgingly buy for dark homes. Continue reading Easy Low-Light Indoor Plants at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 14:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Don’t Wait for This to Happen</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/dont-wait-for-this-to-happen/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Markets are soaring to new all-time highs, and the bears are out in full force. But don't be fooled—this bull market extends beyond the U.S. Today's chart highlights the All-Country World Index, showcasing the global market's performance. It’s at an all-time high too, proving the American bull market is not an outlier. Tune in at 3 p.m. Eastern for my live masterclass, where I'll show you how to position yourself for super performance by following corporate insiders. Don't miss this opportunity! The post Don’t Wait for This to Happen appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 15:55:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The best dog ramps for cars in 2024</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/article/best-dog-ramps-for-cars/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/10165846/HerCcreta-Dog-Ramp-for-Car-1.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Commerce , Parts and Accessories Continue reading The best dog ramps for cars in 2024 The best dog ramps for cars in 2024 originally appeared on Autoblog on Mon, 27 May 2024 12:30:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 17:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How I Live Rent-Free and Car-Free: My Journey to Zero Housing and Transportation Costs</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/how-i-live-without-housing-costs-or-transportation-costs</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>The two largest expenses for most households are housing and transportation. In fact, they account for over half of the average household budget. The BLS Survey of Consumer Expenditures found that in 2022, the average household […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 15:55:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quiz: Which Romantasy Book Should I Read First?</title><link>https://bookriot.com/romantasy-book-quiz/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Black-woman-reading-with-magenta-blouse.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>Have you read any romantasy books?</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 552</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-552/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-552</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>When you are searching for a job, you will inevitably run into unexpected scenarios. You will have questions, experience self-doubt and even feel discouraged. You’ll also experience great wins, meet wonderful people and discover new things about yourself. That’s the roller-coaster of job search. Consider Summary Sunday your resource for getting questions answered and showing […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 552 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 11:37:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fathers’ views on family and work after COVID-19 lockdowns</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/fathers-views-on-family-and-work-after-covid-19-lockdowns/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fathers-views-on-family-and-work-after-covid-19-lockdowns</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Fathers often want to be present for their children and contribute to household tasks, but they can lack opportunities and confidence; they may see themselves as “helpers” instead of parents. Australian fathers in our small study reported that they spent more time with their children during the COVID-19 lockdowns, and they […] The post Fathers’ views on family and work after COVID-19 lockdowns appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'This can no longer be justified': Anger over Rafah attack piles more pressure on Israel</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/28/international-outcry-over-rafah-attack-piles-more-pressure-on-israel-.html</link><description>Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu described the attack as a tragic error.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 10:42:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>An Honest Look at Jessica Alba and Cash Warren's Cutest Family Moments</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1402184/an-honest-look-at-jessica-alba-and-cash-warrens-cutest-moments-with-their-kids?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>Jessica Alba and Cash Warren are in good, honest company. After all, the couple—who recently celebrated their 16th wedding anniversary—have a full house with kids Honor, 15, Haven, 12, and Hayes,...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 02:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>For the Analyst: Peer Benchmarking Methods to Improve Earnings Forecasts</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/21/for-the-analyst-peer-benchmarking-methods-to-improve-earnings-forecasts/</link><description>Peer benchmarking is a vexing task for financial analysts but one that is critical for forecasting earnings. This straightforward measure can help find peers for relative performance, compensation, and valuation benchmarking.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 12:47:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Rational' monetary policies are back, says Turkey's finance chief, as he seeks to stabilize inflation-ridden economy</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/28/rational-monetary-policies-back-turkey-finance-chief-stabilize-inflation-ridden-economy/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Mehmet-Simsek-Turkey-Christopher-Pike-Bloomberg-GettyImages-2152489250-e1716887426958.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Turkey had kept interest rates low amid soaring inflation, against conventional wisdom, leading investors to desert its bond market.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 11:33:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coastal Breeze Style</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/coastal-breeze-style/</link><description>Outfit Details: EPHEMERA Bikini, Zankov Dress, Loro Piana Hat, Marni Bag, Hermes Bangles (similar here, less expensive here), Bottega Venita Sunglasses The weather has… The post Coastal Breeze Style appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 05:00:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Well damnit man</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/ary41L0</link><description>Tags: funny , wtf , random , humor , savage 4309 points, 214 comments.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 12:05:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Red Poppy Flower Patches on Baseball Jerseys Today for Memorial Day</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/27/red-poppy-flower-patches-on-baseball-jerseys-today-for-memorial-day/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Major League Baseball will once again honour those who lost their lives while serving in the United States Armed Forces with a special patch worn on player uniforms. For all MLB games played on Memorial Day, Monday, May 27, 2024, players will wear a red poppy flower patch on the</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 14:12:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cloover wants to speed solar adoption by helping installers finance new sales</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/27/cloover-wants-to-speed-solar-adoption-by-helping-installers-finance-new-sales/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Small operations can lose customers by not offering financing, something the Berlin-based startup wants to change. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Marshall Project Wins Prestigious Robert F. Kennedy Journalism Award for Criminal Justice</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/21/marshall-project-rfk-award</link><description>The award recognizes our 2023 investigation exposing lax prison discipline for abusive guards in New York state prisons.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Salmon Marinade</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/salmon-marinade/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>A great salmon marinade makes your fish flavorful, tender, and juicy! This recipe gives each filet the perfect balance of…</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sean Kingston's Mom Bails Out of Jail After Fraud, Theft Arrest</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/27/sean-kingston-mom-janice-turner-bond-bail-jail-release-theft-fraud-arrest-home-raid/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Sean Kingston's mother is breathing fresh Florida air again -- after spending 4 days behind bars, she's bailed out following her arrest in the raid at Sean's house. Janice Turner got busted a few hours before Sean during the Broward County…</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 07:10:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Get the Care You Need in a COVID-19 World</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/covid-senior-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>What to expect at the doctor’s office, hospitals, and long-term care facilities, the future of telemedicine, and how to get the best care during COVID-19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 19:50:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/how-to-remove-wallpaper/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Wallpaper has made a big comeback as a trendy home design choice. But despite its resurgence, there are still plenty of us dealing with dingy, dated, or downright ugly old wallpaper we don’t want. In our old home, we had to remove wallpaper in so many rooms: the kitchen, the dining room, the foyer, and two different bathrooms! As we traveled from room to room removing wallpaper, we tested 4 different methods, and today we’ll share what we learned. Removing wallpaper doesn’t require special tools or lots of money. It’s a totally doable project for any homeowner. However, it can be a tedious process that can take elbow grease and patience, depending on the size of your room and the stubbornness of your wallpaper. But having removed several rooms worth of decades-old wallpaper, we can confidently say it’s worth the effort! You can also check out more before and afters of our once-wallpapered rooms. Continue reading How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:21:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Data-Backed Glimpse of the Market’s Future</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/a-data-backed-glimpse-of-the-markets-future/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>The bears keep insisting this bull market can't last, but let's dive into the data. The S&amp;P 500 has surged about 48% since its October 2022 lows. Historically, the average gain two years in is 57%, suggesting even more upside by October 2024. Ignore the naysayers and focus on the facts. Join me at 11 a.m. ET for a live masterclass where I'll show you how to align with top corporate insiders. Learn their winning strategies and spot a hot insider opportunity. Don't miss out—secure your spot now! The post A Data-Backed Glimpse of the Market’s Future appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Peugeot family faces rare revolt by shareholders</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/27/peugeot-family-faces-rare-revolt-by-shareholders/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/23161443/robert_peugeot__director_of_the_board_of_french_carmaker_psa_peugeot_citroen__attends_a_news_conference_in_paris.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Earnings/Financials , Peugeot Continue reading Peugeot family faces rare revolt by shareholders Peugeot family faces rare revolt by shareholders originally appeared on Autoblog on Mon, 27 May 2024 11:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Massive Commercial to Residential Conversion is Taking Shape Nationwide—Here’s What Investors Should Know</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/commercial-spaces-are-being-converted-into-151k-residential-apartments-nationwide-in-2024</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>From the boardroom to the bedroom, faced with empty offices as remote employment continues to starve cities of workers, a massive nationwide repurposing is underway to transform workplaces into residential […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 15:16:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Most Popular Shows and Movies on Netflix are Adapted From Books</title><link>https://bookriot.com/most-popular-shows-on-netflix-2023/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/netflix-one-piece-poster.jpeg.optimal.jpeg</image_url><description>Have you watched either of these?</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 21:16:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=signs-your-coworker-is-threatened-by-you</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>While a little competition in the workplace might help bring out the best in everyone involved, an atmosphere rooted in envy, fear, or jealousy can do the exact opposite. This post will help you recognize signs that your coworker is threatened by you, and help you navigate the situation. 1. They Don’t Want You Involved […] The post 10 Clear Signs Your Coworker Is Threatened By You appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:07:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Strong Latine Identity Supports U.S. Latine Children’s Well-Being</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/a-strong-latine-identity-supports-u-s-latine-childrens-well-being/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=a-strong-latine-identity-supports-u-s-latine-childrens-well-being</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key Takeaways for caregivers Children tend to have better health and well-being when they have a strong ethnic identity (affinity and adoption of ethnicity-based self-concept). A traditional Latine cultural value (familismo) that emphasizes family bonds is also associated with better developmental outcomes. Caregivers can support the development of U.S. Latine children (and possibly other children […] The post A Strong Latine Identity Supports U.S. Latine Children’s Well-Being appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 03:03:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tuesday's analyst calls: Cruise stock gets an upgrade, regional bank to rally 30%</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/28/analyst-calls-all-the-market-moving-wall-street-chatter-from-tuesday.html</link><description>A major cruise line operator and a bank in the Midwest were among the stocks being talked about by analysts on Tuesday.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 10:40:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hidden Walmart Fashion Finds TikTok Convinced Me To Buy</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1402157/hidden-walmart-fashion-finds-tiktok-convinced-me-buy?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>We independently selected these deals and products because we love them, and we think you might like them at these prices. E! has affiliate relationships, so we may get a commission if you...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Building LLMs in the Open-Source Community: A Call to Action for Investment Professionals</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/20/building-llms-in-the-open-source-community-a-call-to-action-for-investment-professionals/</link><description>Large language models like ChatGPT are changing the way we think about investing and reshaping roles in the investment profession.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 16:26:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>American company tells Mexico president that his $385m offer to buy its Caribbean property for ecotourism 'substantially undervalues' its crocodile-filled quarries</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/28/vulcan-materials-mexico-president-amlo-385m-offer-caribbean-property-undervalues-crocodile-quarries/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/AP24148663080590-e1716891186418.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Mexican President Andrés Manuel López Obrador has threatened to expropriate the property, claiming the pits it has dug to extract crushed limestone have damaged the area's fragile system of underground rivers and caves.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 11:22:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Colors Of The Sea</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/colors-of-the-sea/</link><description>Outfit Details: Show Me Your Mumu Coverup (also similar here), Good American Swimsuit, Miu Miu Sandals, Valentino Hat, Prada Sunglasses, Hanna Andersson Dress, Teva Sandals &amp; Stella Kids… The post Colors Of The Sea appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 05:00:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Feminist's will be furious</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/ae90N3W</link><description>Tags: women , funny , meme , men 8580 points, 761 comments.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 12:05:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Our Chat with Cards’ President Bill DeWitt III About New City Connect Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/25/our-chat-with-cards-president-bill-dewitt-iii-about-new-city-connect-uniforms/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The St. Louis Cardinals brand new Nike MLB City Connect uniforms will be making their on-field début this afternoon. The red jerseys with “The Lou” scripted across the chest, inspired by the hit song from Nelly, were unveiled on Monday to an overall positive reaction from fans and media alike.</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 17:17:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani looks to battle Reliance, Walmart in India’s e-commerce, payments race, report says</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/27/adani-ecommerce-payments-india/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>India's Adani Group is in discussions to venture into digital payments and e-commerce, according to a report. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 05:45:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Police Tactics at Some Pro-Palestine Protests Ignore Past Lessons</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/18/police-israel-palestine-campus-protests</link><description>While some universities have sought peaceful approaches, others have used aggressive policing that bucks research from the protests following George Floyd’s murder.</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>John Wayne Casserole</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/john-wayne-casserole/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>This delicious John Wayne Casserole is Mexican comfort food at its finest! Layers of seasoned ground beef, creamy cheddar cheese…</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chris Brown's Daughter Royalty Celebrates 10th Birthday</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/27/chris-brown-daughter-rodeo-royalty-birthday-party-nia/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Chris Brown's little girl ain't so little anymore -- his daughter Royalty's celebrating her 10th birthday today, and it looks like she's a big Beyoncé fan! Chris and Royalty were super close and in the pics her mom, Nia Guzman, posted from the…</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 07:10:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Personal Shopper: A Savvy Black Entrepreneur Guides You to Eczema-Friendly Clothes, Creams, Cosmetics, and More</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/savvy-black-entrepreneur-guides-eczema-friendly-clothes-creams-cosmetics?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>A savvy black entrepreneur guides you on an eczema-friendly shopping spree.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:54:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aglaonema Plant – Complete Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/aglaonema-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Aglaonema, also called the Chinese Evergreen Plant, is an easy-care houseplant that lives happily in many lighting conditions – even a dark corner of our daughter’s room. There are dozens of different Aglaonema varieties, most with large tropical foliage and colors ranging from silvery-green, red, and even vibrant pink. They’re also tough to kill, so they’re a great option for forgetful plant owners or anyone looking for an easy win in the plant department. These truly have been very low maintenance for us. We purchased our two Aglaonemas (pronounced ag-lee-oh-neem-ah ) to put atop our daughter’s closet. It’s sometimes hard to distinguish different varieties, but we believe that’s an Aglaonema Silver (right) and either a Candy Cane or Princess Silver Queen (left). Aglaonema Quick Facts Here’s what you need to know about your Aglaonema at a glance: Latin name : Aglaonema is the genus under which there are 21 recognized species . Continue reading Aglaonema Plant – Complete Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:47:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Profit from the Market’s Appetite</title><link>https://stocksurgedaily.com/profit-from-the-markets-appetite/</link><image_url>https://stocksurgedaily.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/money.svg</image_url><description>Hey, Ross here. Last week showed us that even after a brief slowdown, the markets are still on an upward trajectory—and it's clear from today's Bitcoin chart that we're just getting started. The bull flag pattern I highlighted is unfolding right before our eyes, with Bitcoin surging nearly 10% in just four days. This movement isn't just about Bitcoin; it reflects a broader market craving for risk, and today, I'll show you how to leverage this appetite to your advantage. Ready to join the insiders who are already capitalizing on this trend? Join me tomorrow at 11 a.m. Eastern for a can’t-miss masterclass. The post Profit from the Market’s Appetite appeared first on Stock Surge Daily .</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 14:46:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Genesis Neolun concept reportedly becoming GV90 electric SUV</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/05/27/genesis-neolun-concept-reportedly-becoming-gv90-electric-suv/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1062x597/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/05/22105425/genesis_neolun_concept.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Green , Genesis , Crossover , SUV , Concept Cars , Electric , Future Vehicles , Luxury , Special and Limited Editions Continue reading Genesis Neolun concept reportedly becoming GV90 electric SUV Genesis Neolun concept reportedly becoming GV90 electric SUV originally appeared on Autoblog on Mon, 27 May 2024 10:30:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>9 Vital Questions to Ask When Vetting Your Real Estate Investing Team</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/questions-to-ask-when-vetting-your-real-estate-investing-team</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Asking these questions will help you find team members who align with your investment goals.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Riot’s Deals of the Day for May 26, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/book-riots-deals-of-the-day-for-may-26-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/deals-052624.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>A fresh take on Peter Pan, a book-saving cat, a jungle expedition gone wrong, and more of today's best book deals.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 551</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-551/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-551</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Job search requires writing and marketing skills. It also requires strong verbal communication. If these skills are not part of your normal work function, you’ll want some help. That’s what this week’s Summary Sunday is all about. There’s no doubt that LinkedIn is one of THE most powerful tools in your career toolbox. It contains […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 551 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 11:37:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Children caught between highly conflicted divorced parents at greater risk of mental health problems</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/children-caught-between-conflicted-divorced-parents/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=children-caught-between-conflicted-divorced-parents</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Interparental conflict after divorce escalates the risk of mental health problems in children and adolescents. Elevated levels of conflict between parents can also induce fear and worry in children about their future and whether they will be adequately taken care of. In turn, a greater fear of abandonment puts children at […] The post Children caught between highly conflicted divorced parents at greater risk of mental health problems appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 08:59:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fed's Kashkari wants to see 'many more months' of positive inflation data before a rate cut</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/05/28/feds-kashkari-wants-to-see-many-more-months-of-positive-inflation-data-before-a-rate-cut.html</link><description>The Federal Reserve should wait for significant progress on inflation before cutting rates, Minneapolis Federal Reserve President Neel Kashkari said Tuesday.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 08:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Jennifer Love Hewitt Watches Pimple Popping Videos Before Filming</title><link>https://www.eonline.com/news/1402091/why-jennifer-love-hewitt-watches-pimple-popping-videos-before-filming-difficult-scenes?cmpid=rss-syndicate-genericrss-us-top_stories</link><image_url>https://akns-images.eonline.com/eol_images/Entire_Site/2018223/rs_125x40-180323122205-EGoogleNews.png</image_url><description>Jennifer Love Hewitt will go to great lengths to, uh, extract some real emotion. Before filming her more emotional scenes, "I like to watch pimple popping videos," the 9-1-1 star admitted to E!...</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sustainability Reporting: Navigating Assurance Practices</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/17/sustainability-reporting-navigating-assurance-practices/</link><description>Don't be lulled into a false sense of security by the word "assurance" when evaluating sustainability reports. Assurance practices vary, and investors would be wise to learn more about the different levels of coverage.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 17:57:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wisconsin law that banned collective bargaining for most public employees back in court</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/28/wisconsin-law-ban-collective-bargaining-most-public-employeescourt-unions-sue/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/AP24142556347932-e1716890809474.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The court is controlled 4-3 by liberals, a flip from when it upheld the law a decade ago under 5-2 conservative control.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 11:09:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Walmart Summer Fashion Under $50</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/05/walmart-summer-fashion-under-50/</link><description>Thank you to Walmart for sponsoring this post. I have a passion for finding beautiful fashion pieces for women and… The post Walmart Summer Fashion Under $50 appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 05:00:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>White</title><link>http://9gag.com/gag/a9yLbD6</link><description>Tags: random , wholesome , girl , wtf , meme 9773 points, 312 comments.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 12:05:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ligue 1’s Lille OSC Put Unique Spin on Traditional Chevron for 2024-25 Home Kits</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/24/ligue-1s-lille-osc-put-unique-spin-on-traditional-chevron-for-2024-25-home-kits/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Club's traditional chevron, which they've used in some form since the 1940s, appears on new kits made up of several tonal mini-chevrons</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 22:01:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ledger starts shipping its high-end hardware crypto wallet</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/05/27/ledger-starts-shipping-its-high-end-hardware-crypto-wallet/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Ledger, a French startup mostly known for its secure crypto hardware wallets, has started shipping new wallets nearly 18 months after announcing the latest Ledger Stax devices. The updated wallet features an E-Ink display and has been designed in partnership with Tony Fadell, one of the main designers behind the iPod. E-Ink technology is generally […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 05:45:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Susan Chira to Step Down as The Marshall Project’s Editor-in-Chief in January</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/05/16/susan-chira-eic-step-down</link><description>Under her stewardship, the news nonprofit more than doubled in size, opened local newsrooms and won its second Pulitzer Prize.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Memorial Day Menu Plan</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/memorial-day-menu-plan/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>This Memorial Day Menu Plan makes holiday planning a breeze! I’ve even included a shopping list, so you can spend…</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Britney Spears Claims Someone Stole All Her Jewelry</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/27/britney-spears-claim-jewelry-stolen-instagram-video-sherriff-police-report-theft/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Britney Spears says she's been the victim of theft ... telling her millions of Instagram followers someone stole all her jewelry -- but, she hasn't filed a police report yet. The singer-songwriter took to IG Sunday night and shared a video she took…</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 07:10:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Behind the Spike in Colorectal Cancer Among Young Americans</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/colorectal-cancer/news/20240515/behind-the-spike-in-colorectal-cancer-cases?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Colorectal cancer cases increased a whopping 333% among 15- to 19-year-olds and 185% among 20- to 24-year-olds from 1999 to 2020.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:59:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Corn Plant – Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/corn-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Corn plants ( Dracaena fragrans ) are popular low-maintenance houseplants you’ve probably seen at the nursery, home improvement store, or doctor’s office. I even had one in my college dorm room! You can recognize them by their spear-shaped leaves and woody, cane-line trunks that can grow up to 6 feet tall indoors. But did you know there are several varieties of corn plants? We didn’t! Heck, we didn’t even realize some of our smaller houseplants were in the same corn plant family! Currently, we own two smaller varieties of corn plants, pictured above. The one on the left is a Dracaena Limelight ( Dracaena fragrans ‘Limelight’ ) and the taller plant is a Draecanea Dorado ( Dracaena fragrans ‘Dorado’ ). We actually have several limelights around because we love their vibrant color on shelves, tabletops, and windowsills. Corn Plant Quick Facts Latin name : Dracaena fragrans Common names : Corn plant, cornstalk plant, false palms Light : Bright, indirect light but can tolerate lower-light conditions Watering : Keep soil moist, but not soggy. Continue reading Corn Plant – Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 17:37:33 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>