<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 06:56:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Turning a “Failed” Property Into a $7K/Month Rental by Doing THIS Instead</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-421</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>A rental property that doesn’t cash flow can be a nightmare for new investors. But when the numbers no longer work, remember that not all is lost. Pivoting to another […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 07:02:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>UK probes HPE’s planned $14B Juniper Networks acquisition</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/19/uk-probes-hpes-planned-14b-juniper-networks-acquisition/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The U.K.’s Competition and Markets Authority (CMA) has announced an initial “phase 1” investigation into Hewlett Packard Enterprise’s (HPE) planned acquisition of Juniper Networks. HPE announced plans to acquire Juniper Networks back in January, a deal designed to unify their respective strengths in the networking and IT infrastructure realm, spanning servers, storage, consulting services, routing, […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 11:53:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Minneapolis Cop Who Beat Him Pleaded Guilty. He Still Fears the Department Won’t Change.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/16/police-minneapolis-beating-jaleel-stallings</link><description>Jaleel Stallings was swept up in the chaos of protests over George Floyd’s murder. The outcome changed his life.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Federal Experts Talk Bird Flu ‘What Ifs’ in WebMD Live Event</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/cold-and-flu/news/20240516/federal-experts-talk-bird-flu-what-ifs?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>WebMD brought together experts from four federal agencies to talk prevention, monitoring, and what the “what ifs” of bird flu might look like.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:50:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maximalism: The New Renter-Friendly Trend Landlords Can’t Overlook</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-974</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Want to really stand out in your market? A few renter-friendly interior design ideas can make a world of difference, elevating a run-of-the-mill property into one that attracts tenants and […]</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 07:02:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meta AI removes block on election-related queries in India while Google still applying limits</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/19/meta-ai-removes-block-on-election-related-queries-in-india-while-google-still-applying-limits/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Meta AI removes restrictions in answering election-related queries in India while Google is still restricting them. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 11:23:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>More States Restricting ‘Excited Delirium’ as Cause of Death in Police Custody</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/15/police-custody-excited-delirium-meaning</link><description>Authorities use the term to describe the condition of some people who die. But some medical organizations say it’s useless or racist pseudoscience.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What’s Next in Health Care for Older Adults: Questions and Answers With John Whyte, MD</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/blog-aging-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>As WebMD’s chief medical officer, John Whyte, MD, is in a unique position to see both the current state of medical care for America’s older adults and the way things are trending for the future. We asked him to share his insight on a few topics, along with a bit of advice.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:29:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rent Prices Are “Guaranteed” to Increase Over the Next Two Years—Here’s Why</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rent-prices-are-guaranteed-to-rise-over-the-next-two-years</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>With only 600,000 apartment units being built this year, supply will continue to be nowhere near demand.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 21:16:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Abridge became one of the most talked about healthcare AI startups</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/18/how-abridge-became-one-of-the-most-talked-about-healthcare-ai-startups/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Ask any of the health-focused VCs to name one of the top AI startups and one name comes up over and over again: a company based in Pittsburgh called Abridge. And it’s a startup that launched before OpenAI was a household name and LLMs entered the common Valley vocabulary. In 2019, Shiv Rao, a practicing […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 05:08:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Criminal Justice Journalist Wrestles With Doubts in the Jury Box</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/14/journalist-serves-on-jury-criminal-trial</link><description>A longtime journalist serving on a jury must weigh the flaws of the system against the holes in the gun and drug case he heard.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Get the Care You Need in a COVID-19 World</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/covid-senior-health-care?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>What to expect at the doctor’s office, hospitals, and long-term care facilities, the future of telemedicine, and how to get the best care during COVID-19.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 19:50:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Inflation Hedges: Top 5 Investments for a Rock-Solid Portfolio</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/secure-your-portfolio-with-these-five-inflation-proof-investments</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Consider these kinds of investments to protect yourself from the next inflationary wave, whenever it comes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 20:47:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kilimo helps farmers save water and get paid for it</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/18/kilimo-helps-farmers-save-water-and-get-paid-for-it/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Cheap irrigation has transformed many regions around the world into breadbaskets, but it also means that there can be little left for other uses. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 05:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Behind the Black Shield: The History of a Cleveland Institution</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/13/black-shield-history-police-cleveland</link><description>How one of the oldest Black policing organizations in the country shaped law enforcement in Cleveland.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Personal Shopper: A Savvy Black Entrepreneur Guides You to Eczema-Friendly Clothes, Creams, Cosmetics, and More</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/skin-problems-and-treatments/eczema/features/savvy-black-entrepreneur-guides-eczema-friendly-clothes-creams-cosmetics?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>A savvy black entrepreneur guides you on an eczema-friendly shopping spree.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:54:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Landlord’s Guide to Legally Breaking a Lease</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/can-a-landlord-break-a-lease</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Learn the valid reasons, legal process, and proactive measures for landlords to legally break a lease while minimizing risks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 19:44:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fisker failed because it wasn’t ready to be a car company</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/06/18/fisker-bankruptcy-failure-problems/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Two years ago, an employee at Fisker Inc. told me that the most pressing concern inside the EV startup was not whether its Ocean SUV would get built. Fisker was outsourcing the manufacturing of its first EV to highly respected automotive supplier Magna, after all. The startup’s November 2022 start-of-production target was aggressive, but not […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 23:02:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Serving Time for Their Abusers’ Crimes</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/13/abuse-domestic-violence-survivors-liability-prison</link><description>The Marshall Project found nearly 100 people who were punished for the actions of their abusers under little-known laws like “accomplice liability.”</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Behind the Spike in Colorectal Cancer Among Young Americans</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/colorectal-cancer/news/20240515/behind-the-spike-in-colorectal-cancer-cases?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><image_url>https://img.webmd.com/dtmcms/live/webmd/consumer_assets/site_images/logos/webmd/web/rss-webmd-logo.gif</image_url><description>Colorectal cancer cases increased a whopping 333% among 15- to 19-year-olds and 185% among 20- to 24-year-olds from 1999 to 2020.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:59:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>