<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 14:06:24 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Chelsea Hope to Burn Bright in New Home Kit – Plus Other Recent European Kit Launches</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/16/chelsea-hope-to-burn-bright-in-new-home-kit-plus-other-recent-european-kit-launches/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Other clubs unveiling kits for 2024-25 include Juventus, Brighton &amp; Hove Albion, Nottingham Forest, U.S. Lecce, Como 1907, Stade Brestois 29, Real Sociedad, Mallorca, Leganés</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 18:38:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amber Rose Rocks the House at RNC, Explains Backstory to Trump Support</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/15/amber-rose-speaks-republican-national-convention-rnc-trump/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Amber Rose showed up at the Republican National Convention to kick off a week's worth of speeches -- proving to be a powerful speaker and explaining why she backs Donald Trump. The model and social media influencer -- who once famously dated Kanye…</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 14:06:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MLS Reaches Into Its Past For Retro-Inspired Third Kits For Five Clubs</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/16/mls-reaches-into-its-past-for-retro-inspired-third-kits-for-five-clubs/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>MLS x Adidas Archive Collection includes jerseys, jackets and sneakers for Inter Miami, LA Galaxy, LAFC, Portland Timbers and Sporting Kansas City</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 17:14:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Video Shows What Happened to Donald Trump's Shoes During Assassination Attempt</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/16/donald-trump-shoes-secret-service-assassination-attempt-shooting/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>The mystery behind Donald Trump's shoes after he was nearly assassinated has now come into full focus -- thanks to a new video that surfaced. WBEN News in Buffalo, New York, obtained the 10-second clip shot from a different angle behind the stage…</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 14:06:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Las Vegas Raiders Unveil 65th Season Logo</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/15/las-vegas-raiders-unveil-65th-season-logo/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Las Vegas Raiders will celebrate their 65th season this year with a commemorative logo, which the franchise unveiled on Monday afternoon.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 21:45:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jaylen Brown Watches Bronny James, Appears To Say LeBron's Son Is Not 'A Pro'</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/16/jaylen-brown-watches-bronny-james-appears-lebrons-son-not-a-pro/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Jaylen Brown got an up-close view of Bronny James on Monday night ... and the Celtics star's first assessment of LeBron's son did not appear to be a glowing one. The NBA Finals MVP had courtside seats for Bronny's Summer League matchup against…</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 14:06:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Look At Every Uniform In EA Sports’ College Football 25 Video Game</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/15/a-look-at-every-uniform-in-ea-sports-college-football-25-video-game/college/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>YouTuber Eric Rayweather shared a 43-minute video that shows every team's uniform combination in the beta version of College Football 25.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 11:05:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump's Doctor Says Part of His Ear Got Blown Off, No Surgery Needed</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/16/trump-doctor-ronny-jackson-ear-blown-off-shot-no-surgery-needed-bandage/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Donald Trump's doctor says the ex-Prez had a good part of his ear blown clean off when he got shot -- but surprisingly, he insists DT ain't gonna need to go under the knife to fix it. Dr. Ronny Jackson -- who was the White House physician under the…</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 14:06:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Designing the 2024 MLB All-Star Game Logos</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/15/designing-the-2024-mlb-all-star-game-logos/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Baseball’s brightest stars have gathered in the Lone Star State for the annual Major League Baseball All-Star Game, hosted by the Texas Rangers in Arlington. Every year, alongside the big game, the Home Run Derby, the fan events, and all the other fun that comes with hosting the Mid-Summer Classic,</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 05:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jack Black Cancels Tour After Tenacious D Bandmate Makes Trump Shooting Quip</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/16/jack-black-donald-trump-tenacious-d-shooter-comment-concert-cancelled/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Jack Black has pulled the plug on his tour after his Tenacious D bandmate made a birthday wish ... grousing that the would-be-assassin didn't take out Donald Trump. Jack says he was blindsided by Kyle Gass' remark on the heels of the shooting. KG…</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 14:06:24 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>