<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 01:07:08 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>West Virginia Mountaineers Reveal Coal Mining-Inspired Alternate Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/03/west-virginia-mountaineers-reveal-coal-mining-inspired-alternate-uniforms/college/</link><description>On Thursday, just days after it unveiled an entirely new uniform set, West Virginia revealed a black alternate design that pays homage to the state's coal mining history.</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 02:25:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kyle Richards No Longer Using Mauricio Umansky’s Last Name Online</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/03/kyle-richards-drops-last-name-mauricio-umansky/</link><description>Kyle Richards is distancing herself from estranged husband Mauricio Umansky in an whole new way -- she's dropped his last name from at least one social media profile. "The Real Housewives of Beverly Hills" star's Instagram account got a noticeable…</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 01:07:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MLB, Nike Announces Return of Larger Player Names, Fix to Grey Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/03/mlb-nike-announces-return-of-larger-player-names-fix-to-grey-uniforms/baseball/</link><description>Major League Baseball and Nike today announced they will fix some of the problems with the new uniforms introduced for the 2024 season. The decision follows feedback from players and clubs and months of fan and media complaints, which pointed to several areas needing improvement. Starting in the 2025 season,</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 20:58:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Khloe Kardashian Hints She Might Be Open to Dating Women</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/03/khloe-kardashian-hints-open-dating-women-lesbian/</link><description>Khloe Kardashian seems open to dipping her toe into the lady pond ... saying as much on social media this week -- or at the very least, strongly suggesting it. The reality TV star hopped on X this week to let folks know she's keeping her options…</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 01:07:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nats, Orioles to Play in MLB’s First-Ever All-City Connect Uniform Game</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/03/nats-orioles-to-play-in-mlbs-first-ever-all-city-connect-uniform-game/baseball/</link><description>For the first time in Major League Baseball history, two teams will wear their Nike MLB City Connect uniforms in the same game. This morning, the Washington Nationals announced they will don their cherry blossom-themed City Connect uniforms when they host the Baltimore Orioles on Tuesday, May 7 for the</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 15:40:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rachel Zegler Feared for Her Safety in Public Amid 'Snow White' Backlash</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/03/rachel-zegler-feared-safety-hardest-year-life-birthday-snow-white-backlash/</link><description>Rachel Zegler just hit the big 2-3 this week -- and while she's looking forward to a new year of life, she notes age 22 was brutal for her ... and a big reason seems to be 'Snow White.' The actress posted some telling messages to her Instagram…</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 01:07:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cincinnati Bengals Reveal Updated Turf Design</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/02/cincinnati-bengals-reveal-updated-turf-design/football/</link><description>The Cincinnati Bengals are in the process of installing new FieldTurf at Paycor Stadium and will have an updated design as a result.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 22:33:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lakers Fire Darvin Ham After Two Seasons</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/03/lakers-fire-darvin-ham-two-seasons/</link><description>Darvin Ham is out of the job -- the Los Angeles Lakers just fired their head coach after two seasons on Friday ... days after the Purple and Gold were booted from the playoffs in the first round. Rumors of a change on the bench started right after…</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 01:07:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Liverpool FC Pays Homage to Treble-Winning 1984 Squad With 2024-25 Home Kit</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/05/02/liverpool-fc-pays-homage-to-treble-winning-1984-squad-with-2024-25-home-kit/soccer/</link><description>Front and back of shirt feature yellow pinstripe pattern that spells out "YWNA" for club motto, "You'll Never Walk Alone"</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:19:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gypsy Rose Rides TMZ Tour Bus, Dines at Lisa Vanderpump's Restaurant</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/05/03/gypsy-rose-tmz-tour-bus-lisa-vanderpump-restaurant-sur-los-angeles/</link><description>Gypsy Rose Blanchard's brief trip to Los Angeles this week ended up chock-full of memories -- and it's because she had the ultimate tourist experience ... with some help from TMZ! GRB hopped on the TMZ Celebrity Tour Thursday ... and, she was…</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 01:07:08 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>