<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 06:50:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>What Do Experts Really Know? Embracing the Unknown</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/29/what-do-experts-really-know-embracing-the-unknown/</link><description>Confidence is a necessary but insufficient factor in long-term investing success. Raising the metaknowledge quotient of the investment team can help protect against the surprises that lurk in left-tail events and remain unknown, until they’re known.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 16:08:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Senate set to pass internet safety bill pushed by parents of kids who died by suicide</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/07/30/senate-internet-safety-bill-pushed-parents-kids-died-by-suicide/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/GettyImages-494189202-e1722334914579.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>It would be the first major effort by Congress in decades to hold tech companies more accountable for the harm that they cause.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 11:24:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Investment Manager Selection Is Hotting Up. Are You Ready for the Tough Questions?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/25/investment-manager-selection-is-hotting-up-are-you-ready-for-the-tough-questions/</link><description>Investment managers are being caught off guard by tougher questions from an increasingly sophisticated allocator market. Are you prepared for your next beauty parade?</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 03:17:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>California man fights state’s largest wildfire to within 70 feet of his house one month after insurance company drops his coverage</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/07/30/california-man-fights-wildfire-70-feet-house-insurance-company-drops-coverage/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/AP24211186454077-e1722333114864.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Ron Ward had lost insurance coverage as companies increasingly drop California homeowners due to the growing risk of wildfires in the state, in part due to hotter weather and arid conditions caused by climate change.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 10:54:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Measuring Corporate Impact: The Gold Is in the Details</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/24/measuring-corporate-impact-the-gold-is-in-the-details/</link><description>Do the products and services of the companies you invest in create negative or positive material outcomes?</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 12:09:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>White House says there’s no need to restrict ‘open source’ AI—for now at least</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/07/30/white-house-no-need-restrict-open-source-ai-for-now/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/GettyImages-1765585110-e1722331989331.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>“We recognize the importance of open systems," said Alan Davidson, an assistant secretary of the U.S. Commerce Department.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 10:35:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is Widespread Crypto Adoption Inevitable?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/22/is-widespread-crypto-adoption-inevitable/</link><description>New technologies always face resistance, but demographic shifts imply there is a fierce tailwind behind crypto adoption, politically, economically, and financially.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 12:38:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump says he ‘can also make a case for not’ debating Kamala Harris</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/07/30/donald-trump-make-case-for-not-debating-kamala-harris/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/AP24210092673298-e1722331552229.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Trump, in an interview with Fox News Channel that aired Monday night, was pressed several times about committing to debating Harris before giving a squishier answer than he had in recent days.</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 10:28:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: Shocks, Crises, and False Alarms</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/07/19/book-review-shocks-crises-and-false-alarms/</link><description>Carlsson-Szlezak and Swartz attempt to add fresh thinking on framing macro shocks that may often prove to be false alarms. Any general reader will obtain some key fresh insights with this work, and CFA charterholders will be offered an alternative to the conventional Wall Street approach to macro discussions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 13:06:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Johnnie Walker maker Diageo sees first sales drop since the pandemic—but Guinness and ready-made cocktails save the day</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/07/30/johnnie-walker-don-julio-maker-diageo-first-sales-drop-since-pandemic-guinness-women-ready-made-cocktails/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/GettyImages-2153682289-e1722329372754.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Diageo’s CEO Debra Crew said that despite pockets of weakness, the “merit of our portfolio is that we really do have very broad options for the consumer.”</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 10:22:42 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>