<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 12:07:10 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Brooklyn Nets Subtly Update Logos, Introduce New Secondary Mark For 2024-25 Season</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/07/brooklyn-nets-subtly-update-logos-introduce-new-secondary-mark-for-2024-25-season/basketball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Brooklyn Nets have made several changes to their logo set for the 2024-25 season, including introducing a new secondary logo that depicts a stylized net.</description><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 19:12:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Steve Carell's 'Despicable Me 4' Smashes July 4th Weekend Box Office</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/07/despicable-me-4-steve-carell-smash-holiday-fourth-july-box-office/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Steve Carell might not be able to steal the moon ... but, his new movie's off to such a great start, the producers may be able to buy it when all is said and done. "Despicable Me 4" -- once again starring Carell as lovable villain-turned-father Gru…</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 12:07:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PSG Pay Homage to Eiffel Tower With New Away Kit – Plus More European Kit Launches</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/05/psg-pay-homage-to-eiffel-tower-with-new-away-kit-plus-more-european-kit-launches/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Other clubs unveiling 2024-25 kits include Napoli, Wolves, West Ham, Stade de Reims, Mallorca, Real Betis, Villarreal, Bochum, Stuttgart, Mainz 05 and Union Berlin</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 20:20:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Margot Robbie Reportedly Pregnant with First Child</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/07/margot-robbie-pregnant-first-child-tom-ackerley/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Margot Robbie's about to give birth to her own little Barbie or Ken ... 'cause the megastar's pregnant according to reports! The actress and her husband Tom Ackerley are expecting their first child together, PEOPLE reported Sunday ... ending a…</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 12:07:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Look at the New NHL Practice Jersey Design</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/04/a-look-at-the-new-nhl-practice-jersey-design/hockey-2/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Thanks to the Utah Hockey Club, we got ourselves a look at the new NHL practice jersey design. With the switch from Adidas to Fanatics for 2024-25, we knew there’d be some changes to the on-ice NHL uniform. We’ve already seen that each team’s jersey will now include the Fanatics</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 22:20:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Congressman Adam Schiff Says Biden's Age is Keeping Him From Beating Trump</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/07/adam-schiff-congressman-job-biden-donald-trump-age-kamala-harris/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Congressman Adam Schiff -- a prominent Democrat has added his voice to the growing number questioning Joe Biden's mental fitness. The California congressman -- who's currently running for Senate -- stopped by "Meet the Press" Sunday morning to…</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 12:07:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MLB Teams Wearing USA-Themed Caps Today for Fourth of July</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/04/mlb-teams-wearing-usa-themed-caps-today-for-fourth-of-july/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>All 30 Major League Baseball teams will wear stars-and-stripes-themed caps on-field during today’s games in honour of Independence Day in the United States. This year, all 30 clubs will wear a cream-coloured crown, with teams again having the option of a red or navy blue visor and button. One more</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 16:34:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Porn Star Jesse Jane Cause of Death Revealed</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/07/porn-star-jesse-jane-cause-death-drug-overdose-fentanyl/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Porn star Jesse Jane's official cause of death is an overdose ... TMZ has confirmed. TMZ has learned Jesse died of an accidental fentanyl and cocaine overdose according to the Oklahoma City Medical Examiner's office. We broke the story back in…</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 12:07:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2024 MLB All-Star Game Uniforms Revealed</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/03/2024-mlb-all-star-game-uniforms-revealed/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Major League Baseball has officially unveiled the uniforms their best players will wear when they take the field at Globe Life Field in Arlington later this month. The uniforms, as you’d expect, incorporate some of that Texas style, with an Old West style typeface across the chest and again in</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 02:02:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Billie Eilish Holds Lit Firework in Bikini for Fourth of July Weekend</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/07/billie-eilish-busty-display-bikini-pic-fourth-of-july/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Billie Eilish lit up the internet with her recent post ... posting a pic of herself holding a lit firework -- with just a bikini and towel covering her up! The singer-songwriter posted the photo Saturday as part of a longer photo series showing her…</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 12:07:10 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>