<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 06:39:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>A Slew of New Rental Laws Is Determining Who Landlords Can Rent To</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/slew-of-landlord-laws-are-going-to-determine-who-landlords-can-rent-to</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>New laws in California, New York, and elsewhere could eliminate the former red flags that landlords may have used to disqualify potential renters.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 20:47:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>India clings to cheap feature phones as brands struggle to tap new smartphone buyers</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/13/india-clings-to-cheap-feature-phones-as-brands-struggle-to-tap-new-smartphone-buyers/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>India is struggling to get new smartphone buyers, as millions of Indians don’t go for an upgrade and continue to be on feature phones. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 03:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How a Supreme Court Ruling Could Affect a Case Involving Police Abuse of Youth</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/13/supreme-court-bankruptcy-sackler-boy-scouts</link><description>Another court must now decide how the landmark ruling will impact the Boy Scouts abuse settlement, which involves victims of police sexual abuse.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Top 5 Alternative Investments for Real Estate Investors in 2024</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/best-alternative-investments-in-2024</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Good real estate investors know that diversification is important. These five alternative investments are great ways to diversify.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 18:28:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meet the soft robots that can amputate limbs and fuse with other robots</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/13/meet-the-soft-robots-that-can-amputate-limbs-and-fuse-with-other-robots/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Roboticists at The Faboratory at Yale University have developed a way for soft robots to replicate some of the more unsettling things that animals and insects can accomplish — say, a reptile self-amputating a limb, or ants building bridges by temporarily fusing their bodies. In one demo video, we see a soft quadruped robot crawling […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 22:19:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jackson, Mississippi, Wants Curfew Centers to Cut Crime. Here’s What Other Cities Learned.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/09/jackson-mississippi-youth-curfew-centers</link><description>After a teen’s murder, city officials hope a curfew and youth centers will get kids off the street. Young people are skeptical.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 11:00:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rookie Reply: Build Your Portfolio OR Pay Off Debt &amp; Tenant Conflict 101</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-431</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Buying a house is a HUGE decision, whether you’re an experienced investor or a first-time homebuyer. The last thing you want is to get in over your head with a […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 07:02:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>If you’re an AT&amp;T customer, your data has likely been stolen</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/13/if-youre-an-att-customer-your-data-has-likely-been-stolen/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>This week, AT&amp;T confirmed it will begin notifying around 110 million AT&amp;T customers about a data breach that allowed cybercriminals to steal the phone records of “nearly all” of its customers. The stolen data contains phone numbers and AT&amp;T records of calls and text messages during a six-month period in 2022, the company says. If […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 21:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Love Beyond Bars: Miguel and Silvia</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/05/photo-essay-wrongful-conviction-love-story</link><description>While Miguel Solorio did 25 years for a crime he didn’t commit, his wife, Silvia, was right by his side. Here’s their California love story in pictures.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BiggerNews: Rate Cut Chances Increase as New “Affordable” Markets Emerge</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-987</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Will the new jobs report finally prompt the Fed to cut rates, leading to you scoring a lower mortgage rate? With multifamily rents still falling, should we fear a nosediving […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 07:02:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Here’s the full list of 28 US AI startups that have raised $100M or more in 2024</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/13/heres-the-full-list-of-28-us-ai-startups-that-have-raised-100m-or-more-in-2024/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>In the first half of 2024 alone, more than $35.5 billion was invested into AI startups globally. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Crime Rates and the 2024 Election: What You Need to Know</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/27/trump-and-biden-spar-over-crime-rates-ahead-of-their-debate-what-do-we-really-know</link><description>As crime data again becomes a flashpoint in the presidential campaign, experts push for better national statistics.</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fat FI by 23: Building a 7-Figure Income &amp; 8-Figure Portfolio in 3 Years</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-545</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Fat FI and generational wealth in THREE years?! How is that possible? The sooner you forge good money habits, the sooner YOU can achieve your FI goal. Today’s guest wanted […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 07:01:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Whistleblowers accuse OpenAI of ‘illegally restrictive’ NDAs</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/13/whistleblowers-accuse-openai-of-illegally-restrictive-ndas/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Whistleblowers have accused OpenAI of placing illegal restrictions on how employees can communicate with government regulators, according to a letter obtained by The Washington Post. Lawyers representing anonymous whistleblowers sent the letter to Securities and Exchange Commission Chair Gary Gensler. The letter refers to a separate, formal complaint asking the SEC to investigate OpenAI’s severance, […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 18:37:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Death Row Prisoner’s Parting Interview</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/06/24/texas-death-row-prisoner-final-interview</link><description>Days before his scheduled execution in Texas, Ramiro Gonzales speaks on faith, legacy — and apologizing to the family of his victim, Bridget Townsend.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>