<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 06:48:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>From $17K/Year Teacher Salary to Financial Freedom with Repeatable Rentals</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-1003</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>How does a teacher with a LOW salary achieve financial freedom, let alone invest in real estate? Surprisingly, it’s not as hard as you think, and if you repeat the […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 10:00:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Conduit’s cross-border payments expand from LatAm into Africa with $6M round</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/12/conduits-cross-border-payments-expand-from-latam-into-africa-with-6m-round/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>Cross-border payments for businesses in emerging markets remain significantly untapped, despite small to large businesses using banks and legacy fintechs to transact trillions of dollars in transaction volume annually. A report by Airwallex forecasts that the value of cross-border payments will grow by 60%, reaching $250 trillion by 2027. Between 2018 and 2022, the value […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 10:58:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘Deliberate Indifference’: Court Rulings Challenge Extreme Heat Conditions in Prisons</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/10/texas-heat-louisiana-prison</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>“If it’s 103 outside, it may be 107 to -8 inside of your cell,” said a man who worked in the fields while imprisoned in Texas.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Short-Term Rental Demand Returns, So Why Are Hosts Making Less?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-242</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>A couple of years ago, everyone was expecting an “Airbnbust,” where short-term rental investments would sit vacant, hosts would be forced to sell, and hotels would take the reigns as […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 10:00:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharti will become BT’s biggest shareholder after buying a 25%, $4B stake from Altice</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/12/bharti-will-become-bts-biggest-shareholder-after-buying-a-25-4b-stake-from-altice/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>BT, the U.K.’s former incumbent telecoms carrier, is picking up a major new investor today as telecoms companies look for stronger footing in the rapidly-shifting technology and communications market. Bharti, the Indian tech and telecoms giant that owns Airtel, said it would purchase a 24.5% stake currently owned by Altice. Based on BT’s market cap […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 08:40:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tim Walz on Criminal Justice: 5 Things to Know</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/06/tim-walz-kamala-harris-vp-criminal-justice</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Where Minnesota Gov. Tim Walz, Vice President Kamala Harris’ running mate, stands on policing, guns, prison reform and other issues.</description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Use “Asset Management” to Build Wealth (Even with a Small Portfolio!)</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-443</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>You DON’T need to scale your real estate portfolio to start building wealth. Whether you own a single rental property or one hundred doors, the size of your portfolio isn’t […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 10:00:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elon Musk’s X targeted with nine privacy complaints after grabbing EU users’ data for training Grok</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/11/elon-musks-x-targeted-with-eight-privacy-complaints-after-grabbing-eu-users-data-for-training-grok/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>X, the social media platform owned by Elon Musk, has been targeted with a series of privacy complaints after it helped itself to the data of users in the European Union for training AI models without asking people’s consent. Late last month an eagle-eyed social media user spotted a setting indicating that X had quietly […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>They Exposed Police Misconduct. Now They’re Paying a Steep Price.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/03/police-congress-corruption-whistleblower</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Whistleblower laws have advanced in public and private sectors, but protections for police who report illegal or unethical behavior lag far behind.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are EV Chargers the Next Rent-Increasing Amenity?</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/can-ev-chargers-help-you-increase-rent</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>Electric vehicle sales are rising. Does it make sense to add an EV charging station at your property, and can you raise rent accordingly?</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 20:16:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>India’s Kazam powers up to roll out EV charging in Southeast Asia</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/11/indias-kazam-powers-up-to-roll-out-ev-charging-in-southeast-asia/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Kazam, an Indian EV charging solution provider, has raised $8 million to expand its footprint in the country and enter Southeast Asian markets. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 05:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Drawing Attention</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/01/news-inside-issue-17</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture6.png</image_url><description>News Inside Issue 17 features the opinions of justice-affected people on Trump’s felonies, and a nonfiction comic about death penalty mitigation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How the Financial Policies of Trump and Harris Could Impact Real Estate Investors</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/how-the-financial-policies-of-trump-and-harris-could-impact-real-estate-investors</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>With the election just three months away, it's important to take a look at how each candidate's policies would impact the economy and, ultimately, investors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 18:10:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Scott Painter is selling a beach house to start a new vehicle software company</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/08/11/scott-painter-autonomy-ads-vehicle-subscription-softwar/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Autonomy founder Scott Painter is spinning out a new company called Autonomy Data Services, or ADS, he tells TechCrunch in an exclusive interview. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>These Private Centers Lack Oversight. Cuyahoga County Judges Send Kids Anyway.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/08/01/juvenile-justice-detention-prison-youth-treatment-cuyahoga-county</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Courts are increasingly sending children to private youth care centers, spending millions while detention center overcrowding persists.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>