<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 07:25:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Why Your Portfolio Should Include Scarce Assets</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/10/why-your-portfolio-should-include-scarce-assets/</link><description>Portfolios that include both productive and scarce assets can deliver similar performance to the S&amp;P 500 with less risk than those that hold only productive assets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:34:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ex-Peloton director says disclosing pregnancy hit job prospects: ‘100% of the companies I told went from scheduling interviews to declining to bring me in for a final round’</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/13/ex-peloton-director-kate-winick-disclosing-pregnancy-hit-job-prospects-scheduling-interviews-final-round/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1419239018-e1715597829752.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Kate Winick was reassured that "companies just want to hire the right people" after being laid off from her director role at Peleton last year while pregnant—she's still job hunting.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 12:23:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coiled Tight: Smaller Companies Are Primed for Outperformance</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/08/coiled-tight-smaller-companies-are-primed-for-outperformance/</link><description>Small-cap companies are poised for a rebound. The sector is best approached through an active investment strategy where expertise and a deep understanding of the individual businesses and their risk-and-reward characteristics are necessary for success.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 12:40:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Smartphone giant Xiaomi is making a new move on Tesla</title><link>https://fortune.com/asia/2024/05/13/smartphone-giant-xiaomi-tesla-selling-suv-model-y-2025/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2151868758-e1715597589665.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>An SUV would mark a big expansion of Xiaomi’s $10 billion EV endeavor, spearheaded personally by billionaire co-founder Lei Jun.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 11:55:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Investment Returns Are NOT Random</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/07/investment-returns-are-not-random/</link><description>Are investment returns random across time as Burton Malkiel suggests in his book, A Random Walk Down Wall Street? There is notable disagreement on this topic. This research finds that practitioners may need to rethink their portfolio optimization routines.</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:22:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Beijing narrowly escapes having to cover the debts of developer Country Garden</title><link>https://fortune.com/asia/2024/05/13/country-garden-makes-interest-payment-avoids-guarantor-paying-debt-china-real-estate-crisis/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2074404077-e1715592401291.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Last week, Country Garden revealed that it had missed an interest payment on onshore bonds guaranteed by a state-owned financial firm.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 11:45:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Generational Wealth: Does the Apple Fall Far From the Tree?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/06/generational-wealth-does-the-apple-fall-far-from-the-tree/</link><description>There is strong evidence that most “rich families” will be poorer after several generations. Some of the reasons for this are systemic like taxes. But most factors that diminish a family’s wealth over generations are the choices that heirs make.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 12:37:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Global megarich are paying up to $2 million a week for superyacht rentals but smaller boat charters are down</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/13/super-yacht-rentals-megarich-smaller-charters/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-864197582-e1715591935495.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>IYC CEO Raphael Sauleau said he’s seeing more customers willing to pay a higher premium for the ultimate ocean experience.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 10:52:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>State Capitalism in Private Markets: Mission Creep</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/03/state-capitalism-in-private-markets-mission-creep/</link><description>Governments relish mingling in markets. Yet, if past policies are any guide, taxpayers are being shortchanged.</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 12:30:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Roger Corman: 'King of the Bs' who directed 'Little Shop of Horrors' has died at 98</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/13/roger-corman-little-shop-of-horrors-francis-ford-coppola-martin-scorsese-died-98/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/AP24133073798593-e1715593778656.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Starting in 1955, Corman helped create hundreds of B-movies as a producer and director, among them “Black Scorpion,” “Bucket of Blood” and “Bloody Mama.”</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 10:51:39 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>