<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 08:52:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Book Review: The New World Economy in 5 Trends</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/24/book-review-the-new-world-economy-in-5-trends/</link><description>A diligent economist and an eclectic bookworm serve up an analysis of megatrends that will have the greatest impact on economies and investments: innovation, productivity, climate, multiglobalization, debt, and aging.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 12:22:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elon Musk earns praise from Nvidia co-founder Jensen Huang ahead of shareholder vote on pay package—‘Tesla is far ahead in self-driving cars’</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/27/elon-musk-tesla-nvidia-jensen-huang-shareholder-vote-pay-package-self-driving-cars/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-1820547400-e1716811071708.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The ringing endorsement from Huang comes amid Musk's recent pivot to AI as the Tesla boss quietly scrapped his vision of growing volumes over tenfold to 20 million EVs a year by 2030.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 13:24:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Factor Strategies Belong in Your Completion Portfolio Toolkit</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/23/factor-strategies-belong-in-your-completion-portfolio-toolkit/</link><description>Why wouldn't you include factor strategies in your completion portfolio? A review of the two commonly used approaches for managing institutional assets highlights their symbiotic nature.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 19:09:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mexico prepares to elect first woman leader as millions of domestic workers wonder if it will improve 'modern slavery'</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/27/mexico-elect-first-woman-leader-millions-domestic-workers-improve-modern-slavery/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2154689488-e1716811920159.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>"At least by having a woman, maybe things will be different."</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 13:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>For the Analyst: Peer Benchmarking Methods to Improve Earnings Forecasts</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/21/for-the-analyst-peer-benchmarking-methods-to-improve-earnings-forecasts/</link><description>Peer benchmarking is a vexing task for financial analysts but one that is critical for forecasting earnings. This straightforward measure can help find peers for relative performance, compensation, and valuation benchmarking.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 12:47:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Europe-Israel relations take a hit as Spain, Ireland and Norway prepare to formally recognize a Palestinian state</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/27/europe-israel-relations-spain-ireland-norway-recognize-palestinian-state/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2154344449-e1716808895153.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Israeli Foreign Minister Katz accused Spain of “rewarding terror” by recognizing a Palestinian state, and said that “the days of the Inquisition are over.”</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 12:24:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Building LLMs in the Open-Source Community: A Call to Action for Investment Professionals</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/20/building-llms-in-the-open-source-community-a-call-to-action-for-investment-professionals/</link><description>Large language models like ChatGPT are changing the way we think about investing and reshaping roles in the investment profession.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 16:26:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lina Khan’s noncompete crackdown could leave most doctors and nurses out in the cold</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/27/lina-khan-noncompete-ban-doctors-nurses/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2153111984-e1716587577244.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Provider groups are disappointed that the Federal Trade Commission’s new rule may not protect those who work for nonprofit hospitals and health care facilities, which employ the largest number of medical professionals.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 12:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sustainability Reporting: Navigating Assurance Practices</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/17/sustainability-reporting-navigating-assurance-practices/</link><description>Don't be lulled into a false sense of security by the word "assurance" when evaluating sustainability reports. Assurance practices vary, and investors would be wise to learn more about the different levels of coverage.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 17:57:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Abraham Lincoln museum in spotlight again after paying $15,000 for disputed flag</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/27/abraham-lincoln-museum-in-spotlight-again-after-paying-15000-for-disputed-flag-its-prized-6-5m-stovepipe-hat-tied-to-president-was-also-questioned/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/AP24143664216025-e1716806141101.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>A director was fired in 2019 for sending without approval a copy of the Gettysburg Address, written in Lincoln's hand, to a Texas exhibit operated by conservative political commentator Glenn Beck.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 11:38:25 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>