<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 12:03:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>MLS Throws It Back to the ’90s With New All-Star Kits</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/02/mls-throws-it-back-to-the-90s-with-new-all-star-kits/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Kit design "celebrates the best MLS has to offer and honors the iconic style and flash of ‘90s soccer on the 30th anniversary of the last time the United States hosted the World Cup"</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 15:51:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vince Vaughn, JB Smoove, Julius Randle Roll Up To Cosm L.A. Opening For UFC 303</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/01/cosm-los-angeles-ufc-303-debut-vince-vaughn-jb-smoove-julius-randle-ronnie-lott-celebrity/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Hollywood stars, sports legends, and a billionaire or two had a kick-ass view for UFC 303, but none of them were at T-Mobile Arena ... instead, Vince Vaughn and a gang of other celebs partied and watched fights at a new, super cool immersive…</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 12:03:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bismarck Larks honor ranchers with Heartland Holy Cow identity</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/02/bismarck-larks-honor-ranchers-with-heartland-holy-cow-identity/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The collegiate summer level Bismarck Larks will pay tribute to the ranching community of North Dakota (and roughly 19 surrounding US states) when they play a game as the Heartland Holy Cows this summer. The identity features a startled cow with a halo over its head, playing off both the</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 12:13:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>President Biden's Debate Gaffes Causing White House Divide, Says Axios Reporter</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/01/president-biden-debate-performance-causing-white-house-divide-alex-thompson/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>President Biden's debate gaffes are ticking off some folks who work in the White House, because they've reportedly been kept away from him ... and now it's causing a divide among staffers. Alex Thompson, the national political correspondent for…</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 12:03:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BYU Cougars Unveil 1996 Throwback Football Uniforms</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/07/01/byu-cougars-unveil-1996-throwback-football-uniforms/college/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>As part of its 100th season celebration, BYU has unveiled 1996 throwback uniforms that will be worn in the Big XII opener against Kansas State on Sept. 21.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 20:03:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Flavor Flav Getting Signature Meal on Red Lobster Menu</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/01/red-lobster-flavor-flav-faves-signature-menu-meal/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Flavor Flav and Red Lobster are trying everything to save a sinking ship -- including a new menu addition based on Flav's favorite flavors. The seafood chain announced the launch Monday of Flavor Flav's signature menu item -- a massive combo meal…</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 12:03:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>New York Mets Honor Willie Mays, Jerry Grote With Jersey Patches</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/30/new-york-mets-honor-willie-mays-jerry-grote-with-jersey-patches/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The New York Mets will honor the lives of former players Willie Mays and Jerry Grote by wearing memorial patches on their jerseys for the remainder of the season.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 21:43:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Boeing Flight in Severe Turbulence, Video Shows Passenger Stuck in Ceiling</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/01/boeing-air-europa-man-stuck-overhead-bin-flight-turbulence-injures-30/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>A transatlantic passenger is feeling lucky to be alive after severe turbulence sent him hurtling through the cabin of a Boeing jet ... and planted him in the airliner's ceiling. Check out the clip -- you can see the man's feet sticking out from…</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 12:03:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NFL Second, Third Helmet Concept Series – AFC North</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/30/nfl-second-third-helmet-concept-series-afc-north/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Our newest concept series that creates second and/or third helmet designs for every NFL team continues with the AFC North.</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 18:19:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Horizon' Star Michael Rooker Says Kevin Costner Film Is Cinema, Not TikTok Crap</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/07/01/horizon-american-saga-michael-rooker-real-cinema-box-office-kevin-costner/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Michael Rooker says folks are sleeping on Kevin Costner's new movie saga ... telling us the film is a throwback to classic Hollywood and a departure from the "crap" TikTok generation. We got Michael, who stars in Kevin's new epic "Horizon: An…</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 12:03:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>