<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 02:37:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Book Review: My Value Creation Journey</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/06/14/book-review-my-value-creation-journey/</link><description>Bartley J. Madden has produced a book that challenges business leaders and investment professionals to think outside the box systematically to solve difficult problems.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 18:04:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A rivalry that predates the Civil War is about to heat up with a vote on subsidizing a new stadium</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/06/15/kansas-city-chiefs-new-stadium-subsidy-construction-bonds-vote-royals-missouri-rivalry/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/AP24165830372104-e1718492608499.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The Kansas Legislature's top leaders endorsed helping the Chiefs and professional baseball's Kansas City Royals finance new stadiums in Kansas ahead of a special session set to convene Tuesday.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 00:16:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Private Markets’ Governance: A New Era</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/06/14/private-markets-governance-a-new-era/</link><description>Now that the SEC Private Fund Adviser rules have been struck down, it's incumbent on the industry to demonstrate how private ordering can work.</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 17:49:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A rare flesh-eating bacteria with a 'terrifying' mortality rate that can kill people in 48 hours is spreading in Japan</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/06/15/flesh-eating-bacteria-terrifying-mortality-rate-group-a-streptococcus-shock-syndrome-japan/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/GettyImages-1301753164-e1718491179790.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>“As soon as a patient notices swelling in foot in the morning, it can expand to the knee by noon, and they can die within 48 hours.”</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 23:51:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Interplay Between Cap Rates and Interest Rates</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/06/13/the-interplay-between-cap-rates-and-interest-rates/</link><description>What is the relationship between cap rates and interest rates? It's not as straightforward as you may think.</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 15:55:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meet the co-owner of the NBA's Dallas Mavericks: A casino mogul trying to bring gambling to a reluctant state</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/06/15/nba-dallas-mavericks-owner-patrick-dumont-las-vegas-sands-casino-texas-legalized-gambling/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/GettyImages-2156682785-e1718489306513.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>“The NBA is a multifaceted business. It’s a media business, a hospitality business and a culinary business. It’s all about experience."</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 23:27:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Still Misperceived? A Fresh Look at Bitcoin Volatility</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/06/12/still-misperceived-a-fresh-look-at-bitcoin-volatility/</link><description>Is Bitcoin considerably more volatile than other asset classes? It's important to approach this question analytically and with an open mind because perceptions do not always match reality.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 18:02:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Colliding hot and cold fronts whipsaw the U.S. with extreme heat, flooding, and a chance of snow</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/06/15/extreme-weather-climate-change-severe-heat-wave-warning-flooding-snow/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/AP24164655290369-e1718487726524.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>While most of the country bakes, parts of Montana have been placed under winter storm watches with a potential for wet snow Monday night.</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 22:53:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FX Bubbles: Through the Lens of Shiller and Sornette</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/06/11/fx-bubbles-through-the-lens-of-shiller-and-sornette/</link><description>The theories and models introduced by Robert Shiller and Didier Sornette are as applicable to the foreign exchange market as they are to the stock market.</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 19:20:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>U.S. debt could threaten the economic growth that's needed to keep the burden sustainable, former IMF official says</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/06/15/us-debt-crisis-interest-expense-economic-growth-deficit-sustainability-gdp-ratio/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/GettyImages-1498234835-e1718479759252.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>"Even absent this dire scenario, meeting additional interest obligations as the debt ratio rises could require the federal government to cut discretionary spending, with negative implications for economic growth."</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 21:44:47 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>