<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 07:25:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Cardinals &amp; Giants Pay Tribute to Negro Leagues with Throwback Uniforms at Rickwood Field Next Week</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/12/cardinals-giants-pay-tribute-to-negro-leagues-with-throwback-uniforms-at-rickwood-field-next-week/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The special throwback uniforms for the Major League Baseball and Minor League Baseball games at Rickwood Field next week have been unveiled. The Major League game, officially known as “MLB at Rickwood Field,” will be played on June 20th. The San Francisco Giants and St. Louis Cardinals will wear uniforms</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 17:47:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Superintendent Won't Accept Apology From Dad Who Stormed Graduation Stage</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/12/wisconsin-superintendent-baraboo-school-graduation-breaks-silence-dad-apology/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>The Wisconsin high school official who got shoved aside by the father of a graduating senior is speaking out on the incident ... saying an apology here is too little, too late. Superintendent Rainey Briggs -- who was onstage at Baraboo High during…</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 07:25:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Baltimore Orioles Add Blue T. Rowe Price Patch to Jerseys</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/12/baltimore-orioles-add-blue-t-rowe-price-goat-patch-to-jerseys/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The Baltimore Orioles have announced a new partnership with T. Rowe Price, a global investment management firm headquartered in Baltimore. The partnership will include adding their corporate logo to the sleeves of the Orioles jerseys. This patch made its debut last night during their game against the Atlanta Braves at</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 15:28:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Logan Paul Grants Donald Trump Interview Request, Gunning For Joe Biden Next</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/12/logan-paul-grants-donald-trump-interview-request-impaulsive-joe-biden/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Logan Paul's got a yuuuuuuge guest on his next podcast episode ... it's none other than President Donald Trump -- and TMZ Sports is told this may not be the WWE Superstar's only toe dip into politics. Sources with direct knowledge tell us the…</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 07:25:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Athletics Announce New Uniforms for Sacramento; Las Vegas Unis In-Progress</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/11/athletics-announce-uniform-change-for-sacramento-shift-las-vegas-design-process-underway/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>The President of the Oakland Athletics gave the world an update about the future of the team’s uniforms as the club prepares for a chaotic few seasons. Speaking with the Las Vegas Review-Journal, A’s president Dave Kaval said the club has already begun the process of developing the team’s uniforms</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 03:13:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DoorDash Driver's Racist Slur At Black Customer Caught On Ring Video</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/12/doordash-driver-racist-slur-customer-ring-video/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>A Nashville DoorDash driver was caught on doorbell footage hurling a racist slur at a Black customer -- a despicable act that led to his firing. In a shocking TikTok clip posted Tuesday by customer Christina Derrica, the delivery man drops her…</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 07:25:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bayer Leverkusen Home Kit Headlines Unveilings From Germany and Beyond</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/11/bayer-leverkusen-home-kit-headlines-kit-unveilings-from-germany-and-beyond/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Other unveilings include newly promoted Bundesliga teams FC St. Pauli and Holstein Kiel, along with French side RC Lens and Portugal's FC Porto</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Check Out Kevin Spacey's Baltimore Home He's Going to Lose</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/12/kevin-spacey-baltimore-home-losing-auction-piers-morgan-interview/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Kevin Spacey is crying about losing his home and owing millions in legal fees ... and TMZ has the first look inside the Baltimore pad he says is going up for auction. No wonder Kevin is upset ... he used to live in an East Coast palace right on the…</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 07:25:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Messi Tops List of Best-Selling MLS Jerseys Once Again</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/06/11/messi-tops-list-of-best-selling-mls-jerseys-once-again/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Rest of top five includes Messi's Inter Miami teammate Luis Suárez; reigning MVP Luciano Acosta of FC Cincinnati; Columbus Crew's Cucho Hernández and LA Galaxy's Riqui Puig</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 21:11:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coldplay Pauses Concert After Man With Israeli Flag Falls Trying To Rush Stage</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/06/12/coldplay-pause-concert-man-israeli-flag-falls-rush-stage/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>A Coldplay concert in Greece hit the pause button after a man draped in an Israeli flag fell while trying to rush the stage ... just one of the various gestures from the pro-Israel crowd. Footage has surfaced from Coldplay's gig in Athens this week…</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 07:25:28 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>