<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 07:31:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>FI With 5 Kids and Debt-Free in Just Over a Decade!</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-566</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>Does FIRE seem impossible while raising a family? We’re about to prove that you CAN have it all. Emily and Joel are financially independent while raising five kids and still […]</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 10:00:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pinterest launches a feature to let users remix collages created by others</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/24/pinterest-launches-a-feature-to-let-users-remix-collages-created-by-others/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture8.png</image_url><description>Pinterest created an engaging format with collages last year, which allows users to combine images and cutouts to create new content. The company is now banking on people creating more of them by introducing a Remix feature. Just like the Remix feature on short video apps, such as Instagram and Snap, the idea behind Pinterest’s feature is […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mississippi Court Candidates Tell You Why They Should Be Elected</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/09/24/mississippi-court-candidates-tell-you-why-they-should-be-elected</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>The Marshall Project - Jackson and Mississippi Today asked the candidates to explain why people should vote for them. Here’s who responded.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Baselane’s Survey of Investors Gives Inside Look at What’s Really Happening in Real Estate</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/baselane-real-estate-investor-survey-2024</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture3.png</image_url><description>The 2024 Baselane Real Estate Investor Survey reveals optimism among investors despite rising costs. Key takeaways include: Investors Are Growing Portfolios But Skeptical No, the sky is not falling on […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 20:02:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WP Engine sends cease-and-desist letter to Automattic over Mullenweg’s comments</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/23/wp-engine-sends-cease-and-desist-letter-to-automattic-over-mullenwegs-comments/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>Mullenweg, who co-created WordPress, last week criticized WP Engine for raking in profits without giving much back to the open source project. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 07:54:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meet the People Running for Mississippi’s Supreme Court and Other Courts</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/09/24/mississippi-judge-guide-supreme-court-appeals-hinds-county</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>We profiled candidates for two state Supreme Court seats and other courts, and asked each to tell you in their own words why they should be elected.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>These Cities Are Set to Have Rising Home Prices for Longer—Here’s Why</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/cities-with-income-growth-show-where-prices-are-expected-to-rise</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>There is generally a positive relationship between income growth and price appreciation in cities (correlation varies by city). In a previous article I published on BiggerPockets on cities with the […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 19:44:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GitHub will allow enterprise cloud customers to store data in the EU</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/23/github-will-allow-enterprise-cloud-customers-to-store-data-in-the-eu/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Starting from October 29, GitHub says that all enterprise cloud customers will be able to select an EU region to store all their code. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How We Survived Extreme Heat in Prison</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/09/19/prison-journalists-how-to-survive-extreme-heat</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture1.png</image_url><description>Incarcerated journalists detail the first signs of a heat wave in prison — and how they’ve coped with record-breaking temperatures.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Hire a Virtual Assistant for Real Estate Investing for Just $5/Hour</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-461</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture10.png</image_url><description>Want to work less, make more, and do it all by spending as little as five dollars per hour? Great! You’ll need to know how to hire a virtual assistant […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 10:00:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fintech Jupiter in talks to buy a stake in SBM Bank India</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/23/fintech-jupiter-in-talks-to-buy-a-stake-in-sbm-bank-india/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture7.png</image_url><description>In the latest instance of an Indian fintech startup pursuing strategic partnerships with traditional banking institutions, neobank Jupiter is in talks to acquire a stake in SBM Bank India, three sources familiar with the matter told TechCrunch. Jupiter, backed by Tiger Global and NuBank, is in discussions to buy a 5% to 9.9% stake in […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 05:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Marshall Project to Host Inaugural Sing Sing Prison Film Festival</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/09/19/the-marshall-project-to-host-inaugural-sing-sing-prison-film-festival</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture9.png</image_url><description>Incarcerated jury will choose best criminal justice documentary.</description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How to Know Whether You’ll Scale (or Fail) in Real Estate</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-254</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture5.png</image_url><description>Your real estate business could fail if you don’t do this right. We’ve seen it happen time and time again. A business finds success, starts growing at lightning speed to […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 10:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Crypto scammers hack OpenAI’s press account on X</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/23/crypto-scammers-hack-openais-press-account-on-x/</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture2.png</image_url><description>OpenAI’s official press account on X appears to have been compromised by the same cryptocurrency scammers who compromised the accounts of company leadership in previous months. Late Monday afternoon, OpenAI Newsroom, an account OpenAI recently created to spotlight product- and policy-related announcements, posted about a supposedly new OpenAI-branded blockchain token, “$OPENAI.” “We’re very happy to […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 23:39:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Robert Roberson’s Death Penalty Case Shows How Justice System Fails People With Autism</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/09/18/texas-autism-death-penalty-roberson</link><image_url>https://lead-mark.github.io/snippets/genNewsImagesTwo/Picture4.png</image_url><description>He was convicted in his daughter’s death. Those who believe he’s innocent argue his diagnosis helps explain how he ended up facing execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>