<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 06:55:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>For the Analyst: Peer Benchmarking Methods to Improve Earnings Forecasts</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/21/for-the-analyst-peer-benchmarking-methods-to-improve-earnings-forecasts/</link><description>Peer benchmarking is a vexing task for financial analysts but one that is critical for forecasting earnings. This straightforward measure can help find peers for relative performance, compensation, and valuation benchmarking.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 12:47:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Renault boss lament's Volkswagen's inability to 'work as a team' as joint cheap EV plan collapses</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/05/23/renault-ceo-luca-de-meo-volkswagen-work-as-team-byd-affordable-ev-twingo-project-collapses/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2128587164-e1716460334324.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Renault CEO Luca de Meo had been trying to collaborate on an affordable version of the Twingo.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:49:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Building LLMs in the Open-Source Community: A Call to Action for Investment Professionals</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/20/building-llms-in-the-open-source-community-a-call-to-action-for-investment-professionals/</link><description>Large language models like ChatGPT are changing the way we think about investing and reshaping roles in the investment profession.</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 16:26:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biden’s tariffs on Chinese EVs make sense—but only for a while</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/23/biden-tariffs-chinese-ev-tech-politics/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2121899877-e1716460987541.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The Biden administration aims to create a defensible moat so that U.S. automakers’ efforts to build competitive EVs are not wiped out by Chinese imports.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:46:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sustainability Reporting: Navigating Assurance Practices</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/17/sustainability-reporting-navigating-assurance-practices/</link><description>Don't be lulled into a false sense of security by the word "assurance" when evaluating sustainability reports. Assurance practices vary, and investors would be wise to learn more about the different levels of coverage.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 17:57:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How do I choose the right cofounder for my startup?</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/23/ask-andy-startups-choosing-a-cofounder-financial-stability/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/DUNN-WEB.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Bonobos and Pie founder Andy Dunn answers questions about finding the right cofounder and the trade-off between startup life and family stability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Power of Clicks, Likes, and Shares: Promote the Right Kind of Financial Content</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/16/the-power-of-clicks-likes-and-shares-promote-the-right-kind-of-financial-content/</link><description>Not all financial content creators on social media are created equal. A broad differentiation can be made between influencers, knowledge sharers, and aspiring thought leaders.</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 14:03:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jamie Dimon says there's a chance the Fed could further hike rates instead of cutting</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/05/23/jamie-dimon-jerome-powell-base-rate-cut-could-raise/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2152634442_b537f4-e1716457715123.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>"Do I think that rates can go up a little bit? Yes I do. And if they do is the world prepared for it? Not really."</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:23:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why the New T+1 Settlement Cycle Matters: A Global Index Provider’s Perspective</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/05/14/why-the-new-t1-settlement-cycle-matters-a-global-index-providers-perspective/</link><description>Shorter settlement periods are meant to protect market participants. But the new T+1 settlement cycle for US equities may have undesirable knock-on effects for financial market participants around the world, including index fund managers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 16:54:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>France lost control of parts of New Caledonia</title><link>https://fortune.com/asia/2024/05/23/france-lost-control-new-caledonia-macron-visiting-third-largest-producer-ev-metal-nickel/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/GettyImages-2153622051-e1716458224991.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The Pacific territory of 270,000 people has been in turmoil since May 13, when violence erupted over plans to extend voting rights to more residents, which indigenous Kanaks say would diminish their electoral influence.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 10:58:51 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>