<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Aggregated RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/aggregated_feed.xml</link><description>This is an aggregated feed of the most recent 5 entries from each RSS source.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 08:23:03 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>AI to the Rescue? Overhauling the US Power Grid on the Path to Net Zero</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/15/ai-to-the-rescue-overhauling-the-us-power-grid-on-the-path-to-net-zero/</link><description>Once known as secure and profitable investments, utilities are now viewed as enterprises fraught with financial risks. Investors should favor utilities that employ AI and other digital strategies to minimize damage from natural disasters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 21:24:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Does a Stock’s Price Influence Its Risk Profile?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/12/does-a-stocks-price-influence-its-risk-profile/</link><description>As a stock falls in value, it becomes more sensitive to market movements and its total volatility increases.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Managing Regret Risk: The Role of Asset Allocation</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/10/managing-regret-risk-the-role-of-asset-allocation/</link><description>Regret risk is a quantifiable phenomenon. The answer for some clients may be equally weighted portfolios.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 13:04:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Art and Science of DC Plan Investment Design</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/08/the-art-and-science-of-dc-plan-investment-design/</link><description>Defined contribution plan sponsors need to take a disciplined approach to investment menu construction.</description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From the Archives: Daniel Kahneman on Better Decision Making</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/05/from-the-archives-daniel-kahneman-on-better-decision-making/</link><description>Daniel Kahneman shared four simple strategies for better decision making in finance and in life.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 12:33:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Boeing’s mid-air blowout no surprise considering company’s safety culture, says FAA panelist and aerospace engineer whose brother died in 737 Max crash</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/17/boeing-mid-air-blowout-no-surprise-safety-culture-faa-panelist-aerospace-engineer-737-max-crash/</link><description>“I would have thought that they would have ‘gotten it’ five years ago,” said Javier de Luis, the brother of Graziella de Luis, who was killed when a 737 Max flown by Ethiopian Airlines crashed in March 2019.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 12:39:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>‘No one wants to see a picket line on Sesame Street’ but that’s exactly what’s happening as writers unanimously vote for strike</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/17/sesame-street-writers-strike-wga-pay-union/</link><description>"Millions of parents and families around the world are going to have a lot of questions,” a union leader said.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 12:25:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Beware, Swifties. A major British bank just issued a warning after fans lost an estimated $1 million in Taylor Swift concert ticket scams</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/04/17/beware-swifties-a-major-british-bank-just-issued-a-warning-after-fans-lost-an-estimated-1-million-in-taylor-swift-concert-ticket-scams/</link><description>“Cruel fraudsters have wasted no time in targeting her most loyal fans as they rush to pick up tickets for her must-see concerts,” Lloyds Bank said.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 12:24:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Canada will soak the rich with capital gains tax jump to raise billions for housing in market where Gen Z can’t catch a break</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/17/canada-soak-rich-capital-gains-tax-jump-raise-billions-housing-gen-z/</link><description>Prime Minister Justin Trudeau’s administration has been sinking in opinion polls, which show that he’s losing younger voters who are frustrated about the high cost of housing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 12:17:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Disney’s multibillion-dollar theme park facelift gets unanimous approval from Anaheim council</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/17/disney-land-anaheim-approval-theme-park-renovation-california/</link><description>It would be the biggest expansion of Disney’s Southern California theme parks in decades.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 12:14:50 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>