<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 12:43:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The Changing Nature of Cannabis Consumption: Investment Opportunities</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/08/13/the-changing-nature-of-cannabis-consumption/</link><description>For investors in the space, the changing cannabis consumption landscape opens challenges and opportunities in product creation, marketing, and targeting new consumer groups.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:46:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How Starbucks’ new CEO Brian Niccol went from fast-food Frankenstein to Chipotle’s redeemer</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/08/13/who-is-starbucks-ceo-chipotle-brian-niccol-career/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/MS_BrianNiccol_090.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Niccol helped create Taco Bell’s mega-viral Doritos Locos Taco before leading Chipotle’s food safety crisis turnaround.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:34:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From Sandpiles to Angel Investments</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/08/12/from-sandpiles-to-angel-investments/</link><description>The presence of power law returns in angel investing, with the potential for significant contributions from a handful of investments, has implications for portfolio construction, investment strategies, and diversification.</description><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 13:19:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I’m a Gen Zer starting a career in homebuilding. Skipping college was the best decision I ever made</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/08/13/gen-zer-on-starting-homebuilding-career-while-skipping-college-and-student-debt/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/gen-zer-Julieanna-Etter-e1723562525199.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>College can bring success. It can also bring student debt and regret.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:17:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: Pause to Think</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/08/09/book-review-pause-to-think/</link><description>This book is direct, delightful, and articulate in suggesting that we take a slow rather than fast approach to getting things thoughtfully done. It touches the minds and hearts of investment professionals.</description><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 12:59:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ford and Mazda beg nearly 500,000 owners to stop driving older cars with deadly air bags</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/08/13/ford-mazda-beg-owners-stop-driving-old-cars-with-takata-air-bags/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/GettyImages-157462549-1-e1723561673340.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The warning covers more than 374,000 Ford, Lincoln and Mercury vehicles, as well as nearly 83,000 Mazdas.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 16:09:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is Illiquidity a Blessing in Disguise for Some Investors?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/08/07/is-illiquidity-a-blessing-in-disguise-for-some-investors/</link><description>Rather than running away from illiquidity, investment professionals, investors, and regulators alike should recognize its potential benefits and consider a more balanced approach.</description><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 17:13:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>EU warns Elon Musk over X compliance—he fires back with vulgar ‘Tropic Thunder’ meme</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/08/13/elon-musk-european-union-commission-thierry-breton/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/GettyImages-2162688843_23739a-e1723550263276.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>The EU Commission forced to defend claims a strongly worded letter to Elon Musk was proof Brussels is interfering in U.S. elections.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 14:37:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Scenario Planning, Foresight, and the Power of Imagination: Navigating an Uncertain Future</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/08/05/scenario-planning-foresight-and-the-power-of-imagination-navigating-an-uncertain-future/</link><description>By fostering resilience through the consideration of various outcomes, investment practitioners can better anticipate and manage the complexities and disruptions that characterize today's dynamic environment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 17:28:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Starbucks poaches Chipotle CEO Brian Niccol in surprise leadership shake-up</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/08/13/starbucks-ceo-brian-niccol-chipotle/</link><image_url>https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Chiptole-CEO-Thumb-1.jpg?w=2048</image_url><description>Laxman Narasimhan was ousted after just over a year in the CEO role.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 14:28:37 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>