<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 03:02:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>My Tenant Was Airbnbing Their Apartment Without Me Knowing. It Happens More Than You Think.</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/my-tenants-were-airbnbing-my-apartment-without-me-knowing</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Renting has its horror stories, and sometimes it gets out of control. Jeff gives us an inside look at what happened when one of his tenants rented out his property without him knowing, plus stories from other landlords.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 21:24:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Autonomous delivery startup Nuro is gearing up for a comeback</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/27/autonomous-delivery-startup-nuro-is-gearing-up-for-a-comeback/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>The California Department of Motor Vehicles this week granted Nuro approval to test its third-generation R3 autonomous delivery vehicle in four Bay Area cities, giving the AV startup a positive boost after facing some setbacks and financial struggles. The approval gives Nuro the ability to test its driverless delivery vehicle in Mountain View, Palo Alto, […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 19:52:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What These Decisions Tell Us About Kamala Harris’ Approach to Criminal Justice</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/27/kamala-harris-prosecutor-california-police-election-crime</link><description>From the death penalty to school truancy and diversion programs, here are some key steps Harris took as a district attorney and attorney general.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mortgage Rate Gaps: Tracking the States With the Tightest Lock-In Effects</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/states-with-the-tightest-lock-in-effects</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>With higher interest rates, the lock-in effect has created a low inventory environment. Homeowners in these states are the most locked-in.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 21:05:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ghostery’s CEO says regulation won’t save us from ad trackers</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/27/ghosterys-ceo-says-regulation-wont-save-us-from-ad-trackers/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>With Ghostery turning 15 years old this month, TechCrunch caught up with CEO Jean-Paul Schmetz to discuss the company's strategy and the state of ad tracking. © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Love Beyond Bars: Raymond and Cassandra</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/26/photo-essay-raymond-flanks-wrongful-conviction</link><description>Raymond Flanks spent nearly 39 years in Louisiana lockups for a murder he didn’t commit. Luckily, he found love with an old friend, Cassandra Delpit.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 11:00:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BiggerNews: Multifamily Market Update + Where to Find Deals NOW</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-995</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Multifamily real estate is still offering some significant opportunities to investors—you just need to know where to look! Although the past two years have been rough for multifamily, with falling […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 07:02:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple reaches its first contract agreement with a US retail union</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/27/apple-reaches-its-first-contract-agreement-with-a-us-retail-union/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Two years ago, workers at an Apple Store in Towson, Maryland were the first to establish a formally recognized union at an Apple retail store in the United States. Now they’re the first to reach a tentative contract agreement. According to the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers’ Coalition of Organized Retail Employees, which […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 18:37:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Problem With Labeling Trump a ‘Felon’</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/25/donald-trump-felon-election24</link><description>Here’s why language used to describe any person convicted of crimes matters, and affects more than the former president.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 23:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rookie Reply: What EVERY Rookie Must Learn Before Investing in Real Estate</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-437</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Not quite ready to invest in real estate? Maybe you’re still getting your finances in check or saving for a bigger down payment. In any case, don’t sit on your […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 07:02:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OpenAI comes for Google with SearchGPT</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/27/openai-comes-for-google-with-searchgpt/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>OpenAI is testing SearchGPT, a new AI search experience to compete directly with Google. The feature aims to elevate search queries with “timely answers” from across the internet and allows the user to ask follow-up questions. The temporary prototype is currently only available to a small group of users and its publisher partners for testing […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 18:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Photos: Three Years of a Family’s Grief and Healing After a Fatal Police Shooting</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/25/family-photos-cleveland-police-shooting-belmonte</link><description>Photographer Michael Indriolo documents an East Cleveland family’s search for peace after the 2021 police shooting of their 19-year-old brother.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 11:00:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is FIRE Dead? No, But Here’s Why Most WON’T Achieve It</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/money-549</link><image_url>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/pocket.svg</image_url><description>Is the FIRE movement dead? In 2024, more people are catching on to the huge downsides of pursuing financial independence, retire early. Strict frugality, massive sacrifice, working harder than ever…is […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 07:01:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>WazirX to ‘socialize’ $230 million security breach loss among customers</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/27/wazirx-to-socialize-230-million-security-breach-loss-among-customers/</link><image_url>https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/cropped-cropped-favicon-gradient.png?w=32</image_url><description>Indian cryptocurrency exchange WazirX announced on Saturday a controversial plan to “socialize” the $230 million loss from its recent security breach among all its customers, a move that has sent shockwaves through the local crypto community. The Mumbai-based firm, which suspended all trading activities on its platform last week following the cyber attack that compromised […] © 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 18:03:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sending Unarmed Responders Instead of Police: What We’ve Learned</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/07/25/police-mental-health-alternative-911</link><description>There are more than 100 response teams nationwide, but experts say more research on their impact is needed.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 11:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>