<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 11:47:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>The Midwest All-Stars, an MLB Team that Lasted Just One Game in 1970</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/19/the-midwest-all-stars-an-mlb-team-that-lasted-just-one-game-in-1970/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>What happens when a league’s schedule makers forget to include a team for an entire weekend? In 1970, the American League was forced to solve that exact problem when they inadvertently left the Boston Red Sox off the Grapefruit League schedule entirely over the weekend of March 7-8. Of course,</description><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 20:30:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dramatic Video Shows Severe Flooding in Connecticut, 2 Dead</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/19/severe-flooding-connecticut/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Severe flooding in Connecticut turned peaceful country roads into a disaster scene when at least a foot of water pounded down Sunday night. The rainfall was much more than your everyday summer storm, as residents in Connecticut and parts of New…</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 11:47:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NFL Second, Third Helmet Concept Series – AFC West</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/18/nfl-second-third-helmet-concept-series-afc-west/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Our newest concept series that creates second and/or third helmet designs for every NFL team continues with the AFC West.</description><pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 17:07:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nev Schulman Fights Back Tears Recalling Aftermath of Accident</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/19/nev-schulman-cries-accident-aftermath/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Nev Schulman is still coming to terms with his traumatic bike accident, which left him with a broken neck and other injuries ... explaining his situation could've been a lot worse. We caught up with the "Catfish" star on "TMZ Live" Monday -- Nev…</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 11:47:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>First Look at the 2025 MLB Spring Training Logos</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/17/first-look-at-the-2025-mlb-spring-training-logos/baseball/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Is it that time of the year already? This week, Major League Baseball released its new official logos for its 2025 Spring Training schedule. This year’s logos for the annual six-week slate of exhibition games include an all-new primary mark, a slightly modified alternate design, and designs for both the</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 16:08:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jax Taylor Leaving Treatment, Planning to Film 'The Valley' Again</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/19/valley-jax-taylor-leaving-treatment/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Jax Taylor is ready to get back to work ... we've learned the reality star is planning to check out of treatment ... and he has big plans for his return home. Sources close to Jax tell TMZ ... the Bravo personality plans to leave the inpatient…</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 11:47:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2024-25 European Football Kit Preview: Serie A</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/17/2024-25-european-football-kit-preview-serie-a/soccer/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>123rd season of top-flight soccer in Italy kicks off on Saturday, August 17, with defending champs Inter Milan taking on Genoa CFC</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paris Hilton Documents Charred Personal Items After Trailer Fire</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/19/paris-hilton-trailer-fire-aftermath/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Paris Hilton is no longer sliving her best life ... instead, she's mourning some of her valuables which were destroyed in a trailer fire last week. TMZ broke the story ... the heiress-turned-DJ's makeup trailer went up in flames in downtown Los…</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 11:47:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CFL Running Back Becomes First Pro Football Player to Wear Guardian Cap in Regular Season Game</title><link>https://news.sportslogos.net/2024/08/16/cfl-running-back-becomes-first-pro-football-player-to-wear-guardian-cap-in-regular-season-game/football/</link><image_url>https://content.sportslogos.net/news/2020/06/cropped-slnet-505x505trans-32x32.png</image_url><description>Saskatchewan Roughriders running back Thomas Bertrand-Hudon wears concussion prevention cover in game against Montreal Alouettes on Friday, August 16</description><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 03:05:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Yung Gravy Says He Wasn't Asking 'Hawk Tuah' Girl Out on Date When He Slid In DM</title><link>https://www.tmz.com/2024/08/19/yung-gravy-responds-haliey-welch/</link><image_url>https://assets.tmz.com/www.tmz.com/main/default/cache/images/feedlogo2.v2014_05_09_134122.gif</image_url><description>Yung Gravy isn't mad at Haliey Welch for rebuffing him in the DMs ... telling us he's still a big fan! We got the "Betty" rapper at LAX, and our photog asked him about the "Hawk Tuah" girl claiming he slid in her DMs to ask her out. Haliey told us…</description><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 11:47:06 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>