<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 06:59:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>What Price Risk? Unpacking the Equity Risk Premium</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/24/what-price-risk-unpacking-the-equity-risk-premium/</link><description>Stocks are a good wager over the long term, on favorable odds. But stocks remain a bet, and investors must grasp how much returns can vary over long time horizons.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jamie Dimon says America needs to ‘take a deep breath’ before facing off with China, because the U.S. is actually in a ‘very good position’ to negotiate</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/26/jamie-dimon-america-china-trade-negotiations/</link><description>"We have all the food, water and energy we need."</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 11:46:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Equity Income Investing Redux</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/22/equity-income-investing-redux/</link><description>No doubt the past year has been difficult for equity income investors. But history, inherent biases, mean reversion, and the current market backdrop point to a comeback.</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 17:19:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Huawei reportedly keeps getting advanced chips, even as the U.S. tries to tighten the screws on China's semiconductor industry</title><link>https://fortune.com/asia/2024/04/26/huawei-homegrown-chip-pura-70-smartphone-mate-60-pro-us-chip-controls-apple/</link><description>Huawei's latest smartphone, the Pura 70, features another advanced chip according to a teardown by the consultancy TechInsights.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 11:21:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Book Review: Enrich Your Future</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/18/book-review-enrich-your-future/</link><description>This engaging book is simultaneously memorable and humorous. The numerous sports analogies will have you smiling as you absorb Larry Swedroe's unforgettable investment precepts.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 18:07:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Walmart CEO started his career unloading trailers at the warehouse</title><link>https://fortune.com/2024/04/26/walmart-ceo-doug-mcmillon-career-unloading-trailers-warehouse-promotion-boss/</link><description>Walmart's CEO went from earning $6.50 an hour to $25 million a year—here are his three tips for climbing the corporate ladder like him</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 11:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CAPE Is High: Should You Care?</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/17/cape-is-high-should-you-care/</link><description>A simple analysis shows that Robert Shiller's cyclically adjusted price-to-earnings ratio changed in the 1990s and that mean-reversion concerns may be misplaced. If CAPE changed three decades ago, however, there is nothing preventing it from doing so again.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 15:18:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aviation results: European carriers EasyJet and Jet2 fly to new heights, while Airbus prepares to overtake Boeing as headwinds continue</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/04/26/aviation-earnings-results-european-carriers-easyjet-jet2-wizz-air-airbus-boeing-heathrow/</link><description>It's been an eventful few days for aviation players—from Airbus to Heathrow. Here's how they fared.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 11:12:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AI to the Rescue? Overhauling the US Power Grid on the Path to Net Zero</title><link>https://blogs.cfainstitute.org/investor/2024/04/15/ai-to-the-rescue-overhauling-the-us-power-grid-on-the-path-to-net-zero/</link><description>Once known as secure and profitable investments, utilities are now viewed as enterprises fraught with financial risks. Investors should favor utilities that employ AI and other digital strategies to minimize damage from natural disasters.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 21:24:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The financial services gender pay gap in Europe is so large</title><link>https://fortune.com/europe/2024/04/26/gender-gap-in-europe-is-so-large-fewer-than-one-in-10-highest-earning-bankers-being-female/</link><description>Just 183 out of 2,017 people earning more than $1.1 million were female in 2022.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 11:09:43 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>