<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from each RSS source, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 06:49:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>8 Historical Fiction Books Set in Ireland to Transport You Back in Time</title><link>https://bookriot.com/historical-fiction-books-set-in-ireland/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/ireland.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>What Irish historical fiction did we miss?</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Take a video tour of Ferrari's spotless new 'e-building' factory</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/06/23/take-a-video-tour-of-ferraris-spotless-new-e-building-factory/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/crop/804x452+204+43/resize/800x450!/format/jpg/quality/85/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/06/21152333/Ferrari-video-tour.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Plants/Manufacturing , Ferrari Continue reading Take a video tour of Ferrari's spotless new 'e-building' factory Take a video tour of Ferrari's spotless new 'e-building' factory originally appeared on Autoblog on Sun, 23 Jun 2024 13:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Target taps Shopify to add sellers to its third-party marketplace</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/06/24/target-taps-shopify-to-add-sellers-to-its-third-party-marketplace.html</link><description>Target is partnering with Shopify as it looks for ways to drive online traffic and get back to sales growth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 11:19:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 557</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-557/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-557</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Searching for a new job requires clarity on what you want to do and where you want to do it. You need a solid strategy but most importantly you need tenacity. In short, job search is more than hitting the apply button. This week’s summary provides resources, tools and information to help you carry out […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 557 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 11:37:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Children’s digital media exposure as a backdrop for multilingual learning</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/childrens-digital-media-exposure-as-a-backdrop-for-multilingual-learning/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=childrens-digital-media-exposure-as-a-backdrop-for-multilingual-learning</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Multilingual children use digital media regularly, in all their home languages. Digital media use may affect multilingual children’s early language learning by reducing opportunities for back-and-forth conversations with adults. This finding is similar to results of studies of digital media and language learning for children learning only one language. When using […] The post Children’s digital media exposure as a backdrop for multilingual learning appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 20:27:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>S’mores Crack</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/smores-crack/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>S’mores crack is a quick way to enjoy the classic s’more experience without a campfire. Featuring a buttery graham cracker…</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Best Air Purifying Plants</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/best-air-purifying-plants/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>We love any excuse to buy more plants, and you may have heard they can improve your home’s indoor air quality. But before you blow your paycheck in the name of a healthier home, let’s dive deeper into plants’ air purifying powers. We’ll share which plants we recommend and what benefits you can actually expect from them. We’ve heard for years about how plants act as natural air filters for your home. So let’s dive a little deeper, shall we? 7 Air Purifying Plants If you just came here for a list, our favorite air purifying houseplants are bulleted below. The best part is these are all beautiful, low-maintenance plants. Many also appear on our best low-light indoor plants list too! Dracaena (including Corn Plant ) Snake Plant Aglaonema English Ivy Pothos Bamboo Palm Spider Plant There are certainly more that could be included here, but we narrowed it to the ones that are most often cited by experts AND the plants that we think look best too. Continue reading Best Air Purifying Plants at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 14:15:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Amazon Sundays</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/06/amazon-sundays-6-23-24/</link><description>Outfit Details: Shirt, Bikini Top &amp; Bottoms, Claw &amp; Water Bottle Welcome to Amazon Sundays, filled with the latest from… The post Amazon Sundays appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Inspiring Music Journals to Get In Your Hands</title><link>https://bookriot.com/inspiring-music-journals/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/music-journal-chamasatelier-etsy.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>Whether you're a musician or just a music lover, there's something for you. - Anne Mai Yee Jansen</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Max Verstappen wins F1 Spanish Grand Prix ahead of Lando Norris</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/06/23/max-verstappen-wins-f1-spanish-grand-prix-ahead-of-lando-norris/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1200x675/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/06/23121648/f1_spanish_grand_prix_2024.jpeg</image_url><description>Filed under: Motorsports Continue reading Max Verstappen wins F1 Spanish Grand Prix ahead of Lando Norris Max Verstappen wins F1 Spanish Grand Prix ahead of Lando Norris originally appeared on Autoblog on Sun, 23 Jun 2024 12:18:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 17:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sweltering temperatures persist across the U.S., while floodwaters inundate the Midwest</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/06/24/sweltering-temperatures-persist-in-the-us-floodwaters-inundate-midwest.html</link><description>Temperatures soared across the U.S., while residents were rescued from floodwaters that forced evacuations across the Midwest.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 11:10:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>5 Ways to Speed Up Your Job Search</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/5-ways-to-speed-up-your-job-search/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=5-ways-to-speed-up-your-job-search</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Is it possible to speed up your job search when the hiring decisions lie in the hands of employers? Yes, there are definitely things you can do to increase your odds. Taking control over what you can control is what I call a proactive job search. Too often job seekers over-rely on posted jobs to […] The post 5 Ways to Speed Up Your Job Search appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 11:04:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>La exposición de los niños a los medios digitales como contexto para el aprendizaje multilingüe</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/la-exposicion-de-los-ninos-a-los-medios-digitales-como-contexto-para-el-aprendizaje-multilingue/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=la-exposicion-de-los-ninos-a-los-medios-digitales-como-contexto-para-el-aprendizaje-multilingue</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Puntos clave para los cuidadores Los niños multilingües usan frecuentemente los medios digitales y los usan en los distintos idiomas que se hablan en su hogar. El uso de los medios digitales (por ej., la televisión, el computador o los “smartphones”) puede afectar negativamente el desarrollo del lenguaje en los niños que son multilingües porque […] The post La exposición de los niños a los medios digitales como contexto para el aprendizaje multilingüe appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 20:26:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Firecracker Meatballs</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/firecracker-meatballs/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Get ready to spice up your dinner with these firecracker meatballs! Juicy beef meatballs are baked to perfection and then…</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A Weekend In New Orleans With Kids</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/new-orleans-with-kids/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Since our travel guides to Charleston with kids and Palm Springs with kids have elicited requests for more travel ideas with kids, we’re back with an overdue recap of our 3-night trip to New Orleans. We’d never been to The Big Easy before and were impressed by how family-friendly the city is. It’s not all booze, beads, and Bourbon Street! So here’s a look at where we stayed, what we did, and what we’re excited to do next time we go back – because we will definitely go back! The four of us (well, five if you count our chihuahua!) went to NOLA for 3 nights in November of 2022. At the time, our kids were 8 and 12 years old. So unfortunately we can’t vouch for our suggestions being a good fit for toddlers or younger children. Although I’m sure ours would’ve loved the Louisiana Children’s Museum and Storyland playground back in the day! Continue reading A Weekend In New Orleans With Kids at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 17:17:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I Love Italy Part 2</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/06/i-love-italy-part-2/</link><description>As we continue our journey through Italy, I’m sharing more about my favorite styles to stay cool and comfortable during… The post I Love Italy Part 2 appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 05:00:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The News Book Riot Covered This Week</title><link>https://bookriot.com/the-news-book-riot-covered-this-week/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/Untitled-design12.png</image_url><description>Books sales jump, Libro.fm's best-selling audiobooks from its first decade, JAMES to be a movie, and much more. This week was a busy one.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 22:39:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>European carmakers face Chinese retaliation for EU tariffs</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/06/23/european-carmakers-eu-tariffs-china-retaliation/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1200x675/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/04/30093040/2025_mercedes-benz_s-class_35.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Government/Legal Continue reading European carmakers face Chinese retaliation for EU tariffs European carmakers face Chinese retaliation for EU tariffs originally appeared on Autoblog on Sun, 23 Jun 2024 12:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Monday's analyst calls: Micron a top pick, Goldman says buy IBM shares</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/06/24/analyst-calls-all-the-market-moving-wall-street-chatter-from-monday.html</link><description>Two tech stocks were among the names being talked about by analysts on Monday.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 10:47:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 556</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-556/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-556</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Artificial Intelligence is impacting every area of our lives, including job search. This will require each of us to become better critical thinkers to identify the noise from the genuine. Keeping up with the changes in the world of work takes effort, but that’s one reason you are here – each week you’ll discover interesting […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 556 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 11:55:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Becoming Confident in Parenting Abilities</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/confidence-in-parenting/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=confidence-in-parenting</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Parental self-efficacy (i.e., a parent’s confidence in their own ability to care for their infant and respond to the infant’s needs) is the first step to a good parent-child relationship. Research has explored the development of maternal self-efficacy beginning during pregnancy and continuing after childbirth. Mothers who have previous childbirth and […] The post Becoming Confident in Parenting Abilities appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 10:06:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ground Beef and Broccoli</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/ground-beef-and-broccoli/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Get ready to enjoy a delicious and easy ground beef and broccoli stir-fry that’s perfect for a quick weeknight dinner.…</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>9 Easy Low-Light Indoor Plants</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/easy-low-light-indoor-plants/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>I used to think every houseplant needed a sunny corner or bright windowsill to thrive. But it turns out many of our favorite go-to houseplants do just fine in shady corners and low-light locations. So before you write off your house as too dark to sustain plant life, check out this list of the best indoor plants for low light. You might be surprised at how many good options there are! Our upstairs family room is the brightest room we’ve ever owned thanks to big unobstructed windows on all 4 sides. But most of our indoor plants live downstairs, where we get far less natural light. Luckily, that hasn’t stopped us from growing our collection of happy healthy houseplants. 9 Houseplants That Don’t Need A Lot Of Light Here are our favorite low-light indoor plants. We list a lot more info on them below, but here’s a quick list to bring on your next trip to the plant store: Snake Plant ZZ Plant Pothos Heartleaf Philodendron English Ivy Aglaonema Cast Iron Plant Monstera Parlor Palm Perhaps our favorite part of this list is that these aren’t ugly “consolation plants” that people begrudgingly buy for dark homes. Continue reading 9 Easy Low-Light Indoor Plants at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 14:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Check List</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/06/summer-checks/</link><description>Outfit Details: Celine Blazer (similar, less expensive here), Sir Top (similar here) Adam Lippes Skirt, Chanel Bag, Alaia Flats (similar here and here), Saint Laurent Sunglasses Checks are at… The post The Check List appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 05:00:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>10 Excellent Black Historical Audiobooks</title><link>https://bookriot.com/10-excellent-black-historical-audiobooks/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/American-Daughters-cropped-.png</image_url><description>Read these ten beautifully written Black historical audiobooks set around the world, from France to Nigeria.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When will the U.S. get its first $25,000 EV? Sooner than you think</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/06/23/when-will-the-u-s-get-its-first-25000-car-sooner-than-you-think/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1200x675/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/06/21150315/100th_european_motor_show.jpeg</image_url><description>Filed under: Green , Chevrolet , Ford , Jeep , Tesla , Electric Continue reading When will the U.S. get its first $25,000 EV? Sooner than you think When will the U.S. get its first $25,000 EV? Sooner than you think originally appeared on Autoblog on Sun, 23 Jun 2024 11:00:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>South Korea plant fire kills 22 people after lithium battery combustion</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/06/24/fire-at-south-korea-battery-plant-kills-at-least-16-people-report.html</link><description>A fire that broke out at a South Korean lithium battery plant has killed 22 people, local officials said</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 10:16:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 555</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-555/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-555</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>Staying up-to-date with today’s job search can feel overwhelming. That’s why I publish this summary, to help share trends and issues impacting job seekers. In this week’s summary, you’ll learn about: If you enjoyed any of these resources, be sure and follow them or subscribe to their newsletters. To subscribe to Summary Sunday, here’s the […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 555 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 11:47:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A case for public preschool: New study reveals preschool benefits to be longer-lasting and substantial</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/benefits-of-public-preschool/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=benefits-of-public-preschool</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Preschool lays a foundation for elementary school students to succeed. In the United States, as children approach kindergarten entry, it is increasingly common for 4-year-olds to be in non-parental group care and education, often in a center- or school-based setting where they can learn alongside peers. For children from low-income communities, […] The post A case for public preschool: New study reveals preschool benefits to be longer-lasting and substantial appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 08:26:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Grilled Bourbon Steak</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/grilled-bourbon-steak/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Fire up the grill for these mouthwatering Grilled Bourbon Steaks! Marinated in a blend of whiskey, brown sugar, and savory…</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/how-to-remove-wallpaper/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Wallpaper has made a big comeback as a trendy home design choice. But despite its resurgence, there are still plenty of us dealing with dingy, dated, or downright ugly old wallpaper we don’t want. In our old home, we had to remove wallpaper in so many rooms: the kitchen, the dining room, the foyer, and two different bathrooms! As we traveled from room to room removing wallpaper, we tested 4 different methods, and today we’ll share what we learned. Removing wallpaper doesn’t require special tools or lots of money. It’s a totally doable project for any homeowner. However, it can be a tedious process that can take elbow grease and patience, depending on the size of your room and the stubbornness of your wallpaper. But having removed several rooms worth of decades-old wallpaper, we can confidently say it’s worth the effort! You can also check out more before and afters of our once-wallpapered rooms. Continue reading How To Remove Wallpaper: 4 Proven Methods at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:21:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Walmart’s Latest Discoveries</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/06/walmarts-latest-discoveries/</link><description>Thank you to Walmart for sponsoring this post. Explore Walmart’s latest selects just in time for summer and the Fourth… The post Walmart’s Latest Discoveries appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 16:30:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Best Book Deals of the Day for June 23, 2024</title><link>https://bookriot.com/the-best-book-deals-of-the-day-for-june-23-2024/</link><image_url>https://s2982.pcdn.co/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/deals-062424.jpg.optimal.jpg</image_url><description>A missed love connection, the meaning and experience of joy, a drag show mystery, and more of today's best book deals.</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>2024 Dodge Charger Daytona EV reportedly delayed 90 days, to August</title><link>https://www.autoblog.com/2024/06/23/2024-dodge-charger-daytona-ev-reportedly-delayed-90-days-to-august/</link><image_url>https://s.aolcdn.com/images/dims3/GLOB/legacy_thumbnail/1200x675/format/jpg/quality/100/https://s.aolcdn.com/os/ab/_cms/2024/06/23025859/2024_dodge_charger_ev.jpg</image_url><description>Filed under: Green , Plants/Manufacturing , Dodge , Coupe , Electric , Future Vehicles , Performance , Sedan Continue reading 2024 Dodge Charger Daytona EV reportedly delayed 90 days, to August 2024 Dodge Charger Daytona EV reportedly delayed 90 days, to August originally appeared on Autoblog on Sun, 23 Jun 2024 10:30:00 EDT. Please see our terms for use of feeds . Permalink | Email this | Comments</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>'Intense' stage of Gaza fighting is close to end, Israel's Netanyahu says</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2024/06/24/israels-netanyahu-signals-intense-stage-of-gaza-fighting-close-to-end.html</link><description>Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu has signaled that the "intense" phase of fighting in the war-torn Gaza enclosure is close to ending.</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 09:48:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summary Sunday: Issue 554</title><link>https://careersherpa.net/summary-sunday-issue-554/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=summary-sunday-issue-554</link><image_url>https://careersherpa.net/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/cropped-careersherpa-icon-512x512-2-32x32.png</image_url><description>We all need trusted sources for job search. Searching the internet and watching Tiktok videos isn’t always the best solution. There is and always has been conflicting advice and opinions when it comes to job search and especially resumes. (If you’ve ever asked 10 people for feedback on your resume then you know what I […] The post Summary Sunday: Issue 554 appeared first on Career Sherpa .</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 11:13:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fathers’ views on family and work after COVID-19 lockdowns</title><link>https://childandfamilyblog.com/fathers-views-on-family-and-work-after-covid-19-lockdowns/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=fathers-views-on-family-and-work-after-covid-19-lockdowns</link><image_url>https://childandfamilyblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cropped-cfb-favicon-3-32x32.png</image_url><description>Key takeaways for caregivers Fathers often want to be present for their children and contribute to household tasks, but they can lack opportunities and confidence; they may see themselves as “helpers” instead of parents. Australian fathers in our small study reported that they spent more time with their children during the COVID-19 lockdowns, and they […] The post Fathers’ views on family and work after COVID-19 lockdowns appeared first on Child and Family Blog .</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 00:05:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cowboy Queso</title><link>https://therecipecritic.com/cowboy-queso/</link><image_url>https://therecipecritic.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/02/cropped-favicon-32x32.png</image_url><description>Get ready to rustle up some serious flavor with this Cowboy Queso! Packed with zesty sausage, hearty beans, and a…</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aglaonema Plant – Complete Care Guide</title><link>https://www.younghouselove.com/aglaonema-plant-care-guide/</link><image_url>https://www.younghouselove.com/wp-content/uploads//2022/04/cropped-YHLFavicon2022-PinkBlock-150x150.png</image_url><description>Aglaonema, also called the Chinese Evergreen Plant, is an easy-care houseplant that lives happily in many lighting conditions – even a dark corner of our daughter’s room. There are dozens of different Aglaonema varieties, most with large tropical foliage and colors ranging from silvery-green, red, and even vibrant pink. They’re also tough to kill, so they’re a great option for forgetful plant owners or anyone looking for an easy win in the plant department. These truly have been very low maintenance for us. We purchased our two Aglaonemas (pronounced ag-lee-oh-neem-ah ) to put atop our daughter’s closet. It’s sometimes hard to distinguish different varieties, but we believe that’s an Aglaonema Silver (right) and either a Candy Cane or Princess Silver Queen (left). Aglaonema Quick Facts Here’s what you need to know about your Aglaonema at a glance: Latin name : Aglaonema is the genus under which there are 21 recognized species . Continue reading Aglaonema Plant – Complete Care Guide at Young House Love.</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:47:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summer Straw</title><link>https://juliaberolzheimer.com/2024/06/summer-straw/</link><description>Outfit Details: Emporio Sirenuse Top (similar here), Erdem Skirt, Alaia Flats (similar here and here), Chanel Bag, Prada Necklace, Celine Sunglasses (similar here, less expensive here) Summer isn’t complete without… The post Summer Straw appeared first on Julia Berolzheimer .</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 05:00:56 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>