<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Interleaved RSS Feed</title><link>http://example.com/interleaved_feed.xml</link><description>This is an interleaved feed of the most recent entries from multiple RSS sources, skipping any feeds with errors.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 06:56:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Receivership Real Estate: The Hidden Inventory Only Experts Know About w/Jake Flothe</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/on-the-market-212</link><description>When housing inventory is low, where do you go? Foreclosure rates are down, short sales are a hassle, and the open housing market has barely any sellers—is there a better […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 07:02:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>OpenAI inks strategic tie-up with UK’s Financial Times, including content use</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/29/openai-inks-strategic-tie-up-with-uks-financial-times-including-content-use/</link><description>OpenAI, maker of the viral AI chatbot ChatGPT, has netted another news licensing deal in Europe, adding London’s Financial Times to a growing list of publishers it’s paying for content access. As with earlier OpenAI’s publisher licensing deals, financial terms of the arrangement are not being made public. The latest deal looks a touch cozier […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 09:15:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>They Killed Their Abusive Partners. Now Their Sentences Could Be Reconsidered.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/27/oklahoma-oregon-minnesota-domestic-violence</link><description>Oklahoma could re-examine how it punishes people whose crimes came after years of domestic abuse. Other states may follow.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>You Give Me (Spring) Fever</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/women/features/you-give-me-spring-fever?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>New Season Brings Boost of Energy, but Also Unplanned Pregnancies</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 16:57:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>$80,000/Year Cash Flow &amp; Financial Freedom with 7 Properties (in 3 Years!) w/Sarah Msuya</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/rookie-399</link><description>What’s YOUR reason for investing in real estate? For today’s guest, it was to achieve financial freedom and have a flexible schedule. By focusing on education, forming partnerships, and, most […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 07:02:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ethiopian plastic upcycling startup Kubik gets fresh funding, plans to license out its tech</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/28/kubik-seed-extension/</link><description>Kubik, a plastic upcycling startup, has raised a $1.9 million seed extension, months after announcing initial equity investment. The startup’s latest investment is from African Renaissance Partners, an East African venture capital firm; Endgame Capital, an investor with a bias for technologies around climate change; and King Philanthropies, a climate and extreme poverty investor. The […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 07:00:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Being Trans in Prison Is Really Like</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/26/trans-prison-voices-gender-essay</link><description>Amid a wave of anti-trans legislation, and the violence that often follows, four people share their experiences in the criminal justice system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 11:00:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Older Adults: 9 Nutrients You May Be Missing</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/missing-nutrients?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>With age, your body doesn’t absorb nutrients well, so every calorie you consume must be packed with nutrition. Here are 9 nutrients older adults often need more of.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 16:57:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>3 Ways We Find Real Estate Deals Even During the Harshest Housing Markets</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/real-estate-944</link><description>It seems like everyone is wondering how to find real estate deals in today’s supply-constrained market. With housing inventory still hovering around historical lows, finding a cash-flowing, appreciating rental property […]</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 07:02:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ChatGPT’s ‘hallucination’ problem hit with another privacy complaint in EU</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/28/chatgpt-gdpr-complaint-noyb/</link><description>OpenAI is facing another privacy complaint in the European Union. This one, which has been filed by privacy rights nonprofit noyb on behalf of an individual complainant, targets the inability of its AI chatbot ChatGPT to correct misinformation it generates about individuals. The tendency of GenAI tools to produce information that’s plain wrong has been […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 06:00:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Enduring Use of Solitary, and New Proposed Limits That Will Likely Fail (Again)</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/20/solitary-confinement-reform-oklahoma-washington-florida</link><description>Isolation’s damaging effects are widely known. But many facilities confine people — even youth — virtually all day, sometimes in shower stalls.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Immunity Challenge: How aging affects your immune system</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/seniors-boost-immunity?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>How does getting older affect your immune system? How can you keep those effects to a minimum? Your answers are here.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 16:57:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Think Passive Real Estate Is Safe? Here Are 9 Hidden Risks That Could Cost You</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/passive-real-estate-investment-risks</link><description>You can’t eliminate all risk from investments. After all, the zombie apocalypse could strike tomorrow and probably wipe out your entire portfolio. But you can reduce risk, even among high-return […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 20:06:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Humanoid robots are learning to fall well</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/28/humanoid-robots-are-learning-to-fall-well/</link><description>The savvy marketers at Boston Dynamics produced two major robotics news cycles last week. The larger of the two was, naturally, the electric Atlas announcement. As I write this, the sub-40 second video is steadily approaching five million views. A day prior, the company tugged at the community’s heart strings when it announced that the […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 21:15:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Officials Failed to Act When COVID Hit Prisons. A New Study Shows the Deadly Cost.</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/18/covid-prison-deaths-data</link><description>People in prison died at 3.4 times the rate of the free population, with the oldest hit hardest. New data holds lessons for preventing future deaths.</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What Helps When It’s Hard to Chew and Swallow?</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/eating-problems?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Trouble chewing and swallowing? WebMD shares six ways to make everything go down a little easier.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 16:57:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gen Z Is Dominating Their Parents in Homeownership—According to New Report</title><link>https://www.biggerpockets.com/blog/gen-z-homeownership-outpacing-parents</link><description>When it comes to homeownership, Gen Z might be ahead of the curve. According to data from real estate firm Redfin, more Gen Zers owned their home at 24 than their parents did (millennials and […]</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 19:59:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tesla profits tumble, Fisker flatlines, and California cities battle for control of AVs</title><link>https://techcrunch.com/2024/04/28/tesla/</link><description>Welcome back to TechCrunch Mobility — your central hub for news and insights on the future of transportation. Sign up here — just click TechCrunch Mobility — to receive the newsletter every weekend in your inbox. Subscribe for free. Welp, Tesla earnings happened this week — and yeah that was a lot. A lot of what, you ask? A […]
© 2024 TechCrunch. All rights reserved. For personal use only.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 19:00:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Parents Paying for Their Children’s Crimes</title><link>https://www.themarshallproject.org/2024/04/13/michigan-school-shooting-parents</link><description>Experts warn about a wave of legal consequences for parents like the Crumbleys, while some states consider prosecutions for kids as young as 10.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Foods to Keep You Healthy as You Age</title><link>https://www.webmd.com/healthy-aging/features/longevity-foods?src=RSS_PUBLIC</link><description>Staying healthy as you enter your golden years has a lot to do with your diet. Here are some foods that are good for your heart, your brain, your bones, and your muscles.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 16:57:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>